<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 19:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3723472</guid>
      <title>Giant, green emerald found in Zambia mine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGemfields, the world's largest producer of green stones, has discovered a giant, green emerald in Zambia.The emerald weighs more than 1.1 kilograms and was discovered in Kagem, the world's largest emerald mine located in Zambia.A statement released by Gemfields said that the emerald has "remarkable clarity and a perfectly balanced golden green hue."Emeralds in the Kagem mine were reportedly formed 450 million years ago due to a rare combination of in situ minerals and magma from the Earth's crust which then developed into emerald crystals.The gem is being called "Inkalamu" which means lion in the local Bemba language in Zambia.The uncut emerald was discovered in an open-pit mine on October 2 by a geologist and a veteran emerald miner.Several pieces are expected to be cut from the 5,655-carat emerald and will be auctioned in Singapore this month.Most of the emeralds in the world are mined from Zambia, Colombia and Brazil. As a result, emeralds are even more precious than diamonds due to their scarcity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Uncut emerald and where the emerald was discovered on a map2. Golden green uncut emerald3. Where the emerald was discovered4. Uncut emerald turning into tiny piecesVOICEOVER (in English): "The emerald weighs more than 1.1 kilograms and was discovered in Kagem, the world's largest emerald mine located in Zambia.""A statement released by Gemfields said that the emerald has 'remarkable clarity and a perfectly balanced golden green hue.'""The uncut emerald was discovered in an open-pit mine on October 2 by a geologist and a veteran emerald miner.""Several pieces are expected to be cut from the 5,655-carat emerald and will be auctioned in Singapore this month."SOURCES: CNN, Gemfields, Forbes, https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/massive-emerald-found-in-zambia/index.htmlhttps://gemfields.com/gemfields-introduces-inkalamu-the-5655-carat-lion-emerald/https://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonydemarco/2018/10/29/a-5655-carat-emerald-discovered-in-zambia/#17f21e64b414***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/01/3723472/3723472_BEBD2B2877134E94BD4E8840ACEBCB97_181101_3723472_Giant__green_emerald_found_in_Zambia_mine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/2C6/81F/2C681FFC98924B54BF14A2553F231FEC_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, emeralds, Zambia, gemstones, emerald stones, green stones, Kagem emerald mine, Inkamalu, Lion Emerald, emerald crystal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3723061</guid>
      <title>Could the Democrats regain the majority of seats in the U.S. Senate?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA total of 44 Democrats and 50 Republicans are up for reelection, with six toss-up seats available.Democrats are projected to win seats for the Senate in Washington, California, New Mexico,  Hawaii, Minnesota, New York, Virginia, Maine,  Vermont, Rhode Island, Massachusetts, Connecticut, Delaware, and Maryland, according to political site and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics.Polling data seems show the public leaning toward voting Democrat in Minnesota, Wisconsin, Michigan, and New Jersey. Democrats are also likely to win in Ohio, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia.Republicans are projected to win in Utah, Wyoming, and Nebraska. Republicans are also likely to win in Mississippi and North Dakota, while Texas and Tennessee are also leaning Republican.If Democrats win the majority in the Senate, they could possibly move to impeach Supreme Court justice Brett Kavanaugh and President Trump, reports Business Insider.Only a total 19 federal officials have been impeached in U.S. history, including a senator, a cabinet secretary, 15 judges and two presidents.The first president to be impeached was Andrew Johnson in 1868 for dismissing Edwin M. Stanton as secretary of war. President Bill Clinton was impeached in 1998 for lying under oath in regards to alleged sexual relations with a White House intern.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Proportion of Democrats vs Republicans in the Senate2. States where Democrats are projected to win3. States which are likely to vote Democrats4. States Republicans are projected and likely to win inVOICEOVER (in English): "A total of 44 Democrats and 50 Republicans are up for reelection, with six toss-up seats available.""According to political site and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics, Democrats are projected to win seats for the Senate in Washington, California, New Mexico,  Hawaii, Minnesota, New York, Virginia, Maine,  Vermont, Rhode Island, Massachusetts, Connecticut, Delaware, and Maryland.""Polling data seems show the public leaning toward voting Democrat in Minnesota, Wisconsin, Michigan, and New Jersey. Democrats are also likely to win in Ohio, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia.""Republicans are projected to win in Utah, Wyoming, and Nebraska. Republicans are also likely to win in Mississippi and North Dakota, while Texas and Tennessee are also leaning Republican. "SOURCES: Real Clear Politics, Business Insider, https://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2018/senate/2018_elections_senate_map.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/can-brett-kavanaugh-be-impeached-from-the-supreme-court-2018-10***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 03:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/01/3723061/3723061_1421C9797AE94F90964E24AD77ED124B_181101_3723061_Could_the_Democrats_regain_the_majority_of_seats_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/344/D79/344D79704A7F439A937361FB7906BCCB_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US Senate, US Senate elections, Democrats, Republicans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3724125</guid>
      <title>Oceans are absorbing more heat than previously estimated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe world's oceans have absorbed considerably more heat than previously estimated, according to a new study. The results, published in the journal Nature on Wednesday, found that seas around the globe may be absorbing up to 60 percent more heat since the 1990s than earlier estimates calculated, according to Scientific American. Researchers calculated the oceans have absorbed around 13 zettajoules of heat energy every year between 1991 and 2016, CNN reports.The findings suggest the earth is more sensitive to greenhouse gas emissions than previously thought. Rather than relying on direct ocean measurements, the researchers looked at the amount of oxygen and carbon dioxide in the atmosphere since 1991. As oceans warm up, their ability to absorb oxygen and carbon dioxide decreases, thus more of those gases remain in the air. By measuring the changes in atmospheric oxygen and carbon dioxide levels, while also controlling for other factors such as human greenhouse gas emissions, the team was able to estimate how much heat the oceans have absorbed over the past few decades. Warmer oceans could potentially lead to sea levels rising faster than forecasted, dying off of coral reefs, increasingly powerful storms, faster rates of melting sea ice and affecting ocean currents, CNN reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Oceans absorbing heat energy2. Researchers measured atmospheric oxygen and carbon dioxide, rather than direct ocean measurements3. Oxygen and carbon dioxide in the air above oceans4. Warmer ocean effectsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study published in the journal Nature found that oceans may be absorbing up to 60 percent more heat since the 1990s than earlier estimates calculated." "According to Scientific American, researchers calculated seas have absorbed around 13 zettajoules of heat energy every year between 1991 and 2016." "Rather than relying on direct ocean measurements, the researchers looked at the amount of oxygen and carbon dioxide in the atmosphere since 1991." "As oceans warm up, their ability to absorb oxygen and carbon dioxide decreases, thus more of those gases remain in the air." "By measuring the changes in atmospheric oxygen and carbon dioxide levels, while also controlling for other factors such as human greenhouse gas emissions, the team was able to estimate how much heat the oceans have absorbed over the past few decades." "According to CNN, warmer oceans could potentially lead to sea levels rising faster than forecasted, dying off of coral reefs, increasingly powerful storms, faster rates of melting sea ice and ocean currents being affected." SOURCES: Scientific American, Wired, CNNhttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-oceans-are-heating-up-faster-than-expected/https://www.wired.com/story/the-sea-may-be-absorbing-way-more-heat-than-we-thought/https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/01/australia/ocean-warming-report-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 11:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/02/3724125/3724125_BFC52D32A3B74474B2F203F03D62BD70_181102_3724125_Oceans_are_absorbing_more_heat_than_previously_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/4DC/5C2/4DC5C2A14A084DE0878F5B59967E151A_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, oceans absorbing heat, global warming, climate change, seas absorbing more heat, greenhouse gas emissions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3724115</guid>
      <title>Adolescents who give up marijuana show improved cognition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAdolescents who regularly use cannabis but stop for 30 days have better memory and improved cognition compared to those who continue to use pot, according to a new study. According to NPR, a study published in the Journal of Clinical Psychiatry on Tuesday found that when young people stop using marijuana their verbal learning and memory improve. Researchers at Massachusetts General Hospital looked at 88 participants age 16 to 25, who were regular users of marijuana. According to the study's lead author, Randi Schuster, director of neuropsychology at Massachusetts General Hospital's Center for Addiction Medicine, the researchers recruited a range of participants. Some of the young people smoked once per week, while others smoked almost daily. Participants were randomly assigned into an abstaining group or a non-abstaining group.  Volunteers had their urine tested weekly and were also given a variety of tasks testing their attention and memory. Researchers found that after four weeks, there was no noticeable difference in attention scores between the two groups. However, memory scores for nonusers improved, while users' memory scores remained relatively steady. The study concluded that adolescents learn better when they are not using cannabis, and that some of the deficits from usage appear to be reversible. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. When young people stop smoking cannabis, verbal learning and memory improve2. Participants were divided into  abstaining and non-abstaining groups3. Participants were given weekly urine tests and tests for attention and memory4. After four weeks, attention scores were similar in both groups, but memory for nonusers was higher than usersVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NPR, a study published in the Journal of Clinical Psychiatry on Tuesday found that when young people stop using marijuana, their verbal learning and memory improve." "Researchers at Massachusetts General Hospital looked at 88 participants age 16 to 25, who were regular users of marijuana. Participants were randomly assigned into an abstaining group or a nonabstaining group."  "Volunteers had their urine tested weekly and were also given a variety of tasks testing their attention and memory." "Researchers found that after four weeks, there was no noticeable difference in attention scores between the two groups. However, memory scores for nonusers improved, while users' memory scores remained relatively steady." SOURCES: NPR, CBC Newshttps://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2018/10/30/662127406/when-adolescents-give-up-pot-their-cognition-quickly-improveshttps://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/youth-cannabis-memory-study-1.4884846***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 11:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/02/3724115/3724115_83B2614094E04CF6946FC1A89146C52B_181102_3724115_Adolescents_who_give_up_marijuana_show_improved__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/18A/1E2/18A1E2538A434D1D9CFF66C7B1CB9D14_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, adolescents cognition, memory loss, improved cognition, attention]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3723869</guid>
      <title>Explaining U.S. Birthright citizenship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBirthright citizenship is defined as a constitutional right for any child born in the United States to automatically gain U.S. citizenship.The 14th Amendment states that "All persons born or naturalized in the United States, and subject to the jurisdiction thereof, are citizens of the United States and of the State wherein they reside."The amendment was ratified in 1868 to guarantee citizenship for all. This included former slaves, who at the time didn't have the right to own property, roam freely or even stay in the country.However, it was still never clearly defined whether or not children born of immigrants in the U.S. were automatically U.S. citizens.Then came the case of Wong Kim Ark. Wong was the son of Chinese immigrants and was born in California. After he returned from a trip to China in 1895, the federal government tried to stop him from re-entering the U.S. under the Chinese Exclusion Act. His case ended up in court, and after a years-long battle, the Supreme Court in 1898 ruled that Wong was in fact a U.S. citizen, as he was born in the U.S. Meanwhile, despite all this, Native Americans were still consistently denied rights given to others born in the U.S. until Congress finally granted citizenship to all Native Americans in 1924.President Donald Trump has announced plans to issue an Executive order to end birthright citizenship, the Supreme Court would still have the power to overturn the Executive order and interpret the Constitution on its own.Other than the U.S., there are 30 other nations in the world that recognize birthright citizenship including Argentina, Brazil, Canada, Panama and Mexico.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Icon of a baby, US Flag and US passport2. Explaining the 14th Amendment3. Showing the 14th Amendment4. Map of countries which allow birthright citizenshipVOICEOVER (in English): "Birthright citizenship is defined as a constitutional right for any child born in the United States to automatically gain U.S. citizenship.""The 14th Amendment states that 'All persons born or naturalized in the United States, and subject to the jurisdiction thereof, are citizens of the United States and of the State wherein they reside.'""The amendment was ratified in 1868 to guarantee citizenship for all. This included former slaves, who at the time didn't have the right to own property, roam freely or even stay in the country.""Other than the U.S., there are 30 other nations in the world that recognize birthright citizenship including Argentina, Brazil, Canada, Panama and Mexico."SOURCES: Voice of America, The Atlantic, Vox, USA Today, Quartz, Business Insider,https://www.voanews.com/a/how-us-birthright-citizenship-emerged-endured/4636423.htmlhttps://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/10/birthright-citizenship-constitution/574381/https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2018/10/birthright-citizenship-other-countries-trump/574453/https://www.vox.com/2018/7/23/17595754/birthright-citizenship-trump-14th-amendment-executive-orderhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/10/30/birthright-citizenship-explained-president-donald-trump-immigration/1817034002/https://qz.com/1443855/what-us-birthright-citizenship-actually-gets-you/https://www.businessinsider.com/countries-that-recognize-birthright-citizenship-jus-soli-2018-10***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 06:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/02/3723869/3723869_8960A0FA1346498B8A507C91D6C195B6_181102_3723869_Explaining_U_S__Birthright_citizenship_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1D3/E80/1D3E80AEE75E44EF8E83099446351842_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, birthright citizenship, jus soli, us birthright citizenship, US Constitution, the 14th Amendment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3725559</guid>
      <title>How the Democrats could impeach Trump or Kavanaugh</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe upcoming midterm elections are poised to determine whether or not the Democrats can take back the House and the Senate.Members of the Democratic Party have said they will push for impeachment for President Trump and Justice Brett Kavanaugh should they regain control, NBC reports.The impeachment process begins with the House Judiciary Committee reviewing charges against an official and determining if there are grounds for impeachment.The full House of Representatives votes on one or more articles of impeachment, and if at least one gets a simple majority vote, the official is indicted and considered impeached.From there, the proceedings move to the Senate for a trial presided over by the Supreme Court Chief Justice, with the Senate acting as jury.In order to get a conviction, a supermajority, or two-thirds of the senators must find the official guilty. Once convicted, he is immediately removed from office.The Democrats will need to win 218 seats during the midterm elections to regain control over the House of Representatives and initiate impeachment proceedings. Polls indicate that they have a good chance of doing so, according to CNN and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics.However, the Democrats are much less likely to win enough seats in the Senate to ensure a two-thirds majority vote for conviction.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. House Judiciary Committee reviewing charges2. Simple majority vote needed from House of Representatives to impeach3. Depiction of Senate trial with Supreme Court Chief Justice presiding4. Two-thirds majority vote needed in Senate to convict5. Democrats need 218 seats to retake House of Representatives, likely to win6. Democrats not as likely to win enough seats to retake SenateVOICEOVER (in English): "The impeachment process begins with the House Judiciary Committee reviewing charges against an official and determining if there are grounds for impeachment.""The full House of Representatives votes on one or more articles of impeachment, and if at least one gets a simple majority vote, the official is indicted and considered impeached.""From there, the proceedings move to the Senate for a trial presided over by the Supreme Court Chief Justice, with the Senate acting as jury.""In order to get a conviction, a supermajority, or two-thirds of the senators must find the official guilty. Once convicted, he is immediately removed from office.""The Democrats will need to win 218 seats during the midterm elections to regain control over the House and initiate impeachment proceedings.""Polls indicate that they have a good chance of doing so.""However, the Democrats are much less likely to win enough seats in the Senate to ensure a two-thirds majority vote for conviction."SOURCES: NBC, CNN, Real Clear Politics, New York Timeshttps://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/impeaching-kavanaugh-rouses-progressive-democrats-after-confirmation-n917376https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/31/politics/nancy-pelosi-house-democrats-midterms-voting/index.htmlhttps://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2018/house/2018_elections_house_map.htmlhttps://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2018/senate/2018_elections_senate_map.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/05/17/us/politics/how-the-impeachment-process-works-trump-clinton.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/05/3725559/3725559_2A7D5871E31D4FF4B9DF5D21CE1FE338_181105_3725559_How_the_Democrats_could_impeach_Trump_or_Kavanau_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F3D/E7E/F3DE7E986EA84CD5A0395F3E455A7851_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, trump, kavanaugh, impeachment, donald trump, brett kavanaugh, how to impeach, US impeachment process, impeachment trial, democrats impeach trump, democrats impeach kavanaugh]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3725537</guid>
      <title>High levels of cellphone radiation linked to cancer in male rats</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have found evidence of links between tumors in male rats and exposure to radio frequency radiation.A final report released on Thursday by the U.S. National Toxicology Program details an experiment in which about 3,000 rats and mice were exposed to whole body radio frequency radiation nine hours a day for up to two years. Rats began exposure to the radiation in the womb while mice started at 5-6 weeks old. The radiation used in the experiment was similar to those emitted by 2G and 3G mobile phones. The rodents lived in specially designed chambers with isolated rooms where a transmitting antenna subjected the rats to RFR fields with frequencies of 900 and 1900 megahertz. The study found evidence that radiation exposure was associated with the emergence of tumors in the hearts, brains, and adrenal glands of male rats. However, cancers found in female rats and male and female mice weren't conclusively linked to radio frequency radiation exposure.The research cost $30 million and was ongoing for a decade. The NTP's goal was to gather information on the effects of mobile phone radiation on rats in response to the increasing universality of cellphone use among humans. However, NTP scientists and the U.S. Food and Drug Administration stated that the results of the research do not directly affect humans since the rodents were exposed to extreme levels of cellphone radiation, which surpass the current safety limits on mobile phone radiation. The results also do not apply to Wi-Fi signals or phones that use 4G or 5G technologies, these use different methods of signal modulation that the NTP did not study in their research.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Introduction and duration of research2. Details of rats experimented on3. Details of experiment: how it was carried out.4. Results of experiment: cancer on male ratsVOICEOVER (in English): "A U.S. National Toxicology Program experiment exposed about 3,000 rats and mice to whole body radio frequency radiation nine hours a day for up to two years."  "Rats began exposure to the radiation in the womb while mice started at five to six weeks old.""Rodents lived in specially designed chambers, where a transmitting antenna subjected them to RFR fields with frequencies of 900 and 1900 megahertz.""The study found evidence that exposure to radiation is associated with tumor development in the hearts, brains and adrenal glands of male rats."SOURCES: National Toxicology Program, New York Timeshttps://ntp.niehs.nih.gov/results/areas/cellphones/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/01/health/cellphone-radiation-cancer.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/05/3725537/3725537_1BB88A75C0D14C27A157194E7FCC66C1_181105_3725537_High_levels_of_cellphone_radiation_linked_to_can_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DC1/427/DC142719F70C432F99C7FC7AA56890D6_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, health, tumor, cancer, research, mobile phone, cellphone use, cellphone radiation, experiment, research, studies, national toxicology program, cancer research.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3725515</guid>
      <title>Migrant caravan begins 'route of death' stretch in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThousands of Central American migrants have resumed their march toward the United States on Sunday after disagreements a day before over the route north.  According to the Associated Press, most of the approximately 4,000 migrants are now moving along what some are referring to as the "route of death" to the town of Cordoba around 124 miles away. The next portion of the journey will be one of the longest yet, as the migrants will now have to pass via the sugar fields and fruit groves of Veracruz, a state where hundreds of migrants have gone missing in recent years due to kidnappers looking for ransom payments. A large majority of the migrants are trying to escape rampant poverty, gang violence and political unrest in the countries of Honduras, Guatemala, El Salvador and Nicaragua. Mexico now has three caravans totalling more than 6,000 migrants spread out over 300 miles of highway in the states of Chiapas, Oaxaca and Veracruz. President Trump has ordered more than 7,000 active duty troops to be deployed throughout Texas, Arizona and California along the Mexican border in response to the caravan. According the Associated Press, President Donald Trump could sign an order next week allowing for mass detention of migrants caught entering the U.S. and bar anyone caught crossing illegally from claiming asylum.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Migrant caravan marching towards Cordoba2. Migrants marching through state of Veracruz3. Majority of migrants are from Honduras, Guatemala, El Salvador and Nicaragua4. Mexico now has 3 migrant caravans in three different statesVOICEOVER (in English): "Thousands of Central American migrants have resumed their march toward the United States on Sunday." "According to the Associated Press, most of the approximately 4,000 migrants are now moving along what some are referring to as the "route of death" to the town of Cordoba around 124 miles away." "The next portion of the journey will be one of the longest yet, as the migrants will now have to pass through Veracruz, a state where hundreds of migrants have gone missing in recent years due to kidnappers looking for ransom payments." "A large majority of the migrants are trying to escape rampant poverty, gang violence and political unrest in the countries of Honduras, Guatemala, El Salvador and Nicaragua." "Mexico now has three caravans totalling more than 6,000 migrants spread out over 300 miles of highway in the states of Chiapas, Oaxaca and Veracruz." SOURCES: NBC News, Chicago Tribune, Geopolitical Futureshttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/migrant-caravan-embarks-route-death-through-mexico-n931041https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-migrant-caravan-20181104-story.htmlhttps://geopoliticalfutures.com/tracking-central-american-migrant-caravans/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 10:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/05/3725515/3725515_01A41CE0DEE241C28F62A9F3686E61AF_181105_3725515_Migrant_caravan_begins__route_of_death__stretch__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/925/597/925597472F934D4780CC2BCB5688EE63_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, migrant caravan, migrant, President Trump, US southern border, US Mexico border]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3726149</guid>
      <title>Trump's border wall could threaten Texas plants and wildlife</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIf the Trump administration's proposed border wall goes ahead with construction, plants and wildlife could be threatened in Texas. According to NPR, the federal spending bill approved in September includes $1.6 billion in 2019 for wall construction, which could begin as early as February.  In October, the Department of Homeland Security issued a waiver to 28 laws protecting public lands, wildlife and the environment in order so that construction could go ahead. In July, scientists published a paper highlighting the negative impacts of the border wall on wildlife by eliminating, degrading or fragmenting habitats. A wall would block access to water and food, and inhibit seasonal migrations. According to Phys.org, in a letter published in March in the journal Frontiers of Ecology and the Environment, other researchers also expressed worry the wall could damage the increasingly rare Tamaulipan thornscrub ecosystem. Other species that would be affected are the endangered wildflower Zapata bladderpod and the threatened whiskerbush cactus.  According to the researchers, negative impacts could be reduced by limiting physical barriers and accompanying roads, while considering building structures that allow animals to pass through and barrier alternatives like electronic sensors.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Trump's proposed border wall could harm plant and wildlife in Texas2. Border wall would affect wildlife habitats3. Border wall would affect ecosystem and plant life in the area4. How negative impacts could be lessenedVOICEOVER (in English): "If the Trump administration's proposed border wall goes ahead with construction, plants and wildlife could be threatened in Texas." "In July, scientists published a paper highlighting the negative impacts of the border wall on wildlife by eliminating, degrading or fragmenting habitats. A wall would block access to water and food, and inhibit seasonal migrations." "According to Phys.org, other researchers in a letter published in March in Frontiers of Ecology and the Environment, were also worried the wall could damage the increasingly rare Tamaulipan thornscrub ecosystem. "Other species that would be affected are the endangered wildflower Zapata bladderpod and the threatened whiskerbush cactus."  "According to the researchers, the negative impacts could be lessened by limiting physical barriers and accompanying roads, barriers that allow animals to pass and barrier alternatives like electronic sensors."  SOURCES: NPR, Phys.orghttps://www.npr.org/2018/11/01/660671247/butterfly-preserve-on-the-border-threatened-by-trumps-wallhttps://phys.org/news/2018-03-border-wall-texas-animals-scientists.html ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/06/3726149/3726149_54B62D5A62B3443E9E8F00F914B2DF34_181106_3726149_Trump_s_border_wall_could_threaten_Texas_plants__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C52/131/C52131385DB74E8CA062487BF9DF1310_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, President Trump, Trump border wall, US southern border wall, border wall wildlife, border wall plantlife]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3726059</guid>
      <title>Screen time linked to mental health problems in kids and teens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has linked excessive gaming, watching TV, or on smartphones to anxiety and depression in kids as young as two.Research published in Preventive Medicine Reports found that children and teens may have less curiosity, self-control, emotional stability, and a greater inability to finish tasks after just an hour of screen time a day.Researchers analyzed a random sample of over 40,000 surveys from the 2016 National Survey of Children's Health, which looked at kids aged 2 to 17.Adolescents aged 14 to 17 face the highest risk. Those who spent more than seven hours a day on screens were twice as likely to be diagnosed with anxiety and depression than those who spent only an hour.But younger kids and toddlers whose brains are still developing were also affected. Preschoolers with high screen use were twice as likely to lose their temper. Forty-six percent of youngsters were also more likely to not be able to calm down once excited.The findings validate the daily screen time limits set by the American Academy of Pediatrics  one hour for ages 2 to 5, and two for school-aged kids and adolescents.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Just one hour of screen time can negatively impact children and teens2. Adolescents most at risk for mental health problems due to screen time3. Younger kids whose brains are still developing also affected by screen time4. American Academy of Pediatrics daily screen time limitVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in Preventive Medicine Reports found that children and teens may have less curiosity, self-control, emotional stability, and a greater inability to finish tasks after just an hour of screen time a day.""Adolescents face the highest risk. Those who spent more than seven hours a day on screens were twice as likely to be diagnosed with anxiety and depression than those who spent only an hour.""But younger kids and toddlers whose brains are still developing were also affected. Preschoolers with high screen use were twice as likely to lose their temper.""The findings validate the daily screen time limits set by the American Academy of Pediatrics  one hour for ages two to five, and two for school-aged kids and adolescents."SOURCES: Preventive Medicine Reports, San Diego State University, The Independenthttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2211335518301827?via%3Dihubhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/10/181029150931.htmhttps://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/smartphones-mental-health-two-year-olds-anxiety-depression-tablets-a8617091.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/06/3726059/3726059_3674AE3E4279422998FFAFA614C9F1FD_181106_3726059_Screen_time_linked_to_mental_health_problems_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C07/23D/C0723D84970947A3949C55DB9BD93E93_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, screen time, mental health, anxiety, depression, kids mental health, children mental health, excessive screen time, smartphones, gaming, television, social media]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3726048</guid>
      <title>Study finds diverse gut bacteria of immigrants change once they arrive in the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGeographical location impacts the diversity of microbes present in a person's body, with some places corresponding to much more microbe diversity than others, according to a study published in the journal Cell.The study found that immigrants tend to eat a more Westernized diet, rich in sugar, fats and protein after arriving in the U.S., resulting in a 15 percent loss of microbiome diversity.The dominant species of the gut bacteria changed from a bacteria called "Prevotella" to a bacteria called "Bacteroides," which is commonly found in Western microbes. The "Prevotella" bacteria helps in digesting fibrous foods commonly found in Asia.As microbiome diversity in the body decreases, the risk of obesity and diabetes increases.The study was conducted with the Hmong and Karen community from Southeast Asia and found that first and second generation U.S. immigrants had an additional drop of 5-10 percent of gut bacteria, and ended up with similar gut bacteria to those whose families have a longer history in the U.S.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. World map, difference of microbes in bodies2. Western diet, pile of sugar, pile of fat and pile of protein3. Prevotella gut bacteria and Bacteroides gut bacteria4. Depiction of obesity, diabetes and a chart showing an increase of these two diseasesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the journal Cell, geographical location impacts the diversity of microbes present in a person's body, with some places corresponding to much more microbe diversity than others.""The study found that immigrants tend to eat a more Westernized diet, rich in sugar, fats and protein after arriving in the U.S., resulting in a 15 percent loss of microbiome diversity.""The dominant species of the gut bacteria changed from a bacteria called 'Prevotella' to a bacteria called 'Bacteroides,' which is commonly found in Western microbes." "As microbiome diversity in the body decreases, the risk of obesity and diabetes increases."SOURCES: The Washington Post, Quartz, NPR, Cell journal, Gizmodo, https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2018/11/02/immigrants-arrive-with-flourishing-gut-microbes-then-americas-diet-trashes-them/?utm_term=.ee228551ed2chttps://qz.com/1447740/immigrants-who-move-to-the-us-quickly-develop-an-american-microbiome/https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/11/01/662652885/immigrating-to-the-u-s-get-ready-for-a-new-gut-microbiome-and-maybe-more-poundshttps://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(18)31382-5https://gizmodo.com/immigrants-to-the-u-s-rapidly-gain-a-new-microbiome-1830149580***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/06/3726048/3726048_C6A42E45A19F492192C6F0B631F7DB67_181106_3726048_Study_finds_diverse_gut_bacteria_of_immigrants_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/443/6D3/4436D3F97E7545F18E6FF30ADD112C03_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, immigrants, gut bacteria, Prevotella, microbes, Bacteroides, microbiome diversity, diverse gut bacteria, microbes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3726648</guid>
      <title>Can antimatter fall upwards?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists at CERN plan to drop antimatter into a vacuum chamber to see if gravity affects it the same way it affects matter.Antimatter is identical to matter in every way, except that it has a negative charge, according to New Atlas.If matter and antimatter touch and interact with one another, they cancel each other out and annihilate each other.The first test scientists plan to conduct is called the ALPHA-g experiment in which the researchers will trap antihydrogen atoms in a vertical vacuum chamber and test to see what effect gravity has on the atoms.In the second experiment called GBAR, antihydrogen atoms generated from antiprotons will be subjected to a fall of 20 centimeters to see what effect gravity has on them.Scientists predict that antimatter should fall down like regular matter, but there is a one in a million chance that it could move upwards instead.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Antimatter molecule and vacuum chamber 2. ALPHA-g experiment3. GBAR experiment4. Prediction of how antimatter could fallVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists at CERN plan to drop antimatter into a vacuum chamber to see if gravity affects antimatter the same way it affects matter.""In the first experiment, the scientists plan to conduct is called the ALPHA-g experiment in which the researchers will trap antihydrogen atoms in a vertical vacuum chamber and test to see what effect gravity has on the atoms.""In the second experiment called GBAR, antihydrogen atoms generated from antiprotons will be subjected to a fall of 20 centimeters to see what effect gravity has on them.""Scientists predict that antimatter should fall down like regular matter, but there is a one in a million chance that it could fall up instead."SOURCES: New Atlas, Forbes, Digital Trends, Phys.org, https://newatlas.com/cern-antimatter-gravity-experiments/57090/https://www.forbes.com/sites/startswithabang/2018/10/26/is-anti-gravity-real-science-is-about-to-find-out/#5d69f2fa49a7https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/cern-antimatter-gravity/https://phys.org/news/2018-11-antimatter-gravity-cern.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 08:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/07/3726648/3726648_C2A5FB6D08B04F538521EBE51B09EE57_181107_3726648_Can_antimatter_fall_upwards__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DEF/0FB/DEF0FBA4E21A49F0859EACCA72C9D1B7_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, science, physics, antimatter, matter, matter vs antimatter, CERN, gravity experiment, antimatter gravity experiment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3726577</guid>
      <title>Taiwan would consider hosting U.S. warships on Taiping Island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan would consider allowing U.S. warships access to the largest of the Spratly Islands in the South China Sea for regional security purposes if requested by Washington. In response to a hypothetical question at the legislature on Monday, Taiwan's defense minister, Yen Teh-fa, said Taiwan could allow U.S. vessels to dock at Taiping Island for humanitarian operations, according to the SCMP. Six different countries including Taiwan and China lay claims to parts of the South China Sea. At the parliament panel meeting, Yen said Taiwan would consider allowing US vessels access to Taiping Island for humanitarian or regional security grounds if it were in the best interests of the country. According to lawmaker John Chiang, the regular presence of US aircraft carrier groups in international waters of the South China Sea were aimed at keeping China's military expansion in check. The U.S. Navy routinely conducts freedom of navigation sorties in international waters near the islets of the South China Sea, which draws heavy protests from China. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Taiping Island and U.S. warship2. U.S. vessel approaching Taiping Island3. U.S. carrier group sailing through open waters4. U.S. vessel conducting a freedom of navigation sortie in the South China SeaVOICEOVER (in English): "Taiwan would consider allowing U.S. warships access to the largest of the Spratly Islands in the South China Sea for regional security purposes if requested by Washington." "The SCMP reports in response to a hypothetical question at the legislature on Monday, Taiwan's defense minister, Yen Teh-fa, said Taiwan could allow U.S. vessels to dock at Taiping Island for humanitarian or regional security grounds." "Opposition lawmaker John Chiang said the regular presence of U.S. aircraft carrier groups in international waters of the South China Sea were aimed at keeping China's military expansion in check." "The U.S. Navy routinely conducts freedom of navigation sorties in international waters near the islets of the South China Sea, which draws heavy protests from China." SOURCES: SCMPhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/2171756/taiwan-will-consider-hosting-us-warships-spratly-island***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 07:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/07/3726577/3726577_B0645A3DF9C5468B9A1739885A5FC124_181107_3726577_Taiwan_would_consider_hosting_U_S__warships_on_T_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/83B/7E7/83B7E73BAE9849068500078ED6DEBE35_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Taiwan Taiping Island, South China Sea, Spratly Islands, US Navy, US warships]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3726572</guid>
      <title>A bubbling mud pool threatens infrastructure in California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA boiling mud pool originating from a geyser is slowly making its way in Southern California. According to Los Angeles Times, the mud pool, dubbed the "Slow One," began moving six months ago, advancing at an unprecedented rate. It began covering a distance of 18 meters over a few months, but now covers the same distance in a single day.The geyser is in close proximity to the San Andreas fault and is a result of seismic movements in the area. According to Live Science, earthquakes created deep fractures underground that allowed gases to move to the earth's surface, creating boiling mud pools heated by carbon dioxide.Despite its closeness to the famous fault, there is no data suggesting that the recent activities could lead to a large earthquake. However, local authorities are fearful for the damage this geologic phenomenon could cause to local infrastructure.Boiling mud has already forced the Union Pacific Railroad to build temporary tracks after the mud seeped through a barrier they had built to prevent it from damaging the railroad. The geyser is also threatening damage to a petroleum pipeline, fiber-optic telecommunications lines and a portion of a major highway. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. General location of Niland Geyser. 2. Explainer: How the Niland Geyser was created. 3. Movement of Niland Geyser mud on map. 4. Effects of Niland Geyser mud on infrastructure. VOICEOVER (in English): "The Niland Geyser, now named the 'Slow One',is located in California  near the San Andreas Fault." "The 'Slow One' is a result of seismic activity in the area. Earthquakes created deep fractures underground that allowed gases to move to the Earth's surface, creating boiling mud pools heated by carbon dioxide. " "According to The Los Angeles Times, the mud from the geyser began moving six months ago, advancing at an unprecedented rate.  First, moving 18 meters over a few months, to covering the same distance in a single day " "Barrier's built by the Union Pacific Railroad have failed to stop the boiling mud from reaching the tracks and forced them to construct temporary tracks. A petroleum pipeline, fiber-optic telecommunications lines and a portion of a nearby highway could also be damaged by the mud flow. " SOURCES: Los Angeles Times, Live Science. https://www.livescience.com/63998-mud-pool-creeping-across-california.htmlhttp://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-niland-mud-pot-20181101-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 07:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/07/3726572/3726572_A51DF1BA064C435EBCBA436CD3E58EB7_181107_3726572_A_bubbling_mud_pool_threatens_infrastructure_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/10C/A23/10CA235DB64A4B84AC3A7378B5251240_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, geyser, geyser eruption, mud pool, california, earthquake, geology, seismic, damage, infrastructure, nature, San Andreas, earthquake.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3727376</guid>
      <title>Could Trump be impeached by a Democratic House?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. midterm elections saw the Democratic Party take back control of the House of Representatives. Could a presidential impeachment now follow?According to CNN's national exit polls, 40 percent of voters want President Trump impeached. Seventy-seven percent of Democrats supported the move, compared to only five percent of Republicans and 33 percent of independents.With Democrats now in control of the House, they can initiate impeachment proceedings with an investigation by the House Judiciary Committee, and then vote to impeach with a simple majority.To get a conviction, they will need a two-thirds majority vote in the Senate. But with the Republicans remaining in control of the Senate with a 51-seat majority, this outcome is unlikely.While impeachment is a possibility, democratic leaders have indicated it is not the priority. They are, however, expected to launch investigations into the Trump administration.The Democratic House has plans to look into the president's tax returns, which he has refused to disclose, and restart the investigation into possible collusion with Russia.Trump said he would respond should the Democrats use their newly acquired investigative powers on him, adding that there may be retribution from the Republican Senate, reports Bloomberg.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Percentage of Democratic voters who want Trump impeached2. Impeachment investigation initiated by House Judiciary Committee3. Simple majority vote in House of Representatives needed to impeach4. Two-thirds majority vote in Senate needed to convict5. Republicans remain in control of Senate 6. Democrats launching investigations into Trump administration7. Democrats could look into Trump's tax returns, Russian collusionVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNN's national exit polls, 40 percent of voters want President Trump impeached. Seventy-seven percent of Democrats supported the move, compared to only five percent of Republicans and 33 percent of independents.""With Democrats now in control of the House, they can initiate impeachment proceedings with an investigation by the House Judiciary Committee, and then vote to impeach with a simple majority.""To get a conviction, they will need a two-thirds majority vote in the Senate.""But with the Republicans remaining in control of the Senate with a 51-seat majority, this outcome is unlikely.""While impeachment is a possibility, democrat leaders have indicated it is not the priority. They are, however, expected to launch investigations into the Trump administration.""The Democratic House has plans to look into the president's tax returns, which he has refused to disclose, and restart the investigation into possible collusion with Russia."SOURCES: CNN, Washington Post, Bloomberg, CBS, Independent, USA Todayhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/07/politics/investigations-house-democrats/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/07/politics/exit-polls-impeachment/index.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/midterm-elections-democrats-flip-house-as-gop-expands-senate-majority/2018/11/07/94d62430-e27d-11e8-8f5f-a55347f48762_story.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-07/trump-vows-war-like-posture-if-democrats-investigate-him?srnd=premiumhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/will-democrats-impeach-trump-now-that-they-control-the-house/https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/midterm-elections-2018-democrats-republicans-donald-trump-white-house-impeachment-a8620676.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2018/11/06/midterm-elections-2018-donald-trump-stakes-congress/1843578002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/08/3727376/3727376_13EB4A502EB54C919908FCE986B49A2A_181108_3727376_Could_Trump_be_impeached_by_a_Democratic_House__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/74B/707/74B7071276214F599F20BA979F71A7B3_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US midterms, midterm elections, midterms, midterm election results, impeachment, trump impeachment, trump, democrat house, republican senate, democrats, kavanaugh]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3727369</guid>
      <title>China unveils new stealth drone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation has debuted a next-generation stealth combat aircraft called CH-7.The unmanned aircraft has a wingspan of 22 meters, a length of 10 meters, and a cruise altitude of 10 to 13 km. It also has the ability to stay in the air for 15 hours, according to the Global Times.The CH-7 is capable of launching weapons such as anti-radiation missiles, long-distance precision-guided bombs, and more. It can also intercept radar electronic signals and detect high-value targets.The combat aircraft is currently being exhibited at the AirShow China 2018 exhibition in Zhuhai from November 6 to 11.The aircraft is scheduled to make its first flight in 2019 and will be available for mass production by 2022 if everything goes according to plan.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. CH-7 aircraft2. The length of the aircraft, as well as the aircraft in the air3. CH-7's weapons4. Other capabilities of the CH-7VOICEOVER (in English): "The China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation has debuted a next-generation stealth combat aircraft called CH-7.""According to the Global Times, the unmanned aircraft has a wingspan of 22 meters, a length of 10 meters, and a cruise altitude of 10 to 13 km. It also has the ability to stay in the air for 15 hours.""The CH-7 is capable of launching weapons such as anti-radiation missiles, long-distance precision-guided bombs, and more.""It can also intercept radar electronic signals and detect high-value targets."SOURCES: New York Times, Global Times, The Washington Post, The Drivehttps://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2018/11/06/world/asia/ap-as-china-new-drone.htmlhttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1125928.shtmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/china-unveils-stealth-combat-drone-in-development/2018/11/06/57a59898-e23c-11e8-ba30-a7ded04d8fac_story.html?utm_term=.d6bd5c890194http://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/24645/chinas-biggest-airshow-offers-more-evidence-of-beijings-stealth-drone-focus***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/08/3727369/3727369_6AEB689AAB0E45B5A9EFF514A6DAC630_181108_3727369_China_unveils_new_stealth_drone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9F6/635/9F6635BF204848D3A4621E9C7CC9095A_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, stealth drone, CH-7, China CH-7, combat aircraft, china combat aircraft CH-7]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3727169</guid>
      <title>China increases security spending in Xinjiang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBeijing has increased security expenditures in Xinjiang, where it's reported to have detained ethnic Muslim minorities.According to an analysis of Chinese government budget by U.S. think tank the Jamestown Foundation, spending on security-related construction in the western region of Xinjiang rose by 213 percent in 2017.The spending pattern is consistent with the construction and operation of highly secure political re-education camps meant to detain Uighurs.Mass disappearances of Uighur minorities since 2017 likely resulted in imprisonment in these camps, where former detainees say they had to endure intense political and cultural indoctrination.But while prison spending increased by 94 percent, formal prosecutions stagnated, indicating that many are detained without a trial or with minimal due process.China claims the institutions are vocational training centers, but figures show vocational spending in the same year actually decreased by 7 percent.The country's human rights record is set to be reviewed by the UN human rights council, which is expected to focus on its treatment of minorities like Uighurs and Tibetans, reports the Guardian.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Spending on security-related construction in Xinjiang up by 213% in 20172. Depiction of political re-education camps for Uighurs3. Depiction of Uighurs detained with minimal due process4. Vocational expenditures decreased by 7%VOICEOVER (in English): "An analysis of Chinese government budget by a U.S. think tank revealed that spending on security-related construction in Xinjiang rose by 213 percent in 2017.""The spending pattern is consistent with the construction and operation of highly secure political re-education camps meant to detain Uighurs.""But while prison spending increased by 94 percent, formal prosecutions stagnated, indicating that many are detained without a trial or with minimal due process.""China claims the institutions are vocational training centers, but figures show vocational spending in the same year actually decreased by 7 percent."SOURCES: Jamestown Foundation, Reuters, The Guardian, CNNhttps://jamestown.org/program/xinjiangs-re-education-and-securitization-campaign-evidence-from-domestic-security-budgets/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang-idUSKCN1NB0AThttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/06/china-human-rights-xinjiang-un-councilhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/06/asia/xinjiang-uyghur-crackdown-china-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/08/3727169/3727169_9E5242C415254696AB6AF5DF786ADD8B_181108_3727169_China_increases_security_spending_in_Xinjiang_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/3C9/776/3C9776F15199483BA7BF8ADC2BC076AD_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, uyghur, uighur, xinjiang, uyghur crackdown, uyghur camp, china surveillance, minorities, Muslim minorities, ethnic minorities, China, education camps, China human rights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3727089</guid>
      <title>How do we know Earth is round?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOur planet's shape can be verified in many ways.Earth's globe-like shape can be easily observed in the shadow it casts on the moon's equally round surface. The shadow is always curved at any given time of the lunar phases.Earth's round edges can also be seen in the horizon. Objects nearing it seem to "appear" and "disappear," depending on which way they are moving. We can see this effect when we observe ships in the ocean. If we were to see the horizon from above, we would also be able to see Earth's surface curve at the edges. Earth's circular form also determines the time zone differences we experience. Time zones are a result of Earth's rotation on its axis.Its spherical shape allows for this as its sides would be exposed to sunlight at a given time while the other side remains dark. This would not be possible over a flat surface. We can also observe the properties of other planets in our solar system. According to Futurism, planets' spherical shapes allow for an equal distribution of gravity. If Earth were a disc-like body, its gravity would pull us at different degrees depending where we stand. Gravity cannot be distributed evenly on non-spherical surfaces.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Earth's shape proven by shadow on moon2. Earth's shape proven by horizon3. Earth's shape proven by time zones4. Earth's shape proven by gravityVOICEOVER (in English): "The Earth's spherical shape can be easily observed in the shadow it casts on the moon's equally round surface. The shadow is always curved at any given time of the lunar phases.""Earth's round edges can also be seen in the horizon. Objects nearing it seem to 'appear' and 'disappear' depending on the direction they are moving towards. We can see this effect when we observe ships in the ocean. If we were to see the horizon from above, we would also be able to see Earth's surface curve at the edges." "The Earth's circular form also determines the time zone differences we experience. Time Zones are a result of Earth's rotation on its axis.""It's spherical shape only allows for one if its sides to be exposed to sunlight at a given time while the other side is dark. This would not be possible over a flat surface." "We can also observe the properties of other planets in our solar system. According to Futurism, planets' spherical shape allow for an equal distribution of gravity. If Earth were a disc-like body, its gravity would pull us at different degrees depending on where we stand. Gravity cannot be distributed evenly on non-spherical surfaces." SOURCES: Popular Science, Futurism. https://www.popsci.com/10-ways-you-can-prove-earth-is-roundhttps://futurism.com/why-are-the-planets-spherical***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 02:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/08/3727089/3727089_07A037A1D4924A8DB45EFCB5F06A64DC_181108_3727089_How_do_we_know_Earth_is_round__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9FC/998/9FC998D15014478F80934615D593CBFA_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sphere, globe, earth, flat earth, earth is not flat, gravity, curve, horizon, surface.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3728080</guid>
      <title>How a Florida recount works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWith extremely close margins in the races for U.S. senate and agriculture commissioner, and a governor's race that is nearing the threshold, it appears as if Florida could be headed for recounts.According to the Miami Herald, unofficial statewide results have to be reported to the state elections office before a recount can be officially ordered. Counties must turn in their unofficial returns by noon on Saturday, Nov. 10. The secretary of state is required to order a machine recount if the margin in a statewide election is less than 0.5 percent. Losing candidates can refuse a recount. If an automated recount is ordered, the second round of unofficial returns would be due from counties by 3 p.m. on Thursday Nov. 15.    In a machine recount, damaged ballots are copied, all ballots are re-scanned and then the number of total votes cast according to the machines are compared with the number of votes initially tallied by the county.If the machine recount numbers are similar, the vote is counted as accurate. And if the margin in the race is larger than 0.25 percent, the results are counted as official. If the margin after the second round of machine counting falls below 0.25 percent, then Florida can order a manual recount for federal and state elections. A manual recount involves counting each overvote and undervote by hand. An overvote refers to voters marking more choices than permitted on the ballot. An undervote means the voter made no choice or fewer than the number of allowable choices on the ballot.   On Nov. 16, overseas and military ballots are counted. Counties need to give official returns by noon on Nov. 18. Official results from counties are then certified by the state on Nov. 20. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Machine recount ordered if margin is less than 0.5 percent2. Scenarios if machine recount margin is greater or less than 0.25 percent3. Manual recount4. Overvote and undervote examplesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Florida secretary of state is required to order a machine recount if the margin in a statewide election is less than 0.5 percent." "In a machine recount, damaged ballots are copied, all ballots are re-scanned and then the number of total votes cast according to the machines are compared with the number of votes initially tallied by the county.""If the machine recount numbers are similar, the vote is counted as accurate. And if the margin in the race is larger than 0.25 percent, the results are counted as official." "If the margin after the second round of machine counting falls below 0.25 percent, then Florida can order a manual recount for federal and state elections." "A manual recount involves counting each overvote and undervote by hand." "An overvote refers to voters marking more choices than permitted on the ballot. An undervote means the voter made no choice or fewer than the number of allowable choices on the ballot."   SOURCES: Miami Heraldhttps://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/election/article221342415.htmlhttps://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/election/article221348405.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/09/3728080/3728080_850A0223819B4648A27B1DC7FCE06EE1_181109_3728080_How_a_Florida_recount_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DA7/2DF/DA72DF2C612248C697E6897144978DAB_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Florida vote recount, vote recount, manual recount, machine recount, recount explainer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3728063</guid>
      <title>Midterm elections made history with notable firsts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe midterm elections turned out to be a historic night of firsts for Native American, Muslim, LGBT and female candidates. According to NPR, congress will see its first Native American and Muslim congresswomen, its first lesbian mom in Congress and the first openly gay man elected as a governor. South Dakota and Maine elected their first female governors, Tennessee and Arizona are sending their first women to the Senate, and Massachusetts and Connecticut selected their first black women to the House. According to CBS News, Democrat Sharice Davids, a member of the Ho-Chunk Nation, won Kansas' 3rd District seat, while Democrat Debra Haaland, a member of the Pueblo of Laguna won in New Mexico's 1st District to become the first Native American congresswomen. Democrats Ilhan Omar of Minnesota and Rashida Tlaib of Michigan both won their house races to become the first Muslim women in Congress. In Colorado, Democrat Jared Polis became the first openly gay man elected as governor. According to CBS News, more than 90 women were elected to the House, making it the most number of women to win House seats in American history.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Midterms were firsts for Native American, Muslim, LGBT and female candidates2. Native American candidates elected to Congress3. Muslim candidates elected to Congress4. First openly gay governorVOICEOVER (in English): "The midterm elections turned out to be a historic day of firsts for Native American, Muslim, LGBT and female candidates." "According to CBS News, Democrat Sharice Davids, a member of the Ho-Chunk Nation, won Kansas' 3rd District seat, while Democrat Debra Haaland, a member of the Pueblo of Laguna won in New Mexico's 1st District to become the first Native American congresswomen." "Democrats Ilhan Omar of Minnesota's 5th Congressional District and Rashida Tlaib of Michigan's 13th Congressional District both won their house races to become the first Muslim women in Congress." "In Colorado, Democrat Jared Polis became the first openly gay man elected as governor."SOURCES: NPR, CBS News, The Guardianhttps://www.npr.org/2018/11/07/665118634/the-midterm-elections-have-made-history-with-these-notable-firsts?utm_campaign=storyshare&utm_source=twitter.com&utm_medium=socialhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/election-2018-night-of-firsts-with-historic-wins-for-muslims-native-americans-women-and-lgbt-candidates/https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/06/midterms-2018-first-history-making-election-wins***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/09/3728063/3728063_91F0195A72754531AA67AFD3345B6836_181109_3728063_Midterm_elections_made_history_with_notable_firs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/22E/0CE/22E0CEA8AFCE4AF7875180C483BA8DFB_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Midterm elections, Midterm elections 2018, Midterm election firsts, Midterm elections notable firsts, Elections historic firsts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3727916</guid>
      <title>HORMONE BOOSTS REGENERATION OF AMPUTATED LIMBS IN FROGS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers led by Tufts University scientists have developed a wearable bioreactor that uses progesterone to induce tissue regeneration. The device was tested on adult aquatic African clawed frogs, a species already capable of partial limb regeneration.The 3-D printed bioreactor is made from silicon and filled with hydrogel. The gel is a mix of silk proteins that aid healing and progesterone, a hormone that prompts tissue repair.According to their study, published in the journal Cell Reports, frogs in the experiment had one of their hind legs amputated approximately at the center of the femur. The wounds of the frogs were either treated with the bioreactor, protected by the device without progesterone or left untreated. All groups had their devices removed after 24 hours. After nine and a half months, the the group that had worn the bioreactors with progesterone grew a paddle-like structure with bones, nerves and blood vessels. Those which did not grew a cartilaginous spike-like structure. The use of progesterone proved to alter the limbs at an functional and anatomical level. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Introduction of African clawed frog2. Introduction of experimentation groups3. Explanation of components of bioreactor: progesterone and hydrogel4. Results: Bioreactor proves to aid in tissue regenerationVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers led by Tufts University scientists have developed a wearable bioreactor that uses progesterone to induce tissue regeneration. The device was tested on adult aquatic African clawed frogs, a species already capable of partial limb regeneration.""According to their study, published in the journal Cell Reports, frogs in the experiment had one of their hind legs amputated.""The wounds were either treated with the bioreactor, protected by the device but without progesterone or left untreated. ""The 3-D printed bioreactor is made from silicon and filled with hydrogel. The gel is a mix of silk proteins and progesterone, a hormone that prompts tissue repair.""All groups had their devices removed after 24 hours. After nine and a half months, the the group that had worn the bioreactors with progesterone grew a paddle-like structure with bones, nerves and blood vessels. Those which did not grew a cartilaginous spike-like structure."SOURCES: Cell Reporthttps://www.cell.com/cell-reports/fulltext/S2211-1247(18)31573-0?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS2211124718315730%3Fshowall%3Dtrue***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 07:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/09/3727916/3727916_AEE1329B3DB141298073D85C96D9D335_181109_3727916_HORMONE_BOOSTS_REGENERATION_OF_AMPUTATED_LIMBS_I_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/2C7/4AA/2C74AAE49ADF4B5C805175585A68E2A8_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hydrogel device, spike, frog, bioelectricity, regeneration, limb, bioreactor, research, study, experiment.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3727896</guid>
      <title>China set to build new 'supersonic' train</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina plans to develop next-generation vehicles similar to Elon Musk's Hyperloop.Reuters reports that Chinese automaker Geely has signed a deal with the China Aerospace Science and Industry Corp. to build a network of ultra-fast trains.The proposed system will use magnetic levitation to allow the trains to float inches above the rail tracks, which eliminates ground friction and increases speed. Like the Hyperloop, the trains will be propelled through vacuum tubes to reduce air resistance.Though not technically supersonic, the trains will travel faster than conventional ones at speeds of up to 1,000 kph, with an aim to reach 4,000 kph in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Geely, CASIC sign agreement to develop ultra-fast train2. Depiction of magnetic levitation technology3. Depiction of trains propelled through vacuum tube4. Depiction of initial and future train speedVOICEOVER (in English): "Chinese automaker Geely has signed a deal with state-owned China Aerospace Science and Industry Corporation to build a network of ultra-fast trains.""The proposed system will use magnetic levitation to allow the trains to float inches above the rail tracks. "This eliminates ground friction and increases speed.""Like the Hyperloop, the trains will be propelled through vacuum tubes to reduce air resistance." "Though not technically supersonic, the trains will travel faster than conventional ones. "This will initially be at speeds of up to 1,000 kph, with an aim to reach 4,000 kph in the future."SOURCES: Reuters, Telegraph, Bloomberghttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-zj-geely-hldg-casic-trains/geely-china-aerospace-firm-agree-to-work-on-supersonic-trains-idUSKCN1NB0XVhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/06/chinese-car-billionaire-signs-deal-build-supersonic-trains/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-06/chinese-car-billionaire-li-sets-sights-on-supersonic-trains***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 06:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/09/3727896/3727896_446214D7F3244A0885A8C41170ED3C63_181109_3727896_China_set_to_build_new__supersonic__train_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/200/CB1/200CB18C58FC46AD9F783C623707DDFD_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, supersonic train, china supersonic train, maglev, hyperloop, elon musk, future transportation, next generation trains, Geely, CASIC]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3729632</guid>
      <title>How the Thousand Oaks shooting unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA dozen people are dead after a gunman opened fire inside a packed bar in California last Wednesday night.USA Today reports that over a hundred college students were inside the Borderline Bar & Grill in Thousand Oaks for Country College Night when gunman Ian David Long approached outside and shot the security guard with a .45-caliber Glock 21.The 28-year-old then threw a smoke bomb inside the premises and shot at employees near the front, before firing into the crowd of people on the dance floor.Scared patrons began fleeing. Some used bar stools to break the windows and escape.Others ran out the back, hid under pool tables, in the attic, or in the bathroom.Ventura County deputy Ron Helus was first at the scene with a highway officer. They engaged the suspect in a shootout, but Deputy Telus was shot several times and later died. In all, 12 people were killed in the shooting.According to the Los Angeles Times, Long was dead when officers found him at the scene, and an autopsy later determined he had died from a self-inflicted gunshot.Long had been a former Marine machine gunner, and is said to have carried the attack out with military efficiency, though authorities have yet to determine a motive.A former coach described him as physically combative during his teen years, while  a mental health specialist that assessed him recently thought he could be suffering from PTSD.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman shoots security guard outside bar2. Gunman throws smoke bomb, shoots at people behind bar3. Patrons fleeing bar as gunman continues firing; deputy injured in shootout4. Gunman dies from self-inflicted gunshotVOICEOVER (in English): "Over a hundred college students were inside a Thousand Oaks bar when gunman Ian David Long approached outside and shot the security guard with a .45-caliber Glock 21.""The 28-year-old then threw a smoke bomb inside and shot at employees near the front, before firing into the crowd of people on the dance floor.""Scared patrons began fleeing. Some used bar stools to break the windows and escape.""A Ventura County deputy arrived at the scene with a highway officer and engaged the suspect in a shootout, but was shot several times and later died. In all, 12 were killed in the shooting.""Long reportedly shot himself, and was dead when officers found him at the scene."SOURCES: USA Today, CNN, Los Angeles Times, Ventura County Starhttps://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/2018/11/08/thousand-oaks-shooting-timeline/1931287002/https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/11/08/thousand-oaks-shooting-victims/1932896002/https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/09/us/california-thousand-oaks-shooting-how-it-unfolded/index.htmlhttp://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-ln-borderline-shooter-20181110-story.htmlhttps://www.vcstar.com/story/news/2018/11/08/thousand-oaks-shooting-timeline-what-happened-shooter-ian-david-long/1930716002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/12/3729632/3729632_E72EBC7A255346D79C45FD3FCD5FEF9A_181112_3729632_How_the_Thousand_Oaks_shooting_unfolded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/04C/FC1/04CFC1E1F5814DBBA0C41921EBB2FC44_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, shooting, mass shooting, thousand oaks, thousand oaks shooting, california shooting, timeline, california shooting timeline]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3729448</guid>
      <title>Harvard astrophyscists claim space rock could be an alien probe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[New theoretical research by Harvard scientists suggests that the solar systems first interstellar object might be an alien probe.Oumuamua was first observed by the Panoramic Survey Telescope and Rapid Response System in Hawaii in October 2017. The name means a messenger that reaches out from the distant past in Hawaiian.Research published in the journal Nature last year says it is the first interstellar object to enter our solar system and said it would travel inside it for over a year. Scientists werent sure if it was an asteroid or a comet, so they referred to it as an interstellar object. Oumuamua is 800 meters in length and 80 meters in width, according to Astronomy.com.Scientists speculated last year that it may consist of materials like metals or rocks.A yet-to-be-published theoretical study accepted in Astrophysical Journal Letters puts forward a number of theories on the object, including ideas that it may be extraterrestrial in origin. They theorize Oumuamua might be using a light sail to travel.This technology uses light to propel objects through space. The researchers write that it could be used to transport cargo between planets or stars. Another theory, the researchers describe as a more exotic scenario, is that Oumuamua is a fully working space probe sent to Earth by an alien civilization. However this claim has been disputed by other astronomers.Astrophysicist Alan Fitzsimmons told the AFP that this wasnt evidence of alien life.He explained that Oumuamua has already show characteristics similar to that of a comet from another star system.When NASA observed it last year, they said the object was traveling at 64,000 kph. The space agency noted Oumuamua would exit the solar system in January 2019 after passing through Saturns orbit. Its next destination is the Pegasus constellation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/12/3729448/3729448_1941B9A230B7432FAF3CBC2B3E2CC4CE_181112_3729448_Harvard_astrophyscists_claim_space_rock_could_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BCC/131/BCC131BF6E25476F9A346E1E8ACECF45_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Educational,animation,3D,graphics,Next Animation,Next Media,feature,sidebar,video,explainer,image,illustration,graphic,Oumuamua,Harvard,alien spacecraft,oumuamua trajectory,solar system,interstellar object,oumuamua interstellar object]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3729332</guid>
      <title>Xinhua News Agency debuts AI news anchors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese state media is using "virtual" anchors to read the news.Xinhua News Agency partnered with search engine Sogou.com to create artificial intelligence news anchors. These are said to be digital composites that deliver the news.The composites use the likeness of real Xinhua presenters. However, facial expressions and mouth movements are synthesized and animated via deep learning.AI anchors are able to read out any text inputted by human editors into its system, using synthetic voices created through composite audio recorded from the human anchors.The virtual anchors are reportedly able to read out any text written by human editors into their program. This is said to use synthetic voices created through composite audio recorded from human anchors.Xinhua has two AI anchors, one delivering news in English and another in Chinese. They claim these can work 24 hours a day on its website and social media.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Xinhua News Agency's artificial intelligence news anchors 2. Digital composites combine human likeness with animated expressions, mouth movements3. Text inputted into system, read out using synthetic voice4. Anchors can work 24 hours, delivering news in English and ChineseVOICEOVER (in English): "Xinhua News Agency partnered with search engine Sogou.com to create artificial intelligence news anchors. "These are said to be digital composites that deliver the news.""The composites use the likeness of real Xinhua presenter. However, facial expressions and mouth movements are synthesized and animated via deep learning.""The virtual anchors are reportedly able to read out any text written by human editors into their program.""This is said to use synthetic voices created through composite audio recorded from human anchors.""Xinhua has two AI anchors, one delivering news in English and another in Chinese. "The state-run news agency claims they can work 24 hours a day on its website and social media." "They say this reduces production costs and increases efficiency."SOURCES: Xinhua News Agency, South China Morning Post, BBChttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-11/08/c_137591813.htmhttps://www.scmp.com/tech/innovation/article/2172235/xinhua-news-agency-debuts-ai-anchors-partnership-search-engine-sogouhttps://www.bbc.com/news/technology-46136504***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/12/3729332/3729332_355981030A28434AA3EDB104F54B16B4_181112_3729332_Xinhua_News_Agency_debuts_AI_news_anchors_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/666/AFA/666AFA5865B24E9F921DB509F7869375_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, AI anchor, AI news anchor, artificial intelligence, Xinhua, Xinhua AI anchor, virtual news anchor, AI clone, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3729291</guid>
      <title>Mushroom and bacteria turn light into clean energy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team from the Stevens Institute of Technology have developed a 'power mushroom' able to create renewable energy. According to their study, published in the paper Nano Journal, the team used button mushrooms due to their optimal levels of humidity and temperature which make them exceptional hosts to bacteria.  They then employed 3D printing technology to create a pattern of graphene nanoribbons on the cap of a living mushroom. They then printed cyanobacteria on top of the pattern using special 'bio-ink'.This bacteria was selected due to its efficiency in converting sunlight to energy. According to researchers who participated in the study it has 'an internal quantum efficiency of nearly 100%.'The team is calling this 'engineered bionic symbiosis'. The mushroom provides the cyanobacteria with shelter and nutrients which allows the bacteria to thrive and in turn create more energy. Exposing mushroom to light triggers cyanobacterial photosynthesis during which the bacteria releases electrons that are in turn captured by the strips of graphene. According to a news release by the American Chemical Society, the team managed to generate 65 nanoamps of electric energy. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Button mushrooms bacteria-friendly cap 2. 3D printing of graphene nanoribbons on mushroom3. Cyanobacteria 3D printed on mushroom: Explanation of its qualities4. "Power mushroom" creates 65 nanoamps of electric energyVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Nano Letters, American Chemical Societyhttps://pubs.acs.org/doi/ipdf/10.1021/acs.nanolett.8b02642https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2018-11/acs-abm110218.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 01:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/12/3729291/3729291_118FF8C890614B5CBEE624140CCD199A_181112_3729291_Mushroom_and_bacteria_turn_light_into_clean_ener_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/7FE/8AF/7FE8AFAE8EE74E048346BEDD81134CF9_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, renewable energy, renewable and nonrenewable sources, clean energy, clean energy technology, bioengineering, climate change.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3730313</guid>
      <title>Forecasted Santa Ana winds could feed Woolsey fire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFire officials are concerned high Santa Ana winds forecasted for the next several days could help spread the 85,500-acre Woolsey fire in Ventura and Los Angeles counties.   According to the L.A. Times, the fire, which has killed two people and caused the evacuation of more than 250,000 people from Malibu to Thousand Oaks, was only 15 percent contained as of Sunday night. The forecast is calling for wind gusts of 40 miles per hour or stronger over the next few days. According to officials, the blaze has destroyed more than 177 buildings, with around 57,000 structures still at risk.Firefighters are now concerned that potential wind gusts could suddenly change directions, affecting the fire.  Strong winds could also hamper the effectiveness of aerial water and retardant drops. As of Sunday, several parts of Los Angeles and Ventura counties  including Malibu, Agoura Hills, Westlake VIllage, Hidden Hills and parts of West Hills, Monte Nido, Gated Oaks and Topanga  remained under voluntary or mandatory evacuation orders. Wildfires across the state have burned nearly 200,000 acres and killed at least 31 people, according to fire officials. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Santa Ana winds blowing through hills on fire2. Wind gusts of 40 mph or stronger forecasted3. Wind changing directions4. Winds effects on fire fightingVOICEOVER (in English): "Fire officials are concerned high Santa Ana winds forecasted for the next several days could help spread the 85,500-acre Woolsey fire in Ventura and Los Angeles counties."   "The forecast is calling for wind gusts of 40 mph or stronger over the next few days." "Firefighters are now concerned that potential wind gusts could suddenly change directions, affecting the behavior of the fire."  "Strong winds could also hamper the effectiveness of aerial water and retardant drops, restricting firefighters to battle the blaze solely from the ground."    SOURCES: LA TIMEShttp://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-woolsey-fire-latest-20181111-story.html?outputType=amp***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/13/3730313/3730313_8FDAF585CA0348219736293AAF646840_181113_3730313_Forecasted_Santa_Ana_winds_could_feed_Woolsey_fi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C0E/34B/C0E34B89F14C405CB203758EB07251A2_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, California fires, California wildfires, California Woolsey fire, Santa Ana winds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3729925</guid>
      <title>China's plans to modify the weather</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Chinese Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation is planning to send rain-inducing machines across the Tibetan Plateau to increase rainfall in the region.Tens of thousands of machines will be installed on the Tibetan mountains and is expected to increase rainfall by up to 10 billion cubic meters a year over an area of 1.6 million square kilometers, reports the South China Morning Post.The machines will produce fine silver iodide particles which would then be lifted into the air with the winds.These particles will then be circulated into the atmosphere.Each rain machine is expected to create a 4.8-kilometer-long strip of clouds.Lei Fanpei, the president of the corporation, told the South China Post that modifying Tibet's weather "is a critical innovation to solve China's water shortage problem."The mountains of Tibet provide a huge source of water in China as its glaciers and underground reservoirs supply water to the Yangtze, Mekong and the Yellow River. However, this isn't the first time China made plans to modify the weather. The country has manipulated the weather during the 2008 Beijing Olympics in order to prevent it from raining during the event.China had even artificially induced snow a couple of years ago in Beijing, according to a report from China Daily.China plans to monitor the system through weather satellites and supplement silver iodide particles from planes and drones in order to maximize its effect.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rain-inducing machine and Tibetan Plateau2. Tibetan mountains, vertical bar chart and rain icon3. Silver iodine particles being released into the air4. Silver iodine particles causing it to rainVOICEOVER (in English): "The Chinese Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation is planning to send rain-inducing machines across the Tibetan Plateau to increase rainfall in the region.""The South China Morning Post reports tens of thousands of machines will be installed on the Tibetan mountains and is expected to increase rainfall by up to 10 billion cubic meters a year over an area of 1.6 million square kilometers.""The machines will produce fine silver iodide particles which would then be lifted into the air with the winds.These particles will then be circulated into the atmosphere.""Each rain machine is expected to create a 4.8-kilometer-long strip of clouds."SOURCES: Forbes, News.com.au, South China Morning Post, China Daily, Business Insider, Fox News, https://www.forbes.com/sites/trevornace/2018/05/10/china-is-launching-a-massive-weather-control-machine-the-size-of-alaska/#989099763155https://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/inventions/china-will-control-its-weather-through-building-thousands-of-rainseeding-machines/news-story/18ce7bb1ce39ba66baa6ec01d6c51aa2https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2138866/china-needs-more-water-so-its-building-rain-making-network-threehttp://www.chinadaily.com.cn/china/2016-09/14/content_26793165.htmhttp://www.chinadaily.com.cn/2009-11/11/content_8954008.htmhttps://www.businessinsider.com/china-sets-aside-millions-to-control-the-rain-2016-7https://www.foxnews.com/science/chinas-massive-plan-to-control-the-weather***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 03:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/13/3729925/3729925_9E400B5A51D34E33AC95AF60229F2FA8_181113_3729925_China_s_plans_to_modify_the_weather_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1E1/FFD/1E1FFD7310A94A3B87525D39D222C5D0_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space, China weather system, rain-inducing machines, china weather control, china weather machine, rain-inducing machines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3729919</guid>
      <title>Trump hotel in Bali could contribute to water crisis</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA project to develop a Trump hotel in Bali could threaten the island's water supply. On August 14, 2015, then-presidential candidate Donald Trump signed an agreement in collaboration with Indonesian investor Hary Tanoesoedibjo's MNC Group to develop the Trump International Hotel and Tower Bali, the SCMP reports.The proposed "six-star" resort and 18-hole golf course are set to be built on a cliff-top site previously home to the Pan Pacific Nirwana Bali, according to the SCMP. Of particular concern is the proposed development's environmental impact on the water supply. According the NPR, Audubon International estimates the average American golf course requires about 312,000 gallons of water a day.According to Deutsche Welle, over half of Bali's groundwater is used by the island's tourism industry. The industry's water demands are putting Bali's rice terraces and subak irrigation system at risk. Deep bore wells drilled by hotels and villa-based resorts have led to saltwater leaking into and contaminating groundwater. The tourism industry has caused as many as 260 of Bali's 400-plus rivers to dry up, Vice reports.If the Trump development is completed as planned, it would be the largest resort on the island. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of proposed Trump hotel and golf course2. Golf courses require around 312,000 gallons of water a day3. Tourism uses half the island's groundwater and threatens subak irrigation system4. Borewells and dried up rivers in BaliVOICEOVER (in English): "A project to develop a Trump hotel in Bali could threaten the island's water supply." "The SCMP reports the proposed "six-star" resort and 18-hole golf course are set to be built on a cliff-top site previously home to the Pan Pacific Nirwana Bali.""Of particular concern is the proposed development's environmental impact on the water supply. According the NPR, Audubon International estimates the average American golf course requires about 312,000 gallons of water a day.""Deutsche Welle reports over half of Bali's groundwater is used by the island's tourism industry. The industry's water demands are putting Bali's rice terraces and subak irrigation system at risk." "Deep borewells drilled by hotels and villa-based resorts have led to saltwater leaking into and contaminating groundwater." "Meanwhile, Vice reports the tourism industry has caused as many as 260 of Bali's 400-plus rivers to dry up."SOURCES: SCMP, DW, NPR, Vice https://www.scmp.com/magazines/post-magazine/travel/article/2171904/trumps-new-hotel-bali-draws-attention-islandshttps://www.dw.com/en/trump-hotel-threatens-to-suck-bali-dry/a-46130974?maca=en-Twitter-sharinghttps://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=91363837https://www.vice.com/en_asia/article/qvexem/balis-tourism-is-sucking-the-island-dry***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 02:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/13/3729919/3729919_7C2E6B47B73D475FB2E48E71580B7892_181113_3729919_Trump_hotel_in_Bali_could_contribute_to_water_cr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/0DD/E6F/0DDE6FEAAFF048C7A9EB3A3007BCB9CA_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump Hotel, Trump Hotel Bali, Trump MNC Group, Trump, Hary Tanoesoedibjo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3731050</guid>
      <title>El Chapo trial begins in New York amid tight security</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe trial of accused Mexican drug lord Joaquin 'El Chapo' Guzman has begun in New York amid unprecedented security measures.According to the New York Times, the El Chapo case will be heard by an anonymous jury, each of whom are driven to and from their homes to the Federal Court in Brooklyn by armed escorts.Heavily armed federal marshals and officers with bomb-sniffing dogs have been deployed to stand guard outside the courthouse. Inside, visitors must pass through metal detectors before entering the courtroom.El Chapo himself is transported from solitary confinement in Manhattan to court via police motorcade, which includes an ambulance and SWAT team, and shuts down the Brooklyn Bridge each time.More than a dozen witnesses are set to take the stand during the trial, and risk retribution by doing so. Because of this, the court has taken steps to conceal their identities, and have even barred courtroom artists from drawing them, reports Al Jazeera.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Anonymous jurors driven to and from their homes by armed escorts2. Federal marshals, officers with bomb-sniffing dogs guard courthouse3. Visitors go through metal detectors before entering courtroom4. Police motorcade takes El Chapo from prison to courtVOICEOVER (in English): "The El Chapo case will be heard by an anonymous jury, each of whom are driven to and from their homes to the Federal Court in Brooklyn by armed escorts.""Heavily armed federal marshals and officers with bomb-sniffing dogs have been deployed to stand guard outside the courthouse.""Inside, visitors must pass through metal detectors before entering the courtroom.""El Chapo himself is transported from solitary confinement in Manhattan to court via police motorcade, which also includes an ambulance and SWAT team, and shuts down the Brooklyn Bridge each time."SOURCES: CNN, Al Jazeera, New York Timeshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/13/us/el-chapo-guzman-new-york-trial/index.htmlhttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/trial-mexico-el-chapo-heavy-security-181113133401793.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/02/06/nyregion/el-chapo-jurors-trial-secrecy.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/15/3731050/3731050_B48F67387BAF4D058EB1DB576A57D1CD_181115_3731050_El_Chapo_trial_begins_in_New_York_amid_tight_sec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BED/855/BED8554C191243FB9D3F1E14BB19D4EC_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, el chapo, chapo, chapo trial, security measures, guzman trial, heavy security, armed escorts, SWAT, security detail]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3730580</guid>
      <title>Hidden missile bases in North Korea seen in satellite images</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSatellite images have located 13 of an estimated 20 undeclared missile operating bases in North Korea.Specifically, the Sakkanmol missile base, which is around 85 miles from Seoul, is shown in satellite images to be located amidst mountainous terrain.The Sakkanmol missile base includes barracks, underground facilities to house the transporter-erector-launches (TELs) or mobile-erector-launchers (MELs), and vehicle maintenance and storage, according to a study by a Washington think tank.Satellite images also show the base's checkpoint, headquarters building, maintenance depots and entrances to underground tunnels that could potentially hide the missiles and the trucks that transport them.The missile operating bases are not launch facilities. However, missiles could be launched from there in an event of an emergency.Victor Cha, a prominent North Korean expert, claims the missile bases are actively in use and are not "decaying."This comes amid reports that North Korea was dismantling a key missile site in July.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korea on map2. Sakkanmol missile base and Seoul3. Facilities seen on the Sakkanmol missile base4. Other facilities on the Sakkanmol missile base with missile and truckVOICEOVER (in English): "Satellite images have located 13 of an estimated 20 undeclared missile operating bases in North Korea.""Specifically, the Sakkanmol missile base, which is around 85 miles from Seoul, is shown in satellite images to be located amidst mountainous terrain. ""According to a study by a Washington think tank, the Sakkanmol missile base includes barracks, underground facilities to house the transporter-erector-launches (TELs) or mobile-erector-launchers (MELs), and vehicle maintenance and storage.""Satellite images also show the base's checkpoint, headquarters building, maintenance depots and entrances to underground tunnels that could potentially hide the missiles and the trucks that transport them."SOURCES: New York Times, USA Today, CNN, NPR, The Washington Post, Beyond Parallel, https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/12/us/politics/north-korea-missile-bases.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/11/12/north-korea-has-least-13-secret-ballistic-missile-bases/1976942002/https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/12/politics/north-korea-hidden-missile-bases/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/2018/11/12/667028095/commercial-satellites-reveal-north-korean-missile-basehttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2018/11/12/newly-revealed-north-korean-missile-bases-cast-doubt-value-trumps-summit-with-kim-jong-un/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.657bd33ef5a5https://beyondparallel.csis.org/north-koreas-undeclared-missile-operating-bases/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/14/3730580/3730580_D0BEB8A617674349AFEBBA64936F7C33_181114_3730580_Hidden_missile_bases_in_North_Korea_seen_in_sate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DA0/527/DA0527C5F1C3407880E3F52B712DF5A3_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea, missile bases, missile operating bases, north korean missile bases, north korean missile program]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3730500</guid>
      <title>Two men attempt to cross Antarctica solo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo explorers began their expedition earlier this month to try to cross Antarctica on their own, without any support.Colin O'Brady is a seasoned athlete who has a world record in climbing the top of the highest peaks in all seven continents in just 132 days, while Louis Rudd decided to make this expedition to honor his friend who taught him about polar exploration.O'Brady and Rudd began their journey on the Ronne Ice Shelf, which is 600-feet thick, in Antarctica and plan to finish on Ross Ice Shelf, taking around two months, reports the New York Times.They could be skiing up to 12 hours a day in winds of up to 100 mph, according to Gear Junkie.To make their trip, the two men had to carry equipment such as sleeping bags that can withstand temperatures of -40 degrees Fahrenheit, portable solar panels, cross-country skis, satellite phones, and a GPS tracker among other things.During their expedition, they will have to carry Nordic sleds, called pulks, with them along with food, cooking fuel, camping gear and skis covered with synthetic skin for better traction.The only person who has successfully completed a solo journey on Antarctica is Felicity Aston who went on a 1,084-mile solo journey from the Ross Ice Shelf to the Ronne Ice Shelf on Antarctica and received a Guinness World Record, according to reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Antarctica map2. Skiing in Antarctica3. Equipment the men took with them4. What the men would have to take with them during their expeditionVOICEOVER (in English): "The New York Times reports Colin O'Brady and Louis Rudd began their journey on the Ronne Ice Shelf, which is 600-feet thick, in Antarctica and plan to finish on Ross Ice Shelf, taking around two months.""According to Gear Junkie, they could be skiing up to 12 hours a day in winds of up to 100 mph.""To make their trip, the two men had to carry equipment such as sleeping bags that can withstand temperatures of -40 degrees Fahrenheit, portable solar panels, cross-country skis, satellite phones, and a GPS tracker among other things.""During their expedition, they will have to carry Nordic sleds, called pulks, with them along with food, cooking fuel, camping gear and skis covered with synthetic skin for better traction."SOURCES: The New York Times, Gear Junkie, The Star, Business Insider, https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/11/sports/antarctica-race.htmlhttps://gearjunkie.com/solo-antarctic-crossings-2019https://www.thestar.com/sports/2018/11/10/two-adventurers-push-each-other-and-past-each-other-to-be-first-to-cross-antarctica-solo.htmlhttp://uk.businessinsider.com/solo-trek-across-antarctica-colin-obrady-2018-11?r=US&IR=T***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 02:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/14/3730500/3730500_EF68769C834249F9809CD0B3A8FEE9D3_181114_3730500_Two_men_attempt_to_cross_Antarctica_solo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FEC/0B7/FEC0B7B886564FF19A8606E1F775F85E_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Antarctica, Antarctica expedition, Ross Ice Shelf, Ronne Ice Shelf, polar exploration, antarctica exploration, antarctica expedition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3731389</guid>
      <title>Congo's worst Ebola outbreak to last six more months</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe latest Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is expected to last until mid-2019.The outbreak in the country's North Kivu Province has already killed more than 200 people, reports CNBC.Ebola commonly affects humans and nonhuman primates, and is caused by an infection with a group of viruses within the genus Ebolavirus, according to the CDC.The disease spread extensively in the town of Beni in North Kivu Province due to the dense local population, but also because of "tradi-modern" health centers, which patients tend to visit even though they aren't regulated.These health centers reportedly didn't have running water for handwashing, and patients would reuse needles to inject medicine.The WHO told reporters it will be "at least another six months" before they can declare the Ebola outbreak over, according to NBC News.This is the tenth Ebola virus epidemic the Democratic Republic of Congo has faced since its first epidemic back in 1976.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. DR Congo on map2. Zaire ebolavirus and Sudan ebolavirus3. "Tradi-modern" health centers4.  Inset of needles and running waterVOICEOVER (in English): "The latest Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is expected to last until mid-2019.""According to the CDC, Ebola commonly affects humans and nonhuman primates, and is caused by an infection with a group of viruses within the genus Ebolavirus.""The disease spread extensively in the town of Beni in the North Kivu Province because of the dense local population and also because of 'tradi-modern' health centers, which patients tend to visit even though they aren't regulated.""These health centers reportedly didn't have running water for handwashing, and patients would reuse needles to inject medicine."SOURCES: CNBC, NBC News, Reuters, BBC News, The Guardian, ABC News, CNN, CDChttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/13/congos-ebola-outbreak-to-last-at-least-6-more-months.htmlhttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/ebola-outbreak-congo-likely-last-6-more-months-who-says-n935751https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo-who/congos-ebola-outbreak-to-last-at-least-six-more-months-who-idUSKCN1NI1ZFhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-46167340https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/11/ebola-outbreak-death-toll-tops-200-in-democratic-republic-of-the-congohttps://abcnews.go.com/International/democratic-republic-congos-current-ebola-outbreak-worst-countrys/story?id=59103407https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/12/health/ebola-congo-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/vhf/ebola/about.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 07:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/15/3731389/3731389_7737C4726AA941B6AA7FE4DD4D480EBD_181115_3731389_Congo_s_worst_Ebola_outbreak_to_last_six_more_mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D11/1A5/D111A5837D4B440A84EE7D0FAAA067FD_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ebola virus, virus, viral outbreak, Congo, West Africa, ebola outbreak, congo ebola outbreak, ebola outbreak in congo,ebola outbreak news, ebola outbreak congo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3731276</guid>
      <title>Ancient Egyptian tomb found to contain cat mummies, statues</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEgypt's Ministry of Antiquities has announced that dozens of mummified cats and wooden cat statues have been discovered in the ancient city of Memphis, Egypt.Along with the mummified cats and wooden cat statues, a painted wooden cobra and a crocodile sarcophagi were also found.Gilded statues of a lion, a cow and a falcon were also discovered, along with wooden snakes and crocodiles.Objects such as amulets, canopic jars and papyri baskets were also discovered in the tomb.The artifacts are regarded to be around 6000 years old.Ancient Egyptians were often buried with their mummified animals and statues as a way to bring pets with them to the afterlife.The animals were also buried as food offerings for not just the deceased, but as offerings to the gods as well.The ministry is hoping the discoveries will attract more tourists to visit Egypt's heritage sites.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mummified cat and wooden cat statue 2. Painted wooden cobra and a crocodile sarcophagi3. Amulets, canopic jars and papyri baskets4. Mummies buried with mummified catsVOICEOVER (in English): "Egypt's Ministry of Antiquities has announced that dozens of mummified cats and wooden cat statues have been discovered in the ancient city of Memphis, Egypt.""Along with the mummified cats and wooden cat statues, a painted wooden cobra and a crocodile sarcophagi were also found.""Objects such as amulets, canopic jars and papyri baskets were also discovered in the tomb.""Ancient Egyptians were often buried with their mummified animals and statues as a way to bring pets with them to the afterlife."SOURCES: NPR, Live Science, The Washington Post, The Independent, The Guardian, https://www.npr.org/2018/11/11/666704847/archaeologists-discover-dozens-of-cat-mummies-100-cat-statues-in-ancient-tombhttps://www.livescience.com/64065-photos-cat-mummies-saqqara-egypt.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2018/11/11/archaeologists-have-discovered-dozens-cat-mummies-an-ancient-egyptian-tomb/?utm_term=.348958daba6dhttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/archaeology/ancient-egypt-cat-mummies-scarab-tomb-saqqara-cairo-archaeology-a8628886.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/nov/11/dozens-of-cat-mummies-found-in-6000-year-old-tombs-in-egypt***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/15/3731276/3731276_1508DF76DB074CCCB5257CA5FF400D02_181115_3731276_Ancient_Egyptian_tomb_found_to_contain_cat_mummi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/7A7/021/7A7021F513604EBF80D03173E068414D_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, egypt, mummies, egyptian mummies, ancient egyptian tomb, mummified cats, mummified animals, egyptian cat statues]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3731259</guid>
      <title>Microfiber pollution could be reduced with these laundry balls</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA laundry ball designed to catch microfibers from clothes could help reduce the plastics pollution entering the ecosystem. At four inches in diameter and made from recycled rubber, the Cora Ball imitates the way a coral reef filters tiny particles from flowing water. When washed with clothing, the laundry ball captures microfibers that come off during the wash. According the company, the ball captures between a quarter to a third of the microfibers per wash. A typical household 13-pound laundry load can shed up to 700,000 microfibers, says marine science researcher Imogen Napper form the University of Plymouth in the U.K., as reported by the BBC.The little plastic fibers are too small for water treatment plants to remove, so many of them make it into the oceans.According to the BBC, researchers say one cubic meter of ocean can contain 100,000 pieces of microplastic, which can then be consumed by marine life, to be eaten by humans.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Laundry ball mimics the way a coral reef filters water2. Laundry ball can remove 25 to 30 percent of microfibers per wash3. Microfibers too small for treatment plant getting discharged into seas4. Microfibers are then consumed by fish, which are consumed by humansVOICEOVER (in English): "A laundry ball designed to catch microfibers from clothes could help reduce the plastics pollution entering the ecosystem. "At four inches in diameter and made from recycled rubber, the Cora Ball imitates the way a coral reef filters tiny particles from water." "When washed with clothing, the laundry ball captures microfibers that come off during the wash. According the company, the ball captures between a quarter to a third of the microfibers per wash." "According to the BBC, a typical household 13-pound laundry load can shed up to 700,000 microfibers." "The little plastic fibers are too small for water treatment plants to remove, so many of them make it into the oceans.""According to the BBC, researchers say one cubic meter of ocean can contain 100,000 pieces of microplastic, which can then be consumed by marine life, to be eaten by humans."  SOURCES: BBChttps://www.bbc.com/news/business-46137804***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/15/3731259/3731259_43C68A03A7724D87A3DB1CFDF9DFDF17_181115_3731259_Microfiber_pollution_could_be_reduced_with_these_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D55/48E/D5548EDB56AD4EF9BF8F41ADC6FDCAEE_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic pollution, microfiber pollution, cora ball, laundry ball]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3731166</guid>
      <title>"Ghost boats" washing up on Japanese coasts believed to be from North Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNumerous wooden boats presumed to be from North Korea have washed up on the coasts of Japan.The Associated Press reports the number of ships has increased dramatically in recent years. One-third of these 'ghost boats' touch ground on the coasts of Japan's northern island of Hokkaido. Some are carry dead bodies.The North Korean boats might be traveling into farther and more dangerous waters in an attempt to reel in larger catches and increase sources of protein for the country. North Korea is struggling to provide its people with sustainable food sources.The boats most likely cannot withstand rough seas due to their deteriorated states. Japanese coast guards say 95 boats have washed up in Japan so far this year, forcing them to increase security measures.Last year the coast guard recorded a total of 104 "ghost boats", a total of 30 bodies and 40 live crew members. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. "Ghost boats" appearing on Japanese coast2. Depiction of distance travelled by North korean boats to Hokkaido3. North Korean boats fishing in rough waters 4. Japanese coast guards find "ghost boats"VOICEOVER (in English):"Numerous run-down boats presumed to be from North Korea have washed up on the coasts of Japan.""The Associated Press reports the number of ships has increased dramatically in recent years. One-third of these 'ghost boats' touch ground on the coasts of Japan's northern island of Hokkaido. Some are carrying dead bodies.""The North Korean boats might be travelling into farther and more dangerous waters in an attempt to reel in larger catches and increase sources of protein for the country. North Korea is struggling to provide its people with sustainable food sources.""The boats most likely cannot withstand rough seas due to their deteriorated states. Japanese coast guards say 95 boats have washed up in Japan so far this year, forcing them to increase security measures."SOURCES: Associated Presshttps://apnews.com/7034d434b69847d9b284f718087f52c3***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 01:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/15/3731166/3731166_9BE36FDA2EA849D79545C890C5F031A8_181115_3731166__Ghost_boats__washing_up_on_Japanese_coasts_beli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/06B/C86/06BC8690944F4CEC8B703AD7EDFAF41C_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, North Korea,Tokyo, ghost ship, shores, fishing, food shortage, north korea ghost ship, dprk ghost ship, north korea escape, fleeing north korea, north korea defection, dprk escape]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3732167</guid>
      <title>Migrants begin to reach U.S.-Mexico border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGroups of Central American migrants who have made their way across Mexico and are looking for asylum in the United States have begun arriving in the border city of Tijuana. According to NBC 7 News, the first groups of migrants began arriving on Sunday, Nov. 12 in trucks and buses. An estimated 1,660 migrants were in the Tijuana area as of Thursday. According to CNN, Mexico's Baja California state have estimated that as many as 9,000 more migrants could eventually arrive at the border. Many of these migrants will now begin the long asylum process. People who fear for their safety in their home country because of their race, religion, nationality, political beliefs or membership in a group can apply for asylum. To be considered, an individual must apply for asylum within a year of reaching the U.S. An applicant is allowed to stay within the U.S. while their case is pending. Individuals seeking asylum are housed in detention centers until they can be interviewed. In the U.S. while waiting for a court hearing, applicants must wear ankle monitors. According the CNN, migrants seeking asylum will most likely have to wait several weeks, if not longer, because of current bottlenecks at US ports of entry.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Migrants arriving in Tijuana2. Migrants waiting in line to apply for asylum3. Migrants applying for asylum4. Migrants seeking asylum are held in detention centers, if allowed into U.S., they must wear an ankle monitor until their court hearingVOICEOVER (in English): "The first groups of migrants began arriving on Sunday, Nov. 12 in trucks and buses. An estimated 1,660 migrants were in the Tijuana area as of Thursday." "According to CNN, Mexico's Baja California state have estimated that as many as 9,000 more migrants could eventually arrive at the border." "Many of these migrants will now begin the long asylum process. People who fear for their safety in their home country because of their race, religion, nationality, political beliefs or membership in a group can apply for asylum." "To be considered, an individual must apply for asylum within a year of reaching the U.S. An applicant is allowed to stay within the U.S. while their case is pending." "Individuals seeking asylum are housed in detention centers until they can be interviewed. In the U.S. while waiting for a court hearing, applicants must wear ankle monitors." SOURCES: NBC 7, CNNhttps://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/What-You-Need-to-Know-About-the-Migrant-Caravans-Arrival-to-the-US-Mexico-Border-500612751.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/15/americas/migrants-tijuana/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/16/3732167/3732167_8EDFB3788ABD4F94B5128D87C77428B4_181116_3732167_Migrants_begin_to_reach_U_S__Mexico_border_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/603/15F/60315F9FEF98487E833F06FFEB0A7F5A_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, migrant caravan, migrants, US Mexico border, asylum, asylum process]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3732159</guid>
      <title>Omnidirectional wind turbine claims first in James Dyson Awards</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn omnidirectional wind turbine meant to hang from skyscraper balconies has won first prize in the 2018 James Dyson Awards. According to New Atlas, the O-Wind Turbine  a crooked, vented spherical device  is designed to generate electricity in the chaotic wind conditions of urban areas. Modern cities and their skyscrapers alter wind patterns, causing three-dimensional vortices where wind is constantly changing directions.  Taking inspiration from NASA's "tumbleweed" technology, a team from Lancaster University designed a turbine with a somewhat spherical shape, covered in vents that have large inlets and small outlets for air to pass through. Because of Bernoulli's principle, differences in pressure cause the turbine to rotate clockwise around a single fixed axis regardless of which direction the wind comes from. The rotational energy from the turbine can then be used to run a generator and produce electricity. According to team member Nicolas Gonzalo, the device could allow, "people living in apartments to generate their own electricity." RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. O-Wind turbine and wind blowing through city2. O-Wind turbine design3. O-Wind turbine rotating regardless of wind direction4. O-Wind turbine hanging from apartment balconiesVOICEOVER (in English): "The O-Wind Turbine  a crooked, vented spherical device  is designed to generate electricity in the chaotic wind conditions of modern urban metropolises." "Taking inspiration from NASA's "tumbleweed" technology, a team from Lancaster University designed a turbine with a somewhat spherical shape, covered in vents that has large inlets and small outlets for air to pass through." "Because of Bernoulli's principle, differences in pressure cause the turbine to rotate clockwise around a single fixed axis regardless of which direction the wind comes from." "The rotational energy from the turbine can then be used to run a generator and produce electricity." SOURCES: New Atlashttps://newatlas.com/2018-dyson-award-winner-o-wind-turbine/57221/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/16/3732159/3732159_804AB12A86DB43B9ABF1546D4B77258E_181116_3732159_Omnidirectional_wind_turbine_claims_first_in_Jam_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D08/CA3/D08CA3F141DB443ABB5D90E55BF9B991_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, urban wind turbine, omnidirectional urban wind turbine, o-wind turbine, o-wind omnidirectional wind turbine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3732002</guid>
      <title>Article 13 explained: Why YouTube may block access in Europe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANYouTube may soon start blocking Europeans from viewing content on the platform due to radical new proposals for European copyright law known as Article 13.        Currently, individuals are responsible for ensuring they are within their rights to publish copyrighted material to the internet. The new law, Article 13 of the EU's Copyright Directive, changes this. It places enhanced responsibility on the website. Online platforms would be expected to have automated checks in place to filter out uploads containing copyrighted content.YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki explained in a Nov. 12 post on the YouTube Creator Blog that songs such as Despacito use various copyrights, and not all rights holders are known. It's because of this uncertainty and the financial risk associated with it, that YouTube may block Europeans users from viewing such content in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of how the law currently stands2. Depiction of the so-called upload filter3. Depiction of multiple copyrights in a single work4. Depiction of freedom of expression concernsVOICEOVER (in English): "Article 13 refers to proposed copyright legislation in the European Union." "Currently individuals are responsible for ensuring they are within their right to publish copyrighted material to the internet.""Article 13 changes this. It places enhanced responsibility on the website and makes them liable for copyright infringement.""Online platforms would be expected to have automated checks in place to filter out uploads containing copyrighted content.""YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki explained that songs such as Despacito use various copyrights, and not all rights holders are known.""It's because of this uncertainty and the financial risk associated with it, that YouTube may block Europeans users from viewing such content in the future.""Critics warn that this will hurt freedom of expression as automated systems cannot discern what constitutes fair use and what is infringement." "Many people rely on fair use to use segments of copyrighted content for commentary, satire and other works."SOURCES: YouTube Creator Blog, Wired, Julia Reda MEPhttps://youtube-creators.googleblog.com/2018/11/i-support-goals-of-article-13-i-also.htmlhttps://www.wired.co.uk/article/what-is-article-13-article-11-european-directive-on-copyright-explained-meme-banhttps://juliareda.eu/eu-copyright-reform/censorship-machines/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 07:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/16/3732002/3732002_58E73C7903DE4F42995E298AF263E33C_181116_3732002_Article_13_explained__Why_YouTube_may_block_acce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F07/3E4/F073E41E30884EE1B1629D1312F6E521_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[article 13, copyright directive, copyright law, European law, European parliament, YouTube, Automation, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3731998</guid>
      <title>The European Union's law-making process explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe European Union makes laws that shape 28 nations of Europe.According to European Parliament information, E.U. legislation is ideated by the European Commission. After a law is drafted there, it's sent onto the European Parliament for a reading. If the parliament wants amendments, it will note them, before sending them onto the next step in the process.The council may alter parliament's amendments to the draft, and send it back to them for a second reading. If parliament accepts, the proposal becomes law. They can also ask for further changes and if the Council accepts these, it becomes law.If not, both can choose not to adopt the draft or enter into negotiations known as 'concilation'. During this, an equal amount of parliamentarians and council members attempt to agree on a joint text for the draft. If they can't agree, it isn't adopted.If they do agree, the draft is sent back to both the parliament and council for a third and final reading. At this stage, no more amendments can be made to the draft.  Both have to approve the draft text for it to become law. If either rejects it, the proposal is discarded.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of E.U. Commission and E.U. Parliament2. Depiction of E.U. Parliament and E.U. Council reading a draft proposal3. Depiction of E.U. 'concilation' process4. Depiction of proposal becoming lawVOICEOVER (in English): "E.U. legislation is ideated by the European Commission. After a law is drafted there, it's sent onto the European Parliament for a reading.""If the parliament wants amendments, it will note them, before sending them onto the next step in the process.""The draft proposal is then sent onto the European Council. This body comprises Europe's elected national leaders and one council president.""The council may alter parliament's amendments to the draft, and send it back to them for a second reading. If parliament accepts, the proposal becomes law. "They can also ask for further changes and if the Council accepts these, it becomes law." "If not, both can choose not to adopt the draft or enter into negotiations known as concilation." "During this, an equal amount of parliamentarians and council members attempt to agree on a joint text for the draft. If they can't agree, it isn't adopted.""If they do agree, the draft is sent back to both the parliament and council for a third and final reading. At this stage, no more amendments can be made to the draft. "Both have to approve the draft text for it to become law. If either rejects it, the proposal is discarded."SOURCES: European Parliament, European Councilhttp://www.europarl.europa.eu/external/html/legislativeprocedure/default_en.htmhttps://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-making-process_en***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 07:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/16/3731998/3731998_110B5273D5BC494DAA43CDCBBE1D1104_181116_3731998_The_European_Union_s_law_making_process_explaine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/159/EC9/159EC95DF59A4A9CA057A80B2A638BB5_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[european union, europe, brexit, european parliament, european council, european commission, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3731809</guid>
      <title>Amazon chooses location for its new headquarters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAfter 14 months of deliberation, Amazon announced that New York and Virginia are their final choice for the location of their new offices. Amazon's new headquarters, dubbed HQ2,  will be divided between New York City and Arlington, Virginia. Both offices will cover 371,000 square meters and generate 25,000 new jobs.An additional Amazon operation center will be opened in Nashville. The site will span almost 93,000 square meters and generate $230 million in investment as well as open 5,000 full-time job positions.According to Amazon, taxpayers in New York will pay  $48,000 per job, $22,000 in Virginia and $13,000 for Tennessee. According to The New York Times, Amazon will receive more than a billion dollars in tax incentives.Other cities in the country had offered the tech giant even higher incentives. According to The Baltimore Sun, the city of Montgomery County in Maryland had the biggest offer with a bid of over $8 million which included tax incentives and infrastructure and transportation improvements. According to The Amazon blog, the cities were ultimately chosen due to their transit access, diverse talent and business environment. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of size and employment opportunities to be created by Amazon in New York and Northern Virginia  2. Depiction of size and employment opportunities to be created by Amazon in Tennessee3. Explanation of tax incentives4. Representation of elements considered for Amazon's choiceVOICEOVER (in English): "Amazon's new headquarters, dubbed HQ2,  will be divided between New York City and Arlington, Virginia. Both offices will cover  371,000  square meters and generate 25,000 new jobs.""An additional Amazon operation center will be opened in Nashville. The site will span almost 93,000 square meters and generate $230 million in investment as well as open 5,000 full-time job positions.""According to Amazon, taxpayers in New York will pay  $48,000 per job, $22,000 in Virginia and $13,000 for Tennessee. According to The New York Times, Amazon will receive more than a billion dollars in tax incentives.""Amazon said the cities were chosen due to their transit access, diverse talent and business environment."SOURCES: The New York Times, The Amazon blog.https://blog.aboutamazon.com/company-news/amazon-selects-new-york-city-and-northern-virginia-for-new-headquartershttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/13/business/economy/amazon-hq2-va-long-island-city-incentives.html?module=inline***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 02:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/16/3731809/3731809_87096D7B84044F31A188455FB5968EB6_181116_3731809_Amazon_chooses_location_for_its_new_headquarters_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/8D5/324/8D5324DB5B8D448F99FED915233C2B8A_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, technology, consumer tech, gadgets, science, gear, tech, Amazon, Amazon HQ2, New York, Arlington, amazon headquarters, ecommerce, nashville, business, tax, tax incentives, east coast, expansion, queens, new york city, northern virginia, economy, jobs, opportunities, billion.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3733625</guid>
      <title>What will happen if Theresa May's Brexit deal passes?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIf Theresa May's Brexit deal passes into law, what will it mean for the United Kingdom? The Brexit deal consists of two documents. The first is a 585-page agreement ending Britain's relationship with Europe, while the second is a seven-page outline describing the future relationship, according to the Guardian. The transition period would begin on March 29, 2019 and end on December 31, 2020. During this time the U.K. would have to follow all E.U. rules, but would not have membership in its institutions, according to the BBC. The withdrawal agreement would allow for the transition to be extended only once for a limited period, but would require both the U.K. and E.U. to agree for an extension before July 1, 2020. The Brexit draft also includes the calculations for how much the U.K. would need to pay the E.U. to settle all of its obligations.U.K. citizens in the E.U. and E.U. citizens in the U.K. will keep their residency and social security rights after the withdrawal. If by the end of 2020, no long-term trade deal is agreed upon, and if there is no transition period extension, then a backstop of "a single customs territory between the Union and the United Kingdom" would take effect. In a backstop setting, the U.K. is subject to "level playing field conditions" to prevent it from gaining a competitive advantage while in the same customs territory. To exit the backstop it would require bilateral agreement between the U.K. and the E.U. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Transition period and one time extension2. UK paying EU, EU 3. Backstop between UK and EU4. UK is subject to level playing field conditions in backstop settingVOICEOVER (in English): "Under Theresa May's Brexit deal the transition period would begin on March 29, 2019 and end on December 31, 2020. During this period the U.K. must follow all E.U. rules, but would not have membership in its institutions." "The withdrawal agreement would allow for the transition to be extended only once for a limited period, but would require both the U.K. and E.U. to agree for an extension before July 1, 2020." "The Brexit draft also includes the calculations for how much the U.K. would need to pay the E.U. to settle all of its obligations.""U.K. citizens in the E.U. and E.U. citizens in the U.K. will keep their residency and social security rights after the withdrawal." "If by the end of 2020, no long-term trade deal is agreed upon, and if there is no transition period extension, then a backstop of "a single customs territory between the Union and the United Kingdom" would take effect." "In a backstop setting, the U.K. is subject to "level playing field conditions" to prevent it from gaining a competitive advantage while in the same customs territory." "To exit the backstop it would require bilateral agreement between the U.K. and the E.U."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardianhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-46237012https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/15/what-happens-next-if-theresa-may-brexit-deal-passes***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/19/3733625/3733625_7C803ACF29704639B1C3F82C98E95A84_181119_3733625_What_will_happen_if_Theresa_May_s_Brexit_deal_pa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Brexit, Brexit draft, Theresa May Brexit, Brexit backstop]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3733565</guid>
      <title>China's plan for world's most powerful particle collider explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Chinese Institute of High Energy Physics is planning to construct a particle accelerator over the next decade. According to information from the project's website, it is expected to be situated near Qinhuangdao City, east of Beijing. Dubbed the Circular Electron Positron Collider, the project is expected to be five times more powerful than the Large Hadron Collider in Europe. It will be located in a 100-kilometer underground tunnel.The project will be a double ring collider with electron and positrons beams in separate pipes. It will circulate these in opposite directions.If successful, researchers also plan to build a Super Proton-Proton Collider and use it to collide electrons with positrons. Scientists behind the project expect the collider could potentially generate more than a million Higgs particles and others such as W and Z bosons.The researchers have released the design of the collider and plan to build a prototype before the actual collider is built. Construction on the collider is expected to begin in 2022.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Circular Electron Positron Collider2. The Circular Electron Positron Collider underground3. Double ring collider with electron and positrons beams4. Electrons and positrons collidingVOICEOVER (in English): "The Chinese Institute of High Energy Physics is planning to construct a particle accelerator over the next decade. "It is to be situated near Qinhuangdao City, east of Beijing.""Dubbed the Circular Electron Positron Collider, the project is expected to be five times more powerful than the Large Hadron Collider in Europe."It will be located in a 100-kilometer underground tunnel.""The project will be a double ring collider with electron and positrons beams in separate pipes. It will circulate these in opposite directions.""If successful, researchers also plan to build a Super Proton-Proton Collider and use it to collide electrons with positrons." "Scientists behind the project expect the collider could potentially generate more than a million Higgs particles and others such as W and Z bosons."SOURCES: Popular mechanics, CEPC Conceptual Design Report, Institute of High Energy Physics, Gizmodo, China.org.cn, CGTN, Newsweek, The Weekly Observer, Xinhuahttps://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a25101820/china-lhc-particle-collider-cepc/http://english.ihep.cas.cn/doc/3229.htmlhttp://cepc.ihep.ac.cn/CEPC_CDR_Vol2_Physics-Detector.pdfhttps://gizmodo.com/plans-revealed-for-enormous-particle-collider-in-china-1830444169http://www.china.org.cn/china/2018-11/15/content_72605171.htmhttps://news.cgtn.com/news/3d3d514d33416a4e30457a6333566d54/share_p.htmlhttps://www.newsweek.com/china-building-62-mile-long-supercollider-produce-million-higgs-bosons-1212880http://theweeklyobserver.com/c-e-r-n-is-concerned-due-to-chinas-new-strongest-particle-accelerator/65084/http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-11/14/c_129994371.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 07:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/19/3733565/3733565_12E9DDFAE10A4BC6BCC01543F484073F_181119_3733565_China_s_plan_for_world_s_most_powerful_particle__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, Particle Collider, chinese particle collider, chinese particle accelerator,  chinese circular electron positron collider, CEPC, electrons, positrons, antimatter, Higgs proton, science, physics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3733451</guid>
      <title>China's "artificial sun" marks development in nuclear fusion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from China's Hefei Institutes of Physical Science reported its fusion reactor reached 100 million degrees Celsius, over six times the temperature of the sun's core.The reactor is called the Experimental Advanced Superconducting Tokamak, also known as the EAST. The donut-shaped machine supports nuclear fusion by using magnetic fields that keep hot plasma from melting the exterior walls of the tokamak. Nuclear fusion is a thermonuclear process that occurs when the nuclei of two light atoms, usually hydrogen, combine and form a heavier atom, in this case helium. This process results in release of energy in the form of heat and light  the same way by which the sun produces its warmth. Researcher's from the EAST project hope to develop technology that will allow humans to someday extract clean energy from nuclear fusion. Scientists from the ITER project  a multinational experiment aiming to harness nuclear fusion energy  have stated that fusion fuels are expansive and do not release harmful emissions. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of China's Hefei Institutes of Physical Science and depiction temperature reached by the EAST. 2. EAST interior and explanation of magnetic confinement3. Explanation of creation of fusion energy4. Explanation of qualities of fusion energyVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from China's Hefei Institutes of Physical Science reported its fusion reactor reached 100 million degrees Celsius, over six times the temperature of the sun's core.""The reactor is called the Experimental Advanced Superconducting Tokamak, also known as the EAST. The donut-shaped machine supports nuclear fusion by using magnetic fields that keep hot plasma from melting the exterior walls of the tokamak.""Nuclear fusion is a thermonuclear process that occurs when the nuclei of two light atoms combine and form a heavier atom. This process results in release of energy in the form of heat and light.""Scientists from the ITER project  a multinational experiment aiming to harness nuclear fusion energy  have stated that fusion fuels are expansive and do not release harmful emissions."SOURCES: Hefei Institutes of Physical Science, Futurism, ITERhttp://english.hf.cas.cn/new/news/rn/201811/t20181113_201186.htmlhttps://futurism.com/artificial-sun-china-temperature-recordhttps://www.iter.org/sci/fusion***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 04:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/19/3733451/3733451_8122EB08D75E4C0FB224F9DCA7268D05_181119_3733451_China_s__artificial_sun__marks_development_in_nu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, TomoNews, Satire, fusion, fusion energy, physics, global energy, fusion power, iter, fuel, power, hydrogen, atom, plasma, clean energy, science, explained, explainer, education, explain, science video, awe, reliable, unlimited, source, edutainment, experts, china, sun, reactor, power plants, atmosphere, fossil fuels, go green, research, magnetic, source, fusion reactor magnets.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3733423</guid>
      <title>Heatwaves cause male insect fertility to plummet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that sperm counts in male beetles are affected by warmer temperatures.Researchers used red flour beetles as a proxy for humans. They subjected them to five-day "heatwave" conditions of above average temperatures. This damaged male reproductive potential and halved male fertility, according to the study published in Nature Communication.Even if the male beetles were able to procreate in that climate, their offsprings tend to have shorter than average lifespans, according to the researchers. Female beetles were largely unaffected.The researchers also found that successive heatwaves could nearly sterilize males.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dry ground, thermometer, male sperm2. Red flour beetles being subject to heat wave conditions3. Flash red on the beetle4. Successive heatwaves on the beetleVOICEOVER (in English): "As rising temperatures result in more heatwaves, it turns out male sperm count could be affected.""Researchers used red flour beetles as a proxy for humans. They subjected them to a five-day 'heatwave' conditions of above average temperatures.""According to the study published in Nature Communication, the heatwaves damaged male reproductive potential and halved male fertility.""Female beetles were largely unaffected.""The researchers also found that successive heatwaves could nearly sterilize males."SOURCES: The Guardian, The New York Times, BBC News, Nature Communication, https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/13/heatwaves-wipe-out-male-insect-fertility-beetles-studyhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/13/science/sperm-infertility-insects-heat.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-46194383https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-018-07273-z***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 03:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/19/3733423/3733423_35712E21837E446189D34D76B2A31336_181119_3733423_Heatwaves_cause_male_insect_fertility_to_plummet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, climate change,heatwaves, global warming, rising temperatures, red flour beetles, male fertility, climate change, sperm count, male insect fertility]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3734928</guid>
      <title>Six rescued from skyscraper elevator accident in Chicago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSix people were rescued from an elevator after it plummeted more than 80 floors down a Chicago skyscraper.The Chicago Tribune reports that six people stepped into an express elevator on the 95th floor of Chicago's John Hancock Center around midnight on Friday. Two cables holding the elevator broke soon after.The people inside said they felt the elevator moving fast and saw a dust-like material enter the carriage. The elevator fell 84 floors before stopping at the 11th floor.Firefighters had to use a gooseneck camera to determine the elevator's exact location, before then breaking through a brick wall to open the doors and rescue the people trapped inside.The rescue took nearly three hours. A Chicago Fire Department Spokesman told the Chicago Tribune that none of those trapped suffered serious injuries. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Six passengers in elevator; cables holding elevator snaps2. Elevator plummets from 95th to 11th floor3. Camera used to determine exact location in blind elevator shaft4. Firefighters break through a brick wall to rescue passengersVOICEOVER (in English): "Six people stepped into an express elevator on the 95th floor of Chicago's John Hancock Center around midnight on Friday. "Two cables holding the elevator broke soon after.""People inside said they felt the elevator moving fast and saw a material that looked like dust begin seeping in. "The elevator fell 84 floors before suddenly stopping near the 11th floor.""Because of the building's blind-shaft layout, there were no openings between floors." "Firefighters had to use a gooseneck camera to determine the elevator's exact location.""They then broke through a brick wall to open the doors and rescue the people trapped inside."SOURCES: Chicago Tribune, CBS, ABChttps://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-hancock-building-elevator-rescue-20181116-story.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/chicago-elevator-plunges-rescue-875-north-michigan-avenue-building-formerly-the-john-hancock-center/https://abcnews.go.com/US/elevator-drops-84-floors-cables-snap-chicagos-famed/story?id=59299860***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/21/3734928/3734928_D263E231921F45A48D431771C7C13A51_181121_3734928_Six_rescued_from_skyscraper_elevator_accident_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, elevator, elevator rescue, trapped in elevator, elevator falls, hancock center, hancock center elevator, chicago skyscraper, chicago building, dramatic rescue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3734899</guid>
      <title>OSIRIS-REx spacecraft set to take Bennu asteroid sample</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's OSIRIS-REx successfully stretched out its robotic arm for the first time in space, as it readies to take a sample from the asteroid Bennu.According to NASA, the OSIRIS-REx is an asteroid study and sample-return mission which launched from Cape Canaveral on September 8, 2016.The spacecraft is expected to reach the near-Earth asteroid Bennu on December 3, and will then prepare to collect a surface sample in July 2020.It will use the Touch-and-Go Sample Acquisition Mechanism or TAGSAM, an 11-foot robotic arm with three articulating joints, a round sampler head, and three bottles of high-pressure nitrogen gas.Once the arm is unfurled and touches the asteroid surface, nitrogen gas is blasted out to stir up regolith, or loose dirt and rocks, which will then be caught by the sampler head.The entire process will take about five seconds. Collected particles will be stored in a canister with nitrogen allowed to escape, leaving between 60 and 200 grams of material.Once sampling is complete, and the material safe inside a heatproof Sample Return Capsule, the OSIRIS-REx will execute small maneuvers to back away from Bennu.The spacecraft will then journey back to Earth and eject the capsule just outside Earth's atmosphere, to land in the Utah desert in September 2023.Bennu is roughly 4.5 billion years old, and as an ancient relic of our solar system's early days, scientists believe it could shed light on how that system was formed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. OSIRIS-REx spacecraft2. OSIRIS-REx reaching asteroid Bennu3. Parts of OSIRIS-REx's robotic TAGSAM arm4. Nitrogen gas blasted on asteroid surface, debris collected by sampler head5. 60 to 200 grams of material collected  by the instrument6. Sample stored in capsule, OSIRIS-REx maneuvers away from Bennu7. Spacecraft goes back to Earth, capsule lands in Utah in 2023VOICEOVER (in English): "The OSIRIS-REx is an asteroid study and sample-return mission which launched from Cape Canaveral on September 8, 2016.""The spacecraft is expected to reach the near-Earth asteroid Bennu on December 3, and will then prepare to collect a surface sample in July 2020.""To do so, it will use the Touch-and-Go Sample Acquisition Mechanism, an 11-foot robotic arm with three articulating joints, a sampler head, and three bottles of high-pressure nitrogen gas.""Once the arm is unfurled and touches the asteroid surface, nitrogen gas is blasted out to stir up regolith, or loose dirt and rocks, which will then be caught by the sampler head.""The entire process will take about five seconds. Collected particles will be stored in a canister with nitrogen allowed to escape, leaving between 60 and 200 grams of material..""Once sampling is complete, and the material safe inside a heatproof Sample Return Capsule, the OSIRIS-REx will execute small maneuvers to back away from Bennu.""The spacecraft will then journey back to Earth and eject the capsule just outside Earth's atmosphere, to land in the Utah desert in September 2023."SOURCES: NASA, University of Arizonahttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2018/tagsam-testing-complete-osiris-rex-prepared-to-tag-an-asteroidhttps://www.nasa.gov/osiris-rexhttps://www.asteroidmission.org/where-is-the-spacecraft/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/21/3734899/3734899_DD5DE58558D04C58B150523EA13B2F8E_181121_3734899_OSIRIS_REx_spacecraft_set_to_take_Bennu_asteroid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, OSIRIS REx, satellite, asteroid bennu, Bennu, asteroid sample, NASA, TAGSAM, NASA mission, asteroid mission, NASA spacecraft, regolith]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3735627</guid>
      <title>Taiwan prepares for 2018 midterm elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan is set to have midterms on November 24 to select candidates for nine different levels of government, also being called the "nine-in-one" elections.  According to the National Interest, the highest levels up for election are the mayoral and county magistrates of cities and counties, down to the level of village wardens and indigenous district councils.  The minimum voting age in Taiwan is twenty years. Voters must fulfill a four-month residency requirement before being allowed to vote.People need to bring three things with them in order to vote, their ID card, their chop stamp and their polling station slip. As there is no absentee balloting, Taiwanese people must return to the cities where they are officially registered in order to cast their ballots. Local elections are held every four years at intervals between national elections. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nine-in-one elections to be held on Nov. 242. Minimum voting age is 20 years along with a four-month residency requirement 3. People need to bring ID card, chop stamp and polling station slip to vote4. People votingVOICEOVER (in English): "Taiwan is set to have midterms to select candidates for nine different levels of governmentalso being called the "nine-in-one" electionson November 24."     "According to the National Interest, the highest levels up for election are the mayoral and county magistrates of cities and counties, down to the level of village wardens and indigenous district councils."  "The minimum voting age in Taiwan is twenty years. Voters must fulfill a four-month residency requirement before being allowed to vote.""People need to bring three things with them in order to vote, their ID card, their chop stamp and their polling station slip." "As there is no absentee balloting, Taiwanese people must return to the cities where they are officially registered in order to cast their ballots." SOURCES: National Interest, The Diplomat, Wikipediahttps://nationalinterest.org/feature/everything-you-wanted-know-about-taiwans-elections-36257https://thediplomat.com/2018/11/the-mood-ahead-of-taiwans-midterm-elections/https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elections_in_Taiwanhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Taiwanese_local_elections,_2018***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 12:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/22/3735627/3735627_5D90AEFAB1244D3C913C416665497526_181122_3735627_Taiwan_prepares_for_2018_midterm_elections_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Taiwan elections, Taiwan elections 2018, Taiwan midterm elections, Taiwan nine-in-one elections]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3735341</guid>
      <title>Venezuela's smart ID card created with the help of China's ZTE</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Reuters report has uncovered how Chinese telecom giant ZTE is helping Venezuela build a system to monitor its citizens.According to the report, Venezuela's new 'Fatherland' ID was inspired by China's smart cards, which allow the government to track an individual's social, political and economic behavior.Venezuela initially wanted cards embedded with RFID chips, which can track location and data. Ultimately, they used QR codes developed by ZTE to reduce costs.ZTE also built a database for the fatherland cards. The cards are linked to employment and income, property, medical history and political party membership.The Venezuelan government has previously provided incentives to cardholders to encourage adoption of the card  giving cash prizes for rallying voters, for example, or a Mother's Day bonus.Citizens are now being forced to get the cards in order to receive public benefits such as medicine, pension, subsidized food, and fuel.Describing the program as 'blackmail,' Hector Navarro, one of the founders of the Socialist Party in Venezuela, claims Venezuelans who have cards have more rights than those who don't.Mariela Magallanes, an opposition lawmaker in Venezuela, previously investigated unenrolled citizens being deprived of subsidized food boxes, and says the government knows who is vulnerable to pressure."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China's smart ID card and Venezuela's smart ID card2. Differences between China's smart ID card and Venezuela's smart ID card3. What the new smart card is linked to4. Subsides the public won't be able to receive if they don't have a smart cardVOICEOVER (in English): "Venezuela's new 'Fatherland' ID was inspired by China's smart cards, which allow the government to track a citizen's social, political and economic behavior.""Venezuela initially wanted cards embedded with RFID chips, which can track location and data. Ultimately, they used QR codes developed by Chinese telecom giant ZTE to reduce costs.""According to a Reuters report, ZTE also built a database for the fatherland cards. The cards are linked to employment and income, property, medical history and political party membership.""Citizens are now being forced to get the cards in order to receive public benefits such as medicine, pension, subsidized food, and fuel."SOURCES: Reuters, Slatehttps://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/venezuela-zte/?fbclid=IwAR2LhHsuijFn7OFytth4t6CpD5CwnJySGiAqFnZBmTwg99OFIdfFZbsBpOghttps://slate.com/technology/2018/11/venezuela-china-zte-authoritarian-surveillance-social-control-tech.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 06:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/22/3735341/3735341_94FAB62F10A74D659EF76F8BBB5F2AE5_181122_3735341_Venezuela_s_smart_ID_card_created_with_the_help__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,Venezuela, ZTE, China, surveillance, Venezuela smart ID, fatherland card, smart ID cards, carnet de la patria, fatherland database, chinese technology, socialist state, high-tech surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3735268</guid>
      <title>Sprawling termite mounds found in Brazil</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have uncovered tens of millions of termite mounds dating almost 4,000 years, in a remote part of northeast Brazil.According to a new study published in the journal Current Biology, the mounds were made by a species of termite called syntermes dirus, and spread across 230,000 square kilometers.Each conical mound is about 2.5 meters tall and approximately 9 meters wide.The termite mounds contain 10 cubic kilometers of soil, which is equivalent to roughly 4,000 Great Pyramids.Researchers believe the mounds were built as termites carved out extensive networks of undergrounds tunnels to survive, according to Science Magazine.The underground tunnel allows the termites move swiftly in order to feed on dead leaves of caatinga, a specific type of dry, thorny trees whose leaves only falls once a year.The researchers added, "This is the greatest known example of ecosystem engineering by a single insect species."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Termite mounds in northeast Brazil 2. Closeup of termite mounds and termites3. Measurements of termite mounds4. Amount of soil used in termite moundsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have uncovered tens of millions of termite mounds dating back to nearly 4,000 years, in a remote part of northeast Brazil.""The mounds were made by a species of termite called syntermes dirus, and have spread across 230,000 square kilometers.""According to a new study published in the journal Current Biology, each conical mound is approximately 2.5 meters tall and 9 meters wide. ""The termite mounds contain 10 cubic kilometers of soil, which is equivalent to roughly 4,000 Great Pyramids."SOURCES: The New York Times, The Washington Post, Current Biology, Science Magazine, Quartz,https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/science/termite-mounds-brazil.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2018/11/19/termites-built-natural-wonder-earth-size-minnesota/?utm_term=.4f779a188de4https://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(18)31287-9https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/11/these-termite-mounds-are-so-big-you-can-see-them-spacehttps://qz.com/1470634/termite-mounds-the-size-of-britain-discovered-in-brazil/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 04:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/22/3735268/3735268_D1F6845E46884B22A357076ED3F12A45_181122_3735268_Sprawling_termite_mounds_found_in_Brazil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Brazil, termites, termite mounds, syntermes dirus, ancient termite mounds, massive termite mounds, termite mounds Brazil, brazilian termite mounds, caatinga]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3735209</guid>
      <title>Wreck of missing Argentine submarine found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe ARA San Juan was on its way back from a routine expedition in a town called Ushuaia located at the southern tip of South America when it reported technical difficulties.According to Reuters, the wreckage was found by Ocean Infinity  a seabed exploration company hired by Argentinian officials   in a ravine roughly 900 meters below surface.  It was carrying 44 crew members.It first reported a short circuit caused by water that had leaked through the submarine's snorkel and dripped on the battery. Shortly after, officials lost contact with the submarine.Argentine newspaper, La Nacion, says a special investigation commission put together by the Argentinian Ministry of Defense reported that a second explosion may have occurred triggering issues in the control systems which then led to the vessel sinking and imploding due to high underwater pressure. The sail, hull and propeller found in the ocean floor showed signs of implosion. The special investigation commission has also stated that the crew may not have been aware of the severity of the situation as they did not trigger the emergency frequencies installed in all ships. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of submarine route. 2. Explanation of first short circuit in batteries. 3. Depiction of second short circuit, sinking and implosion of the submarine.4. Portrayal of depth at which the debris of the submarine was found. VOICEOVER (in English): "The ARA San Juan was on its way back from a routine expedition at the southern tip of South America when it reported technical difficulties.""It first reported a short circuit caused by water that had leaked through the submarine's snorkel and dripped on the battery. Shortly after, officials lost contact with the submarine.""Argentine newspaper, La Nacion, says a special investigation commission put together by the Argentinian Ministry of Defense reported that a second explosion may have occurred, triggering issues in the control systems which then led to the vessel sinking and imploding due to high underwater pressure."  "According to Reuters, the wreckage was found by Ocean Infinity, a seabed exploration company hired by Argentinian officials. The wreckage was in a ravine roughly 900 meters below surface. It was carrying 44 crew members."SOURCES: La Nacion, Reuters.https://www.lanacion.com.ar/2122846-para-la-comision-de-expertos-asi-habrian-sido-los-momentos-finales-del-ara-san-juanhttps://www.lanacion.com.ar/2193189-10-preguntas-deja-ara-san-juan-quehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-argentina-submarine/argentine-navy-submarine-found-a-year-after-disappearing-with-44-aboard-idUSKCN1NM08B***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 02:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/22/3735209/3735209_678CDA6C1AF340A49E12DE807173ADA6_181122_3735209_Wreck_of_missing_Argentine_submarine_found_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ara-san-juan-submarine, Submarine, San Juan, Argentina, Maritime Transport, argentinian sailors, argentine submarine, mar del plata, argentina, submarine, argentina submarine, atlantic ocean, submarine ara san juan, missing submarine, buenos aires, missing argentine submarine, argentine sub, ara san juan, 44 crew, explosion, search, revelation, oxygen, implosion.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3735195</guid>
      <title>Earth's interior taking in more seawater than previous thought, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSeismic activity around the Mariana Trench have revealed the earth around it could be taking in at least 4.3 times more water than previously thought, according to a new study in the journal Nature.The researchers deployed 19 seismographs to the bottom of the ocean around the trench, and seven land-based seismographs on the Mariana Islands. Two tectonic plates meet at the Mariana Trench, which is where the huge Pacific Plate seems to be sliding under the tiny Mariana Plate, thus letting vasts amount of seawater to pour through the cracks into the earth's crust 30 kilometers below the surface.The researchers believe that the seawater could turn into hydrous minerals due to the high temperature and pressure. The hydrous minerals would then be incorporated into the lower plate and sink deeper into the mantle as the tectonic plate sinks.Chen Cai, lead author of the study, told Live Science there is no missing water in the ocean and that the amount of water going into Earth's interior and coming back out should be equal. However, it appears that there is a disparity, with Chen adding that more studies should be conducted to find out more about the water cycles of our planet.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Mariana Trench, output of a seismograph, water icon and a vertical bar graph 2. Seismograph under the sea and seismograph on land3. One tectonic plate sliding under the other4. Seawater turning into hydrous minerals and tectonic platesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study in the journal Nature, seismic activity around the Mariana Trench have revealed the earth around it could be taking in at least 4.3 times more water than previously thought.""The researchers deployed 19 seismographs to the bottom of the ocean around the trench, and seven land-based seismographs on the Mariana Islands." "Two tectonic plates meet at the Mariana Trench, which is where the huge Pacific Plate seems to be sliding under the tiny Mariana Plate, thus letting vasts amount of seawater to pour through the cracks into the earth's crust 30 kilometers below the surface.""The researchers believe that the seawater could turn into hydrous minerals due to the high temperature and pressure. The hydrous minerals would then be incorporated into the lower plate and sink deeper into the mantle as the tectonic plate sinks."SOURCES: New Atlas, Gizmodo, Popular Mechanics, Live Science, Nature journal, https://newatlas.com/mariana-trench-water-mantle/57239/https://gizmodo.com/observations-from-mariana-trench-show-inner-earth-is-su-1830493943https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a25137453/earth-swallowing-ocean/https://www.livescience.com/64091-earth-is-eating-its-oceans.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-018-0655-4***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 02:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/22/3735195/3735195_74238EE06FEF461E95EA312775FB9869_181122_3735195_Earth_s_interior_taking_in_more_seawater_than_pr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, earth, mariana trench, seawater, earth's interior, subduction zone, hydrous minerals, earth's crust, tectonic plates, water cycles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3736074</guid>
      <title>New Chinese structure in South China Sea may have military aims: U.S. think tank</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new Chinese structure in the South China Sea maybe for military purposes, according to a report from an American think tank.Reuters reports that recent satellite imagery reveals a newly built platform on Chinese-claimed Bombay Reef in the Paracel Islands, that's topped by a radome and solar panels.The purpose of the new structure is unclear. It could be a navigational aid for transiting ships, but the same function can be served by buoys or an already existing lighthouse.According to U.S. based think tank The Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, it's more likely to be military in nature. This is because the reef is directly adjacent to major shipping lanes that run between the Paracels and Spratly Islands.The think tank reckons the strategic position of the structure makes it an ideal location for a sensor array to extend Chinese radar signals or signals intelligence collection.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Platform with radome and solar panels on Bombay Reef2. Platform's possible purpose as navigational aid for ships3. Bombay Reef directly adjacent to major shipping lanes4. Platform as location for sensor arrays to extend Chinese radar signalsVOICEOVER (in English): "Recent satellite imagery reveals a newly built platform on Chinese-claimed Bombay Reef in the Paracel Islands.  "The structure is topped by a radome and solar panels.""The purpose of it is unclear. It could be a navigational aid for transiting ships.""However, that function can be served by buoys or an already existing lighthouse.""U.S. based think tank The Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative claims it's more likely to be military in nature. "This is because the reef is directly adjacent to major shipping lanes that run between the Paracels and Spratly Islands.""The think tank reckons its strategic position makes it an ideal location for a sensor array to extend Chinese radar signals or signals intelligence collection."SOURCES: Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, Reutershttps://amti.csis.org/china-quietly-upgrades-bombay-reef/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-southchinasea-idUSKCN1NQ08Y***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/23/3736074/3736074_3780B65999F84090BD627501B36DB495_181123_3736074_New_Chinese_structure_in_South_China_Sea_may_hav_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, south china sea, bombay reef, paracel islands, south china sea dispute, paracels, radome, radar, solar panels, south china sea shipping lane, spratly islands]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3736007</guid>
      <title>Taiwan to vote on same-sex marriage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan is preparing to vote in an historic vote on marriage equality.On Nov. 24 voters will be asked five referendum questions on same-sex marriage.One question, drafted by opponents to same-sex marriage, asks if voters believe marriage should be restricted to between a man and a woman.Another question, also drafted by same-sex marriage opponents, asks if the voter agrees that education about homosexuality should not be taught in elementary and junior high school under Taiwan's Gender Equity Education Act.Voters will be asked another question, createdby supporters of same-sex marriage, if education about homosexuality should be taught in elementary and junior high school under the Gender Equity Education Act.Another question, drafted by same-sex marriage supporters, asks if the voter agrees to guarantee the rights of same-sex marriage couples under Taiwan's Civil Code. And one question, drafted by same-sex marriage opponents, asks if voters agree that the rights of non-married same-sex couples who live together can be protected. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Taiwan, referendum ballot and the LGBTQ flag2. Question on whether marriage should only be between a man and a woman3. Questions on gender equality education in schools4. Questions on same-sex couplesVOICEOVER (in English): "Taiwan is preparing to vote in an historic vote on marriage equality." "On Nov. 24 voters will be asked five referendum questions on same-sex marriage." "One question, drafted by opponents to same-sex marriage, asks if voters believe marriage should be restricted to between a man and a woman.""Another question, also drafted by same-sex marriage opponents, asks if the voter agrees that education about homosexuality should not be taught in elementary and junior high school under Taiwan's Gender Equity Education Act.""Another question, created by supporters of same-sex marriage, asks if education about homosexuality should be taught in elementary and junior high school under the Gender Equity Education Act.""Another question, drafted by same-sex marriage supporters, asks if the voter agrees to guarantee the rights of same-sex marriage couples under Taiwan's Civil Code.""And one question, drafted by same-sex marriage opponents, asks if voters agree that the rights of non-married same-sex couples who live together can be protected. "SOURCES: The Guardian, Nikkei Asian Review, The BBC, Taiwanese Public Opinion Foudation, Chinese New York Times, United Daily News,  Focus Taiwan, Taipei Timeshttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/22/taiwan-gay-marriage-referendum-votehttps://asia.nikkei.com/Politics/Same-sex-marriage-rights-in-Taiwan-at-risk-in-referendumhttps://www.bbc.com/zhongwen/trad/chinese-news-46016879https://www.tpof.org/%E7%B2%BE%E9%81%B8%E6%96%87%E7%AB%A0/2018%E5%B9%B411%E6%9C%88%E3%80%8C2018%E5%8F%B0%E7%81%A3%E5%85%AC%E6%8A%95%E8%88%87%E5%9C%B0%E6%96%B9%E9%81%B8%E8%88%89%E3%80%8D/https://cn.nytimes.com/asia-pacific/20181028/taiwan-gay-pride-parade/zh-hant/https://udn.com/vote2018/story/12539/3487875https://udn.com/news/story/12539/3477466http://focustaiwan.tw/search/201810160023.aspxhttp://focustaiwan.tw/search/201810090026.aspx?q=referendum%20questionhttp://www.taipeitimes.com/News/taiwan/archives/2018/08/29/2003699406***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 06:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/23/3736007/3736007_B0F2F755934A4334B9B9251987EB6F24_181123_3736007_Taiwan_to_vote_on_same_sex_marriage_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Taiwan, marriage equality, gay rights, taiwan gay rights, LGBTQ, taiwan gay marriage vote, gay marriage referendum in taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3735991</guid>
      <title>Romaine lettuce linked to E. Coli outbreak, says CDC</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHealth officials are warning U.S. consumers not to eat any romaine lettuce as it could be contaminated with a strain of E.Coli.The outbreak has already spread to 11 states across America, along with two provinces in Canada, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.Thirty-two people have already become sick from eating contaminated romaine lettuce in the U.S., according to the BBC.The CDC is encouraging the public to throw out all romaine lettuce and to wash and sanitize drawers and shelves where the romaine lettuce was stored.The recent outbreak is believed to be caused by a strain of E. coli identified as O157:H7 which produces a Shiga toxin. Symptoms of infection can include diarrhea or hemolytic uremic syndrome, a type of kidney failure.In order to prevent E.Coli infections, the CDC encourages people to wash their hands thoroughly before and after preparing and eating food, wash fruits and vegetables under running water and to cook meat thoroughly to kill harmful germs.FDA Commissioner Dr. Scott Gottlieb told CNN that he believes the recent E.Coli outbreak could be associated with the end of harvest season in California as most romaine lettuce in the country in harvested from that region. The CDC, public health officials and the FDA are currently conducting investigations into the outbreak.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Romaine lettuce and E.Coli 2. Map of where the E.Coli has spread3. Sanitizing areas where romaine lettuce used to be kept4. E.Coli strain5. Symptoms of E.Coli infection6. Ways to prevent the spread of E.ColiVOICEOVER (in English): "Health officials are warning U.S. consumers not to eat any romaine lettuce as it could be contaminated with a strain of E.Coli.""According to the CDC, the outbreak has already spread to 11 states across America, along with two provinces in Canada.""The CDC is encouraging the public to throw out all romaine lettuce and to wash and sanitize drawers and shelves where the romaine lettuce was stored.""The recent outbreak is believed to be caused by a strain of E. coli identified as O157:H7 which produces a Shiga toxin.""Symptoms of infection can include diarrhea or hemolytic uremic syndrome, a type of kidney failure.""In order to prevent E.Coli infections, the CDC encourages people to wash their hands thoroughly before and after preparing and eating food, wash fruits and vegetables under running water and to cook meat thoroughly to kill harmful germs."SOURCES: BBC News, CDC, CNN, The Washington Post, https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46284236https://www.cdc.gov/ecoli/2018/o157h7-11-18/index.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/ecoli/ecoli-prevention.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/20/health/romaine-lettuce-e-coli-cdc/index.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/romaine-lettuce-is-not-safe-to-eat-cdc-warns-us-consumers/2018/11/20/726d0ae6-ece9-11e8-96d4-0d23f2aaad09_story.html?noredirect=on&utm_term=.f557e6296a1e***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 05:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/23/3735991/3735991_87AED063A95F477BA23F7770AF94C8DB_181123_3735991_Romaine_lettuce_linked_to_E__Coli_outbreak__says_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, E. Coli,  E. Coli outbreak, US, Canada, romaine lettuce, romaine lettuce e coli outbreak, e coli romaine lettuce, e coli symptoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3735846</guid>
      <title>New NASA Mars lander InSight just days away from landing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe InSight lander will land on Elysium Planitia, a plain located near the equator just 600 kilometers from Curiosity's landing site.Nasa reports that by the time the probe descends to Martian soil it will have travelled 480 million kilometers and spent six months travelling through space.  The InSight lander is packed with two cameras that will aid with navigation and an instrument deployment arm that will place research devices on the planet's surface.It carries three main instruments: A seismometer that measures Mar's seismic waves and detects meteor impacts, a heat probe that will penetrate 5 meters into the surface of the planet to measure its heat flow and interior temperature and two antennas that will help determine the size and composition of the planet's core. As InSight enters Mars' atmosphere it will emit radio signals dubbed 'tones' these signals will be relayed to NASA by two space crafts flying behind the lander called MarCO A MarCO B. The tones carry key information regarding the entry, descent and landing of the lander.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of InSight lander trajectory from Earth to Mars2. Representation of MarCOs following the InSight lander and transmitting its radio signals to Earth3. Portrayal of cameras and deployment arm of InSight lander4. Depiction of InSight's main instruments and their applicationsVOICEOVER (in English): "Nasa reports by the time NASA's InSight lander descends to Martian soil it will have travelled 480 million kilometers and spent six months travelling through space. "The probe will land on Elysium Planitia, a plain just 600 kilometers from Curiosity's landing site located near the equator.""According to NASA, the InSight lander is packed with two cameras that will aid with navigation and an instrument deployment arm that will place research devices on the planet's surface.""It carries three main instruments: A seismometer that measures Mar's seismic waves and detects meteor impacts, a heat probe that will penetrate 5 meters into the surface of the planet to measure its heat flow and interior temperature and two antennas called RISE that will help determine the size and composition of the planet's core. ""As InSight enters Mars' atmosphere it will emit radio signals subbed 'tones' these signals will be relayed to NASA by two space crafts flying behind the lander called MarCOs. "The tones carry key information regarding the entry, descent and landing of the lander. "  SOURCES: NASA.https://www.nasa.gov/feature/jpl/seven-ways-mars-insight-is-differenthttps://mars.nasa.gov/insight/https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/press_kits/insight/landing/download/mars_insight_landing_presskit.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 01:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/23/3735846/3735846_60E191803C5546BCAB20D6D688E66C8F_181123_3735846_New_NASA_Mars_lander_InSight_just_days_away_from_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  current events, education , educational, discovery news, mars, space, NASA, insight, lander, insight lander, mars exploration, explore, can we live on mars, colonize, travel, space travel, land on mars, spacecraft, astronaut, space exploration, NASA mission, 2018 launch, insight lander update, insight lander mission, Curiosity, Elysium Planitia, NASA engineers, Vandenberg Air Force base, santa barbara, launch date, explainer, atmosphere, explained, Astronomy, Geodesy, Seismology, Mars Cube One, MarCO.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3737930</guid>
      <title>Indian authorities struggling to retrieve killed U.S. missionary's body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIndian authorities have said retrieving the body of the killed American missionary from North Sentinel island could be difficult. According to CNN, police and the fishermen who reported seeing 26-year-old John Allen Chau's body last week, went close to the island on Friday and Saturday in an attempt to find a way to recover the body.   The police and fishermen saw a group of islanders armed with bows, arrows and spears guarding something on the beach, the New York Times reported.According to Dependra Pathak, a top police official in the Andaman and Nicobar Islands, "we have mapped the area with the help of these fishermen. We have not spotted the body yet but we roughly know the area where he is believed to be buried." Pathak added the Sentinelese were patrolling the beach around the same spot Chau was killed. Instead of approaching to retrieve the body, police sketched out the crime scene and then sailed away. North Sentinel Island is home to one of the last remaining untouched hunter-and-gatherer societies left in the world. It's about the size of Manhattan with an estimated population of about a few dozen people. India has kept the island off limits in order to prevent Sentinelese from catching modern illnesses and to keep trespassers from being killed.According to Indian law, people are not allowed to travel within five nautical miles of the  island and the Indian Navy patrols is day and night.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Sentinel Island location and islanders2. Indian police approaching the island3. Sentinelese guarding the beach4. Indian police watching Sentinelese from boatVOICEOVER (in English): "North Sentinel Island is home to one of the last remaining untouched hunter-and-gatherer societies left in the world. It's about the size of Manhattan, with an estimated population of about a few dozen people." "Indian authorities have said retrieving the body of the killed American missionary from the island could be difficult.""According to CNN, police and the fishermen who reported seeing 26-year-old John Allen Chau's body last week, went close to the island on Friday and Saturday in an attempt to find a way to recover the body." "According to the New York Times, the police and fishermen saw a group of islanders armed with bows, arrows and spears guarding something on the beach. "According to Dependra Pathak, a top police official in the Andaman and Nicobar Islands, "we have mapped the area with the help of these fishermen. We have not spotted the body yet but we roughly know the area where he is believed to be buried."" "Instead of approaching to retrieve the body, police sketched out the crime scene and then sailed away." SOURCES: New York Times, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/24/world/asia/north-sentinel-island-missionary-killed.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/25/asia/missionary-john-chau-north-sentinel-island-sentinelese/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/26/3737930/3737930_93A89844E0344F5EBEC72C68186405CA_181126_3737930_Indian_authorities_struggling_to_retrieve_killed_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US missionary killed, US missionary body retrieval, US missionary North Sentinel Island, North Sentinel Island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3737766</guid>
      <title>Engineers at MIT fly first plane with no moving parts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEngineers at MIT have designed a plane that flies using only ionic thrust. The aircraft was designed to resemble a glider, it weighs roughly two kilograms and has a 5-meter wingspan. The plane has two rows of wires under its wing. The row at the front end of the wing carries 20,000 volts of positively charged particles called ions. The ions are then attracted to the row on the back end of the wing which carries a negative charge of 20,000 volts. As the ions move to the back row they collide with neutral air pushing it behind the glider and generating electroaerodynamic thrust, driving the aircraft forward. This air is called ionic wind.According to their study, published in the journal Nature, the team tested the glider inside a gym where it managed to sustain flight and travel 60 meters, making it the first solid state flightor flight without moving parts like turbines and propellers.Engineers participating in the study hope this technology can be the first step towards designing aircrafts that are quieter and do not emit combustion emissions. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 2. 3. 4. VOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: http://news.mit.edu/2018/first-ionic-wind-plane-no-moving-parts-1121https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-018-0707-9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/26/3737766/3737766_E9D307E58B3D4C4BAFE2C6FEC30D45D8_181126_3737766_Engineers_at_MIT_fly_first_plane_with_no_moving__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, science, nature video, ionic wind, ion, electroaerodynamic propulsion, lifter, MIT, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Barrett, Steven Barrett, aeronautical engineering, flight, wright brothers, ion drive, engineering, power converter, hover car, electrode, battery, electric, plane, glide, glider, thrust, electric vehicle, technology, tech, sci, explained, explainer.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3737584</guid>
      <title>China to assign social credit scores to citizens by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is planning to launch a social credit system that will assign  "personal trustworthiness points" as a means of monitoring citizens and businesses.Reuters reports that trustworthy individuals will reportedly be provided with more access to society while individuals who are blacklisted will be severely restricted.Credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, character traits, behavior, preferences, and interpersonal relationships will all be considered in calculating a credit score.Data gathered by the system could impact an individual's access to public services and employment. It may also affect a citizen's ability to start a business. People with high trustworthy scores could be given easier market access.Participation is currently not mandatory. Once it becomes required, however, people with low scores could be punished with slower internet speeds, denied travel, and access to certain restaurants, night clubs, golf courses.Beijing plans to implement its social credit system by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Subway riders each with a social credit score2. Individuals deemed trustworthy by the government are on the safe side while those who aren't are blacklisted3. Citizens are given an individual score based on several factors4. Ways citizens could be impacted by their social credit score5. How businesses could be impacted by their social credit score6. Citizens with low scores could have access to certain things restricted7. China wrapped with a Chinese flag and a calendar iconVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, China is planning to launch a social credit system in which the government will assign "personal trustworthiness points" to monitor its citizens and businesses.""Trustworthy individuals will reportedly be provided with more access to society while individuals who are blacklisted will be severely restricted.""Everything from credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, character traits, behavior, preferences and interpersonal relationships will all be taken into account to calculate a credit score.""Data gathered on the system could also impact an individual's right to use public service and employment.""The data could also affect one's ability to start a business. People with high trustworthy scores could be given easier market access."  "Participation is currently not mandatory, however once it is, people with low scores could be also punished with slower internet speeds, denied access to certain restaurants, night clubs, golf courses or not being allowed to travel.""Beijing plans to implement its social credit system by 2020."SOURCES: Reuters, StraitsTimes, The Telegraph, The Independent, The Wired, Xinhuahttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-society-points/beijing-pioneering-citizens-points-system-critics-brand-orwellian-idUSKCN1NP0FT?utm_source=fark&utm_medium=website&utm_content=link&ICID=ref_farkhttps://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/beijing-pioneering-social-credit-systemhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/20/beijing-assign-personal-trustworthiness-points-citizens-2021/https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/china-social-credit-system-flight-booking-blacklisted-beijing-points-a8646316.htmlhttps://www.wired.co.uk/article/chinese-government-social-credit-score-privacy-invasionhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-11/21/c_137622527.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 02:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/26/3737584/3737584_66A76DCEF57A498C9388EE5297E0D848_181126_3737584_China_to_assign_social_credit_scores_to_citizens_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, China Social Credit System, China state surveillance, China social credit score, china social credit score system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3738673</guid>
      <title>Egyptian sarcophagus opened to reveal 3,000-year-old female mummy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA centuries-old coffin containing a well-preserved mummy was recently unveiled in Egypt  the latest in over a dozen ancient discoveries since the beginning of the year.Reuters reports that on Saturday Egyptian authorities opened a 3,000-year-old sarcophagus to reveal the mummified remains of a woman named Thuya, marking the first time such an artifact was unveiled in front of international media.The sarcophagus was one of two found earlier this month in the Al-Assasif necropolis on the western bank of the Nile river.The first was a rishi-style coffin from the 17th dynasty that had been opened earlier and examined by officials.Other finds include five colored masks and around 1,000 Ushabti statues, miniature figurines of servants to serve the dead in the afterlife.The Guardian reports that according to Egypt's antiquities ministry, the tomb belonged to a mummification supervisor at the Temple of Mut in Karnak.Workers had to remove some 300 meters of rubble over five months in order to get to the tomb, the ceiling of which was adorned in colorful paintings that depicted the owner and his family.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sarcophagus opened to reveal 3,000-year-old mummy of a woman2. Two sarcophagi found in Al-Assasif necropolis near Luxor3. First sarcophagus from 17th dynasty examined by officials4. Five masks and 1,000 statuettes found in tombVOICEOVER (in English): "On Saturday, Egyptian authorities opened a 3,000-year-old sarcophagus to reveal the mummified remains of a woman named Thuya, marking the first time such an artifact was unveiled in front of international media.""The sarcophagus was one of two found earlier this month in the Al-Assasif necropolis on the western bank of the Nile river.""The first was a rishi-style coffin from the 17th dynasty that had been opened earlier and examined by officials.""Other finds include five colored masks and around 1,000 Ushabti statues, which are miniature figurines of servants to serve the dead in the afterlife."SOURCES: Reuters, The Guardian, Middle East News Agencyhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-archaeology-discovery/egypt-unveils-previously-unopened-ancient-female-sarcophagus-idUSKCN1NT0POhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/25/mummified-woman-dating-back-3000-years-unveiled-in-egypthttp://www.egypttoday.com/Article/4/60898/Anani-witnesses-opening-of-Pharaonic-sarcophagus-in-Luxor***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/28/3738673/3738673_9E58691082A9414087DFA9ACDB51C502_181128_3738673_Egyptian_sarcophagus_opened_to_reveal_3_000_year_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mummy, mummies, sarcophagus, mummified woman, egyptian tomb, necropolis, egypt, archaeology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3738479</guid>
      <title>Chinese scientists claims to create world's first CRISPR babies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA scientist in China has been under scrutiny for allegedly using CRISPR, a gene-editing tool, to create the first gene-edited babies.In describing his process of gene-editing, He Jiankui said he first "washed" the sperm to separate it from semen and then placed the sperm into a single egg to create an embryo during in vitro fertilization.After the embryo was 3 to 5 days old, CRISPR-cas9 was used to remove a gene called CCR5.The scientist claims he previously experimented on editing the DNA of mice, monkey and human embryos in his lab for several years.He claims he altered the DNA to make the babies immune to HIV, according to the Associated Press. He also claims the gene surgery was a success and produced twin baby girls.The participants of the study were reportedly told that gene-editing was similar to a vaccine and were made to sign a consent form in which they were told that gene editing on an embryo has never been tried before and carries risks.An immediate investigation has been ordered into He's claims of having created the world's first genetically-edited babies, according to the National Health Commission of the People's Republic of China.The hospital He claims to have conducted the research in has denied any involvement with the surgery and said the babies weren't born there.Shenzhen Hermonicare Women's and Children's Hospital also said they plan to conduct an internal investigation on two doctors in their hospital that the Chinese scientist claims were also involved.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. CRISPR gene-editing tool2. Process of gene-editing to create an embryo3. Altering the DNA with CRISPR and HIV virus4. DNA strand and twin baby girls VOICEOVER (in English): "A scientist in China has been under scrutiny for allegedly using CRISPR, a gene-editing tool, to create the first gene-edited babies.""In describing his process of gene-editing, He Jiankui said he first 'washed' the sperm to separate it from semen and then placed the sperm into a single egg to create an embryo during in vitro fertilization.""After the embryo was 3-5 days old, CRISPR-cas9 was used to remove a gene called CCR5.""According to the Associated Press, He claims he altered the DNA to make the babies immune to HIV." "He also claims the gene surgery was a success and produced twin baby girls."SOURCES: The Associated Press, CNN, The New York Times, MIT Technology Review, National Health COmmission of the People's Republic of China,https://www.apnews.com/4997bb7aa36c45449b488e19ac83e86dhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/26/health/china-crispr-gene-editing-twin-babies-first-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/26/health/gene-editing-babies-china.htmlhttps://www.technologyreview.com/s/612458/exclusive-chinese-scientists-are-creating-crispr-babies/http://www.nhc.gov.cn/zhuz/ttyw/201811/314206cbb65d48e38ef30030b0eccbef.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 10:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/27/3738479/3738479_7FA44BECB3E24CBE9FE71D53A503D56C_181127_3738479_Chinese_scientists_claims_to_create_world_s_firs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, crispr babies, crispr gene editing, Chinese scientist, CRISPR, CRISPR technology, gene-editing, DNA, editing DNA, world's first genetically edited babies, CRISPR-cas9, CCR5]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3738198</guid>
      <title>The Leaning Tower of Pisa is losing its tilt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Tower of Pisa may be known for its distinctive tilt, but recent years have seen it becoming slightly more upright.The BBC reports that the Tower of Pisa was constructed on a layer of clay and sand that was softer to the south, and began to tilt by the time the third storey was being built.To compensate for this, the next five levels were constructed with one side shorter than the other, resulting in a structure that is not only tilting, but is also curved.By 1990, the marble tower was leaning six degrees, or 13 feet, according to CNN. Officials feared it might topple over and closed it to the public for corrective work.Cables were attached to the third storey to stabilize the tower. Counterweights and braces were added while soil was removed from the north side to allow it to straighten out.Experts say the Tower of Pisa is now stable, and has lost 1.5 inches of its tilt over the past 17 years, from its reopening in 2001 to the present.CBS reports that at its current pace, it may take another thousand years for the tower to straighten out completely. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tower of Pisa built on clay and sand that's softer on one side2. Tower of Pisa leaning 13 feet3. Tower of Pisa corrective work4. Tower of Pisa straightening out from 2001 to presentVOICEOVER (in English): "The Tower of Pisa was constructed on a layer of clay and sand that was softer to the south, and began to tilt by the time the third storey was being built.""By 1990, the marble tower was leaning six degrees, or 13 feet. Officials feared it might topple over and closed it to the public for corrective work.""Cables were attached to the third storey to stabilize the tower. Counterweights and braces were added while soil was removed from the north side to allow it to straighten out.""Experts say the Tower of Pisa is now stable, and has lost 1.5 inches of its tilt over the past 17 years, from its reopening in 2001 to the present."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardian, CNN, CBS, Leaning Tower of Pisahttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46300789https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/22/leaning-tower-of-pisa-is-leaning-less-than-before-say-expertshttps://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/leaning-tower-of-pisa-tilt-scli-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/the-leaning-tower-of-pisa-is-leaning-less-these-days/?ftag=CNM-00-10aag7ehttps://leaningtowerpisa.com/facts/how/how-pisa-leaning-tower-was-stabilized***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 03:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/27/3738198/3738198_948040BA9DCA44C39A7AAC4AF132870F_181127_3738198_The_Leaning_Tower_of_Pisa_is_losing_its_tilt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, leaning tower of pisa, tower of pisa, leaning tower, pisa, marble tower, pisa restoration, bell tower, italy tower]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3739115</guid>
      <title>New water treatment method is based on a sea creature</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have taken inspiration from a sea creature to create a new kind of water treatment.According to the study published in the journal Nature Nanotechnology, coagulation is a chemical water treatment process that causes colloidal and suspended water-borne particles to group into formations and settle.Conventional coagulants like aluminum sulfate remove large particles but cannot capture smaller dissolved contaminants.Researchers from Yale and Peking University have sought to address this issue. They modeled a nanocoagulant after the sea anemone Actinia to remove a broad range of contaminants in a single step.  Like the Actinia, the nanocoagulant's core-shell structure turns inside out in water.  The shell traps larger particles while the exposed core captures smaller, dissolved ones.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How water coagulation process works2. Conventional coagulants remove only large particles3. Nanocoagulant modelled after sea anemone4. How actinia-like nanocoagulant worksVOICEOVER (in English): "Coagulation is a chemical water treatment process that causes colloidal and suspended particles in water to group into formations and settle.""But while conventional coagulants like aluminum sulfate remove large particles, they are unable to capture smaller dissolved contaminants.""Researchers from Yale and Peking University sought to address this." "They modeled a nanocoagulant after the sea anemone Actinia to remove a broad range of contaminants in a single step.""Like the Actinia, the nanocoagulant's core-shell structure turns inside out in water. "The shell traps larger particles while the exposed core captures smaller, dissolved ones."SOURCES: Nature Nanotechnology, Nature, Yale Universityhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41565-018-0307-8https://sustainabilitycommunity.nature.com/users/194517-jinwei-liu/posts/41419-single-step-water-treatment-with-a-multi-functional-biomimetic-nanocoagulanthttps://seas.yale.edu/news-events/news/water-treatment-breakthrough-inspired-sea-creature***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/28/3739115/3739115_E2DE01B2FBFC4559A14CFC860C14B00B_181128_3739115_New_water_treatment_method_is_based_on_a_sea_cre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, water treatment, actinia, sea anemone, sea creature, coagulation, water coagulation, nanocoagulant, multifunctional nanocoagulant, water filtration, coagulant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3738942</guid>
      <title>Researchers analyze antibiotic resistant bacteria found in ISS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the California Institute of Technology studied bacteria retrieved from the ISS space toilet and exercise platform.According to their study published in the journal BMC Microbiology, all five strains that were analyzed proved to be resistant to several common antibiotics such as penicillin, rifampin, cefazolin, cefoxitin and oxacillin among others. They showed a level of intermediate resistance for ciprofloxacin and erythromycin.Researchers reported that the microbes found on the ISS are a variety of the Enterobacter, a bacterium that causes diseases in newborns and people with weak immune systems.According to experimentation through computer modelling, there is a 79 percent chance that the bacteria could be pathogenic  or likely to cause a disease in humans.Researchers are concerned about the health risks the propagation of such bacterias could pose for astronauts in future missions. The team stated that ''in vivo" experiments would help further understand the true levels of pathogenicity of the bacteria among humans.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of ISS's toilet and gym2. Representation of bacteria's immunity to antibiotics 3. Portrayal of individuals that could be affected by bacteria4. Depiction of level of pathogeny of bacteriaVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the California Institute of Technology studied bacteria retrieved from the ISS space toilet and exercise platform.""All five strains that were analyzed proved to be resistant to several common antibiotics such as penicillin, rifampin and cefazolin among others.""Researchers reported that the microbes found on the ISS are a variety of the Enterobacter, a bacterium that causes diseases in newborns and people with weak immune systems.""According to their study published in the journal BMC Microbiology, there is a 79 percent chance that the bacteria could be pathogenic  or likely to cause a disease in humans." SOURCES: BMC Microbiologyhttps://bmcmicrobiol.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12866-018-1325-2#Sec2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 07:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/28/3738942/3738942_CB185A9D5D9D4475B7A9049D91DCAC98_181128_3738942_Researchers_analyze_antibiotic_resistant_bacteri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, current events, science, ISS, space, bacteria, International space station, NASA, astronauts, disease, space exploration, microbiology, research, health, toilet, pathogenic, superbugs, antibiotic, antibiotic resistance, enterobacter, physics, technology, explainer, tech, California Institute of Technology, humans, microbes.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3738819</guid>
      <title>Frozen sea turtles wash up on Massachusetts shore</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least 219 cold stunned sea turtles have washed ashore in Cape Cod Bay, Massachusetts over the last week.According to the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, cold stunning occurs when the sea turtles are exposed to extreme periods of cold water temperatures.This impairs sea turtles as they are cold-blooded reptiles and depend on external sources for heat. They do not have the ability to warm themselves in cold water.Turtles with the condition suffer from various symptoms including, a decreased heart rate, low blood circulation, shock, pneumonia and death.Robert Prescott, director of the Massachusetts Audubon Society's Wellfleet Bay Wildlife Sanctuary, told the paper the sea turtles were "flash-frozen" in swimming positions. Prescott added changing weather conditions next week may result in more living turtles.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sea turtle washing ashore Cape Cod Bay2. Sea turtle exposed to cold water in the sea3. Impact of the cold water on the sea turtle4. Symptoms of cold stunning VOICEOVER (in English): "At least 219 cold stunned sea turtles have washed ashore in Cape Cod Bay, Massachusetts over the last week.""According to the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, cold stunning occurs when the sea turtles are exposed to extreme periods of cold water temperatures.""This impairs sea turtles as they are cold-blooded reptiles and depend on external sources for heat. They do not have the ability to warm themselves in cold water.""Turtles with the condition suffer from various symptoms including, a decreased heart rate, low blood circulation, shock, pneumonia and even death."SOURCES: USA TODAY, NOAA, NPR, CNN, Ecowatch, Cape Cod Times,https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/26/hundreds-sea-turtles-stunned-cold-wash-up-cape-cod/2112520002/https://www.greateratlantic.fisheries.noaa.gov/protected/stranding/overview/cold.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/2018/11/25/670705681/more-than-200-sea-turtles-stunned-by-cold-wash-up-off-cape-cod-this-weekhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/24/us/dead-sea-turtles-massachusetts/index.htmlhttps://www.ecowatch.com/sea-turtle-cape-cod-weather-2621527394.htmlhttps://www.capecodtimes.com/news/20181123/wellfleet-sanctuary-busy-as-turtles-continue-to-wash-ashore-in-cold***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/28/3738819/3738819_94134B631DA94FD9932F28C2BED6E49F_181128_3738819_Frozen_sea_turtles_wash_up_on_Massachusetts_shor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, Cape Cod,  sea turtles, cold stunning, cape cod cold stunning, cold stunned sea turtles, cold spell, frozen sea turtles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3738806</guid>
      <title>Deforestation in Brazil's Amazon is at the highest level a decade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBrazil has recorded its worst annual deforestation figures in 10 years.An area spanning 7,900 square kilometers of the Amazon rainforest was destroyed between August 2017 and July 2018, according to the BBC.This represents a 13.7 percent increase from last year's figures.Most of the deforestation took place in the Brazilian states of Mato Grosso and Para.In addition to affecting water supplies, deforestation could also cause the rainforest to start releasing greenhouse gases instead of taking in carbon dioxide from the atmosphere, the National Geographic reports.Carlos Nobre, a climate scientist, said if 60 percent of the forest degrades to a savanna, it could result in five or six years' of fossil-fuel emissions being released into the air.Deforestation was responsible for 46 percent of Brazil's greenhouse gas emissions in 2017, according to the Guardian.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.A healthy rainforest, a destroyed rainforest and a thermometer 2. Map of Brazilian states of Mato Grosso and Para3. Destroyed rainforest releasing carbon dioxide into the atmosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, 7,900 square kilometers of the Amazon rainforest was destroyed between August 2017 and July 2018.""This represents a 13.7 percent increase from last year's figures.""Most of the deforestation took place in the Brazilian states of Mato Grosso and Para.""In addition to affecting water supplies, the National Geographic reports deforestation could also cause the rainforest to start releasing greenhouse gases instead of taking in carbon dioxide from the atmosphere."SOURCES: The Guardian, The BBC, National Geographic, Brazil's Ministry of Environment, https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/24/brazil-records-worst-annual-deforestation-for-a-decadehttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-46327634https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2018/11/how-cutting-the-amazon-forest-could-affect-weather/http://www.mma.gov.br/informma/item/15259-governo-federal-divulga-taxa-de-desmatamento-na-amaz%C3%B4nia.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 03:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/28/3738806/3738806_1D5F2B8244D2417C8413F603AA835BCD_181128_3738806_Deforestation_in_Brazil_s_Amazon_is_at_the_highe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, deforestation, tropical forests, Amazon, amazon rainforest, environment, rainforest destruction, tropical forests, brazil deforestation, brazil rainforest deforestation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3738736</guid>
      <title>Scientists research 'dimming sun' to fight climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists from Harvard and Yale suggest using solar geoengineering as a way to combat climate change.Fleets of specially designed aircrafts would fly roughly 20 kilometers above ground in the lower stratosphere.Once there the planes would spray tiny sulphate particulates to block sunlight in a process that is known as stratospheric aerosol injection.According to their research, published in the journal Environmental Research Letters, this technique could cut the rate of global warming in half. Researchers who participated in the study state it would be a 'remarkably inexpensive' process costing around $2 bn to $2.5 bn a year.According to CNN, using this method would not lower greenhouse gas emissions and could also have negative consequences such as extreme shifts in weather and endangering crop yields. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Portrayal of plane flying in Earth's stratosphere2. Depiction of plane spraying sulfate aerosol3. Representation of sulfate aerosol blocking heat from sun4. Depiction of consequences of stratospheric aerosol injectionVOICEOVER (in English): "Fleets of specially designed aircrafts would fly roughly 20 kilometers above ground in the lower stratosphere.""Once there, the planes would release tiny sulphate particulates, which would block sunlight in a process known as stratospheric aerosol injection.""According to their study, published in the journal Environmental Research Letters, this technique could cut the rate of global warming in half.""However, this method could also have negative consequences, such cause extreme shifts in weather and endanger crop yields. "SOURCES: Environmental Research Lettershttp://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/aae98d#erlaae98ds4***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/28/3738736/3738736_55542565D3384CDD90DE1E5CDAFE8739_181128_3738736_Scientists_research__dimming_sun__to_fight_clima_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, news, science, tech, technology, sun, space, aerosole, harvard university, global warming , climate change, climate engineering, planetary engineering, environmental research letters, harvard, greenhouse gases, emissions, sulfate, global dimming, sun dimming, solar radiation management, conspiracy, temperature rise, temperature rising, sea levels rising, droughts, weather, extreme weather.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3739908</guid>
      <title>Russia-Ukraine tensions rise after capture of Ukrainian ships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTensions between Russia and Ukraine rise after a naval confrontation near the Kerch Strait.Two Ukrainian gunboats and a tug boat departed on Sunday morning from the Black Sea port of Odessa and were headed to Mariupol, a north coast city on the Sea of Azov, on November 25th.According to BBC, as the boats approached the Kerch Strait, they were intercepted by Russian boats. Russian coast guard opened fire on the Ukrainian vessels, ramming one of its ships against a Ukrainian boat.Russian fighter jets and helicopters patrolled the area around the strait as the boats attempted to approach the channel. They also blocked the bridge with a tanker.Ukrainian authorities claim six crew members were injured during the encounter, while Russian authorities maintain only of the sailors suffered injuries.Kerch Strait is the only waterway separating Crimea from the Russian mainland. Beyond the strait is The Sea of Azov whichaccording to a 2003 bilateral treatycounts as shared territorial waters. The BBC reports, Russian President Vladimir Putin told German Chancellor Angela Merkel that the Ukrainian navy had "ignored the rules of peaceful passage in the territorial sea of the Russian Federation." Ukrainian President Petro Poroshenko has announced martial law in regions bordering Russia, Belarus, and the separatist region of Trans-Dniester.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of location of Ukrainian and Russian vessel's encounter2. Depiction of Russian coast guard ship hitting Ukrainian tugboat 3. Portrayal of Russian authorities patrolling Kerch Strait4. Representations of injured crewmen according to Ukrainian and Russian authoritiesVOICEOVER (in English): "Two Ukrainian gunboats and a tug boat departed on Sunday morning from the Black Sea port of Odessa and were headed to Mariupol, a north coast city on the Sea of Azov, on November 25th.""According to the BBC, as the boats approached the Kerch Strait, they were intercepted by Russian boats. Russian coast guard opened fire on the Ukrainian vessels, ramming one of its ships against a Ukrainian boat.""Russian fighter jets and helicopters patrolled the area around the strait as the boats attempted to approach the channel. They also blocked the bridge with a tanker.""Ukrainian authorities claim six crew members were injured during the encounter while Russian authorities maintain only of the sailors suffered injuries."SOURCES: BBC, APhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46340283https://www.apnews.com/8a8cd9a266a3440abba77fc6d02f8ce***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/29/3739908/3739908_C4B4EE66E8C54D5E991677C6FE18E5B9_181129_3739908_Russia_Ukraine_tensions_rise_after_capture_of_Uk_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, crimea conflict, ukraine, russia, ukraine russia conflict, crimea russia, crimea 2018, crimea patrol, ukraine russia ship, ukraine martial law, ukraine ships, ukraine crimea, crimea, kremlin, kiev, kerch strait, black sea, tension, escalation, clash, naval, ships, politics, political, political news, conflict, world news, Petro Poroshenko, Vladimir Putin, Putin, vessel, moscow.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3739718</guid>
      <title>Singapore researchers turn plastic bottles into aerogel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the National University of Singapore have found a way to convert plastic bottles into an ultralight super material with various applications.Eco-Business reports that the process involves plastic bottles made from polyethylene terephthalate or PET. These are first shredded into fibers and combined with several chemicals, including hydrochloric acid and polyvinyl acetate.The solution is put in a sonicator where it is mixed using sound energy, then freeze-dried to produce an aerogel that is soft, durable, and flexible. One plastic bottle can produce an A4 sheet of aerogel.According to a press release from the National University of Singapore, the aerogel is versatile, and can serve unique functions depending on the surface treatments. When coated with an amine group, it can be used in pollution masks to absorb dust particles and carbon dioxide.It can absorb large amounts of oil when incorporated with various methyl groups, and withstand temperatures of up to 620 degrees Celsius when coated with fire retardant chemicals.Researchers have listed several practical uses for the aerogels, like cleaning oil spills, building insulation, or as a lightweight thermal lining for firefighter coats.The fabrication process is also quicker and more cost-effective than conventional methods, and easily scalable for mass production. Because of this, the team is hopeful that the technology can help decrease the damage brought about by widespread plastic pollution.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. PET plastic bottles shredded into fibers, combined with chemicals 2. Solution mixed with sonicator, freeze-dried to form aerogel3. Aerogel coated with amines to absorb dust and carbon dioxide4. Aerogel can absorb oil, become heat resistantVOICEOVER (in English): "PET plastic bottles are first shredded into fibers and combined with several chemicals, including hydrochloric acid and polyvinyl acetate.""The solution is put in a sonicator where it's mixed using sound waves, then freeze-dried to produce an aerogel that is soft, durable and flexible.""The aerogel is versatile and can have unique functions with different surface treatments. When coated with an amine group, it can be used in pollution masks to absorb dust particles and carbon dioxide.""It can absorb large amounts of oil when incorporated with various methyl groups, and withstand temperatures of up to 620 degrees Celsius when coated with fire retardant chemicals."SOURCES: National University of Singapore, Eco-Businesshttps://news.nus.edu.sg/press-releases/pet-aerogel-plastic-bottle-wastehttps://www.eco-business.com/news/worlds-first-aerogels-made-from-pet-bottles-to-tackle-plastic-waste/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 09:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/29/3739718/3739718_78E3CBF08B9940B8A2EA5E635376248B_181129_3739718_Singapore_researchers_turn_plastic_bottles_into__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic bottles, aerogel, plastic pollution, plastic waste, PET bottles, plastic bottles, recycling, plastic recycling, national university of singapore, NUS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3739522</guid>
      <title>First tunnel boring machine arrives for Grand Paris Express</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe first tunnel boring machine or TBM to be used for the Grand Paris Express has arrived.The Grand Paris Express project was announced in 2007 and is aimed at developing Greater Paris into a green metropolitan area.The machine will be more than 100 meters long and 10 meters in diameter and will be assembled onsite at Champigny Plateau, according to The Construction Index.Once assembled, the TBM will be able to drill at a depth of 55 feet below the surface at a rate of 10 to 12 meters a day, according to Railway Technology.It will be used to drill a 2.2 kilometer long connecting tunnel between the Champigny operating center and the main tunnel from Line 15 South at Villiers-sur-Marne.The Grand Paris Express plans to build new lines and open to the public in stages starting from 2022, in time for the 2024 Summer Olympics.The express is expected to carry two million passengers a day and run automated trains every 2 to 3 minutes once it opens.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tunnel boring machine2. Measurement of the tunnel boring machine3. Tunnel boring machine drilling underneath the surface4. Connecting tunnel the machine plans to drill VOICEOVER (in English): "The first tunnel boring machine or TBM to be used for the Grand Paris Express has arrived.""The machine will be more than 100 meters long and 10 meters in diameter.""The TBM will be able to drill at a depth of 55 feet below the surface at a rate of 10 to 12 meters a day.""It will be used to drill a 2.2 kilometer long connecting tunnel between the Champigny operating center and the main tunnel from Line 15 South at Villiers-sur-Marne."SOURCES: The Construction Index, Railway-Technology, Tunnelling Journal, The B1M, Ground Engineering, Besix Press Releasehttps://www.theconstructionindex.co.uk/news/view/first-tunnelling-machine-arrives-for-grand-paris-expresshttps://www.railway-technology.com/projects/grand-paris-express/https://tunnellingjournal.com/first-grand-paris-express-tbm-assembly/https://www.theb1m.com/video/first-tbm-for-grand-paris-express-launchedhttps://www.geplus.co.uk/news/first-grand-paris-metro-tbm-arrives-on-site/10027628.articlehttps://press.besix.com/launch-ceremony-for-the-first-tunnel-boring-machine-of-the-grand-paris-express-project***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 05:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/29/3739522/3739522_42FB229CD63F459A98783EB607E0289D_181129_3739522_First_tunnel_boring_machine_arrives_for_Grand_Pa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Grand Paris Express, France, Paris,grand paris express, paris train, tunnel, long tunnel, paris tunnel, grand paris express metro, grand paris express english, tunnel boring machine, 2024 summer olympics, grand paris express project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3740500</guid>
      <title>Japan preparing first aircraft carrier since World War II</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan is planning to upgrade at least on of its ships to an aircraft carrier in preparation for a procurement of around 100 U.S. F-35 stealth fighter jets to counter Chinese military expansion in the Pacific.  According to the Guardian, Japan plans to upgrade its two Izumo-class helicopter carriers to transport and launch fighter jets.The Nikkei News Service reported that Japan was set to purchase 100 F-35s from the U.S. in a deal worth more than US$8.8 billion.According to CNN, the package includes F-35 A and B models. F-35As are similar to conventional fighter jets that use a runway for take off and landing. F-35Bs have short take off and vertical landing capability, meaning they can be used at smaller airports or operate from flattop warships. Japan's Izumo-class carrier is 814 meters long and can carry up to 14 helicopters.According to former US Navy captain and current Hawaii Pacific University Professor Carl Schuster telling CNN, a refitted Japanese carrier would only be able to carry six to eight F-35Bs.     According to Mainichi Shimbun, the carriers would be used to defend Japan's remote south-western islands.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Japan Izumo-class carriers and an F35B performing a vertical take off2. F-35A taking off and F-35B doing a vertical landing3. Izumo class carrier length and helicopter carrying capacity4. F-35-B landing on Izumo-class carrierVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Guardian, Japan plans to upgrade its two Izumo-class helicopter carriers to transport and launch fighter jets.""The Nikkei News Service reported that Japan was set to purchase 100 F-35s from the U.S. in a deal worth more than US$8.8 billion.""According to CNN, the package includes F-35 A and B models. F-35As are similar to conventional fighter jets that use a runway for take off and landing." "F-35Bs have short take-off and vertical landing capability, meaning they can be used at smaller airports or operate from flattop warships." "Japan's Izumo-class carrier is 814 meters long and can carry up to 14 helicopters.""According to former US Navy captain and current Hawaii Pacific University Professor Carl Schuster telling CNN, a refitted Japanese carrier would only be able to carry six to eight F-35Bs." SOURCES: The Guardian, CNN https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/29/japan-to-get-first-aircraft-carrier-since-second-world-war-amid-china-concernshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/29/asia/japan-f-35-fighter-aircraft-carrier-intl/index.html?no-st=1543536735***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/30/3740500/3740500_2C1F891204FC4DDEB668FBB476458C90_181130_3740500_Japan_preparing_first_aircraft_carrier_since_Wor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Japan aircraft carrier, Japan F-35A, Japan F-35B, Japan F-35 deal, Izumo class, Japan Izumo class carrier]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3740451</guid>
      <title>Male birth control gel set to begin human trials</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. scientists are set to trial an experimental male contraceptive that if successful would fill an important public health need and pave the way for reproductive equality.According to a press release from the National Institutes of Health, NES/T is a contraceptive gel whose primary compound is the progestin hormone Nestorone, which reduces sperm by blocking testosterone production in the testes.The gel also contains a concentration of testosterone to maintain blood levels of the hormone, in order to ensure a normal sex drive and other functions.The clear gel is applied daily to the back and shoulders, and absorbed through the skin.To test its efficacy, researchers will study 420 couples for a year. The men will be tracked for up to 16 weeks to ensure sperm levels have declined, with women using an alternative form of birth control. Couples will then use the gel as the sole method of contraception for 52 weeks, to see if it does prevent pregnancy.After the trials, male participants will be observed for several more weeks to check for any after effects, and make sure sperm production returns to normal.Results from the trial are expected in 2022. If successful, it will need to be evaluated in a larger trial before it can obtain FDA approval and be available commercially.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nestorone in male contraceptive gel blocks testosterone production to limit sperm 2. Replacement testosterone in blood maintains normal functions3. Gel applied on back and shoulders4. Details of clinical trialVOICEOVER (in English): "NES/T is a contraceptive gel whose primary compound is the progestin hormone Nestorone, which reduces sperm by blocking testosterone production in the testes.""The gel also contains a concentration of testosterone to maintain blood levels of the hormone, in order to ensure a normal sex drive and other functions.""The clear gel is applied daily to the back and shoulders, and absorbed through the skin.""Researchers will be testing its efficacy by studying 420 couples for a year. Men will be tracked for up to 16 weeks to ensure sperm levels have declined, with women using an alternative form of birth control. After that, couples will rely on the gel alone."SOURCES: National Institutes of Health, University of Washington, CBShttps://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/nih-evaluate-effectiveness-male-contraceptive-skin-gelhttps://newsroom.uw.edu/news/1st-trial-launches-test-male-contraceptive-gel-efficacyhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/researchers-studying-effectiveness-of-male-birth-control-gel/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/30/3740451/3740451_C2D7FD201A354B99A5D54CF7C77C17F9_181130_3740451_Male_birth_control_gel_set_to_begin_human_trials_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, male birth control, male contraceptive, male contraception, birth control, contraception, contraceptive, nestorone, testosterone, family planning, pregnancy prevention]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3740280</guid>
      <title>Research in mice suggests production of brown fat could help battle obesity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at the University of Cambridge believe a molecule present in rats could help fight obesity in humans. Humans have two types of fat, white and brown. White fat stores energy and acts as a thermal insulator. However, excessive amounts could lead to diabetes, heart disease and certain types of cancer. Brown fat, on the other hand, burns calories to generate heat. Scientists from the University of Cambridge detected a molecule in mice called BMP8b. This protein controls the activation of brown fat in the brain and body tissue of mice. According to their study published in the journal Nature, they analyzed mice that had been bred to produce higher levels of the molecule in fat tissue. Researchers discovered that increased levels of the protein caused white fat to become beige  or turn brown burning more calories and generating more energy as a result. They concluded that it could be possible to create a drug that alters fat function in humans just as the BMP8b protein does in mice. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of types of fat and their function in humans2. Depiction of BMP8b protein in mice3. Representation of white fat cells in mice turning into beige fat cells 4. Portrayal of possible drug with similar effect of BMP8b protein for humansVOICEOVER (in English): "Humans have two types of fat, white and brown. White fat stores energy and acts as a thermal insulator. However, excessive amounts could lead to diabetes, heart disease and certain types of cancer. Brown fat, on the other hand, burns calories to generate heat."   "Scientists from the University of Cambridge detected a molecule in mice called BMP8b. This protein controls the activation of brown fat in the brain and body tissue of mice." "According to their study published in the journal Nature, they analyzed mice that had been bred to produce higher levels of the molecule in fat tissue. "Researchers discovered that increased levels of the protein caused white fat to become beige  or turn brown burning more calories and generating more energy as a result." "They concluded that it could be possible to create a drug that alters fat function in humans just as the BMP8b protein does in mice." SOURCES: Naturehttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-018-07453-x#search-menu***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 08:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/30/3740280/3740280_9E59D861C661478A8BA6D3E558FDC359_181130_3740280_Research_in_mice_suggests_production_of_brown_fa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, white fat , brown fat, beige fat, health obesity, fitness, weight loss, research, fat storage, technology, science, sci, tech, molecule, protein, overweight, BMP8b, Cambridge, scientists, University of Cambridge, nature.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3740120</guid>
      <title>Researchers discover greenhouse gas eating ocean bacteria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found several new types of sea-borne microbes that could eat oil and other pollutants.Some of the newly discovered species use hydrocarbons, such as methane and butane, as energy sources, according to a University of Texas at Austin news release.The researchers used the Alvin deep-sea submersible and collected 551 genomes. As many as 22 of those were said to be new species.The microbes found within the Guaymas Basin in the Gulf of California. They were living in hot, deep-sea sediments located 2,000 meters below the surface. Temperatures can rise up to 200 degrees Celsius at this depth due to volcanic activity.Brett Baker, a scientist involved in the research, explained there are huge reservoirs of hydrocarbon gases under the ocean floor. He explained these microbes help prevent greenhouse gases from being released into the atmosphere. Baker added that there is much-unexplored biodiversity in the deep oceans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Microbes under the sea, an oil barrel and CO2 2. What the microbes use as an energy source3. Where the microbes were found4. Ocean floor of the microbesVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have found several new types of sea-borne microbes that eat oil and other pollutants.""According to a University of Texas at Austin news release, some of the newly discovered species use hydrocarbons, such as methane and butane, as energy sources.""The researchers found 551 genomes and 22 of those were said to be new species.""The microbes found within the Guaymas Basin in the Gulf of California.""They were living in hot, deep-sea sediments located 2,000 meters below the surface."Temperatures can rise up to 200 degrees Celsius at this depth due to volcanic activity.""Brett Baker, a scientist involved in the research, explained there are huge reservoirs of hydrocarbon gases under the ocean floor. "Baker explained these microbes help prevent greenhouse gases from being released into the atmosphere."SOURCES: University of Texas, Science Daily, Nature Communications Journalhttps://cns.utexas.edu/news/newly-discovered-deep-sea-microbes-gobble-greenhouse-gases-and-perhaps-oil-spills-toohttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/11/181127092525.htmhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-018-07418-0#Abs1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 05:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/11/30/3740120/3740120_D668B2FD01E447C6A5A25457791B04BF_181130_3740120_Researchers_discover_greenhouse_gas_eating_ocean_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microbes, deep sea microbes, microbes under the sea, hydrocarbons, methane, butane, energy source, Guaymas Basin, new species, deep sea, deep oceans, greenhouse gases, oil, genomes, ocean floor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
