<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3453902</guid>
      <title>Czech brewery uses crayfish biosensors to check water quality</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA Czech beer brewery is using crayfish to help maintain the purity of their water supply.Reuters reports that Protivin Brewery in the Czech Republic's South Bohemian region equipped crayfish with high-tech biosensors that monitor their heartbeat and movement.The crayfish were placed in tanks, which were pumped with water from the same natural spring source the brewery uses to make its beers.Crayfish are able to detect pollutants or impurities in the water, and react to it with changes in their body or behavior.A computer analyzes the data and flags down changes in water quality when three or more crayfish change their pulse activity  with results coming in within 3 minutes.Scientists at South Bohemia University have patented the water system, and plan to upgrade the technology to include a special crayfish-heart monitoring camera.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Crayfish fitted with biosensors2. Crayfish in tank with water from same spring source used to brew beer3. Crayfish react to pollutants in water with changes in body, behavior4. Computer flags down changes in water quality once three or more crayfish reactVOICEOVER (in English): "Protivin Brewery in the Czech Republic's South Bohemian region equipped crayfish with high-tech biosensors that monitor their heartbeat and movement.""The crayfish were placed in tanks, which were pumped with water from the same natural spring source the brewery uses to make its beers.""Crayfish are able to detect pollutants or impurities in the water, and react to it with changes in their body or behavior.""A computer analyzes the data and flags down changes in water quality when three or more crayfish change their pulse activity  with results coming in within 3 minutes."SOURCES: Reutershttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-czech-crayfish-water-purity/crayfish-staff-help-czech-brewery-keep-its-water-as-pure-as-can-be-idUSKCN1C22GP***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 06:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/02/3453902/3453902_D627477A00CC4D17BFF8A78745A4A970_171002_3453902_Czech_brewery_uses_crayfish_biosensors_to_check__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B66/EDF/B66EDFD603E34676A42113D8451B1176_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, crayfish, biosensor, czech brewery, crayfish sensor, czech beer, beer, pure water, water purity, impurities, spring water, protivin brewery, protivin, czech republic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3453887</guid>
      <title>U.S. and Russia team up to build lunar space station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA and Russia's space agency Roscosmos will team up to work on a new space station near the moon.Space agencies from Japan, Europe and Canada are also interested in working on the project that is currently at the conceptual stage of design.According to Popular Science, the two agencies last month signed an agreement to work on the Deep Space Gateway at the International Aeronautics Congress in Adelaide, Australia. The proximity of the station to the moon would create opportunities for lunar missions and future deep space exploration such as missions to Mars, and beyond.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of American and Russian astronauts working together2. Depiction of Deep Space Gateway over the moon3. Depiction of exploration missions on the Moon and Mars4. Other space agencies interested in working on the projectVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: NASA, Popular Science, Inhabitathttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/deep-space-gateway-to-open-opportunities-for-distant-destinationshttps://www.popsci.com/g00/nasa-russia-moon-space-station?i10c.encReferrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS50dy8%3Dhttp://inhabitat.com/us-and-russia-are-teaming-up-to-build-a-lunar-spaceport/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 05:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/02/3453887/3453887_CE3B1602A370477B9A69209E08B9D6BF_171002_3453887_U_S__and_Russia_team_up_to_build_lunar_space_sta_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/07E/B62/07EB627974C44EC78F5F73B6141DB85A_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, moon space station, russia and usa friendship, nasa, roscosmos, lunar space station, deep space gateway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454826</guid>
      <title>How the Las Vegas shooting unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAt least 59 people were killed and 527 injured when a sniper opened fire at a Las Vegas concert on Sunday night. Gunman Stephen Paddock, a 64-year old white male, from Mesquite, Nev., opened fire from the 32nd floor of the Mandalay Bay Hotel towards a country music festival, the Washington Post reported. Authorities found dozens of guns in his hotel room and "in excess of" 19 firearms and bombs at his Nevada residence. At 10:08 p.m., Paddock open fire straight down into the concert venue across the street, a quarter-mile away, according to the Washington Post. Paddock was staying in a suite with two rooms, Las Vegas Sheriff Joseph Lombardo said. Authorities think he fired from both rooms to get better angles. The shooting went on from between five to fifteen minutes, however estimates vary. Authorities were able to locate the shooter because the smoke from his guns set the fire alarm off. A SWAT team entered Paddock's room. Around that time, Paddock killed himself, Lombardo said. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The location of the shooting on the Vegas Strip2. The shooter firing from two different windows in his hotel suite3. The shooting went on for between 5 and 15 minutes4. Guns were found in shooter's hotel room and homeVOICEOVER (in English): "Gunman Stephen Paddock, identified as a 64-year-old white male, opened fire at 10:08 p.m. from the 32nd floor of the Mandalay Bay Hotel toward Route 91 Harvest country music festival.""Paddock was staying in a large suite with two rooms. Authorities believe he used both rooms to shoot from different angles.""The shooting went on from between 5 to 15 minutes, however, estimates vary." "Authorities found dozens of guns in his hotel room and at least 19 firearms and bombs at his Nevada residence."SOURCES: Washington Post, Mercury News, BBChttps://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2017/national/las-vegas-shooting/?utm_term=.190cad717c3bhttp://www.mercurynews.com/2017/10/02/scene-of-las-vegas-shooting-where-was-the-killer/http://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-41479011***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/03/3454826/3454826_E310D2F58225401DAABFC4F0CCDA2C18_171003_3454826_How_the_Las_Vegas_shooting_unfolded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/204/1CC/2041CCD14A0B437A8FBF8A9C7DD0EBFA_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Las Vegas shooting, Mandalay Bay, Stephen Paddock, Vegas shooting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454622</guid>
      <title>Artist and Nevada Museum will launch space sculpture</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAn artist is working with the Nevada Museum of Art to send a satellite sculpture up into space that can be seen from Earth. The "orbital reflector" is a satellite that will serve no military, commercial or scientific purpose, the museum said. The sculpture will be packed inside a small CubeSat that will be launched aboard a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket scheduled for early 2018. Once in orbit at a height of approximately 350 miles (575 km), a 100-foot long diamond-shaped balloon will deploy from the satellite. The balloon will reflect sunlight back to Earth, causing the CubeSat to be visible to the naked eye, according to the museum. It will stay in space for about two months. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The orbital reflector orbiting Earth2. Falcon 9 carrying orbital reflector launching3. Orbital reflector orbit height4. Orbital reflector reflecting sunlight down to EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "The 'orbital reflector' space sculpture is a satellite that will serve no military, commercial or scientific purpose.""Constructed from lightweight material similar to Mylar, it will be launched aboard a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket scheduled for early 2018.""Once in orbit at a height of approximately 350 miles, a 100-foot long diamond-shaped balloon will deploy from the satellite." "The balloon will reflect sunlight back to Earth, causing the CubeSat to be visible to the naked eye. It will stay in space for about two months." SOURCES: Newsweek, Kickstarter Trevor Paglenhttp://www.newsweek.com/elon-musk-spacex-launch-sculpture-art-space-674609https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/nevadaart/trevor-paglen-orbital-reflector?ref=334345&token=671dfe5b***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 06:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/03/3454622/3454622_43AE4BCAAEEB4C63A424222EB0F4CED4_171003_3454622_Artist_and_Nevada_Museum_will_launch_space_sculp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0D3/1F3/0D31F3BF5A8545798E5AEAAAC89779C0_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Orbital Reflector, space sculpture, Orbital Reflector satellite, satellite sculpture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454596</guid>
      <title>Cattle methane emissions higher than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMethane emissions from cattle are much higher than previously thought, according to a new U.S. government funded study. Research published in the journal Carbon Balance and Management says that previous data on methane emissions from livestock were off by 11%Methane gas absorbs more sunlight than carbon dioxide, and as a result, is a significant contributor to rising global temperatures.Previous research failed to account for developments in land and animal use, reported Forbes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Methane impact on map2. Depiction of methane in atmosphere3. Depiction of cow eating and producing methaneVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in the journal Carbon Balance and Management says that previous data on methane emissions from livestock were off by 11%""Previous research failed to account for developments in agricultural land and animal use.""After a cow eats, the food is digested by microbes in its gut and methane is produced as a result.""Methane gas absorbs much more sunlight than carbon dioxide, and as a result, is a significant contributor to rising global temperatures."SOURCES: Carbon Balance and Management, Forbes, The Guardian, EPAhttps://cbmjournal.springeropen.com/articles/10.1186/s13021-017-0084-yhttps://www.forbes.com/sites/samlemonick/2017/09/29/scientists-underestimated-how-bad-cow-farts-are/#7a52c40478a9https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/sep/29/methane-emissions-cattle-11-percent-higher-than-estimatedhttps://www.epa.gov/ghgemissions/overview-greenhouse-gases***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 06:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/03/3454596/3454596_4CD9934AB1C5465381EA0134453D36F6_171003_3454596_Cattle_methane_emissions_higher_than_previously__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C1D/622/C1D622969413468A962CF507B157DB4B_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cow farting and global warming, global warming cattle, cow farting and co2, methane from cattle, cow study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454461</guid>
      <title>11,000 to be evacuated from Vanuatu as volcano erupts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResidents are being evacuated after a volcano on one of Vanuatu's northern islands began to erupt.The Manaro volcano in Ambae is a shield volcano whose summit features three crater lakes. Reuters reports that the volcano began releasing ash and toxic gas in September, and is now spewing rocks and lava amid repeated explosions.Many of the island's water sources were polluted by the eruption, leaving thousands without access to safe drinking water.Islanders are currently being ferried off the island by an assortment of ships and boats. Others have flown out to safety, as the Vanuatu government wants all 11,000 residents evacuated by October 6.The Manaro eruption poses a serious threat, especially with the possibility of deadly volcanic mud called lahar overflowing down the mountain.The volcano last erupted in 2005. Half of the island's population was evacuated and couldn't return until at least three months later.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Manaro Volcano on Ambae island in Vanuatu2. Erupting Manaro volcano spewing ash, smoke, lava 3. People evacuating from the island4. Possible volcanic mudflow from Manaro eruptionVOICEOVER (in English): "The Manaro volcano in Ambae is a shield volcano whose summit features three crater lakes.""The volcano began releasing ash and toxic gas in September, and is now spewing rocks and lava amid repeated explosions.""Islanders are being ferried off the island by an assortment of ships and boats. Others have flown out to safety, as the Vanuatu government wants all 11,000 residents evacuated by October 6.""The Manaro eruption poses a serious threat, especially with the possibility of deadly volcanic mud called lahar overflowing down the mountain."SOURCES: Reuters, The Guardian, Radio New Zealandhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-vanuatu-volcano/dunkirk-style-evacuation-as-vanuatu-volcano-pollutes-drinking-water-idUSKCN1C6141https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/oct/02/planes-ships-barges-the-diy-evacuation-of-vanuatu-volcano-islandhttp://www.radionz.co.nz/international/pacific-news/340636/vanuatu-evacuee-numbers-climb-higher***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 01:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/03/3454461/3454461_0E66D86B8B884240AC8755F9885AD735_171003_3454461_11_000_to_be_evacuated_from_Vanuatu_as_volcano_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/578/BC6/578BC69E71394EFB9B197F89B8BFEFA1_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, volcanic eruption, volcano, eruption, vanuatu eruption, vanuatu volcano, manari volcano, lava, lava flow, volcanic ash, smoke cloud, lahar, volcanic mud, mudflow, mudslide, ambae]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454451</guid>
      <title>How far could the radioactive cloud spread if North Korea tests a nuclear bomb?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new graphic shows the effects an atmospheric burst would have if North Korea were to carry out a nuclear test over the Pacific Ocean. The simulation of the radioactive cloud spreading for two weeks across the globe was posted by Lassina Zerbo, head of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty Organization, on Twitter. The graphic did not include any supporting data such as nuclear payload or height of detonation, the Telegraph reported. Experts say the explosion, fire and radiation created from a hydrogen bomb test over the Pacific Ocean could have catastrophic effects. Aquatic life in the immediate blast zone would be killed instantly, while radioactive isotopes  with the help of wind  could impact other organisms and humans thousands of miles away.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Radioactive isotope cloud spreading across Pacific2. Explosion, fire and radiation from nuclear test 3. Aquatic life being killed in blast, radioactive particles being spread in the air VOICEOVER (in English): "A new graphic shows the effects an atmospheric burst would have if North Korea were  to carry out a nuclear test over the Pacific Ocean." "The head of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty Organization posted the simulation of the radioactive cloud spreading for two weeks across the ocean towards Asia and the U.S.""Experts say the explosion, fire and radiation created from a hydrogen bomb test over the Pacific Ocean could have catastrophic effects." "Aquatic life in the immediate blast zone would be killed instantly, while radioactive isotopes  with the help of wind  could impact other organisms and humans thousands of miles away."  SOURCES: Telegraphhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/29/chilling-graphic-shows-spread-radioactive-cloud-north-korea/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 01:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/03/3454451/3454451_C5135B07EDB6401FB090B84035D6C6CF_171003_3454451_How_far_could_the_radioactive_cloud_spread_if_No_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/54A/252/54A252A2A6FA42438E217D931F1FF5D1_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, North Korea, atmospheric burst simulation, radio-isotope cloud, pacific ocean, nuclear test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455563</guid>
      <title>What is a 'bump stock'?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe man behind Sunday night's atrocity in Las Vegas had 23 firearms in his hotel, including 2 rifles modified with a bump stock, reported Popular Mechanics.Regular semi-automatic rifles require the user to pull the trigger to fire a shot. Bump stock modifications essentially eliminate the need for this.The modification absorbs recoil from the firing rifle, and uses it to bump the trigger into the shooter's stationary finger. This combined with forward positional pressure from the shooter, allows the gun to fire at a rate closer to that of a fully automatic weapon.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Regular semi-automatic rifle with no bump-stock modification.2. Bump-stock modification being added to semi-automatic rifle.3. Depiction of man firing semi-automatic rifle with bump-stock modificationVOICEOVER (in English): "Regular semi-automatic rifles require the user to pull the trigger to fire a shot.""Bump stock modifications essentially eliminate the need for this.""They absorb recoil from the firing rifle, and use it to bump the trigger into the shooter's stationary finger.""This combined with forward positional pressure from the shooter, allows the gun to fire at a rate closer to that of a fully automatic weapon."SOURCES:  POPULAR MECHANICS, BUMP FIRE SYSTEMS, BEARING ARMShttp://bit.ly/2fPOkSBhttp://bit.ly/2xfVX7jhttp://bit.ly/2g9KaSr***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 09:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/04/3455563/3455563_C946D1D134754787AC1C1F71ACAFD929_171004_3455563_What_is_a__bump_stock___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/89C/6D7/89C6D7BDE4A440F693BD7B9D88335995_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Las Vegas, fully auto v bump stock, bump stock fully auto, what is a bump stock, how do bump stock work, bump stock, fully auto, semi auto]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455517</guid>
      <title>Catalonia's referendum for independence, explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEOn October 1, 2017, Catalonia voted for independence, despite opposition from the central Spanish government.The northeast region of Catalonia is one of Spain's 17 autonomous communities. It's home to 7.5 million people, and has its own distinct language, history, and culture, according to the bBC.Catalonia was once under the kingdom of Aragon, which unified with Castile in the 15th century. It remained a state until it was defeated in the 1714 Siege of Barcelona, and its sovereignty was abolished. Under the newly centralized Spanish realm, Catalans were forced to adopt the Castilian language and customs.The region regained autonomy when Spain became a republic in 1931, but lost it again during the Franco dictatorship. Franco's death restored democracy, allowing Catalonia to have its own Parliament, police force, and education system.Though they have a high degree of autonomy, Catalans are not satisfied with the central government.As Spain's wealthiest region, it generates 20% of the national GDP. But high budget cuts during the 2008 financial crisis, and complaints of paying more taxes than they get back have increased separatist sentiment.The Brookings Institute reports that in 2010, the Spanish Constitutional Court reversed a 2006 ruling that granted the region 'nation' status and its own tax system, angering many and fueling the movement for independence.This movement culminated in the October 1 referendum, which Madrid has called illegal.A Catalonian secession would impact the Spanish economy, but also see the region out of the EU. With no free trade, the region's economy could shrink, and the unemployment rate could double.But do all Catalans want independence? Polls taken before the referendum showed that while 70% wanted the right to vote, only 41% sought independence.Still, Madrid's response was aggressive. It arrested Catalan leaders, and took down websites and apps in an effort to thwart the vote.On the day of the referendum, violence erupted as police seized ballots, and forcibly stopped people from voting. Despite the danger, voter turnout was at 42.3%, with nearly 90% of those who voted backing secession.Catalan's president has said he will declare independence within 48 hours if the 'yes' side won. If this happens, Spain will enter a constitutional crisis and may be forced to suspend Catalonia's autonomy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Catalonia one of Spain's 17 autonomous regions, has its own language, culture 2. History of Catalonia in the middle ages3. Catalonia has its own Parliament, police force, and education system  4. Catalonia complaints about budget cuts and taxes 5. Spanish constitutional courts reversed decision about Catalonia 'nation', tax system6. October 1 referendum for independence deemed illegal7. Economic impact of Catalonia secession8. Catalonia referendum violence, voter turnout and resultsVOICEOVER (in English): "The northeast region of Catalonia is one of Spain's 17 autonomous communities. It's home to 7.5 million people, and has its own distinct language, history, and culture.""Catalonia was once under the kingdom of Aragon, which unified with Castile in the 15th century. It remained a state until it was defeated in the 1714 Siege of Barcelona, and its sovereignty was abolished.""The region regained autonomy when Spain became a republic in 1931, but lost it again during the Franco dictatorship. Franco's death restored democracy, allowing Catalonia to have its own Parliament, police force, and education system.""As Spain's wealthiest region, it generates 20% of the national GDP. But high budget cuts during the 2008 financial crisis, and complaints of paying more taxes than they get back have increased separatist sentiment.""In 2010, the Spanish Constitutional Court reversed a 2006 ruling that granted the region 'nation' status and its own ta]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/04/3455517/3455517_5057712FC7A64900A921FA52B6D17099_171004_3455517_Catalonia_s_referendum_for_independence__explain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/085/849/0858498415954193B65A3B7D2E647476_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, catalonia, catalonia referendum, catalexit, catalonia secession, catalan, separatist, catalan independence, catalonia independence, spain, referendum, independence, violence, explainer, catalonia history]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455489</guid>
      <title>What are the different type of volcanoes?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA volcano is an opening in the earth's surface where molten rock can escape. The earth's crust is made up of tectonic plates that shift and move. Volcanoes are often located at the fault lines between these plates. Volcanoes can be active, dormant or extinct, according to Universe Today. There are four major types of volcanoes: cinder cone, composite, shield and lava domes.Cinder cone volcanoes occur when lava is ejected from a volcanic vent. Lava is shot into the air, and pieces accumulate around the vent. Over time, this creates a circular or oval-shaped cone, with a crater at the top. Composite volcanoes contain a conduit system that channels magma to the surface. These volcanoes can have clusters of vents along the sides of the mountain where lava flows out. Shield volcanoes are large, broad volcanoes where lava pours out in thin layers, allowing it to travel farther down the shallow slopes of the volcano. Shield volcanoes build up slowly with hundreds of eruptions creating several layers. Lava domes are created when small masses of thick lava that can't flow far from the source, so domes pile up around the vent. The dome grows by expansion of lava from within, and the mountain forms from material spilling off the sides of the dome.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cinder cone volcano2. Composite volcano 3. Shield volcano4. Lava domeVOICEOVER (in English): "Cinder cone volcanoes occur when lava is ejected from a volcanic vent. Lava is shot into the air, and pieces accumulate around the vent. This creates a circular or oval-shaped cone, with a bowl-shaped crater at the top." "Composite volcanoes contain a conduit system that channels magma to the surface. These volcanoes can have clusters of vents along the sides of the mountain where lava flows out." "Shield volcanoes are large, broad volcanoes where lava pours out in thin layers, allowing it to travel farther down the shallow slopes. They build up slowly with hundreds of eruptions creating many layers." "Lava domes are created when small masses of thick lava can't flow far from the source, so domes pile up around the vent. The dome grows by expansion of lava from within, and the mountain forms from material spilling off the sides of the dome."  SOURCES: Universe Todayhttps://www.universetoday.com/27333/types-of-volcanoes/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 08:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/04/3455489/3455489_D00C5DEC3CA74971959F59B86D7B6487_171004_3455489_What_are_the_different_type_of_volcanoes__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A8F/B58/A8FB58A703D94C2EA495181E3828AA7B_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, volcano, volcano types, cinder cone volcano, composite volcano, shield volcano, lava domes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455480</guid>
      <title>New osteoarthritis pill could help prevent bone loss in diseased joints</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists have found a new drug that can potentially stop bone loss and damage in patients suffering from osteoarthritis.The Daily Express reports that osteoarthritis is a degenerative joint disease caused by the breakdown of protective bone cartilage, often in the knees, hands, hips and spine.The condition has no known cure, but a new drug called M1V-711 has been shown to help reduce bone damage in affected joints.The treatment is based on a molecule involved in bone and cartilage turnovers, and works by interfering with the process that leads to joint breakdown.When tested in patients aged 40 to 80, the drug reduced bone loss in the knees by 65% and improved cartilage thickness in just six months. By contrast, those given a placebo reported a slight increase in bone loss.According to lead investigator Philip Conaghan of the University of Leeds, the drug has very few side effects, and is reportedly the first to target the diseased bone structure, instead of simply managing pain like most existing treatments.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Osteoarthritis symptoms, causes2. New M1V-711 drug for osteoarthritis3. Molecule in M1V-711 interferes with the process that leads to joint breakdown 4. Six month use of drug resulted in reduced bone loss and improved cartilage thicknessVOICEOVER (in English): "Osteoarthritis is a degenerative joint disease caused by the breakdown of protective bone cartilage, often in the knees, hands, hips, and spine.""The condition has no known cure, but a new drug called M1V-711 has been shown to help reduce bone damage in affected joints.""The treatment is based on a molecule involved in bone and cartilage turnovers, and works by interfering with the process that leads to joint breakdown.""When tested in patients aged 40 to 80, the drug reduced bone loss in the knees by 65% and improved cartilage thickness in just six months. By contrast, those given a placebo reported a slight increase in bone loss."SOURCES: The Daily Expresshttp://www.express.co.uk/life-style/health/860834/Arthritis-pill-disabling-bone-loss-and-damage-osteoarthritis-new-treatment***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 08:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/04/3455480/3455480_9A7093B1908A4E8EB01F73EE767AC10B_171004_3455480_New_osteoarthritis_pill_could_help_prevent_bone__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A2/BE5/1A2BE53551484BAAA6C728149D8625B3_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, arthritis, osteoarthritis, arthritis treatment, joint pain, joint treatment, medical trial, joint pain, cartilege, M1V-711]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455249</guid>
      <title>What happens if the Bali volcano erupts?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAn eruption from Bali's Mount Agung volcano is imminent. Authorities have evacuated some 75,000 people in danger zones surrounding areas.The volcano has been quiet for almost five decades, but last week 700 tremors were detected in a single day.  Experts, as well as the Indonesian government believe this to be a sign that Mount Agung is ready to erupt.The last time Mount Agung erupted was in 1963, and the resulting catastrophe killed more than 1,000 people.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of volcano, danger zone and Denpasar city2. Cross section of volcano with magma rising3. Depiction of eruption at Mount Agung4. Depiction of gas after eruption5. Scale of Mount Agung against world's tallest building, Burj Khalifa6. A depiction of Balinese onlookers observing the 1963 Mount Agung eruption.VOICEOVER (in English): "The Indonesian island of Bali is home to some 4.2 million people.""Authorities have evacuated some 75,000 people in danger zones surrounding the Mt Agung volcano."30 miles southwest of it is the island's capital, Denpasar, as well as a busy international airport""The volcano has been quiet for almost five decades, but last week 700 tremors were detected in a single day. "Experts, as well as the Indonesian government believe this to be a sign that Mount Agung is ready to erupt.""If it does erupt, the resulting current of super-heated gas, known as a pyroclastic flow would pose a danger to anyone nearby ""Mount Agung stands at over 3,100 meters tall. That's more than 4 times the size of the  world's tallest building the Burj Khalifa.""However, any resulting ash cloud from an eruption could stretch to heights of 10,000 m or higher.""The last time Mount Agung erupted was in 1963, and the resulting catastrophe killed more than 1,000 people."SOURCES: Channel News Asia, Magma, The Guardian, BBChttp://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asiapacific/once-tremors-detected-bali-volcano-can-erupt-within-hours-9269148https://magma.vsi.esdm.go.id/vona/display.php?noticenumber=2017AGU10https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/27/bali-volcano-will-mount-agung-erupt-and-what-happens-if-it-doeshttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-41395831***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 02:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/04/3455249/3455249_2652B05D222647DE9ACF01D8968EA110_171004_3455249_What_happens_if_the_Bali_volcano_erupts__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A07/C16/A07C164ECA634100BFA9057A11D892F1_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,bali volcano eruption 2017, bali volcano eruption, eruption mt agung, 1963 mt agung eruption, volcano eruption, volcanic eruptions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456145</guid>
      <title>Scotland bans fracking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Scottish government looks set to make fracking illegal in the country following opposition against it from the public.Fracking miners bore a deep pipeline that curves and extends for several miles. Next, they ply it with fracking fluid. This is a cocktail of water, sand and toxic chemicals.Pressure from this creates underground fractures that the sand keeps open. Shale gas then flows back toward the surface where it is extracted for energy use."Opponents to the process fear it may cause cracks to form in near-surface underground rock. Methane gas can seep into and create flammable water.Scottish lawmakers will vote on whether or not to ban fracking later this year, reported Scotland newspaper The National.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of Scotland on globe2. Depiction of pipeline being created3. Depiction of harvested shale gas moving back along pipeline4. Depiction of cracks forming near and underneath Scottish homesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Scottish government looks set to make fracking illegal in the country following opposition against it from the public, but why is the process so controversial?""Fracking miners bore a deep pipeline that curves and extends for miles.""Next, they ply it with fracking fluid. This is a cocktail of water, sand and toxic chemicals.""Pressure from this creates underground fractures that the sand keeps open.""Shale gas then flows back toward the surface where it is extracted for energy use.""Fracking opponents fear the process may cause cracks in near-surface underground rock."Methane gas can seep into these fissures and create flammable water."SOURCES: BBC, The National (Scottish newspaper)http://bbc.in/2xe0Gvghttp://bit.ly/2xTSYDx***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 07:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/05/3456145/3456145_C4EA3C9AE52D4CE18C9247F0285EEFE5_171005_3456145_Scotland_bans_fracking_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A43/0AF/A430AFD4B120494C9AF1D8FFB338528E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, what is fracking, fracking ban in scotland, scotland fracking, fracking in the uk, fracking climate change, fracking water fire, fracking fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3457238</guid>
      <title>Much of the world's honey now has pesticides</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENeonicotinoid pesticides are showing up in honey on every continent with honeybees, according to a new study. "On the global scale, the contamination is really striking," said study coauthor Edward Mitchell, a soil biologist at the University of Neuchtel in Switzerland.Around 200 samples of honey were tested and 75 percent found to contain measurable levels of at least one of the five common neonicotinoids, Science News reported. Neonicotinoids are used on various crops grown in different climates, but still showed up in honey from remote islands with almost no agriculture. The insecticide works by targeting crop-destroying insect's central nervous system. A number of studies have found the insecticide also reduces and weakens honeybee hives. Pesticide levels varied from region-to-region. In North America, 86 percent of samples contained pesticides; Asia, 80 percent; Europe, 79 percent; Africa, 73 percent; the Australian region, 71 percent and South America, 57 percent. Bees and other pollinators are necessary to three-quarters of the world's food crops, but have been declining in number in recent decades, the Guardian reported. Destruction of wild habitats, disease and massive pesticide use are all contributing factors. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Farmers spraying insecticide with honeybees around2. Neonicotinoids targeting locust's central nervous system and harming honeybees3. Pesticide contamination levels varies from region-to-region VOICEOVER (in English): "Neonicotinoid pesticides are showing up in honey on every continent with honeybees. Around 200 samples of honey were tested and 75 percent found to contain measurable levels of at least one of the five common neonicotinoids.""The insecticide works by targeting crop-destroying insect's central nervous system. A number of studies have also found the insecticide reduces and weakens honeybee hives." "Pesticide levels varied between regions. In North America, 86 percent of samples contained pesticides; Asia, 80 percent; Europe, 79 percent; Africa, 73 percent; the Australian region, 71 percent and South America, 57 percent." SOURCES: Science News, Guardian https://www.sciencenews.org/article/much-worlds-honey-now-contains-pesticides-harm-beeshttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/oct/05/honey-tests-reveal-global-contamination-by-bee-harming-pesticides***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 13:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/06/3457238/3457238_2E864D5ABCD84C0BA1852A83E3B2BC27_171006_3457238_Much_of_the_world_s_honey_now_has_pesticides_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CD7/D05/CD7D0565518D4E1A9FFEB0422F6ECB94_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bees, honey pesticide contamination, neonicotinoid, honey neonicotinoid contamination, insecticides, honeybees]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456846</guid>
      <title>Scientists may have found ice around Mars' equator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAfter reexamining old satellite data, scientists may have discovered ice around Mars' equator. A team from the Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory analyzed data from 2002 to 2009 by Mars Odyssey's Neutron Spectrometer (MONS), Science News reported. The neutron spectrometer can't directly detect water, but by measuring neutrons, it can detect hydrogen signature, which could mark the presence of water or other hydrogen-bearing substances, according to Space.com.  Researchers discovered an unexpected amount of hydrogen around the equator by reducing the blurring or "noise" in data using image-reconstruction techniques used for other spacecraft and for medicine, Space.com reported. This improved the spatial resolution of the images to 180 miles (290 km), from the previous resolution of 320 miles (520 km). More research needs to be done to determine if the signature is actual that from water ice. Having water on Mars could mean that future human missions wouldn't need to bring water with them for drinking, cooling equipment or watering plants, thus reducing the number of resources needed for transport.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Researchers analyzed old data from Odyssey satellite2. Hydrogen being detected around Mars' equator3. Representation of spatial resolution improvements 4. Representation of future human mission on MarsVOICEOVER (in English): "After reexamining old satellite data from 2002 to 2009 by Mars Odyssey's Neutron Spectrometer, scientists may have discovered ice around Mars' equator." "The neutron spectrometer can't directly detect water, but by measuring neutrons, it can detect hydrogen signature, which could mark the presence of water or other hydrogen-bearing substances.""Researchers discovered an unexpected amount of hydrogen around the equator by reducing the blurring or "noise" in Odyssey's data using image-reconstruction techniques used for other spacecraft and for medicine.""This improved the spatial resolution of the images to 180 miles, from the previous resolution of 320 miles." "Having water on Mars could mean that future human missions wouldn't need to bring water with them for drinking, cooling equipment or watering plants, thus reducing the number of resources needed for transport." SOURCES: Space.com, Science Newshttps://www.space.com/38330-water-ice-mystery-at-mars-equator.htmlhttp://www.sci-news.com/space/nasas-mars-odyssey-water-ice-martian-equator-05279.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 07:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/06/3456846/3456846_E8CE701A84D24CEAA9F7DB02531CC248_171006_3456846_Scientists_may_have_found_ice_around_Mars__equat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A0A/580/A0A5807E6C1E4D58B1A5238C3958FF5B_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Mars, water Mars' equator, water on Mars, Odyssey satellite data]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456783</guid>
      <title>Turkish archaeologists find tomb believed to be Santa Claus'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists may have found the original tomb of Santa Claus in Turkey.Hurriyet Daily News reports that archaeologists have found an intact shrine underneath the Demre church in Turkey's Antalya province, and suspect it to be the final resting place of St. Nicholas.The area where the church is located is reportedly the same region where St. Nick was born during the 4th century. It was there that the jolly saint formed the reputation for gift-giving that eventually gave rise to the legend of Santa Claus.After his death in 343 AD, the saint was interred in the church, and lay undisturbed until the 11th century.It's widely believed that Italian sailors then took his remains in 1087 and transported them to Bari, where they lie to this day in the Basilica di San Nicola.According to documents obtained by the Turkish archaeologists, however, the remains that were taken supposedly belonged to a local priest.Though many are skeptical, the Turkish team is determined to prove their theory right, and will soon begin the arduous task of removing an intricate mosaic tile by tile in order to get to the untouched tomb.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Shrine found under Demre church2. St. Nicholas originally interred under Demre church3. Remains taken to Bari, Italy in 10874. Bari remains possibly local priest'sVOICEOVER (in English): "Archaeologists have found an intact shrine underneath the Demre church in Turkey's Antalya province, and suspect it to be the final resting place of St. Nicholas.""After his death in 343 AD, the saint was interred in the church, and lay undisturbed until the 11th century.""It's widely believed that Italian sailors then took his remains in 1087 and transported them to Bari, where they lie to this day in the Basilica di San Nicola.""According to documents obtained by the Turkish archaeologists, however, the remains that were taken supposedly belonged to a local priest."SOURCES: Hurriyet Daily News, National Geographichttp://www.hurriyetdailynews.com/body-of-st-nicholas-kept-in-demre-claims-officians-120315http://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/10/santa-claus-st-nicholas-tomb-archaeology-turkey-spd/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 05:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/06/3456783/3456783_942D8A31913E4491BE88523C2DF2AD95_171006_3456783_Turkish_archaeologists_find_tomb_believed_to_be__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6A3/53B/6A353B2F9FAF4F66879B9D66B2377D2A_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, santa claus, st. nicholas, st. nick, christmas, archaeology, archaeologists, demre, demre church, tomb, shrine, temple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456741</guid>
      <title>Apple investigating swelling iPhone 8 battery issues</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENearly half a dozen iPhone 8 Plus owners from around the world have seen their devices cracking and swelling.The swelling in these cases reportedly occurs while the iPhone 8 Plus's lithium-ion battery is charging.  Apple says it is investigating the problem and is in possession of one of the damaged phones.Five iPhone 8 Plus owners in Canada, Greece, Japan, Taiwan and Hong Kong have reported similar issues, reported mobile news website BGR.According to Apple news site MacRumors, it's common for a small number of devices out of the millions made to have some battery issues. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of iPhone 'swelling' during charging2. Depiction of iPhone being examined3. Locations where impacted devices were reported.4. Depiction of iPhones being assembledVOICEOVER (in English): "The swelling in these cases reportedly occurs while the iPhone 8 Plus's lithium-ion battery is charging.""Apple says it is investigating the problem and is in possession of one of the damaged phones.""Five iPhone 8 Plus owners in Canada, Greece, Japan, Taiwan and Hong Kong have reported similar issues.""According to Apple news site MacRumors, it's common for a small number of devices out of the millions made to have some battery issues."SOURCES: BGR, MacRumorshttp://bgr.com/2017/10/04/iphone-8-battery-swelling-more-reports-investigation/http://bgr.com/2017/09/29/iphone-8-battery-explosion-display/https://www.macrumors.com/2017/10/04/iphone-8-plus-battery-failures/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 04:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/06/3456741/3456741_4398649CC8E141CB824F1303D7D80A3C_171006_3456741_Apple_investigating_swelling_iPhone_8_battery_is_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/415/FD8/415FD853616947C2A7E89136271F8AAC_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, swelling iphone, iphone 8 teardown, iphone issues, iphone problems, iphone battery issues, iphone battery problems, iphone 8 charging, Apple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456724</guid>
      <title>Study links black tea to weight loss</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEUniversity of California scientists have connected the effects of drinking black tea to weight loss in mice.The study was published in the European Journal of Nutrition.Over a period of 4 weeks, three groups of mice were fed high-fat, high-sugar diets and compared to a group was given a low-fat, high-sugar diet. Two of the high-fat, high-sugar groups' diets were supplemented with black and green tea."After the 4 weeks scientists found that weight among the mice who consumed tea had lowered to the same level as those on a low-fat, high-sugar diet.Analysis of intestinal samples revealed both black and green tea lessened bacteria associated with obesity and increased bacteria associated with lean muscle mass.Green tea was also shown to be easily absorbed by the liver, while black tea was found to stay in the intestine and help build bacteria that help with metabolism.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of study and how tea was given mice2. Depiction of mice losing weight3. Overview of 4. Impact of black tea and green tea on liverVOICEOVER (in English): "Over a period of 4 weeks, three groups of mice were fed high-fat, high-sugar diets and compared to a group was given a low-fat, high-sugar diet.""Two of the high-fat, high-sugar groups' diets were supplemented with black and green tea.""After the 4 weeks scientists found that weight among the mice who consumed tea had lowered to the same level as those on a low-fat, high-sugar diet.""Analysis of intestinal samples revealed both black and green tea lessened bacteria associated with obesity... and increased bacteria associated with lean muscle mass.""Green tea was also shown to be easily absorbed by the liver, while black tea was found to stay in the intestine and help build bacteria that help with metabolism." SOURCES: University of California Los Angeles, European Journal of Nutritionhttps://newsroom.ucla.edu/releases/black-tea-may-help-with-weight-loss-toohttps://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00394-017-1542-8***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 04:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/06/3456724/3456724_58F28B2BA1CB477881FD32420F03A3F7_171006_3456724_Study_links_black_tea_to_weight_loss_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D3F/D06/D3FD067665424A65B89EBBDE1CCDF152_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tea and weight loss, black tea fat, green tea fat, how does tea help you lose weight, gut bacteria, weight loss in mice, ucla, new weight loss study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456654</guid>
      <title>American gun ownership and gun violence statistics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEIn the wake of the deadly mass shooting in Las Vegas, gun violence and ownership have once again taken center stage in public discussions.According to the UN office on drugs and crime, the U.S. had the highest rate of gun ownership in 2012, with 88 guns for every 100 people. Yemen is second on the list but trails far behind with 54.8 guns.Results from the 2015 National Firearm Survey revealed that handgun ownership in particular has increased by 70%, from 65 million in 1994 to 111 million in 2015. America is one of the countries where the right to bear arms is protected by the constitution. It's also incredibly easy to arm yourself.In 2007, the Small Arms Survey found that half the world's civilian-owned guns were in the U.S. Fifty percent of these were owned by a mere 3% of American adults, according to an unpublished survey from Harvard and Northeastern University.Mass shootings take place in the country more than 11 times as often as other developed nations. One study estimates over 100,000 gunshot victims, and 30,000 gun deaths annually, which totals to $2.8 billion in hospital expenses.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Number of guns in the US per 100 people2. Handgun ownership showed 70% increase in two decades3. Nearly half of all civilian guns in the world in the US4. American gun violence statisticsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the UN office on drugs and crime, the U.S. had the highest rate of gun ownership in 2012, with 88 guns for every 100 people. Yemen is second on the list but trails far behind with 54.8 guns.""Results from the 2015 National Firearm Survey revealed that handgun ownership in particular has increased by 70%, from 65 million in 1994 to 111 million in 2015. ""In 2007, the Small Arms Survey found that half the world's civilian-owned guns were in the U.S. Fifty percent of these were owned by a mere 3% of American adults, according to an unpublished survey from Harvard and Northeastern University.""Mass shootings take place in the country more than 11 times as often as other developed nations. One study estimates over 100,000 gunshot victims, and 30,000 gun deaths annually, which totals to $2.8 billion in hospital expenses."SOURCES: Small Arms Survey, International Journal of Criminal Justice Science, The Guardianhttp://www.smallarmssurvey.org/publications/by-type/yearbook/small-arms-survey-2007.htmlhttp://www.sascv.org/ijcjs/pdfs/Lemieuxijcjs2014vol9issue1.pdfhttps://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2017/oct/02/us-gun-control-ownership-violence-statistics***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 02:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/06/3456654/3456654_9C4733B281544CAABDA925FA72191847_171006_3456654_American_gun_ownership_and_gun_violence_statisti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B0D/896/B0D8960105034C23B74A86DB6A2174BA_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, gun control, gun violence, gun ownership, guns, guns in America, guns in the US, US guns, firearms, US firearms, statistics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458742</guid>
      <title>Police still looking for Vegas shooter's motive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAuthorities are still trying to determine a motive for the deadly Las Vegas shooting that killed 58 people and wounded nearly 500 last weekend. Investigators found a handwritten note with distance and trajectory calculations in shooter Stephen Paddock's hotel room, CBS News reported.  The note was found in Paddock's Mandalay Bay Resort and Casino suite along with 23 firearms and ammunition. Even with over 1,000 leads and tips, authorities still have no credible information about Paddock's potential motive.Police said they believe a Mandalay Bay security guard responding to a door alarm near Paddock's room on the 32nd floor caused the shooter to shift his focus from the Route 91 concert crowd across the street, Undersheriff Kevin C. McMahill told CNN. Officials are confident Paddock was the only shooter, although they are still trying to determine if anyone knew of his plans, CNN reported. Paddock brought the 23 guns and ammunition found in his suite over the course of several days, McMahill said. Investigators still do not know what Paddock planned to do with the 50 pounds of explosives found in his vehicle in the hotel parking garage. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A note with trajectory and distance calculations was found in Paddock's hotel room2. The note was found with 23 firearms and ammunition3. A security guard responding to a door alarm caught Paddock's attention4. Police still don't know what the explosives and ammunition found in Paddock's car were meant forVOICEOVER (in English): "Investigators found a handwritten note with distance and trajectory calculations in Vegas shooter Stephen Paddock's hotel room, although they still have no motive.""The note was found in Paddock's Mandalay Bay Resort and Casino suite along with 23 firearms and ammunition." "Police said they believe a Mandalay Bay security guard responding to a door alarm near Paddock's room on the 32nd floor caused the shooter to shift his focus from the Route 91 concert crowd across the street.""Investigators said they also do not know what Paddock planned to do with the 50 pounds of explosives and 1,000 rounds of ammunition found in his vehicle in the hotel parking garage."SOURCES: CNNhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/10/07/us/las-vegas-shooting-investigation/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 08:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/09/3458742/3458742_1D0435D5395343658FBB2F320608E7B9_171009_3458742_Police_still_looking_for_Vegas_shooter_s_motive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/68F/FCA/68FFCA56755E402FAC52F7ABE0E18E02_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Las Vegas, Mandalay Bay hotel and Casino, Stephen Paddock, Stephen Paddock note]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458723</guid>
      <title>VX found on Kim Jong Nam's alleged killers' clothing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETraces of the nerve agent VX were found on the clothing of Kim Jong Nam's suspected assassins.Kim Jong Nam, the older half-brother North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un, was allegedly assassinated by two women at Kuala Lumpur airport in February this year.Traces of the deadly nerve agent VX was found on their clothing, according to evidence presented in the Malaysian trial of his alleged killers, reported Reuters.Ingested via the skin, VX blocks signals between the nervous system and the body's muscles. This results in paralysis of all muscles, including the diaphragm, and then death via asphyxiation.Further evidence is set to be presented in the trial this week.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Kim Jong Nam's alleged assassination2. Depiction of Nam's alleged assassins with VX3. How VX affects the body4. VX impacting the asphyxiaVOICEOVER (in English): "Kim Jong Nam, the older half-brother of North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un, was allegedly assassinated by two women at Kuala Lumpur airport earlier this year.""Traces of the deadly nerve agent VX was found on the women's clothing, according to  evidence presented during their trial last week in Malaysia.""Ingested via the skin, VX blocks signals between the nervous system and the body's muscles.""This results in paralysis of all muscles, including the diaphragm and eventually death via asphyxiation."SOURCES: Reuters, Straits Times, News.com.au (AFP)https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-malaysia-kim-court/nerve-agent-vx-found-on-shirts-of-women-accused-of-north-korean-murder-expert-says-idUSKBN1CA0UIhttp://www.straitstimes.com/asia/se-asia/kim-jong-nam-murder-trial-prosecution-to-bring-vx-tainted-blood-and-urine-samples-tohttp://www.news.com.au/world/asia/masks-in-court-as-poison-evidence-brought-to-kim-jongnam-murder-trial/news-story/90e49e87e51229f209a78030899bc822***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 08:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/09/3458723/3458723_0A1FAE1CDC024068B2E60B07185F831B_171009_3458723_VX_found_on_Kim_Jong_Nam_s_alleged_killers__clot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/51E/B10/51EB1011AB24401A9D0418018AB75C3D_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kim jong nam assassination, kim jong un, dprk, kim jong nam trial, kim jong nam, kim jong il, vx, venomous agent x]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458700</guid>
      <title>Dimming of star probably caused by dust, not alien structure: NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[New research from NASA may have solved one of the most prevalent astronomy puzzles in recent years.Dyson spheres are theoretical cosmic megastructures. They envelop a planet with energy-absorbing technology which directs power to a central location.Some astronomers previously theorized the dimming of Tabbys Star was caused by this. This star is located 1,280 light years from Earth.New research using data from NASAs Spitzer and Swift space telescopes suggests the dimming is actually due to an dust cloud orbiting the star.Known as circumstellar dust, NASA says these particles are not small enough to fly into space, but also not big enough to block light all the time on all wavelengths.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/09/3458700/3458700_76B3736E193C4FCBA893C3FF5E2091E0_171009_3458700_Dimming_of_star_probably_caused_by_dust__not_ali_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8A5/894/8A58946E2BD44A79B83D6B95DA9222A4_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,abby star,tabby star update,tabby star 2017,dyson sphere,alien megastructure,nasa,aliens and nasa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458689</guid>
      <title>'Smart bandage' heals wounds three times faster than regular dressing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers have designed a 'smart bandage' they say heals skin tissue 3 times faster than a regular medical dressing.It accomplishes this via medication loaded inside the bandage threads and drug delivery can then be controlled via smartphone. The researchers say in the future this could accelerate healing of battlefield wounds.Details of the technology were published in the journal Advanced Functional Material. It was co-developed by MIT, Harvard and the University of Nebraska-Lincoln.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of smart bandage on wound and normal bandage on wound2. Depiction of smart bandage threading3. Depiction of smart bandage being used on male patient4. Depiction of smart bandage being used on U.S. soldierVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers have designed a 'smart bandage' they say heals skin tissue 3 times faster than a regular medical dressing.""It accomplishes this via medication loaded inside the bandage threads.""Drug delivery can then be controlled via smartphone.""The researchers say in the future this could accelerate healing of battlefield wounds."SOURCES: Advanced Functional Materials, University of Nebraskahttp://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/adfm.201702399/fullhttp://news.unl.edu/newsrooms/today/article/smart-bandage-could-promote-better-faster-healing/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 07:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/09/3458689/3458689_3FF81A035B1B44AEBA0940CB69C962EF_171009_3458689__Smart_bandage__heals_wounds_three_times_faster__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/067/319/067319BB4C164E16AD229D5ACC774C91_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, accelerated healing, smart bandage, medical healing, healing quick]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458607</guid>
      <title>New molecule eliminates HIV reservoirs with 'kick and kill' approach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers may have finally found a way to eliminate the HIV reservoirs that often remain hidden in the body.Science Daily reports that HIV spreads by taking over a cell's DNA and using it to make copies of itself. Most AIDS treatments are engineered to block this replication cycle, effectively stopping the spread of the virus.But though these drugs allow patients to live longer, they do not rid the body of the virus, which hides in reservoirs and re-emerges once treatment stops.A new 'kick and kill' approach aims to get rid of these reservoirs by using a synthetic molecule called SUW133 to wake up the dormant virus, which will then be eliminated by antiretroviral therapy.The technique was developed by researchers from UCLA, Stanford, and the National Institutes of Health, and is detailed in a study published in PLOS Pathogens.When tested on HIV-infected mice that had been given antiretroviral drugs, 25 percent of the once-dormant virus cells died within 24 hours of being reactivated.With further development, researchers believe the technique could lower the viral reservoir enough for infected patients to stop antiretroviral treatment.The molecule will also need to be tested on larger animals before it can go to human trials. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Antiretroviral therapy stops spread of HIV virus2. HIV remains dormant in reservoirs3. 'Kick and kill' approach uses molecule to wake up dormant HIV, kills it with antiretroviral therapy4. 'Kick and kill' approach tested on miceVOICEOVER (in English): "HIV spreads by taking over a cell's DNA and using it to make copies of itself. Most AIDS treatments are engineered to block this replication cycle, effectively stopping the spread of the virus.""But though these drugs allow patients to live longer, they do not rid the body of the virus, which hides in reservoirs and re-emerges once treatment stops.""A new 'kick and kill' approach aims to get rid of these reservoirs by using a synthetic molecule to wake up the dormant virus, which will then be eliminated by antiretroviral therapy.""When tested on HIV-infected mice that had been given antiretroviral drugs, 25 percent of the once-dormant virus cells died within 24 hours of being reactivated."SOURCES: Science Daily, PLOS Pathogenshttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/10/171005141836.htmhttp://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1006575***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 05:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/09/3458607/3458607_280208E1BB1747BEA731D92BD932FB40_171009_3458607_New_molecule_eliminates_HIV_reservoirs_with__kic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/00B/971/00B971C4A64C4042BF2E1C5E34E1FB8F_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, HIV, AIDS, HIV virus, AIDS treatment, HIV treatment, AIDS cure, HIV cure, kick and kill, antiretroviral therapy, antiretroviral, antiretroviral drugs, SUW133, dormant HIV]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458597</guid>
      <title>San Francisco bay shark die-offs possibly caused by parasite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists are concerned by a massive shark die-off in San Francisco bay, but are unable to get state funding to research the exact cause.NBC Bay Area reports that two thousand leopard sharks and hundreds of bat rays, smoothhound sharks, striped bass, and halibut have turned up dead on San Francisco Bay between February and July this year.The culprit is suspected to be a parasite known as Miamiensis avidus, which enters the shark's nose and eats away at its brain.When the animal eventually succumbs to the parasite, it either swims aimlessly in circles or beaches itself.But scientists say only a small fraction end up on shore. Sharks aren't naturally buoyant, so the infected ones sink to the bottom of the ocean once they stop swimming.Leopard sharks are the most commonly spotted victims of the parasite, but it's a lesser concern for the California Department of Fish and Wildlife, since the species is not endangered.Scientists fear, however, that other species are also becoming infected and dying, but just aren't washing up on shore. They also worry that the parasite could spread farther along the California coast.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dead shark, marine creatures along San Francisco bay2. Parasite enters shark's nose, eats its brain3. Shark swimming in circles, beaches itself4. Shark stops swimming, sinks to the ocean floorVOICEOVER (in English): "Two thousand leopard sharks and hundreds of bat rays, smoothhound sharks, striped bass, and halibut have turned up dead on San Francisco Bay between February and July this year.""The culprit is suspected to be a parasite known as Miamiensis avidus, which enters the shark's nose and eats away at its brain.""When the animal eventually succumbs to the parasite, it either swims aimlessly in circles or beaches itself.""But scientists say only a small fraction end up on shore. Sharks aren't naturally buoyant, so the infected ones sink to the bottom of the ocean once they stop swimming."SOURCES: NBC Bay Areahttp://www.nbcbayarea.com/investigations/Thousands-of-Sharks-Other-Sea-Life-Mysteriously-Die-in-San-Francisco-Bay-State-Says-No-Funding-Available-to-Determine-Cause-449096583.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 05:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/09/3458597/3458597_E77DA0E3A37B4C99B9B35C2FF7DFBA70_171009_3458597_San_Francisco_bay_shark_die_offs_possibly_caused_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/396/1EC/3961EC508655433AA10AF49D1A97BF77_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, parasite, shark deaths, sharks, marine pathogen, pathogen, single cell parasite, miamiensis avidus, leopard sharks, san francisco bay, brain eating parasite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458509</guid>
      <title>Apple gave Uber 'unprecedented' access to secret backdoor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEApple gave Uber's iPhone app access to a secret backdoor that potentially allows the company to record a user's screen and access other personal information without his or her knowledge. According to Business Insider, Uber does not mention the backdoor is any consumer-facing information included with their app. Apple's backdoor is so powerful, it rarely allows third-party companies to access the feature. Security researcher Will Strafach discovered the situation and told Business Insider, "granting such a sensitive entitlement to a third-party is unprecedented as far as I can tell, no other app developers have been able to convince Apple to grant them entitlements they've needed to let their apps utilize certain privileged system functionality." There's no evidence that Uber used the special iPhone feature. Uber told Business Insider the code was not being used and was a leftover from an earlier version of its Apple Watch app. A majority of iPhone apps use software to enable features like the camera or ApplePay known as "entitlements." Many of these can be easily turned on by outside app creators. But certain entitlements are only used by Apple to allow optimal integration with the iPhone.   Uber's app was found to be the only app other than Apple's own apps granted access to the entitlement, Strafach said in an email to Business Insider.Uber says the entitlement isn't being used, and it is working with Apple to remove the API completely from the app.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman using Uber app on iPhone2. Third-party apps use entitlements, but Apple has special entitlements3. Uber was only app with special entitlement outside of Apple4. Uber removing special entitlement from appVOICEOVER (in English): "Apple gave Uber's iPhone app access to a secret backdoor that potentially allows the company to record a user's screen and access other personal information without his or her knowledge.""A majority of iPhone apps use software to enable features like the camera or ApplePay known as "entitlements," however Apple keeps certain entitlements for itself to allow optimal integration with the iPhone.""Uber was found to be the only app other than Apple's own apps granted access to the entitlement.""Uber says the entitlement isn't being used, and it is working with Apple to remove the API completely from the app."SOURCES: Business Insiderhttp://www.businessinsider.com/uber-iphone-app-secret-access-sensitive-apple-features-2017-10***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/09/3458509/3458509_94C2158E991041038EA0E0A79FF6344D_171009_3458509_Apple_gave_Uber__unprecedented__access_to_secret_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/86D/4E9/86D4E929B8A2467880A2D82CCB4F7F68_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Apple, Uber, Apple Uber secret backdoor, entitlements]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3459500</guid>
      <title>Hotel guard wounded by shooter prior to massacre: Las Vegas police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONELas Vegas authorities say shooter Stephen Paddock shot and wounded a security guard prior to carrying out last Sunday's shooting.Mandalay Hotel security guard Jesus Campos was checking on the Paddock's floor prior to the shooting, reported ReutersPaddock had barricaded his door shut and set up surveillance cameras in the hallway, reported CNN, citing SWAT officers. After seeing Campos on his surveillance, police say Paddock opened fire and wounded the 25-year-old's right leg at 9:59 p.m.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of security guard Jesus Campos checking area2. Depiction of 32nd floor of hotel3. Depiction of security guard Jesus Campos being wounded by shooter Stephen Paddock4. Depiction of security guard Jesus Campos calling police on his radioVOICEOVER (in English): "Police now say Mandalay Hotel security guard Jesus Campos was checking an alarm on the 32nd floor near Stephen Paddock's room prior to the shooting.""Paddock had barricaded his door shut and set up surveillance cameras in the hallway.""After seeing Campos on his surveillance, police say Paddock opened fire and wounded the 25-year-old's right leg at 9:59 p.m.""That's 6 minutes before he began firing at the crowd.""Campos then reportedly stayed on the 32nd floor and called the police on his radio."SOURCES: Reuters, CNN, News.com.au, The Los Angeles Times, New York Times, Las Vegas Review-Journal, Heavy.com, Daily Mailhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-lasvegas-shooting/las-vegas-gunman-fired-on-security-guard-before-mass-shooting-idUSKBN1CE2GMhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/10/09/us/las-vegas-shooting-response/index.htmlhttp://www.news.com.au/world/how-jesus-campos-stopped-las-vegas-gunman-stephen-paddock-while-unarmed-outside-his-room/news-story/cd53b309499c28799e6a7f8e47ccf865http://beta.latimes.com/nation/la-na-vegas-shooting-20171009-story.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/10/09/us/jesus-campos-las-vegas-shooting.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/10/04/us/vegas-shooting-hotel-room.htmlhttps://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/homicides/sheriff-says-las-vegas-shooter-checked-into-mandalay-bay-sept-25/http://heavy.com/news/2017/10/stephen-paddock-shot-jose-campos-before-vegas-shooting-timeline-sheriff-update/http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4964652/Las-Vegas-killer-timeline-chaos-new-revelations.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 09:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/10/3459500/3459500_326E8C3561F044668669A2BAD867A47B_171010_3459500_Hotel_guard_wounded_by_shooter_prior_to_massacre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2B3/3FE/2B33FE6BA8DA4FF4B2CC12A94AADE74B_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, las vegas 2017, stephen paddock, campos, campos paddock, nevada, las vegas incident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3459394</guid>
      <title>Outbreak of infections linked to Petland puppies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAn outbreak of campylobacter infections has been connected to puppies sold by U.S. national pet chain Petland.The CDC says 55 people in 12 states are showing signs of a campylobacter infection. Thirteen people have been hospitalized."The outbreak has been linked to puppies sold in the U.S. pet store Petland. People contract it via contact with the infected dog.Symptoms include fever, stomach cramps, vomiting, bloody diarrhea and usually last seven days. The latest strain is also seemingly resistant to antibiotics.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where the outbreak has taken place2. Depiction of how the bacteria is transmitted3. Depiction of how the bacteria resists antibioticsVOICEOVER (in English): "The CDC says 55 people in 12 states are showing signs of a campylobacter infection.""13 people have been hospitalized.""The outbreak has been linked to puppies sold in the U.S. pet store Petstore.""People contract it via contact with the infected dog.""Symptoms include fever, stomach cramps, vomiting, bloody diarrhea and usually last 7 days." "The latest strain is also seemingly resistant to antibiotics."SOURCES: WTSP, Centers for Disease Control and Preventionhttp://www.wtsp.com/life/pets/cdc-investigating-12-state-outbreak-of-campylobacter-linked-to-puppies/481227709https://www.cdc.gov/campylobacter/outbreaks/puppies-9-17/index.html#petowners***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 06:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/10/3459394/3459394_FA5A87C0E2664AE9AC447CC9FD600C48_171010_3459394_Outbreak_of_infections_linked_to_Petland_puppies_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BDE/AFF/BDEAFF5278994D2B93ECCB0AC8F3C7EA_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cdc, campylobacter petland, campylobacter outbreak, infection outbreak, petland puppies, petland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3459356</guid>
      <title>Madagascar hit by the plague</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMadagascar is currently experiencing an outbreak of the plague with 231 confirmed cases, and at least 33 deaths as of October 6, according to the World Health Organization.  The country usually sees about 400 cases per year, but this outbreak has officials concerned because it has spread to the capital and coastal cities for the first time, Vox reported. This year a large number of the cases are pneumonic plague, which targets the lungs and is passed on by coughing, according to the BBC. It is the most deadly form of the disease and can cause death within 24 hours.  The WHO has delivered more than a million doses of antibiotics to help combat the spread of the disease, according to BBC. Two regions on the island nation have been hit particularly hard, eastern Madagascar and the center of the island in Antananarivo.  Public gatherings have been banned in response to the outbreak. Officials have also put in place screening protocols at the country's main airport. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People wearing face masks on Madagascar street2. Pneumonic plague affects the lungs and spreads through coughing3. The WHO delivered over 1,000,000 antibiotics to Madagascar4. The areas on Madagascar affected by the plagueVOICEOVER (in English): "More than 30 people have died in Madagascar from the plague, with over 230 confirmed cases. The African island-nation usually sees 400 cases of plague a year." "This year a majority of the cases are pneumonic plague, which targets the lungs and is transmitted through coughing. It's the deadliest form of plague and can cause death within 24 hours.""The WHO has delivered more than a million doses of antibiotics to help combat the spread of the disease.""Two regions on the island nation have been hit particularly hard, eastern Madagascar and the center of the island in Antananarivo."  SOURCES: WHO, Vox, BBChttp://www.who.int/mediacentre/news/releases/2017/antibiotics-plague-madagascar/en/https://www.vox.com/science-and-health/2017/10/6/16435536/plague-madagascar-epidemic-2017http://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-41537193***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 05:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/10/3459356/3459356_6BE67C83AD4845B08578F9EFBE5B4F6E_171010_3459356_Madagascar_hit_by_the_plague_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/276/868/276868E7473B4A6B922344712D919A29_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Madagascar, Madagascar plague, pneumonic plague, plague outbreak, WHO plague antibiotics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460184</guid>
      <title>Carbon released from soil may escalate global warming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONECarbon emissions from soil microbes could lead to a further rise in global temperatures, scientists have warned.According to new research published in the journal Science, soil releases more carbon when heated passed a certain point.In 1991, scientists placed heaters 10 cm under soil in the Harvard forest in Massachusetts. They artificially heated that area over 26 years and found that the warmed soil released 17 percent more of its carbon content compared to unheated soil."If the microbes in all landscapes respond to warming in the same way as we've observed in mid-latitude forest soils, this self-reinforcing feedback phenomenon will go on for a while and we are not going to be able to turn those microbes off," explained lead author Jessy Melillo in a University of Chicago news release.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of sun warming soil2. Depiction of soil releasing carbon3. Soil microbe VOICEOVER (in English):  "According to new research published in the journal Science, soil releases more carbon when heated to a certain point.""In 1991, scientists placed heaters 10 cm under soil in the Harvard forest in Massachusetts.""They artificially heated that area over 26 years." "Scientists observed the heated soil release 17 percent more of its carbon content compared to unheated soil." "If warmer soil produces higher carbon emissions in forests around the globe, then the global warming process could speed out of control."SOURCES: Science, University of Chicago, ScienceAlert, The Guardianhttp://science.sciencemag.org/content/358/6359/101https://news.uchicago.edu/article/2017/10/05/carbon-feedback-forest-soils-will-accelerate-global-warming-study-findshttps://sciencealert.com/warming-soil-could-create-a-dangerous-carbon-feedback-loop-scientists-sayhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/oct/05/carbon-emissions-warming-soils-higher-than-estimated-signalling-tipping-points***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/11/3460184/3460184_A76270DEE85A410FA69AF0F1D5593844_171011_3460184_Carbon_released_from_soil_may_escalate_global_wa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DB8/54E/DB854E74D27A4BA3BAB67BC48BD36831_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,soil releases carbon, carbon dioxide, climate change, global warming, science, 26 year study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461024</guid>
      <title>Scientists say $1.8 million worth of gold is flushed down Swiss sewers every year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists say around 43 kg of gold worth around $1.8 million is flushed through Switzerland's sewer system each year. The report was released by researchers at the Swiss Federal Institute of Aquatic Science and Technology, Bloomberg reported. According to the report, the gold is lost through sludge and effluent from the country's waste treatment facilities. Scientists believe the gold flecks originate from the watchmaking industry and gold refineries. Switzerland is a major gold-refining hub with about 70 percent of the world's gold making its way through the country's refineries every year, according to Bloomberg. The study looked at 64 water treatment plants and also found around 3,000 kg of silver worth around $1.7 million.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gold found in Swiss wastewater treatment plants 2. Gold flecks originating from watchmaking industry and gold refineries3. Switzerland refines 70% of the world's gold4. Researchers also discovered silver at sewage treatment plantsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists say around 43 kg of gold worth around $1.8 million is flushed through Switzerland's sewer system each year." "Scientists believe the gold flecks originate from the watchmaking industry and gold refineries." "Switzerland is a major gold-refining hub with about 70 percent of the world's gold making its way through the country's refineries every year.""The study looked at 64 water treatment plants and also found around 3,000 kg of silver worth around $1.7 million."  SOURCES: Bloomberg, CNN, The Vergehttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-10-10/scientists-find-1-8-million-worth-of-gold-in-swiss-wastewaterhttp://money.cnn.com/2017/10/11/news/gold-switzerland-water-sewage-waste/index.htmlhttps://www.theverge.com/2017/10/11/16457674/gold-sewage-switzerland***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 09:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/12/3461024/3461024_520759E031924A02971F2BB2351F54DE_171012_3461024_Scientists_say__1_8_million_worth_of_gold_is_flu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/76D/6EA/76D6EA3AAC784C3E85FD7924D1D2E245_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, gold sewage treatment plants, gold flecks wastewater treatment plants, Swiss gold refineries, Swiss gold sewage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460924</guid>
      <title>Soot-covered, 100-year-old birds can help track air pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers analyzed the amount of soot on birds in museums from Rust Belt cities to track air pollution over the last 135 years. A new paper in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences shows the discoloration of birds in museum collections can be used to estimate the amount of black carbon air over time, Science Daily reported.Researchers from The Field Museum and the University of Chicago sampled over a thousand birds collected over the last 135 years to find out and quantify the effects of soot in the air in Rust Belt cities like Chicago, Detroit and Pittsburgh. To track changes in sootiness, the scientists photographed the birds and measured the light reflected off of them.   They found that older birds were dirtier and new birds were cleaner. The team discovered that soot on birds closely tracks the use of coal over time. Researchers also pointed out that even though newer birds are cleaner, it doesn't necessarily mean U.S. air is less polluted. Many of the pollutants released into the atmosphere today aren't as easily tracked as soot. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Horned larks flying by a coal smokestacks2. Birds have become cleaner over time3. Birds getting measured for amount of soot in their feathers4. Soot on birds closely tracks the use of coal over timeVOICEOVER (in English): "A new paper shows the discoloration of birds in museum collections can be used to estimate the amount of black carbon air over time.""Researchers sampled over a thousand birds collected over the last 135 years to find out and quantify the effects of soot in the air in Rust Belt cities like Chicago, Detroit and Pittsburgh." "To track changes in sootiness, the scientists photographed the birds and measured the light reflected off of them."  "They found that older birds were dirtier and new birds were cleaner. The team discovered that soot on birds closely tracks the use of coal over time." SOURCES: Science Daily, Proceedings of the National Academy of Scienceshttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/10/171009155000.htmhttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/10/04/1710239114***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 07:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/12/3460924/3460924_3798334C156F40FF8AB15DA2C00405E9_171012_3460924_Soot_covered__100_year_old_birds_can_help_track__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ACD/263/ACD26319A3594FF7AEA284CD5C1064FF_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, air pollution, bird feather soot, black carbon pollution, environmental pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460875</guid>
      <title>Malware may have infected millions of users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMillions of visitors to one of the world's most popular adult entertainment websites may have had their computers infected with malware.According to cybersecurity Proofpoint, a user becomes infected after visiting Pornhub and is then redirected to a fake download page. This asks them to download a critical update for Chrome, Firefox or Adobe Flash.If downloaded, their computer would become infected with the Kovter malware. This control of the computer via the registry.The malware uses the computer to click on fake adverts.And, this in turn generates revenue for the malware creators.According to Proofpoint, Pornhub promptly addressed the issue.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of how malware infects PC2. Depiction of malware controlling PC3. Depiction of fake-advertisements4. Money being transferred to malware creatprVOICEOVER (in English): "After visiting the website, users were redirected to a fake download page asking them to download a critical update for Chrome, Firefox or Adobe Flash.""If downloaded, their computer would become infected with the Kovter malware. This then takes control of the computer via the registry""Next, the malware uses the computer to click on fake adverts.""And, this in turn generates revenue for the malware creators." SOURCES: Proofpoint, Guardian, Daily Mailhttps://www.proofpoint.com/us/threat-insight/post/kovter-group-malvertising-campaign-exposes-millions-potential-ad-fraud-malwarehttps://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/oct/10/pornhub-adult-site-users-targeted-malvertising-attack-malware-kovcoregs-kovterhttp://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-4966662/PornHub-users-targeted-advertising-malware-attack.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 06:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/12/3460875/3460875_94F1CB5002C240DB95DEE55426FC5B12_171012_3460875_Malware_may_have_infected_millions_of_users_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DBB/CDD/DBBCDDCC07DF4F329E7DABA300C73EC3_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, malware hack, kovter, kovter malware, kovter virus, Kovter group, malvertising, spamming, pop up malware, infected computer, cybersecurity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3462044</guid>
      <title>CNN: Russian influencers used Pok&#xE9;mon Go to 'meddle' in U.S. politics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA report by CNN claims that Russian-linked election influencers attempted to sway American politics last summer through the mobile game Pokmon Go.CNN reports that they found a word of Russian metadata in a four-page Microsoft Word document sent by email.  That document, CNN says, was part of an email exchange between a writer and a person called Daniel Reed, the Chief Editor of Do Not Shoot Us.DoNotShoot.Us reportedly posed as part of the Black Lives Matter movement, covering stories of police brutality.However, CNN reported that the website's Facebook page was one of many accounts shut down by Facebook after the social network linked them to a Russian business called the Internet Research Agency. That business is said to conduct influence operations on behalf of the Kremlin.CNN speculates that Don't Shoot Us was set up to stoke racial tensions between the black community and the rest of America. The news network claims that in the summer 2016, a Do Not Shoot Us Tumblr page asked users to play mobile monster-catching game Pokmon Go in places where police brutality took place.Users were encouraged to catch a Pokmon, name it after a victim of police brutality and send a screenshot of it to Do Not Shoot Us as part of Amazon gift card contest by email.CNN says the email address provided was the same one Reed used to send the aforementioned writer the email that had a file with Russian metadata attached. The news network found no evidence that anyone took part in the contest.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Russian metadata being found inside document2. Depiction of Facebook closing accounts3. Depiction of Pokmon Go contest instructions4. Overview of situationVOICEOVER (in English):  "CNN says they found a word of Russian metadata in a four-page Microsoft Word document sent by email. "That document, CNN says, was part of an email exchange between a writer and a person called Daniel Reed, the Chief Editor of Do Not Shoot Us.""CNN says that website's Facebook page was one of many accounts shut down by Facebook after the social network linked them to a Russian business called the Internet Research Agency.""That business is said to conduct influence operations on behalf of the Kremlin." "CNN claims that in the summer 2016, a Do Not Shoot Us Tumblr page asked users to play mobile monster-catching game Pokmon Go in places where police brutality took place."Users were encouraged to catch a Pokmon, name it after a victim of police brutality and email a screenshot of it to Do Not Shoot Us as part of an Amazon gift card contest.""CNN says the email address provided was the same one Reed used to send the aforementioned writer the email that contained a file with Russian metadata attached.""The news network found no evidence that anyone took part in the contest."SOURCES: CNNhttp://money.cnn.com/2017/10/12/media/dont-shoot-us-russia-pokemon-go/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 13:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/13/3462044/3462044_F40D6F07E7F6439083FBDBB0563304FB_171013_3462044_CNN__Russian_influencers_used_Pokemon_Go_to__med_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0F8/AC7/0F8AC7CDC1E04418881F1960C244CB90_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, russia pokemon go, russia pokemon go election hacking, russia pokemon go, niantic, election hacking, do not shoot us, putin pokemon go, CNN pokemon russia fake news, pokemon go, nintendo, pikachu]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461733</guid>
      <title>Ring system discovered on dwarf planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONE Scientists in Granada, Spain have discovered a ring system around the dwarf planet HaumeaNamed after that Hawaiian goddess of childbirth, Haumea is orbited by two moons and, according to a new Nature study, a giant ring system.The only other celestial bodies observed to present a ring system Saturn, Jupiter, Neptune and Uranus. Details of the finding were published in the journal Nature.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dwarf planets in solar system2. Haumea's moons and ring3. Other planets' ring systems4. Haumea's 284-year orbit around the Sun versus Earth's 365 daysVOICEOVER (in English): Haumea is one of the solar system's dwarf planets. It's noted for it's American football-like shape. Named after that Hawaiian goddess of childbirth, Haumea is orbited by two moons and, according to a new Nature study, a giant ring system.The only other celestial bodies observed to present a ring system Saturn, Jupiter, Neptune and Uranus.While Earth takes 365 days to orbit the sun, Haumea takes close to 284 years to do so.SOURCES: Guardian, Nature, NASAhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/oct/11/scientists-discover-ring-around-dwarf-planet-haumea-beyond-neptunehttps://www.nature.com/articles/nature24051.epdf?referrer_access_token=6ZcNZLBXHNAoavded71A8NRgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0Nn2Be8IVdyunt-zYVmzk5Ln6r11MMrpWa_clRfZYLpDsHu4xgq_mesNdO_u-Ld0snDpzgyEUbXHiYy-07k5RFTKF4LJcb-eo1h_2R6tRykVgr2NEyAAgCvncEJX4kVi5Qg1MvlbED52TSYaGI0xJFDQ3-6LLt00ADMT-1Jt-23rGafbKL9bIO6CCfCJOuJVI58TbFIcOwybEkylsgHbk7i9ugdfbEAjzm7YX9tF9ObrYnmDt3OdyupVlEZcqguKn8%3D&tracking_referrer=www.theguardian.comhttps://solarsystem.nasa.gov/planets/haumea/indepth***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 08:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/13/3461733/3461733_17F012899A10443780F1B533C54164DD_171013_3461733_Ring_system_discovered_on_dwarf_planet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/183/AD6/183AD6CC1D114AB2959A1BE6ECB11AFA_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, haumea, football planet, ring system, space discovery, haumea dwarf planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461648</guid>
      <title>British sewage plants could be leaking millions of plastic beads into the sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONESewage plants could be leaking millions of tiny plastic beads used for wastewater treatment into seas around the U.K., according to a new report. Dozens of treatment facilities across the country use Bio-Bead plastic pellets to filter chemical and organic contaminants out from sewage, the study from the Cornish Plastic Pollution Coalition (CPPC) said, the Guardian reported. The study found several millions of the 3.5 mm wide pellets had been spilled into the surrounding seas.The Bio-Bead system is used by at least 55 sewage plants around the U.K., according to the CPPC. Bio-Beads are used in the last step of the sewage treatment process before treated effluent water is discharged back into rivers or the sea. The CPPC found no systems are currently in place at sewage plants to handle Bio-Bead spills. Plastic microbeads and industrial pellets, like Bio-Beads, are often mistaken for food by fish, birds and other marine wildlife. The plastic kills animals by blocking the digestive tract, but also as a result of exposure to chemical pollutants like DDT and PCBs that attach to the plastic beads in seawater. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sewage plant releasing plastic Bio-Beads into surrounding sea2. Bio-beads are used to remove chemical and organic contaminants from sewage water3. Bio-beads being released into the ocean4. Ocean fish swallowing contaminated bio-beadsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new report, sewage plants could be leaking millions of tiny plastic beads used for wastewater treatment into British seas.""Fifty-five treatment facilities across the U.K. use the 3.5 mm-wide Bio-Bead plastic pellets to filter chemical and organic contaminants out from sewage.""Bio-Beads are used in the last step before treated effluent water is discharged back into rivers or the sea. Currently no mechanism is in place to stop the beads in the event of a spill."  "Plastic microbeads kill marine life by blocking the digestive tract, but also as a result of exposure to chemical pollutants like DDT and PCBs that attach to the plastic beads in seawater." SOURCES: Guardianhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/oct/11/sewage-plants-are-leaking-millions-of-tiny-plastic-beads-into-britains-seas***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 06:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/13/3461648/3461648_C2981833A5174DD1B30DD1867A7A7127_171013_3461648_British_sewage_plants_could_be_leaking_millions__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A62/39B/A6239BD742D846BCB474F26EFE1F5197_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Bio-Beads, Bio-Beads spilling into sea, plastic microbeads, microbeads, ocean plastic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461533</guid>
      <title>Huge Antarctic hole visible from space gapes open</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA nation-sized body of water known as a polynya has opened up inside the world's southern frozen continent.Scientists say this is the second year in a row the massive hole has appeared. According to National Geographic it is 30,000 square miles in size. This would make it half the size of Florida, around the same size as the UAE and three times as big as Hawaii.Warming waters from changes in the environment are said to play a part in the formation of such holes, as well as weather factors.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Antartica from space 2. Polynya forming3. Comparison of hole to Florida, UAE and Hawaii4. How the hole formsVOICEOVER (in English): "A nation-sized body of water known as a polynya has opened up in Antarctica.""Scientists say this is the second year in a row the massive hole has appeared.""At 30,000 square miles in size, it is half the size of Florida, around the same size as the UAE and three times as big as Hawaii.""Warming waters from changes in the environment are said to play a part in the formation of such holes, as well as weather factors."SOURCES: National Geographic, Inhabitathttp://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/10/sea-ice-hole-antarctica-southern-ocean-spd/https://inhabitat.com/mysterious-giant-hole-cracks-open-in-antarctica/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 04:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/13/3461533/3461533_50FB80FA4A804BE48F2CE88E61FC2009_171013_3461533_Huge_Antarctic_hole_visible_from_space_gapes_ope_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F4D/165/F4D1655C471D43C3832E36CE36A68FB7_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Antarctica hole in the Earth, Polynya, hole in Antarctic ice, antarctica, climate science, changes to antarctica, what is a polynya]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3463748</guid>
      <title>Chinese space station wall fall to Earth in months</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina's Tiangong-1 space station will crash into Earth within the next few months, according to experts. The Tiangong-1 was launched in 2011 as part of China's push to become a space superpower and has been used for manned and unmanned missions, the Guardian reported. In 2016, Chinese officials confirmed that they lost control of the space station and that it would crash to Earth in 2017 or 2018. The station's orbit has been steadily decaying ever since then. Over the past few weeks, the 8.5-tonne station has dipped below 300 km in altitude. When the Tiangong-1 was operational, the lab orbited at an altitude of 370 km.  The lower the altitude, the denser the atmosphere and the faster the Tiangong-1 will burn up. Most of the space station is expected to disintegrate in the atmosphere, but experts say some parts weighing up to 100 kg could reach the Earth's surface, the Guardian reported. China's space agency has told the UN it expects the Tiangong-1 to come down between October 2017 and April 2018.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tiangong-1 launching in 20112. Tiangong-1 floating in space 3. Tiangong-1's decaying orbit4. Tiangong-1 burning up in the atmosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "The Tiangong-1 was launched in 2011 as part of China's push to become a space superpower and has been used for manned and unmanned missions.""In 2016, Chinese officials confirmed that they lost control of the space station and that it would crash to Earth in 2017 or 2018." "Over the past few weeks, the 8.5-tonne station has dipped below 300 km in altitude. When the Tiangong-1 was operational, the lab orbited at an altitude of 370 km." "Most of the space station is expected to disintegrate in the atmosphere, but experts say some parts weighing up to 100 kg could reach the Earth's surface."SOURCES: The Guardian, The Independent https://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/oct/13/tiangong-1-chinese-space-station-will-crash-to-earth-within-monthshttp://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/tiangong-1-chinese-space-station-falling-to-earth-china-cnsa-nasa-when-date-a7999526.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 12:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/16/3463748/3463748_F210CD4E201E41EFB5C7761CACEB7590_171016_3463748_Chinese_space_station_wall_fall_to_Earth_in_mont_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7E3/5D4/7E35D4DC1C094DA1BEBBDE2C925D8C72_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China space station, Tiangong-1, Tiangong-1 falling to Earth, Tiangong-1 crash, Chinese Tiangong-1]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3463545</guid>
      <title>Yellowstone supervolcano could become active faster than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new study suggests Yellowstone's supervolcano could become active in just a few decades if the right conditions developed. Arizona State University researchers analyzed minerals in ancient fossilized ash from the most recent mega-eruption and believe the supervolcano became active after two injections of magma into the reservoir underneath the caldera, National Geographic reported. They found the minerals showed that the critical changes in temperature and composition built up over a few decades. Geologists previously thought it took centuries for supervolcanoes to go active.  Supervolcanoes have an eruption magnitude of 8 on the Volcano Explosivity Index (VEI) and spit out more than 1,000 cubic kilometers (240 cubic miles) of hot rock and ash, according to Science Alert. For now Yellowstone's supervolcano hasn't shown any indications of an eruption, although experts agree there's no way of knowing when the next blast will occur. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Yellowstone caldera with magma chambers underneath2. Magma underneath caldera filling up twice prior to previous eruption3. Researchers studying ash deposits4. A supervolcano explosion erupting a 1,000 cubic kilometer ash cloudVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study of ancient fossilized ash suggests Yellowstone's supervolcano could become active much quicker than previously thought.""Arizona State University researchers looked at fossilized ash deposits from Yellowstone's Lava Creek Tuff and found the volcano became active after two injections of fresh magma." "They found the minerals showed that the critical changes in temperature and composition built up over a few decades." "Supervolcanoes have an eruption magnitude of 8 on the Volcano Explosivity Index and spit out more than 1,000 cubic kilometers of hot rock and ash."SOURCES: National Geographic, Science Alerthttp://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/10/yellowstone-supervolcano-erupt-faster-thought-science/https://www.sciencealert.com/yellowstone-s-supervolcano-could-give-less-warning-of-an-eruption-than-we-thought***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 08:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/16/3463545/3463545_082163C583E4480AB317F428346AB98A_171016_3463545_Yellowstone_supervolcano_could_become_active_fas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1D5/854/1D585428DB6B44FA911BD5E392F1F0D8_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Yellowstone supervolcano, Yellowstone supervolcano eruption, supervolcano, Yellowstone caldera]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464369</guid>
      <title>WiFi networks at risk of 'Krack' hacking attacks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEWiFi networks worldwide could contain a security flaw that lets hackers disrupt internet traffic, according to researchers. A hacker in range of a WiFi network would be able load viruses onto the network, read and gather communications like passwords, credit card numbers and photos sent, the Telegraph reported. Experts call it a "Krack" attack and say it's a "fundamental flaw" in wireless security techniques, with Apple, Android and Windows software all vulnerable to some extent. The Krack attack takes advantage of the "handshake" between device and router to insert a "key" that can decrypt communications to allow things like passwords and credit card data to be stolen, according to the Telegraph. Researchers suggest only connecting to secured WiFi networks and avoiding unsecured networks like those hotels, coffee shops and public spaces.Most banking and online shopping websites use https, an encryption technique that protects against Krack attacks.Security analysts also suggest updating your router, although updates for Krack attacks may not be available yet. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. WiFi networks around the world being affected by a Krack attack2. A WiFi network affected by an attack3. A WiFi network could be affected by a virus or user information could be stolen4. WiFi networks in public places should be avoidedVOICEOVER (in English): "WiFi networks worldwide could contain a security flaw that lets hackers disrupt internet traffic.""Experts call it a "Krack" attack and say it's a "fundamental flaw" in wireless security techniques, with Apple, Android and Windows software all vulnerable to some extent." "A hacker in range of a WiFi network would be able load viruses onto the network, read and gather communications like passwords, credit card numbers and photos sent.""Researchers suggest only connecting to secured WiFi networks and avoiding unsecured networks like those hotels, coffee shops and public spaces."SOURCES: The Telegraph http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/10/16/every-wi-fi-device-risk-unprecedented-krack-attack-security/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 10:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/17/3464369/3464369_4AAD332118E74B439E6C0DAAB09E5B1E_171017_3464369_WiFi_networks_at_risk_of__Krack__hacking_attacks_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E87/387/E87387DBF6A94125BE4622F264918DC3_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, WiFi, WiFi security, Krack attack, Krack hacking attack. WiFi unsecured networks, password theft, credit card data theft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464123</guid>
      <title>Ozone-depleting chemicals found in new study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew research suggests the ozone layer maybe be at threat once again.Scientists looking at data from Taiwan and Malaysia found that the atmosphere is stacked with the chemical dichloromethane.This chemical is said to deplete the ozone layer over Earth. The ozone helps to protect Earth from the sun's cancerous ultraviolet rays.Scientist also discovered large traces of the chemical dichloroethane, another ozone depleting chemical.The findings were published in the open-access journal Atmospheric Chemistry and Physics.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Taiwan, Malaysia and chemicals2. Sun, the Earth and the atmosphere3. Chemicals in atmosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists looking at data from Taiwan and Malaysia found that the atmosphere is stacked with the chemical dichloromethane.""This chemical is said to deplete the ozone layer over Earth. The ozone helps to protect Earth from the sun's cancerous ultraviolet rays.""Scientist also discovered large traces of the chemical dichloroethane, another ozone-depleting chemical."SOURCES: New Atlas, Atmospheric Chemistry and Physics, European Geosciences Unionhttps://newatlas.com/new-threat-to-ozone-layer/51730/https://www.atmos-chem-phys.net/17/11929/2017/https://www.egu.eu/news/357/study-reveals-new-threat-to-the-ozone-layer/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 05:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/17/3464123/3464123_11917B1CE447451BAD13C3C923B8CDA2_171017_3464123_Ozone_depleting_chemicals_found_in_new_study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AE1/707/AE1707DCAD8F414CB8B2767B051A92D0_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ...]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465098</guid>
      <title>Astronomers confirm asteroid not 'space junk'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAstronomers have confirmed an asteroid discovered last summer isn't space debris.Dubbed Earth's "new constant companion" by NASA last summer, 2016 HO3 is a small asteroid orbiting the Sun on a trajectory that overlaps with the planet.The space agency speculates that it is between 120 and 300 feet in size. Some thought it was actually "space junk"  debris from old rockets and satellites  but new research has confirmed that it is indeed an asteroid.The asteroid is a quasi-satellite to Earth. It orbits closer to the sun than Earth does in 6-month period, while the rest of time it falls further behind. This is different to natural satellites, such as the Moon, where orbits are tied solely to a planet or a star.The findings were presented by University of Arizona Professor Vishnu Reddy at the annual Division for Planetary Sciences Conference of the American Astronomical Society in Provo, Utah.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid over Earth2. Space debris3. Orbit of asteroid 4. The Moon orbiting EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Dubbed Earth's 'new constant companion' by NASA last summer, 2016 HO3 is a small asteroid orbiting the Sun on a trajectory that overlaps with Earth." "The space agency speculates that it's between 120 and 300 feet in size.""Some thought it was actually 'space junk'  debris from old rockets and satellites but new research has confirmed that it is indeed an asteroid.""It is a quasi-satellite to Earth that orbits closer to the Sun than Earth does over 6-months, while the rest of time it falls further behind.""This is different to natural satellites, such as the Moon, where orbits are tied only to a planet or a star."SOURCES: Phys.org, NASA, University of Arizonahttps://phys.org/news/2017-10-earth-buddy-asteroid-space-junk.htmlhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=6537https://uanews.arizona.edu/story/earths-new-traveling-buddy-asteroid-not-space-junk***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 10:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/18/3465098/3465098_557C0657169345DDBB5A07DE64C2B175_171018_3465098_Astronomers_confirm_asteroid_not__space_junk__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CA7/F6B/CA7F6B8BD207460481F98E5A62AAF9A7_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  asteroid 2016 ho3, new asteroid, mini moon, nasa asteroid, earth asteroid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465092</guid>
      <title>Iceland opens world's first 'negative emissions' power plant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEIceland has opened the world's first power plant that eliminates more carbon dioxide than it produces. The geothermal plant in cooperation with Climeworks will remove an estimated 50 metric tons of CO2 from the air each year where it will be turned into limestone and stored in the ground, Quartz reported.The process works by pulling CO2 from the ambient air using a special filter. The heat from the power plant warms up the filter which extracts pure carbon dioxide. The gas is then combined with water and pumped 700 meters underground. When the carbon dioxide reaches with basaltic rock, it forms minerals. The project is still in the pilot phase, but researchers at Climeworks believe negative emissions plants could be set up around the world. One major obstacle in place is the price. Climeworks estimates it runs around $600 to extract one ton of carbon dioxide from the air. However if economies of scale can be utilized and more plants open up, that price would drop significantly.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Geothermal plant in Iceland2. The direct capture unit pulling carbon dioxide out of the ambient air3. Carbon dioxide being combined with water and being pumped underground4. Negative emissions power plantVOICEOVER (in English): "The geothermal plant in Iceland in cooperation with Climeworks will remove an estimated 50 metric tons of CO2 from the air each year.""The process works by pulling CO2 from the ambient air using a special filter. The heat from the power plant warms up the filter which extracts pure carbon dioxide." "The gas is then combined with water and pumped 700 meters underground. When the carbon dioxide reaches with basaltic rock, it forms minerals." "The project is still in the pilot phase, but researchers at Climeworks believe negative emissions plants could be set up around the world." SOURCES: Quartz, Inhabitathttps://qz.com/1100221/the-worlds-first-negative-emissions-plant-has-opened-in-iceland-turning-carbon-dioxide-into-stone/https://inhabitat.com/worlds-first-negative-emissions-power-plant-opens-in-iceland/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 10:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/18/3465092/3465092_46AE01A471C5424CAE8986CDC0A19F85_171018_3465092_Iceland_opens_world_s_first__negative_emissions__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CF9/FCE/CF9FCE9AD15645A7A0873E61A6FE7347_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, negative emissions power plant, renewable energy, carbon direct air capture, Iceland negative emissions power plant, carbon dioxide]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465022</guid>
      <title>Startup training crows to pick up cigarette butts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA Dutch startup is working to train crows to pick up cigarette butts, according to Popular Mechanics. Crows are highly intelligent and are able to make and use tools. Cigarette butts are the most littered item on the planet with an estimated 4.5 trillion butts thrown away each year, according to Inhabitat. The startup Crowded Cities plans to use the crows to help rid the streets of cigarette butts by teaching them to swap butts for food. The CrowBar is a device with a large funnel for cigarette butts and a peanut dispenser. It works by training crows using a four-step process. The first step presents food next to a cigarette butt, training the birds to expect food from the machine. Second, the machine only gives out food when the crow arrives at the device, teaching the crow how the machine functions.Third, the device only presents a cigarette butt with no food. The crow then starts to look for the food and in the process, knocks the butt into the funnel, dispensing the food. The fourth step involves removing the cigarette butt, but leaving them scattered around the CrowBar. The crow will then start to pick up butts they find and bring them back to the machine. Crowded Cities is currently in the process of putting together a working prototype, Popular Mechanics reported. The next step for researchers will be to study how collecting toxic cigarette butts affects the crows. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Crows using the CrowBar in city park2. Crows being taught first and second steps in learning process3. Crows being taught the third step4. Crows being taught the final stepVOICEOVER (in English): "The startup Crowded Cities plans to use the CrowBar  a device with a funnel for cigarette butts and a dispenser  to teach crows to pick up cigarette butts in exchange for food." "It trains the crows using a four-step process. The first step presents food next to a cigarette butt, training the birds to expect food from the machine. Second, the machine only gives out food after the crow arrives." "Third, the device only presents a cigarette butt with no food. The crow then starts to look for the food and in the process, knocks the butt into the funnel, dispensing the food." "The fourth step involves removing the cigarette butt, but leaving them scattered around the CrowBar. The crow will then start to pick up butts they find and bring them back to the machine."SOURCES: Popular Mechanics, Inhabitathttp://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/startups/news/a28543/startup-trains-crows-to-pick-up-trash/https://inhabitat.com/this-startup-is-training-crows-to-throw-away-cigarette-butt-litter/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 09:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/18/3465022/3465022_E3E1931EF07D47EABBA876D4700E0788_171018_3465022_Startup_training_crows_to_pick_up_cigarette_butt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/41E/01D/41E01DD9F49B4DF481F13BB64569B5DB_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, CrowBar, Crowded Cities startup, crows cigarette butts, cigarette butt litter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464857</guid>
      <title>Astronomers detect light and gravity from cosmic explosion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEIn an astronomical first, scientists detected light and gravity from what they believe was the collision of two ultra-compact dense neutron stars in galaxy NG 4993.First detected in 2013, a kilonova is a class of supernova explosion resulting from two colliding neutron stars.The Space Telescope Science Institute says each neutron in this case was no wider than Washington, D.C. Typically, they're between 6 and 12 miles in diameter.The Institute added that the stars in question weighed between 10 percent and 60 percent more than our sun."What followed the kilonova is unknown, but NASA astrophysicist Eleonora Troja told Space.com the cosmic explosion may have a formed a black hole.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Milky way and hydra constellation2. Depiction of kilonova 3. Depiction of kilonova emitting different signals4. Depiction of black hole formationVOICEOVER (in English): "Millions of light years from the Milky Way, inside the Hydra constellation is an elliptical galaxy.""It's here astronomers believe they detected both light and gravity from a kilonova event."  "First detected in 2013, a kilonova is a class of supernova explosion resulting from two colliding neutron stars.""The Space Telescope Science Institute says each neutron in this case was no wider than Washington, D.C. Typically, they're between 6 and 12 miles in diameter.""The Institute added that the stars in question weighed between 10 percent and 60 percent more than our sun.""It's the collision of two of these ultra-compact densities that astronomers believe emitted light and gravity strong enough to be observed on Earth.""What followed the kilonova is unknown, but NASA astrophysicist Eleonora Troja speculates the cosmic explosion may have a formed a black hole."SOURCES: European Space Observatory, Hubble Site (Space Telescope Science Institute), Space, Forbes http://www.eso.org/public/news/eso1733/http://hubblesite.org/news_release/news/2017-41https://www.space.com/38478-did-neutron-stars-collision-create-black-hole.htmlhttps://www.space.com/38469-gravitational-waves-from-neutron-stars-discovery-ligo.htmlhttps://www.forbes.com/sites/startswithabang/2017/08/23/beyond-black-holes-could-ligo-have-detected-merging-neutron-stars-for-the-first-time/#4253662f6fbd***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 05:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/18/3464857/3464857_32314C58A1314FDB88B2F7A8C1D28AF2_171018_3464857_Astronomers_detect_light_and_gravity_from_cosmic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/802/CB4/802CB410AC694EEEAE2DC82A0024EDBD_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, neutron star collision, neutron star, black hole formation, neutron star, what is a neutron star, black hole explainer, nasa, eso]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465658</guid>
      <title>Critics call for virtual Trump border wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA Texas sheriff believes a virtual wall at the U.S.-Mexico border would be more effective than a physical wall. Building an actual wall would have to overcome environmental issues, and deal with the abundance of privately owned land along the border, Webb County Sheriff Martin Cuellar said, the Dallas News reported. Cuellar says the wall would also have an adverse effect on Mexican shoppers traveling between both countries and could potentially hurt Texas' economy. The sheriff has been looking for $92 million in funding over five years for a virtual wall that uses technology and agents on the ground as an alternative to a physical wall, according to the Dallas News. His proposed virtual wall would extend around 300 miles from Starr County to Del Rio. Cost estimates for Trump's border wall range from $21 billion to $40 billion.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Trump's border wall being replaced by a virtual wall2. Virtual wall would use technology and agents on the ground3. The virtual wall would extend from Starr County to Del Rio   VOICEOVER (in English): "Texas sheriff Martin Cuellar believes a virtual wall at the US-Mexico border would be more effective than a physical wall." "The sheriff has been looking for $92 million in funding over five years for a virtual wall that uses technology and agents on the ground as an alternative to the wall.""His proposed virtual wall would extend around 300 miles from Starr County to Del Rio." SOURCES: Dallas Newshttps://www.dallasnews.com/news/immigration/2017/10/17/trumps-border-plans-take-shape-critics-call-virtual-wall***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 08:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/19/3465658/3465658_4CAEB7CC25A64398BF8CFA8210E699BA_171019_3465658_Critics_call_for_virtual_Trump_border_wall_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9F5/FD8/9F5FD87FA2034E108D692ABEA3227FEE_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Trump border wall, Trump virtual border wall, virtual border wall, border wall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465625</guid>
      <title>ULA, Bigelow to launch inflatable moon-orbiting habitat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAerospace companies United Launch Alliance and Bigelow Aerospace are collaborating to put a space station in orbit around the moon.According to a press release from ULA, the lunar depot plan is aiming to place a Bigelow B330 inflatable habitat in low lunar orbit by the end of 2022.ULA's Vulcan rocket will launch the B330 into lower Earth orbit, where it will stay for about a year. While there, the habitat will receive supplies and get crew members rotated every few months.Two more Vulcan rockets will then be launched, and their upper stages  called Advanced Cryogenic Evolved Stage, or ACES  left in orbit. After propellant from one ACES is transferred to the other, the fully fueled stage will attach to the B330 and deliver it to its final position orbiting the moon.The companies claim the habitat can serve both as a platform for lunar business development, and a location for NASA to conduct exploration and astronaut training missions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bigelow B330 inflatable habitat to orbit the moon by 20222. B330 to be launched by ULA's Vulcan rocket to lower earth orbit3. Vulcan to launch two rockets, leaving ACES upper stages in orbit. Propellant transferred from one ACES to another4. Fully fueled ACES to propel B330 to lunar orbitVOICEOVER (in English): "The lunar depot plan is aiming to place a Bigelow B330 inflatable habitat in low lunar orbit by the end of 2022.""ULA's Vulcan rocket will launch the B330 into lower Earth orbit, where it will stay for about a year.""Two more Vulcan rockets will then be launched, and their upper stages left in orbit. After propellant from one stage is transferred to the other...""...the fully fueled stage will attach to the B330 and propel it to its final position orbiting the moon."SOURCES: ULA, Spacehttp://www.ulalaunch.com/bigelow-aerospace-and-ula-lunar-depot.aspxhttps://www.space.com/38490-private-lunar-space-station-bigelow-ula.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/19/3465625/3465625_562B3ECC28FF416695610935C69F2A05_171019_3465625_ULA__Bigelow_to_launch_inflatable_moon_orbiting__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D5B/EB9/D5BEB9CCFA654EC8A71D1A41F3E4384A_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, moon habitat, lunar habitat, space station, moon space station, bigelow, ULA, united launch alliance, vulcan rocket, b330, b330 habitat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465478</guid>
      <title>China's concept Martian colony</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina has conceptualized a colony of forest cities on Mars dubbed "New Shanghai".The concept from the Chinese Space Agency, Tonji University and Stefano Boeri Architects would see a spaceship ferry a colony of massive pods containing forest cities from Earth, toward Mars.Once the pods have touched down on the red planet, Inhabitat reports that they would use "eco-systemic seeds" to take root.This colony of forest city giant pods, dubbed New Shanghai, would also reportedly contain an infrastructure and an Earth-like atmosphere.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Conceptual cities in spaceship over Earth 2. Conceptual cities in spaceship over Mars3. Conceptual cities landing4. Inside conceptual cityVOICEOVER (in English): "The concept from the Chinese Space Agency, Tonji University and Stefano Boeri Architects would see a spaceship ferry a colony of massive pods containing forest cities from Earth, toward Mars.""Once the pods have touched down on the red planet, Inhabitat reports that they would use 'eco-systemic seeds' to take root.""This colony of forest city giant pods, dubbed New Shanghai, would also reportedly contain an infrastructure and an Earth-like atmosphere." SOURCES: Inhabitathttps://inhabitat.com/stefano-boeri-architects-envisions-a-vertical-forest-city-on-mars/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 04:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/19/3465478/3465478_931847704463490587D94BF506BC2BED_171019_3465478_China_s_concept_Martian_colony_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2E9/AEA/2E9AEA961F9E493CA7A55433C93C5C79_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mars colony, colonizing mars, china mars, new shanghai, city on mars, forest city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466369</guid>
      <title>Droves of flying insects vanish in Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThree quarters of insects in protected German nature reserves have disappeared, according to new research. Researchers looked at the biomass of flying bugs of flying insects inside 63 German nature reserves. They found that 76% of the total insect population between 1989 and 2016 had been lost.The cause of the decline is unclear, but the fact the insects vanished at a high rate has scientists concerned. They say their findings could be representative of other areas around the world.The study was published this week in the journal PLOS One.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of man driving in forest2. Depiction of study graph3. Depiction of flying insect in forest4. Depiction of resultsVOICEOVER (in English): "The research looked at the biomass of flying insects inside 63 German nature reserves.""It found that between 1989 and 2016 the reserves' total flying insect population had declined by an average of 76 percent." "The cause of the massive drop is unclear, but the fact the insects vanished at such a high rate has scientists concerned.""The researchers say their findings could be representative of other areas around the world."SOURCES: Radboud University, Washington Post, PLOS Onehttp://www.ru.nl/english/news-agenda/news/vm/iwwr/2017/three-quarters-total-insect-population-lost/https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/speaking-of-science/wp/2017/10/18/this-is-very-alarming-flying-insects-vanish-from-nature-preserves/?utm_term=.a4a839d28352http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0185809***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 08:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/20/3466369/3466369_CDE127430E9748B2A9024CF7FF0AF54B_171020_3466369_Droves_of_flying_insects_vanish_in_Germany_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/35B/6EF/35B6EFB2E5E94CD4A2E1CCAA0DB678F7_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bug population, plos one, germany insect study, bug population decline]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466346</guid>
      <title>Study suggests mind remains conscious after body is pronounced dead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearch from the NYU Langone School of Medicine suggests that people's consciousness continue to work even after they have been pronounced dead.According to the study published in the journal Resuscitation, doctors define death as the moment the heart stops beating, cutting off circulation and halting brain and other organ function.Scientists looked at patients who flatlined but were later revived and found that 39% reported some form of awareness while technically dead. Several recalled full conversations, and saw things happening around them- details which were verified by staff present at the time.Theoretically, this could mean the recently deceased are fully aware of their condition, and may even hear the pronouncement of their own death.The study suggests the awareness may be a result of a burst of energy that is released in the brain immediately post-mortem.This finding has been echoed in a 2013 research from the University of Michigan, which observed brain patterns pointing to a 'hyper-alerted state' in nine clinically dead rats.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Heart stops, patient pronounced dead2. Patient revived3. Patient recalls hearing conversations, seeing things after being pronounced dead4. Burst of brain energy during deathVOICEOVER (in English): "Doctors define death as the moment the heart stops beating, cutting off circulation and halting brain and other organ function.""Scientists looked at patients who flatlined but were later revived...""...and found that 39% reported some form of awareness while technically dead. Some recalled conversations, and saw things happening around them- details which were verified by staff present at the time.""The study suggests the awareness may be a result of a burst of energy that is released in the brain immediately post-mortem." SOURCES: Independent, Resuscitationhttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/mind-works-after-death-consciousness-sam-parnia-nyu-langone-a8007101.htmlhttp://www.resuscitationjournal.com/article/S0300-9572(14)00739-4/abstract***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 07:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/20/3466346/3466346_6A1FC2C3C8F34AB9814EFFFB408EA258_171020_3466346_Study_suggests_mind_remains_conscious_after_body_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/131/744/1317441C178B47E2A83364D624E53D96_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, brain dead, life after death, near death experience, after death, technically dead, clinically dead, dead, flatline, flatliners, cardiac arrest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466181</guid>
      <title>LAPD becomes largest police department in U.S. to test drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Los Angeles Police Commission has voted in favor of allowing the LAPD to use drones in a year-long pilot program, the Los Angeles Times reported. This will make the LAPD the largest US police force to use the robotic aerial drones. Only SWAT team members in high-risk situations will be able to fly the drones. They will be deployed for aerial searches and gathering intelligence in tense situations. The drones will also be used in search and rescue missions. Every flight needs to be approved, documented and reviewed, according to Engadget. The Police Commission will receive quarterly reports that will be made public, the Los Angeles Times reported. Weapons and facial-recognition technology are prohibited. LAPD officials have attempted to address privacy concerns by saying the restrictions in place along with strong oversight would be sufficient, although many critics still remain wary. The commission will evaluate the performance of the pilot program after a year in order to decide whether to continue or not. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Police drone flying in representational space2. SWAT member flying a police drone3. The drones will also be used in search and rescue operations4. Drones will not be equipped with weapons or facial recognition technologyVOICEOVER (in English): "The Los Angeles Police Commission has voted in favor of allowing the LAPD to use drones in a year-long pilot program.""Only SWAT team members in high-risk situations will be able to fly the drones. They will be deployed for aerial searches and gathering intelligence in tense situations." "The drones will also be used in search and rescue missions." "Every flight needs to be approved, documented and reviewed. Weapons and facial-recognition technology are also prohibited." SOURCES: Los Angeles Times, Engadgethttp://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-lapd-drones-20171017-story.htmlhttps://www.engadget.com/2017/10/18/la-police-cleared-to-test-drones/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 02:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/20/3466181/3466181_49382F951D164E349AF0E5786E590A5F_171020_3466181_LAPD_becomes_largest_police_department_in_U_S__t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3A7/A46/3A7A46DD22DD4C00AB33D97AA385FE93_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, LAPD drones, LAPD drones pilot program, police drones, aerial drones, drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3467074</guid>
      <title>Moon cave discovery stokes hope for lunar exploration</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA cavernous lava tube was this week confirmed to exist beneath the surface of the moon. The discovery was after by a team of Japanese and American scientists using data from the SELENE and GRAIL spacecraft to acoustically map the enormous lava tube.These tubes are volcanic underground passages formed by flowing lava to funnel the substance. Once the flow stops, the tube remains with features similar to a cave.The chasm is around 100 meters wide and 50 kilometers long, reported the Guardian. It is located in the Marius Hills region of the celestial body.The cave could provide shelter to astronauts during moon missions, protecting them from dangerous cosmic radiation. This could potentially allow for the development of a lunar exploration base.Details of the finding was published in the journal, Geophysical Research Letters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the chasm2. Explanation of lava tubes3. Depiction of spacecraft mapping cave4. Size and location of lava tube5. Depiction of lunar astronauts inside the lava tube6. Depiction of lunar exploration baseVOICEOVER (in English): "A large and cavernous lava tube was this week confirmed to exist beneath the surface of the moon. "These tubes are volcanic underground passages formed by flowing lava to funnel the substance. "Once the flow stops, the tube remains with features similar to a cave." "The discovery was after by a team of Japanese and American scientists using data from the SELENE and GRAIL spacecraft to acoustically map the enormous lava tube.""The chasm is around 100 meters wide and 50 kilometers long and located in the Marius Hills region of the celestial body." "It could provide shelter to astronauts during moon missions, protecting them from dangerous cosmic radiation.""This could potentially allow for the development of a lunar exploration base."SOURCES: Geophysical Research Letters, Asahi Shimbun, The Guardian, Space.com http://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/hub/article/10.1002/2017GL074998/editor-highlight/http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL074998/fullhttp://www.asahi.com/ajw/articles/AJ201710180045.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/oct/19/lunar-cave-discovery-raises-hopes-for-human-colonisation-of-moonhttps://www.space.com/26592-manned-moon-exploration-lunar-pits.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 06:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/21/3467074/3467074_7D32141A8B2042E9AF40B35795DEA577_171021_3467074_Moon_cave_discovery_stokes_hope_for_lunar_explor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FDC/F18/FDCF18AE52E947E89B4DAAB2CA09CD7F_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, moon cave, moon base, human moon colony, nasa, jaxa, colonizing the moon, moon exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468353</guid>
      <title>Broken heart syndrome explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new study details the case of a Texan woman who was left hospitalized with broken heart syndrome after the death of her dog.The study was published in the New England Journal of Medicine.Also known as Takotsubo cardiomyopathy, broken-heart syndrome sees severe weakening of the heart's left ventricle after a stressful event.This pot like shape is where the condition's name comes from. A takotsubo is a Japanese pot used to trap octopuses.According to Harvard Health, experts believe the sheer amount of adrenaline and hormones triggered by the stressful event may temporarily stupefy the heart.Several tests are required to identify the condition as electrocardiogram readings of it are usually identical to a heart attack. Most doctors prescribe heart failure drugs to help with it. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. What happens to the heart during broken heart syndrome2. Depiction of woman suffering from broken heart syndrome 3. Depiction of patient in hospital with doctor4..Depiction of statistics of broken heart syndromeVOICEOVER (in English): "Also known as Takotsubo cardiomyopathy, broken-heart syndrome sees severe weakening of the heart's left ventricle after a stressful event.""Experts believe the sheer amount of adrenaline and hormones triggered by the stressful event may temporarily stupefy the heart.""Symptoms involve a shortness of breath and chest pain.""Several tests are required to identify the condition as electrocardiogram readings of it are usually identical to a heart attack.""Most doctors prescribe heart failure drugs to help.""The condition affects vastly more women than men, and around 1 in 5 of those suffering the condition die from it."SOURCES: New England Journal of Medicine, New York Daily News, Harvard Healthhttp://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMicm1615835#t=articlehttp://nydn.us/2yZrpvShttps://www.health.harvard.edu/heart-health/takotsubo-cardiomyopathy-broken-heart-syndrome***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 11:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/23/3468353/3468353_F6871B81B0A041CB8F0AA5B68DA0256E_171023_3468353_Broken_heart_syndrome_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/62A/EA9/62AEA9F4049043D1AD190EEC6229AA00_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,what is a broken heart, broken heart explained, broken heart syndrome, how does the heart break, heart break hospitalization, Takotsubo cardiomyopathy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468318</guid>
      <title>South Korea to develop monster missile to target DPRK weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONESouth Korea has revealed plans to build a new missile to take on the North, should war break out on the Korean peninsula.Korea Herald reports that the South Korean military is planning to counter Pyongyang's growing weapons capabilities by developing the Hyunmoo-IV, a surface-to-surface missile with an 800-km range and a payload of up to 2 tons.It will be powerful enough to destroy the North's underground military facilities and command centers, and is set to be the final weapon to be mobilized in Seoul's three-tier attack plan.According to Yonhap News, the plan's first step involves launching a KTSSM missile to strike North Korean artillery that have been camouflaged and embedded along the DMZ and on the coast of border islands.Hyunmoo-2 ballistic missiles will then be deployed to neutralize the enemy's nuclear weapons, weapons of mass destruction, and their delivery systems.The development of the 'frankenmissile' is part of army efforts to establish a five-pillar operational concept that can minimize civilian casualties and put an early end to armed conflict.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. South Korean Hyunmoo-IV missile has 800km range, payload of up to 2 tons2. Missile part of three-tier strike plan during war with North Korea3. KTSSM missile mobilized first to destroy North's artillery equipment4. Hyunmoo-II ballistic missile deployed to neutralize nuclear weaponsVOICEOVER (in English): "The South Korean military seeks to counter Pyongyang's growing weapons capabilities by developing the Hyunmoo-IV, a surface-to-surface missile with an 800-km range and a payload of up to 2 tons.""It will be powerful enough to destroy the North's underground military facilities and command centers, and is set to be the final weapon to be mobilized in Seoul's three-tier attack plan.""The plan's first step involves launching a KTSSM missile to strike North Korean artillery that have been camouflaged and embedded along the DMZ and on the coast of border islands.""Hyunmoo-2 ballistic missiles will then be deployed to neutralize the enemy's nuclear weapons, weapons of mass destruction, and their delivery systems."SOURCES: Korea Herald, Yonhap Newshttp://www.koreaherald.com/view.php?ud=20171019000877http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/northkorea/2017/10/19/0401000000AEN20171019011200315.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 10:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/23/3468318/3468318_EDBA43D59D344808AD642399BA3B678F_171023_3468318_South_Korea_to_develop_monster_missile_to_target_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BF0/B67/BF0B67C6D71048B6BA55B85D0E49DA83_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, frankenmissile, monster missile, south korea missile, hyunmoo missile, hyunmoo 4, hyunmoo IV, north korea weapons, korean war, north korea nuclear]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468295</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk to start hyperloop project in Maryland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMaryland officials have given Elon Musk the green light to dig tunnels for a hyperloop project between New York and Washington, the Baltimore Sun reported. Last Thursday, the state issued a conditional utility permit to allow Musk's Boring Co. to dig a 10.3-mile tunnel between the state-owned section of the Baltimore-Washington Parkway, between the Baltimore city line and Maryland 175 in Hanover, according to the Baltimore Sun. The Boring Co. wants to construct two 35-mile tunnels between Baltimore and Washington, D.C., according to Maryland Transportation Secretary Pete Rahn, reported the Baltimore Sun.The U.S. government owns roughly two-thirds of the land Musk's company plans to dig underneath, Ars Technica reported. The 10-mile section approved by Maryland will be the first section of the underground system.   Once completed, the hyperloop trip between Washington and New York would only take 29 minutes. The Boring Co. looks to reduce traffic congestion by creating a low-cost system of tunnels. The company has developed tunneling machines that can efficiently drill through soft soil at only a fraction of the cost of traditional tunneling.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hyperloop pod carrying passengers through tunnel2. The proposed tunnel section between Baltimore and Maryland 1753. Boring machine drilling through soil4. Hyperloop pods traveling through a completed systemVOICEOVER (in English): "Maryland officials have given Elon Musk's The Boring Co. the green light to dig tunnels for a hyperloop project between New York and Washington.""The Boring Co. plans to dig a 10.3-mile tunnel between the state-owned section of the Baltimore-Washington Parkway, between the Baltimore city line and Maryland 175 in Hanover.""The company has developed tunneling machines that can efficiently drill through soft soil at only a fraction of the cost of traditional tunneling."   "According to Musk's estimates, a hyperloop trip between Washington and New York would only take 29 minutes." SOURCES: Baltimore Sun, Ars Technicahttp://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/politics/bs-md-hyperloop-in-baltimore-20171019-story.htmlhttps://arstechnica.com/cars/2017/10/elon-musks-boring-company-is-digging-a-10-mile-tunnel-in-maryland/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 10:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/23/3468295/3468295_F78C61B3CAC5485391D347706D24B6BE_171023_3468295_Elon_Musk_to_start_hyperloop_project_in_Maryland_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AB5/7CC/AB57CC60BA234CCC92814280F4BB0BCD_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hyperloop, The Boring Company, Elon Musk, Maryland hyperloop project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469149</guid>
      <title>New study shows it's possible to sweat blood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA rare condition called hematohidrosis causes people to sweat blood, says a new study. A 21-year-old Italian woman was found to have been bleeding intermittently from her face and palms for three years, according to a study published in the Canadian Medical Association Journal. Episodes seemed to be triggered without warning, although stress would often intensify the bleeding.  She was eventually diagnosed with blood sweating, or hematohidrosis. This condition causes blood to seep out of unbroken skin like normal perspiration.It's most common on the face, ears, nose and eyes and is often associated with fear and emotional stress, according to the National Institutes of Health Genetic and Rare Diseases Information Center, Time reported. The woman was treated with a beta blocker  propranolol  normally used to regulate blood pressure and heart rate. The medicine did not stop the bleeding, but she did experience a "marked reduction" in symptoms.  Medical experts still don't know what causes the condition.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman bleeding from her face and palms2. Woman sweating blood3. The condition is most common in the face, ears, nose and eyes4. Woman taking a beta-blocker to help with her symptomsVOICEOVER (in English): "A 21-year-old Italian woman was found to have been bleeding intermittently from her face and palms for three years.""She was eventually diagnosed with blood sweating, or hematohidrosis. This condition causes blood to seep out of unbroken skin like normal perspiration.""It's most common on the face, ears, nose and eyes and is often associated with fear and emotional stress.""The woman was treated with a beta blocker normally used to regulate blood pressure and heart rate. The medicine did not stop the bleeding, but she did experience a 'marked reduction' in symptoms."  SOURCES: Timehttp://time.com/4993523/sweat-blood-hematohidrosis/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 13:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/24/3469149/3469149_0E5126D47FA84C5AB70098D744FF6D55_171024_3469149_New_study_shows_it_s_possible_to_sweat_blood_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C15/4C0/C154C061935B49A98DC216C406C06F3E_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hematohidrosis, blood sweating, blood crying, stress induced conditions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469046</guid>
      <title>Ovarian cancer found to originate in the fallopian tubes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA preliminary study of ovarian cancer suggests that its roots may lie in the fallopian tubes  a finding that could provide new insight in treating the deadly disease.Science Daily reports that ovarian cancer is the fifth largest cause of cancer deaths in women, as it is often detected late, or is already widespread at the time of diagnosis.Scientists from the Johns Hopkins Kimmel Cancer Center and the Dana Farber Cancer Institute in Boston examined cell samples from women with ovarian tumors and those with cancer risk factors. The analysis revealed that all the women had mutations affecting the cancer-guarding p53 gene, and had lost chromosomes containing one or both BRCA1 and BRCA2 tumor-suppressing genes.They tracked the source of the mutations to the fallopian tubes, where the cancer developed and eventually migrated to the ovaries over a 6.5-year period. Once in the ovaries, the cancer progressed more rapidly, metastasizing within two years.The team's findings will need to be further validated by additional studies, but the results provide a glimmer of hope.With such a large window from fallopian tube to ovarian cancer, scientists believe new methods should be developed to detect and treat the cancer while it's still localized in the tubes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ovarian cancer often widespread at the time of diagnosis2. Cancer mutations found to have disabled gene that guards against cancer, lost tumor suppressing genes3. Mutations originate in fallopian tube, develops into ovarian cancer over 6.5 years4. Cancer metastasizes quickly over two years once in the ovaryVOICEOVER (in English): "Ovarian cancer is the fifth largest cause of cancer deaths in women, as it is often detected late, or is already widespread at the time of diagnosis.""Scientists examined cell samples from women with ovarian tumors and those with cancer risk factors, and found that all had mutations affecting the cancer-guarding p53 gene, and two other tumor-suppressing genes." "They tracked the source of the mutations to the fallopian tubes, where the cancer developed and eventually migrated to the ovaries over a 6.5 year period.""Once in the ovaries, the cancer progressed more rapidly, metastasizing within two years."SOURCES: Johns Hopkins University, San Diego Union Tribune, Science Dailyhttps://hub.jhu.edu/2017/10/23/ovarian-cancer-starts-in-fallopian-tubes/http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/business/biotech/sd-me-ovarian-cancer-20171023-story.htmlhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/10/171023094404.htm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/24/3469046/3469046_AF4C75ED64E14ED289734E88334DFA60_171024_3469046_Ovarian_cancer_found_to_originate_in_the_fallopi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/92E/53A/92E53A2CF6B54DBAAF34BAB19439C4F7_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ovarian cancer, cancer, fallopian tube cancer, cancer cells, tumors, cysts, metastasis, deadly disease, johns hopkins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468806</guid>
      <title>A spacecraft graveyard exists in the middle of the Pacific Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENations around the world bring down old spacecraft when possible in the most remote place on Earth called Point Nemo, Business Insider reported.  Smaller satellites burn up in the atmosphere upon reentry, but larger pieces can reach Earth's surface. The spacecraft graveyard is around 1,450 nautical miles away from any land. It lies in the South Pacific in a no-man's land between Australia, New Zealand and South America, according to the BBC.  This oceanic pole of inaccessibility covers an area around 580 square miles (1,500 sq km) and is home to more than 260 dead spacecraft, mostly Russian, the BBC reported.China lost control of its Tiangong-1 space station in March 2016, which is now expected to crash into the Earth by early 2018. Since the Chinese are not in control of the spacecraft, they are currently unsure where pieces of the station will make contact. Experts won't be able to make predictions until days before Tiangong-1 is expected to break up in the atmosphere.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Space debris falling towards Point Nemo2. Smaller satellite burning up in atmosphere3. Point Nemo4. Point Nemo is about 580 square miles in sizeVOICEOVER (in English): "Nations around the world bring down old spacecraft when possible in the most remote place on Earth called Point Nemo.""Smaller satellites burn up in the atmosphere upon reentry, but larger pieces are able to reach Earth's surface." "The spacecraft graveyard is around 1,450 nautical miles away from any land. It lies in the South Pacific in a no-man's land between Australia, New Zealand and South America.""This oceanic pole of inaccessibility covers an area around 580 square miles and is home to more than 260 dead spacecraft, mostly Russian."SOURCES: Business Insider, BBChttp://www.businessinsider.com/spacecraft-cemetery-point-nemo-google-maps-2017-10http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-41683839***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 06:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/24/3468806/3468806_D4F01BB430034261A14C45069B5C413C_171024_3468806_A_spacecraft_graveyard_exists_in_the_middle_of_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C80/305/C80305EA07E641A99807FA1392CF08D9_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, spacecraft graveyard, spacecraft cemetery, satellite graveyard, Point Nemo, Pacific Ocean satellite debris]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468725</guid>
      <title>Giant balloons provide basic internet access to Puerto Rico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEGiant balloons are now delivering mobile access to hurricane-ravaged Puerto Rico, thanks to a team-up between Google's parent company Alphabet, and AT&T.According to the Federal Communications Commission, more than 68% of cell sites in Puerto Rico are still out of service as of October 20  one month after the island was devastated by Hurricane Maria.Reuters reports that to help restore communications, Project Loon has deployed giant balloons, which use the AT&T network, to provide emergency internet service on the island.The service is limited to those with LTE-enabled phones, and supports text messaging, email, and basic web browsing.The balloons float 20 kilometers up in the stratosphere, providing service to a roughly 5,000 square-kilometer area. Solar panels power daytime operations, while also charging a battery for nighttime use.Though still an experimental technology, Project Loon proved effective in early 2017, when it provided basic connectivity to flood-affected areas in Peru.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 68% of cell sites in Puerto Rico still out of service2. Project Loon balloons use AT&T network to deliver basic internet connectivity3. Those with LTE phones can text, email, browse the internet4. Solar panels power balloons in the day, charge batteries for use at nightVOICEOVER (in English): "More than 68% of cell sites in Puerto Rico are still out of service a month after the island was devastated by Hurricane Maria.""To help restore communications, Project Loon has deployed giant balloons, which use the AT&T network, to provide emergency internet service on the island.""The service is limited to those with LTE-enabled phones, and supports text messaging, email, and basic web browsing.""The balloons float 20 kilometers up in the stratosphere, providing service to a roughly 5,000 square-kilometer area. Solar panels power daytime operations, while also charging a battery for nighttime use."SOURCES: Reuters, X, Federal Communications Commissionhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-puertorico-cellular/alphabet-balloon-project-to-provide-limited-internet-in-puerto-rico-idUSKBN1CP2RNhttps://blog.x.company/turning-on-project-loon-in-puerto-rico-f3aa41ad2d7fhttp://transition.fcc.gov/Daily_Releases/Daily_Business/2017/db1020/DOC-347349A1.pdf***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 04:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/24/3468725/3468725_6A4707D22778493AB7DCAB223D071518_171024_3468725_Giant_balloons_provide_basic_internet_access_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1C7/736/1C7736F3E66B4D198E4D77356DD906B0_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, connectivity, internet access, mobile service, mobile signal, project loon, balloon signal, balloon, puerto rico, hurricane maria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469630</guid>
      <title>Google investigating Pixel 2 XL screen problems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twTechnology giant Google is investigating reports of screenburn issues with its latest smartphone. Android Central editor Alex Dobie reported how a test Google Pixel 2 XL he was sent suffered from screen burn after 7 days of use.Screen-burn usually happens after several years of use. Others have reportedly told of similar issues with the device.A mobile analyst told Reuters, that if the company finds a problem with the device, it may need to halt production of it.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of issue experienced by Android central editor2. Depiction of X-ray of device3. Depiction of Google inspecting device4. Depiction of Google halting production of deviceVOICEOVER (in English): "Android Central editor Alex Dobie reported how a test Google Pixel 2 XL he was sent suffered from screen burn-in after 7 days of use.""This is when graphics burns into the display. It usually happens after several years of use, not one week. Others have reported similar issues with the device.""Technology giant Google is investigating the problem, but a mobile analyst told Reuters, that if the company finds a problem with the device, it may need to halt production."SOURCES: Android Central, Twitter @AlexDobie Reuters, iFixit, CNET,https://www.androidcentral.com/google-pixel-2-xl-screen-burnhttps://twitter.com/alexdobiehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-pixel/googles-latest-iphone-rival-off-to-a-rocky-start-idUSKBN1CS2P6https://www.ifixit.com/Teardown/Google+Pixel+2+XL+Teardown/98093https://www.cnet.com/news/google-pixel-2-xl-review/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 08:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/25/3469630/3469630_3C3F6CEF5E094BEA8BE41EE76CE7D489_171025_3469630_Google_investigating_Pixel_2_XL_screen_problems_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6FD/107/6FD1074A9ABE44FEB1749CF671B9F996_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, pixel 2 xl, google pixel 2, pixel 2 xl screen burn, screen burn-in]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469586</guid>
      <title>Mars ideal for oxygen and carbon monoxide production, suggests study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew research suggests that the carbon-dioxide dense Martian atmosphere might be key to producing oxygen on the red planet.Researchers believe that this abundant resource, combined with the cold Martian temperature and non-thermal plasma can produce oxygen and carbon monoxide.Local production of these gases on Mars could, in theory, help sustain an outpost or even colony on the red planet, and help with the deeper exploration of the solar system.The study was published in the journal Plasma Sources Science and Technology.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Martian atmosphere2. Depiction of carbon dioxide being split into carbon monoxide and oxygen3. Depiction of astronauts on Martian colony4. Depiction of rockets flying on Martian colonyVOICEOVER (in English): "96 percent of the Martian atmosphere is made up of carbon dioxide.""Researchers believe that this abundant resource, combined with the cold Martian temperature and non-thermal plasma can produce oxygen and carbon monoxide.""Local production of these on Mars could, in theory, help sustain an outpost or even colony on the red planet and help with the deeper exploration of the solar system."SOURCES: Plasma Sources Science and Technology, Sci-News, Mirrorhttp://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1361-6595/aa8dcchttp://www.sci-news.com/physics/plasma-technology-oxygen-supply-mars-05340.htmlhttp://www.mirror.co.uk/science/mars-ideal-conditions-creating-life-11393724***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 07:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/25/3469586/3469586_47AF03ED77354A108FD59353A698E34E_171025_3469586_Mars_ideal_for_oxygen_and_carbon_monoxide_produc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F85/F53/F85F5393DBE24805BF12F5AF1D0D24D7_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, News, carbon dioxide to oxygen mars, martian colony, oxygen on mars, co2 on mars, making co2 from oxygen, decomposition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469567</guid>
      <title>China planning to launch social credit system in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEBeijing plans to launch its Social Credit System nationwide by 2020 to rate the trustworthiness of 1.3 billion people by assigning each individual a score.  The goal of the program is to "forge a public opinion environment where keeping trust is glorious. It will strengthen sincerity in government affairs, commercial sincerity, social sincerity and the construction of judicial credibility," according to the Chinese government, Wired reported. Participation currently remains voluntary, but by 2020, it will be mandatory. The Chinese Communist Party has given out eight licenses to private companies to develop systems and algorithms for a social credit score system. The two biggest projects are run by China Rapid Finance and Sesame Credit. Sesame Credit, for example, gives individuals a score between 350 and 950 points based on a private algorithm calculated from five factors: credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, personal characteristics, behavior and preferences and interpersonal relationships.Once the system becomes mandatory, people with low scores could be punished with slower internet speeds, be denied access to certain restaurants, night clubs or golf courses and restricted from traveling. Scores will also affect an individual's rental applications, ability to secure insurance or a loan, as well as social security benefits. Citizens with low scores will be forbidden from certain jobs and from applying to better schools.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Subway riders each with a social credit score2. Citizens are given an individual score based on several factors3. Citizens with low scores could have access to certain things restricted4. Citizens walking down street each with social credit scoresVOICEOVER (in English): "Beijing plans to launch its Social Credit System nationwide by 2020 to rate the trustworthiness of 1.3 billion people by assigning each individual a score.""The system will take things into account such as credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, personal characteristics, behavior and preferences and interpersonal relationships to calculate a score." "Once the system becomes mandatory, people with low scores could be punished with slower internet speeds, be denied access to certain restaurants, night clubs or golf courses and restricted from traveling.""Scores will also affect an individual's rental applications, ability to secure insurance or a loan, as well as social security benefits." SOURCES: Wiredhttp://www.wired.co.uk/article/chinese-government-social-credit-score-privacy-invasion***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 06:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/25/3469567/3469567_55E0BE21A854483890A6E7506F383ED7_171025_3469567_China_planning_to_launch_social_credit_system_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2AE/1A1/2AE1A1545B76435F86F858D07F91D54A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China Social Credit System, China state surveillance, China social credit score]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470418</guid>
      <title>Study shows RNA editing method</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists have found a way to edit from the genetic blueprint inside DNA without altering the molecule itself, according to new research.The study, published in the journal Science, details how DNA instructions directed at proteins can be chemically altered via edits to information in the RNA. The DNA remains unchanged, but proteins build cells based on the edited instructions.The method is not ready for human trials but it could be used to help sufferers of degenerative diseases such as amyotrophic lateral sclerosis in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of DNA, RNA and proteins2. RNA being identified3. DNA information being edited inside the RNA4. Proteins constructing cellVOICEOVER (in English): 'DNA directs protein on how to build cells via RNA.""A new study, published in the journal Science, details how DNA instructions can be chemically altered via edits to information in the RNA." "The DNA remains unchanged, while proteins build cells based on the edited instructions."SOURCES: Science, Los Angeles Times, Engadget, Reuters http://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2017/10/24/science.aaq0180.fullhttp://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-rna-editing-repair-20171025-htmlstory.htmlhttps://www.engadget.com/2017/10/25/new-crispr-alters-rna-gene-editing/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-gene-editing/u-s-scientists-unveil-powerful-new-tools-to-fix-genetic-faults-idUSKBN1CU2R0***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 09:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/26/3470418/3470418_9C3F14B0C6154E479F1AE25CBF9EB465_171026_3470418_Study_shows_RNA_editing_method_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C9F/1C3/C9F1C36CCE684015B7B15A94AF3DE734_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dna, broad institute, dna changes, changing dna, cell manipulation, rna repair, rna editing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470373</guid>
      <title>US Navy sends 3rd aircraft carrier to Pacific</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe aircraft carrier USS Nimitz arrived in the Pacific on Tuesday, bringing the number of carriers to three now operating in the region. The carrier and its accompanying strike group of destroyers, cruisers and submarines has joined the U.S. Navy's 7th Fleet area of operations, the Navy said news releases, CNN reported. The Nimitz now joins the USS Ronald Reagan, which is stationed in Japan year-round, and the USS Theodore Roosevelt, which is currently far east of Japan, according to Business Insider. The Navy reported that the Nimitz just finished three months of in the Middle East battling ISIS, launching 1,322 sorties with 903 pieces of ordnance dropped, according to Military.com.Navy spokeswoman Lt. Mary Walsh described the carrier's activities as standard, and said that the Nimitz would only be in the region temporarily, Military.com reported.  The USS Roosevelt is expected to eventually take the Nimitz's place in the Middle East, according to CNN. Pyongyang hasn't launched a missile in over a month, however tensions still remain high in the region.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The USS Nimitz sailing through the water2. The US now has 3 aircraft carriers in the Pacific3. The USS Nimitz was previously out in the Middle East4. Aircraft launching from the USS NimitzVOICEOVER (in English): "The aircraft carrier USS Nimitz arrived in the Pacific on Tuesday, bringing the number of carriers to three now operating in the region." "The carrier now joins the USS Ronald Reagan, which is stationed in Japan year-round, and the USS Theodore Roosevelt, which is currently far east of Japan.""According to the Navy, the Nimitz just finished three months of in the Middle East battling ISIS, launching 1,322 sorties and dropping 903 pieces of ordnance.""The Navy described the carrier's activities as standard, and said that the Nimitz would only be in the region temporarily."SOURCES: CNN, Business Insider, Military.comhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/10/25/politics/us-navy-three-aircraft-carriers-pacific/index.htmlhttp://www.businessinsider.com/us-navy-third-aircraft-carrier-north-korea-pacific-2017-10http://www.military.com/daily-news/2017/10/25/rare-show-force-navy-now-three-carriers-pacific.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 08:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/26/3470373/3470373_364A17E4C8F94AB5AFE40EAEB280C362_171026_3470373_US_Navy_sends_3rd_aircraft_carrier_to_Pacific_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D8B/CA2/D8BCA2D3925249D5B0EF58E813E9C769_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, North Korea, US aircraft carriers, USS Nimitz, USS Nimitz Pacific Ocean, USS Ronald Reagan, USS Theodore Roosevelt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470262</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia announces $500 billion mega-city plan that spans three countries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Saudi Arabian government says it plans to build a $500 billion mega-city that stretches into Jordan and Egypt, and is completely powered by renewable energy. Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman announced the project on Tuesday at the Future Investment Initiative conference in Riyadh, Business Insider reported.  The project is called NEOM and will measure 10,230 square miles, which is 33 times larger than New York City, according to Business Insider. The $500 billion dollars will come from the Saudi government, its sovereign wealth fund and investors, according to the statement released at the conference, Bloomberg reported. One of the main goals of NEOM will be to diversify Saudi Arabia's economy in an attempt to move it beyond oil. The mega-city will focus on industries such as energy and water, biotechnology, food, advanced manufacturing and entertainment, Business Insider reported. No master plans have been released yet as to what the city will look like.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of NEOM  2. Depiction of futuristic city3. Saudi Arabia attempting to move beyond oil4. NEOM will focus on industries like energy, water, biotech, food, advanced manufacturing and entertainmentVOICEOVER (in English): "The Saudi Arabian government says it plans to build a $500 billion mega-city that stretches into Jordan and Egypt, and is completely powered by renewable energy." "The project is called NEOM and will measure 10,230 square miles, which is 33 times larger than New York City.""One of the main goals of NEOM will be to diversify Saudi Arabia's economy in an attempt to move it beyond oil." "The mega-city will focus on industries such as energy and water, biotechnology, food, advanced manufacturing and entertainment."SOURCES: Bloomberg, Business Insiderhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-10-24/saudi-arabia-to-build-new-mega-city-on-country-s-north-coasthttp://www.businessinsider.com/saudi-arabia-mega-city-jordan-egypt-oil-2017-10***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/26/3470262/3470262_FC8CE32DC91E49EF9A9621F1652BF605_171026_3470262_Saudi_Arabia_announces__500_billion_mega_city_pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/081/8B4/0818B44069BC486CBCBEAA720793FFDD_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Saudi Arabia mega-city, NEOM mega-city, NEOM project, NEOM city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470222</guid>
      <title>Russia preparing to test new Satan-2 ballistic missile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONERussia is preparing to test-launch its latest nuclear-armed intercontinental ballistic missile, which it claims can get through America's defense shield. The RS-28 Sarmat, or Satan-2, weighs over 100 metric tonnes, with Russian state-linked media claiming it has a 10,000-km range, according to the Independent.Moscow says the Satan-2 is capable of destroying an area the size of Texas.The RS-28 Sarmat is equipped with multiple hypersonic warheads  MIRVs  to help it evade missile defense systems. The Russian government says the new missile can carry a payload of up to 15 warheads. The first test-launches are slated to be held at the Plesetsk testing ground in western Russia by the end of the year.   Russia is planning for the RS-28 to enter service by the start of the next decade as a part of its ongoing push to modernize its nuclear arsenal. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. An RS-28 Sarmat launching2. The RS-28 is capable of destroying an area the size of Texas3. RS-28 MIRV warhead4. RS-28 can carry a payload of up to 15 warheadsVOICEOVER (in English): "The RS-28 Sarmat, or Satan-2, weighs over 100 metric tonnes, with Russian state-linked media claiming it has a 10,000-km range.""Moscow says the Satan-2 is capable of destroying an area the size of Texas.""The RS-28 Sarmat is equipped with multiple hypersonic warheads  MIRVs  to help it evade missile defense systems." "Russia says the new missile can carry a payload of up to 15 thermonuclear warheads." SOURCES: The Independent http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/russia-icbm-test-nuclear-weapons-rs-28-sarmat-defence-systems-plesetsk-cosmodrome-a8016696.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 04:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/26/3470222/3470222_9B21393F793546A492ED312037692FD2_171026_3470222_Russia_preparing_to_test_new_Satan_2_ballistic_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ECF/16B/ECF16B09EE7846E19837B1699D3C0DE2_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Russia, ballistic missile, Russia Satan-2 missile, ICBMs, MIRVs, RS-28 Sarmat missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3471087</guid>
      <title>'DNA spray' used on fleeing suspects to help track them down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEPolice in the UK are deploying a chemical liquid that clings to clothes and skin in order to crack down on moped-riding bandits.According to SelectaDNA, officers can spray fleeing offenders with a tagging spray, which marks them and their vehicles with an invisible dye.The spray contains DNA code, with each can bearing a unique chemical signature.The odorless liquid can only be seen under UV light. It cannot be scrubbed off, and can remain on a person's clothes and skin for months.The spray not only helps identify suspects, but also serves to effectively link them to their specific crime.According to the Pontefract and Castleford Express, one 18-year-old has already been charged and sentenced with the help of the tagging spray. At least two other teens have been arrested for moped-related crimes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fleeing criminals sprayed with DNA tagging spray2. Each spray can contains specific DNA3. Odorless, colorless spray detected using UV light, cannot be removed4. Suspects can later be identified and tied to a specific crime using sprayVOICEOVER (in English): "Officers can spray fleeing offenders with a tagging spray, which marks them and their vehicles with an invisible dye.""The spray contains DNA code, with each can bearing a unique chemical signature.""The odorless liquid can only be seen under UV light. It cannot be scrubbed off, and can remain on a person's clothes and skin for months.""The spray not only helps identify suspects, but also serves to effectively link them to their specific crime."SOURCES: Evening Standard, Huddersfield Daily Examiner, SelectaDNA, Pontefract and Castleford Expresshttps://www.standard.co.uk/news/crime/police-trial-chemical-spray-in-bid-to-clamp-down-on-surge-of-mopedenabled-crime-in-london-a3668081.htmlhttp://www.examiner.co.uk/news/west-yorkshire-news/new-dna-spray-help-police-13813800https://www.selectadna.co.uk/news/uk-police-first-dna-spray-secures-arrest-of-scrambler-bike-criminalshttp://www.pontefractandcastlefordexpress.co.uk/news/teen-sentenced-following-police-s-first-use-of-dna-tagging-spray-1-8823733***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 07:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/27/3471087/3471087_3C05DCE5C6DE494896FEC78A933DC4A3_171027_3471087__DNA_spray__used_on_fleeing_suspects_to_help_tra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D46/BAE/D46BAE1272324057A93259BD3D869BE2_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dna tagging spray, dna spray, selectaDNA, dna, dna marker, criminals, crime, anti theft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3471041</guid>
      <title>India to send rover to the moon in 2018</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Indian Space Research Organization has announced plans to send a rover to the moon early next year, nearly a decade after its first lunar journey met with mixed success.First Post reports that the spacecraft for India's Chandrayaan-2 moon mission is comprised of an orbiter, a lander, and a rover, which will first slingshot around Earth before being going into lunar orbit.The lander will attempt a controlled or soft landing near the moon's south pole, while the orbiter travels around the moon.Once on the surface, the lander will take thermal measurements and deploy the six-wheeled rover to explore the lunar terrain.Among the things the mission will pay close attention to are abrasive particles known as lunar dust, which pose a significant challenge to human colonization of the moon.The Chandrayaan-2 will be carried into space by the GSLV Mark II rocket, and is scheduled to launch from an island in the Bay of Bengal in March 2018.India will carry out the final testing phase for the spacecraft in the coming weeks. The program's budget for the mission is relatively small, at only 93 million dollars.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chandrayaan-2 spacecraft components2. Lander touches down on Moon's south pole; orbiter goes around Moon3. Lander to take thermal measurements of surface, deploy rover to explore terrain4. Chandrayaan-2 set for March 2018 launchVOICEOVER (in English): "The spacecraft for India's Chandrayaan-2 moon mission is comprised of an orbiter, a lander, and a rover, which will first slingshot around Earth before being going into lunar orbit.""The lander will attempt a controlled or soft landing near the moon's south pole, while the orbiter travels around the moon.""Once on the surface, the lander will take thermal measurements and deploy the six-wheeled rover to explore the lunar terrain.""The Chandrayaan-2 will be carried into space by the GSLV Mark II rocket, and is scheduled to launch from an island in the Bay of Bengal in March 2018."SOURCES: Nature, First Posthttps://www.nature.com/news/india-gears-up-for-second-moon-mission-1.22870http://www.firstpost.com/india/isro-is-going-to-launch-the-chandrayaan-2-mission-on-a-gslv-mkii-in-march-2018-4089655.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 06:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/27/3471041/3471041_A9DA16DAC3D548D4B0AFA5C8E5126711_171027_3471041_India_to_send_rover_to_the_moon_in_2018_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/81D/167/81D167062D90484BAB8A3D5CEF2A02DB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, moon mission, india moon rover, india moon mission, chandrayaan, chandrayaan 2, moon rover, lunar mission, india space program, ISRO]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470996</guid>
      <title>First European underwater diner planned for Norway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEDesign firm Snhetta this week unveiled concept art for Europe's first subsea restaurant on the Norwegian coast.Aptly dubbed Under, Inhabitat reports that the establishment will provide viewers with a panoramic view of the seabed.Diners will also be able eat locally procured seafood while taking in the view of underwater life.Under is said to be heated via thermal technology from the seabed, and will also double as a marine research center.Under set to open in early 2019, reported CNN.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of restaurant from outside2. Depiction of restaurant underwater3. Depiction of restaurant's underwater window4. Depiction of restaurant's exteriorVOICEOVER (in English): "Design firm Snhetta this week unveiled concept art for Europe's first subsea restaurant on the Norwegian coast.""It's concrete shell looks like a giant half-sunken cinder block.""Aptly dubbed Under, Inhabitat reports that the establishment will provide viewers with a panoramic view of the seabed.""Diners will also be able eat locally procured seafood while taking in the view of underwater life.""Under is said to be heated via thermal energy gathered from the seabed. It will also double as a marine research center."SOURCES: https://inhabitat.com/is-it-green-concrete/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 05:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/27/3470996/3470996_FE1D37B24F60477FBC4882D5F21AC533_171027_3470996_First_European_underwater_diner_planned_for_Norw_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C98/7E8/C987E84B55614C71B054223B74FA0802_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, underwater restaurant, underwater dining, subsea diner, underwater diner, unique dining experiences]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3473028</guid>
      <title>Experimental vaccine targets HIV's protective shield</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEUniversity of Maryland and Duke University researchers have designed a new vaccine that was able to stimulate an immune response against HIV's protective shield.According to the study published in the journal Cell Chemical Biology, HIV virus cells are covered with a protective protein called GP120, which itself is covered by a sugar shield to help bolster its defenses.Some infected individuals who can keep the virus at bay without medication often have have antibodies that attack the protein.There has been little success in creating a similar vaccine, because the sugars found in the shield resemble sugars in the human body. It's also difficult to engineer antibodies that can be effective against the multiple strains of HIV, which frequently mutate.Using a synthetic chemistry method, scientists have now designed a vaccine combining a gp120 fragment and a sugar molecule, and tested it on HIV-infected rabbits.The vaccine prompted the rabbits' immune systems to produce antibodies that physically bound to gp120 found in four dominant HIV strains.It takes roughly two years to build immunity against HIV, so despite sticking to the virus, the antibodies weren't able to prevent further infection.But the vaccine's ability to induce a strong immune response in a short amount of time is encouraging, and researchers believe further studies can produce a vaccine that can ultimately neutralize the deadly virus.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Protective protein-sugar shield around HIV2. HIV-immune individuals found with antibodies that attack gp120 protein3. Protein-sugar vaccine injected into rabbits4. Rabbits produced antibodies that bound to gp120VOICEOVER (in English): "HIV virus cells are covered with a protective protein called gp120, which itself is covered by a sugar shield, to help bolster its defenses.""Some infected individuals who can keep the virus at bay without medication often have have antibodies that attack the protein."semble sugars in the human body.""Using a synthetic chemistry method, scientists have now designed a vaccine combining a gp120 fragment and a sugar molecule, and tested it on HIV-infected rabbits."The vaccine prompted the rabbits' immune systems to produce antibodies that physically bound to gp120 found in four dominant HIV strains."SOURCES: Cell Chemical Biology, University of Marylandhttp://www.cell.com/cell-chemical-biology/fulltext/S2451-9456(17)30331-8https://cmns.umd.edu/news-events/features/4011***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 10:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/30/3473028/3473028_B9EC75FCC4EF4ABDA784704CBE0746DA_171030_3473028_Experimental_vaccine_targets_HIV_s_protective_sh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B62/7BC/B627BC1D13394187A26B6B728D91656D_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hiv vaccine, hiv cure, aids cure, aids vaccine, hiv, aids, gp120, hiv shield, hiv sugar shield, university of maryland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472952</guid>
      <title>What is superfetation?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA California woman reportedly conceived while pregnant in a extremely case of superfetation.During pregnancy, a woman's body stops producing eggs but in some extremely rare cases eggs are still produced after one has been fertilized.This is called superfetation. In reported cases, this is where a woman conceives another child while already pregnant.Unlike a twin pregnancy, superfetation is when two fetuses grow separately inside the same woman at different rates.In 2009, a doctor speaking to ABC in 2009 about a case of superfetation, said she could only find 10 cases of it in medical literature.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Egg production while pregnant2. Sperm fertilizing egg3. Inside the womb4. Statistics on superfetationVOICEOVER (in English): "During pregnancy, a woman's body stops producing eggs but in some extremely rare cases eggs are still produced after one has been fertilized." "This is called superfetation. In reported cases, this is where a woman conceives another child while already pregnant."  "Unlike a twin pregnancy, superfetation is when two fetuses grow separately inside the same woman at different rates." "In 2009, a doctor speaking to ABC in 2009 about a case of superfetation, said she could only find 10 cases of it in medical literature."SOURCES: New York Post, Sacramento Bee (Washington Post), ABChttp://nypost.com/2017/10/25/i-rented-out-my-womb-and-they-took-my-own-son/http://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article181563751.htmlhttp://abcnews.go.com/Health/ReproductiveHealth/pregnant-woman-pregnant-julia-grovenburg-conceives-consecutively/story?id=8656369***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 08:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/30/3472952/3472952_8827129B968D45A692938182D76F7A2F_171030_3472952_What_is_superfetation__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/00A/397/00A3970DFB7F41A8B7C0A5C75B8DBAC0_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, superfetation, what is is superfetation, pregnant while pregnant, getting pregnant while pregnant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472912</guid>
      <title>Paralyzed man stands again after experimental epidural treatment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA man paralyzed following a serious motorcycle injury has regained the ability to stand and move his legs after receiving an experimental epidural treatment. Andrew Meas was paralyzed from the chest down after his spine was broken at the sixth and seventh cervical vertebrae in a accident nearly 10 years ago, Newsweek reported. Meas has spent four years in physical rehabilitation, but has also been receiving an experimental treatment called spinal cord epidural stimulation (scES) from a research team at the University of Louisville, Quartz reported.    The device sends electrical signals to motor neurons telling them to move. Meas was one of four patients to receive the implant. At the end of the study, Meas was able to move his legs, stand on both feet or one foot entirely on his own. The other three patients did regain some leg movement, but not to the degree Meas experienced. The results from the study, published in the Oct. 26 Scientific Reports, show that the nervous system may be more resilient than previously thought. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Meas was paralyzed from the chest down after a motorcycle accident2. Meas receiving the epidural treatment3. The device sends electrical signals to motor neurons4. Meas can now move his legs, stand on both feet or one foot all on his ownVOICEOVER (in English): "Andrew Meas was paralyzed from the chest down after his spine was broken at the sixth and seventh cervical vertebrae in a motorcycle accident nearly 10 years ago.""Meas has spent four years in physical rehabilitation, but has also been receiving an experimental treatment called spinal cord epidural stimulation.""The device sends electrical signals to motor neurons telling them to move." "At the end of the study, Meas was able to move his legs, stand on both feet or one foot entirely on his own."SOURCES: Scientific Reports, Newsweek, Quartz https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-14003-whttp://www.newsweek.com/paralyzed-man-stands-moves-own-spinal-cord-repair-693579https://qz.com/1113210/scientists-helped-a-paralyzed-man-walk-again-with-an-experimental-epidural-therapy/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 08:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/30/3472912/3472912_9A28F484889E47949C4C01C40DE227D8_171030_3472912_Paralyzed_man_stands_again_after_experimental_ep_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0B7/D7D/0B7D7DC0F33741268CE562DE7B2AACF9_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, paralyzed, experimental epidural treatment, spinal cord epidural stimulation, experimental treatment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472862</guid>
      <title>Research shows Yellowstone Caldera the result of two super eruptions, not one</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETwo super eruptions made the iconic Yellowstone Caldera what it is today not one, according to new research. Scientists analysed samples of shell sediment and volcanic ash from the Santa Barbara Basin. From these they were able to determine that the Yellowstone Caldera was formed by two volcanic eruptions 170 years apart.Each eruption was so powerful that it lowered the temperature of the planet and altered the climate, New Atlas reported. These two volcanic winters reportedly took place just as Earth was recovering from an ice age hundreds of thousands of years ago.The findings were presented last week the annual meeting of the Geological Society of America. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of area samples were found2. Depiction of eruption3. Depiction of Earth temporarily cooling4. Depiction of ice age environmentVOICEOVER (in English): "The researchers analysed samples of shell sediment and volcanic ash from the Santa Barbara Basin.""From these they were able to determine that the Yellowstone Caldera was formed by two volcanic eruptions 170 years apart.""Each eruption was so powerful that it lowered the temperature of the planet and altered the climate.""These two volcanic winters reportedly took place just as Earth was recovering from an ice age hundreds of thousands of years ago."SOURCES: New Atlas, Geological Society of Americahttps://newatlas.com/yellowstone-supervolcano-eruption-caldera/51931/http://www.geosociety.org/GSA/News/Releases/GSA/News/pr/2017/17-60.aspx***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 07:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/30/3472862/3472862_F6CED71BC236488791BBE3E47F6C3E79_171030_3472862_Research_shows_Yellowstone_Caldera_the_result_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2F6/D88/2F6D8837F2D04447AF928C47CCF12FCC_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, yellowstone caldera, super eruption, mega eruption, volcano, ice age]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472857</guid>
      <title>Stanford's underground fibre optic earthquake lab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers are using miles of optical cable beneath the Stanford university campus to observe earthquakes.According to a news release from the university, scientists used laser interrogators from company Optasense to record seismic activity on the cables.Stanford Geophysics professor Biondo Biondi says every meter of cable in the 3-mile long network acts as a sensor. "We can continuously listen to  and hear well  the Earth using pre-existing optical fibers that have been deployed for telecom purposes," Biondi said.The technology could one day be used by civil engineers to design buildings more capable of withstanding earthquakes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of cable being constructed2. Depiction of network3. Depiction of sensors observing earthquake4. Depiction of technology being used by civil engineers.VOICEOVER (in English): "Stanford researchers are using miles of optical fiber cable installed beneath their university campus in a figure-8 shape to observe earthquakes.""They used laser interrogators from company Optasense to record and listen to seismic activity on the cables.""The technology could one day be used by civil engineers to design buildings more capable of withstanding earthquakes."SOURCES: Stanford University, Stamen Design, Victoria and Albert Museum https://news.stanford.edu/2017/10/19/building-billion-sensors-quake-monitor-optical-fibers/https://stamen.com/work/big-glass-microphone/https://www.vam.ac.uk/bigglassmic***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/30/3472857/3472857_98D38D48F0D8400B9248894AB04BF634_171030_3472857_Stanford_s_underground_fibre_optic_earthquake_la_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AC5/7C8/AC57C8A12DC1479892B28168CBE44983_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, earthquake detection, earthquake early warning, stanford, the big glass, stamen, stanford earthquake, fibre optic cables]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3473732</guid>
      <title>United Airlines begins longest nonstop flight from U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEUnited Airlines has launched the longest nonstop flight from the U.S. from its Los Angeles hub to Singapore. The 14,000-km trip takes 17 hours, 55 minutes to Singapore and 15 hours, 15 minutes coming back, according to Forbes. The flight will operate once a day on a Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner with 252 seats combined in Economy, Economy Plus and Business. The world's two longest routes belong to Qatar Airways' Doha-Auckland route at 14,536 km and Emirates' Dubai-Auckland route at 14,193 km. In terms of scheduled flying time though, the new United route will be the longest, due to the strong headwinds on the westbound portion of the flight, USA Today reported. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The flight path from LAX to Singapore2. The United Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner flying3. The flight distances of the 3 longest commercial flight routes 4. The United flight has the longest flight time due to strong headwinds on the westbound routeVOICEOVER (in English): "United Airlines has launched the longest nonstop flight from the U.S. from its Los Angeles hub to Singapore." "The 14,000 km trip takes 17 hours, 55 minutes to Singapore and 15 hours, 15 minutes coming back.""The world's two longest routes belong to Qatar Airways' Doha-Auckland route at 14,536 km and Emirates' Dubai-Auckland route at 14,193 km." "In terms of scheduled flying time though, the new United route will be the longest, due to the strong headwinds on the westbound portion of the flight." SOURCES: Forbes, USA Today https://www.forbes.com/sites/martinrivers/2017/10/29/united-airlines-launches-longest-nonstop-flight-from-us-soil/#4c17b920669chttps://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/todayinthesky/2017/10/30/uniteds-new-18-hour-flight-longest-ever-u-s-airline/812690001/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/31/3473732/3473732_2A64982107014B828E229B25730D6A6F_171031_3473732_United_Airlines_begins_longest_nonstop_flight_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2A9/D43/2A9D438FDFA74D5BBD9F25986805A640_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, United Airlines, United Airlines longest nonstop flight, long haul flights, Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3473623</guid>
      <title>Bloodhound Super Sonic Car clocks 210 miles per hour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Bloodhound Super Sonic Car performed its very first public run last week, clocking in a speed of 210 miles per hour, reported the BBC.When complete, the car will be fitted with two engines. One of which is a jet engine that is also on the Eurofighter aircraft.  This can clock in speeds of 650 miles per hour.The second is a rocket engine. This is expected to help it travel at over 1,000 miles per hour.The car is also comprised of over 3,500 parts, many of which are tailor-made.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of car travelling at 210 mph2. Depiction of car travelling at 650 mph3. Depiction of car travelling at 1,000 mph 4. Depiction of car partsVOICEOVER (in English): The Bloodhound Super Sonic Car performed its very first public run last week, clocking in a speed of 210 miles per hour.When complete, the car will be fitted with  two engines. One of which is a jet engine that is same as the one found on the Eurofighter aircraft. This can clock in speeds of 650 miles per hour.The second of which will be a rocket engine. This is expected to help it travel at over 1,000 miles per hour.The car is also comprised of over 3,500 parts, many of which are tailor-made.SOURCES: Bloodhound Super Sonic, BBC, http://www.bloodhoundssc.comhttp://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-41747995***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 07:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/31/3473623/3473623_481E5F68EC0C4B47821D17F55469D1A1_171031_3473623_Bloodhound_Super_Sonic_Car_clocks_210_miles_per__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9D3/1C4/9D31C4F180AA49A09ECD2594E40FDD84_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, worlds fastest car, bloodhound ssc, bloodhound super sonic, driving at 1000 mph, 1000 mile per hour car, fastest car ever made]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3473469</guid>
      <title>Walmart to expand use of robots in stores</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEWalmart is enlisting automated help to improve out-of-stock issues and mislabeled items.Reuters reports that the robots are equipped with a camera and lights tha scan the aisles to check stocks, and identify mislabeled or wrongly-priced items.The robot passes the data to human employees, who then restock the shelves and fix any errors.The retail giant stresses that the machines will not replace staffers, and are merely there to help them.The robots are 50 percent more productive than human employees at shelf-scanning, and are capable of doing it faster and more accurately.Walmart has been trialing robots in California, Pennsylvania, and Arkansas for the past three years, and will be expanding to 50 more locations in January 2018.So if you live in El Paso, Fort Worth, or Jacksonville, it seems the robots are coming.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Walmart robots scan shelves to identify out of stock, missing, or misplaced items2. Robots pass data to store employees, who restock shelves, fix mistakes3. Robots can scan shelves more quickly, and accurately4. Walmart to put robots in more than 50 U.S. storesVOICEOVER (in English): "Walmart robots are equipped with a camera and lights that scan the aisles to check stocks, and identify mislabeled or wrongly-priced items.""The robot passes the data to human employees, who then restock the shelves and fix any errors.""The robots are 50 percent more productive than human employees at shelf-scanning, and are capable of doing it faster and more accurately.""Walmart has been trialing robots in California, Pennsylvania, and Arkansas for the past three years, and will be expanding to 50 more locations in January 2018."SOURCES: Reutershttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-walmart-robots/wal-marts-new-robots-scan-shelves-to-restock-items-faster-idUSKBN1CV1N4***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 04:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/10/31/3473469/3473469_96FCCF7B2C72484BA7FAFF57F3A9AC40_171031_3473469_US_WALMART_ROBOTS_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8D7/D81/8D7D8144147D457F82D17819A00D0BF8_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,walmart robots,walmart,robot scanner,shelf scanner,empty shelves,out of stock]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
