<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>4046424</guid>
      <title>U.K. switches on giant floating power plant with twin turbines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCNBC reports that a massive tidal turbine that can generate 2 megawatts of electricity has started to feed power to the U.K.'s grid. Located in the waters off the Orkney islands, the giant turbine, called O2, is about the size of a Boeing 747 and weighs 680 metric tons. The O2 turbine floats like a boat and can be towed by small tugboats to any position, where it is then connected to anchors and a thick electrical cable that feeds its power to the grid. Next, the O2 lowers its giant arms that support two 20-meter-long turbine blades. As sea water has more than 800 times the density of air, these blades produce more electricity than similarly sized wind-turbine blades produce  enough to power 2,000 U.K. homes per year. One of the biggest problems with power turbines is that they need their parts maintained regularly. The O2 solves this problem by having its arms attached to massive hydraulic hinges that can easily lift the blades up to the surface for easy access. Another great advantage of tidal systems like the O2 is that tides are very predictable, compared to wind and sunshine.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show globe turning and zooming into location in Orkney Islands2. Compare size of O2 turbine to 747 airliner, then show O2 towed into position3. Show underwater view as O2 is anchored and connected to thick power cable4. Underwater view as O2 lowers its 2 big arms with 2 big turbine blades5. Show above water view as O2's huge hinges engage to raise its 2 big arms6. View form above, show tide streaming fast around O2 bladesVOICEOVER (in English): "CNBC reports that a massive tidal turbine that can generate 2 megawatts of electricity has started to feed power to the U.K.'s grid.""Located in the waters off the Orkney islands, the giant turbine, called O2, is about the size of a Boeing 747 and weighs 680 metric tons.""The O2 turbine floats like a boat and can be towed by small tugboats to any position, where it is then connected to anchors and a thick electrical cable that feeds its power to the grid.""Next, the O2 lowers its giant arms that support two 20-meter-long turbine blades.""As sea water has more than 800 times the density of air, these blades produce more electricity than similarly sized wind-turbine blades produce  enough to power 2,000 U.K. homes per year.""One of the biggest problems with power turbines is that they need their parts maintained regularly.""The O2 solves this problem by having its arms attached to massive hydraulic hinges that can easily lift the blades up to the surface for easy access.""Another great advantage of tidal systems like the O2 is that tides are very predictable, compared to wind and sunshine."SOURCES: CNBC, BBChttps://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/07/28/worlds-most-powerful-tidal-turbine-starts-to-export-power-to-grid-.htmlhttps://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-north-east-orkney-shetland-57991351***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 04:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/08/02/4046424/4046424_B0F9C982CCD44D0F98E2460522696CC0_210802_4046424_U_K__switches_on_giant_floating_power_plant_with_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fall of warness, orkney, islands, o2, orbital marine, power, marine, tidal, turbine, energy, alternative, sustainable, renewable, tide, electricity, largest, giant, electrical, grid, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046439</guid>
      <title>UNESCO honors ancient solar calendar made of 13 huge towers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Guardian reports that the oldest solar observatory in the Americas has been awarded UNESCO World Heritage status and dubbed "a masterpiece of human creative genius." Chankillo is a 2,300-year-old archeological ruin that lies in a desert valley in northern Peru.Its most famous features are 13 stone towers built around 220 B.C. The towers functioned as a calendar that used the rising and setting arcs of the sun to mark equinoxes and solstices. It was also used to define the precise time of year to within one or two days.The site includes an imposing triple-walled hilltop complex, known as the Fortified Temple. Archeologists believe the site was likely abandoned in the early first century A.D. and was largely forgotten until the 19th century. No human remains have been found at the ruins and little is known about the culture. Chankillo program director Ivan Ghezzi says the site was built at a time of great conflict and social strife, and the Chankillo society was the product of a process of "Balkanization" that followed the collapse of the even older Chavín culture.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show workers restoring Chankillo's ancient towers, zoom out to show scale of towers2. Globe map rotates and zoom to location on globe, show side view of towers3. Show 2 Chankillo-era people watching sun rising behind 13 towers of Chankillo4. Show fortified temple, then show temple and towers on map, adding observation point5. Zoom to observation point, show view from point as sun rises in each notch over year,6. … adding dates of each notch's sunrise date, then show return notches from other side as sun returns from December solstice to June solsticeVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that the oldest solar observatory in the Americas has been awarded UNESCO World Heritage status and dubbed 'a masterpiece of human creative genius.'""Chankillo is a 2,300-year-old archeological ruin that lies in a desert valley in northern Peru.""Its most famous features are 13 stone towers built around 220 B.C. The towers functioned as a calendar that used the rising and setting arcs of the sun to mark equinoxes and solstices. It was also used to define the precise time of year to within one or two days.""The site includes an imposing triple-walled hilltop complex, known as the Fortified Temple.""Archeologists believe the site was likely abandoned in the early first century A.D. and was largely forgotten until the 19th century.""No human remains have been found at the ruins and little is known about the culture.""Chankillo program director Ivan Ghezzi says the site was built at a time of great conflict and social strife, and the Chankillo society was the product of a process of 'Balkanization' that followed the collapse of the even older Chavín culture."SOURCES: The Guardian, Al Jazeerahttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/28/chankillo-oldest-solar-observatory-in-the-americas-awarded-unesco-world-heritage-statushttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/7/29/peruvian-solar-observatory-thai-forest-park-in-un-heritage-list***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 05:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/08/03/4046439/4046439_E8F89C0C475549F984768701B9A6146F_210803_4046439_UNESCO_honors_ancient_solar_calendar_made_of_13__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Oldest, solar, observatory, calendar, chavin, Chankillo, peru, unesco, world, heritage, site, 13 towers, temple fortress, fortified temple, archaeologist, archaeology, archeology, culture, ruins, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
