<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3970307</guid>
      <title>Astronomers say they might have found a new 'minimoon' orbiting Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Earth's busy orbit is occupied by space junk, nearly 5,000 artificial satellites, the Moon and now a possible temporary resident 'minimoon' called 2020 CD3. Live Science reports that the University of Arizona's Steward Observatory first spotted the captive space rock.Citing a NASA astronomer working with the university, the outlet reports that the space rock is 1.9 meters to 3.5 meters in diameter. Light reflection from the possible minimoon is consistent with carbon-rich asteroids. Other observatories have yet to confirm the sighting.It is not uncommon for Earth to capture temporary natural satellites, but most are too small to be detected. This minimoon has been orbiting our planet for close to three years and it is expected to leave in April to continue its journey around the Sun.Citing a study published in Arxiv.org, the outlet reports there is a possibility that the minimoon would be recaptured by the moon's gravity well and become a natural lunar satellite, which is a theoretical class of objects astronomers think might exist.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Possible sighting of minimoon 2020 CD32. 2020 CD3 is probably a carbon-rich asteroid about 1.9 meters to 3.5 meters in diameter3. The object is believed to have been in orbit for three years and might leave in April 4. The minimoon could become a natural satellite of the moonVOICEOVER (in English): "The Earth's busy orbit is occupied by space junk, nearly 5,000 artificial satellites, the Moon and now a possible temporary resident 'minimoon' called 2020 CD3. Live Science reports that the University of Arizona's Steward Observatory first spotted the captive space rock.""Citing a NASA astronomer working with the university, the outlet reports that the space rock is 1.9 meters to 3.5 meters in diameter. Light reflection from the possible minimoon is consistent with carbon-rich asteroids. Other observatories have yet to confirm the sighting.""It is not uncommon for Earth to capture temporary natural satellites, but most are too small to be detected. This minimoon has been orbiting our planet for close to three years and it is expected to leave in April to continue its journey around the Sun.""Citing a study published in Arxiv.org, the outlet reports there is a possibility that the minimoon would be recaptured by the moon's gravity well and become a natural lunar satellite, which is a theoretical class of objects astronomers think might exist."SOURCES: LiveScience.com. Space.com (YouTube)https://www.livescience.com/mini-moon-discovered.htmlhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DpsuIHzk1Y8***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/02/3970307/3970307_0E7931C9FDD74DDB93CD62479D520103_200302_3970307_Astronomers_say_they_might_have_found_a_new__min_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, minimoon, mini-moon, natural satellite, second moon, captured object, asteroid, 2020 CD3, University of Arizona, Steward Observatory, Catalina Sky Survey, U.S., space, science, astronomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970178</guid>
      <title>Antarctic research center begins construction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA British architectural firm has designed a research center called the Discovery Building for the British Arctic Survey research team in Antarctica.  Construction began on January 30, 2020.The building's exterior will be made with metal panels that are pale blue in color to prevent high ultraviolet rays from causing degradation to the structure, according to a press release from the architectural firm. The color is also a reference to the Antarctic sky.The Discovery Building will also have a wind deflector along its roofline that will be used to deflect cold air in the Antarctic so that the wind will travel down the structure's facade. This will help to minimize snow accumulation around the building.The structure also consists of a control tower from its roof. The tower will provide a 360° view of the area.The Discovery Building will also contain a medical facility, offices and recreational spaces among other facilities.The structure is expected to be completed in 2023.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New research center2.  What the building's exterior will be made out of3. Features of the building4. The building's control towerVOICEOVER (in English): "British architectural firm Hugh Broughton Architects have designed a research center called the Discovery Building for the British Arctic Survey research team in Antarctica." "Construction began on January 30, 2020.""According to a press release from the architectural firm, the building's exterior will be made with metal panels that are pale blue in color to prevent high ultraviolet rays from causing degradation to the structure.""The color is also a reference to the Antarctic sky.""The Discovery Building will also have a wind deflector along its roofline that will be used to deflect cold air in the Antarctic so that the wind will travel down the structure's facade." "This will help to minimize snow accumulation around the building.""The structure also consists of a control tower from its roof. The tower will provide a 360° view of the area."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Hugh Brougton Architects, https://inhabitat.com/bas-breaks-ground-on-energy-efficient-discovery-building-to-study-climate-change-in-antarctica/https://hbarchitects.co.uk/https://hbarchitects.co.uk/discovery-building-rothera-research-station/https://www.dezeen.com/2020/02/18/hugh-broughton-architects-antarctic-research-centre-discovery-building/https://www.bas.ac.uk/media-post/new-discovery-building-at-rothera-research-station-breaks-ground/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 03:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/02/3970178/3970178_C1199FAB669B4B70A78D6DEC9F0B5DC5_200302_3970178_Antarctic_research_center_begins_construction_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Discovery Building Antarctica, British Antarctic Survey, antarctica climate change, antarctic research building, Hugh Broughton Architects, rothera research station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970172</guid>
      <title>'Doomsday vault' receives its largest ever deposit of seeds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Svalbard[c] Global Seed Vault is a repository that houses a collection of seeds from around the world in order to safeguard plant genealogy amid the growing threat of climate change.According to a press release from Crop Trust, the vault received a new deposit of seeds consisting of several hundred plant species on February 25 from different institutions around the world. This is said to be the largest deposit it has ever received.These contents include common staple crops, vegetables, herbs and even wild plant relatives.Global Seed Vault's website explains that it has previously received large varieties of rice, wheat and barley crops among others.The vault is located on the tectonically inactive Norwegian island of Spitsbergen.It has been constructed 130 meters above sea level in order to keep the seeds dry and to allow easy maintenance in the event of a power failure.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Global Seed Vault and what its purpose is2. The repository received a new deposit of seeds recently3. Previously, the vault had received rice, wheat and barley crops4. Where the vault is located5. How it had been constructedVOICEOVER (in English): "The Svalbard[d] Global Seed Vault is a repository that houses a collection of seeds from around the world in order to safeguard plant genealogy amid the growing threat of climate change.""According to a press release from Crop Trust, the vault received a new deposit of seeds consisting of several hundred plant species on February 25 from different institutions around the world. This is said to be the largest deposit it has ever received.""These contents include common staple crops, vegetables, herbs and even wild plant relatives.""Global Seed Vault's website explains that it has previously received large varieties of rice, wheat and barley crops among others.""The vault is located on the tectonically inactive Norwegian island of Spitsbergen.""It has been constructed 130 meters above sea level in order to keep the seeds dry and to allow easy maintenance in the event of a power failure."SOURCES: New Atlas, Crop Trust, Seed Vault, The Verge, The Local Nohttps://newatlas.com/environment/global-seed-bank-largest-deposit/https://www.croptrust.org/press-release/major-seed-deposit-at-the-svalbard-global-seed-vault/https://www.seedvault.no/https://www.theverge.com/2020/2/24/21151298/doomsday-svalbard-vault-seed-deposit-cherokee-nationhttps://www.thelocal.no/20200225/norways-arctic-doomsday-vault-stocks-up-on-60000-more-food-seeds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/02/3970172/3970172_DB2E9D42357D454DB125CA49C02EFED8_200302_3970172__Doomsday_vault__receives_its_largest_ever_depos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, global seed bank, arctic seed vault, climate change, global warming, svalbard, seed vault, food seeds, storing food seeds, storing food seeds in norway, doomsday vault,  norway, svalbard global seed vault]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970162</guid>
      <title>Chang'e 4 probe reveals what's underneath the far side of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's Chang'e 4 lunar mission has provided a glimpse into what lies beneath the far side of the moon.On January 3, 2019, the Chang'e 4 lunar probe landed on the floor of the Von Karman crater, on the moon's south pole. CNN reports that several hours after touchdown, the Chang'e 4 deployed the Yutu-2 to roam and explore the surface.According to a paper published in Science Advances, the rover used its Lunar Penetrating Radar to send radio signals to the lunar subsurface, up to a depth of 40 meters.Paper author Li Chunlai says this is three times the depth that the Chang'e 3, China's previous mission, was able to measure.After combining the radar image with tomographic data and quantitative analysis, researchers found that the subsurface was made primarily of highly porous, granular material, embedded with boulders of different sizes.According to CNN, this is likely due to the moon being frequently hit by meteors and other space debris during the early days of the solar system.When an object strikes the moon, the impact ejects a wave of material. The cratered surface becomes the top layer over time, with layers of boulder and fine debris buried beneath.Researchers say the findings could shed more light on the geological evolution of the moon's dark side. And as Yutu-2 continues to explore the area, the team is also looking into the possibility of returning samples to Earth. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chang'e 4 landing on the moon's far side2. Deployment of Yutu-2 rover 3. Yutu-2 rover using lunar penetrating radar on moon's subsurface4. Radar penetrating three times the depth compared to Chang'e 35. Subsurface consisting of larger rocks embedded in porous material6. Layers resulted from frequent impacts on moon surfaceVOICEOVER (in English): "On January 3, 2019, the Chang'e 4 lunar probe landed on the floor of the Von Karman crater, on the moon's south pole.""CNN reports that several hours after touchdown, the Chang'e 4 deployed the Yutu-2 to roam and explore the surface.""According to a paper published in Science Advances, the rover used its Lunar Penetrating Radar to send radio signals to the lunar subsurface, up to a depth of 40 meters.""Paper author Li Chunlai says this is three times the depth that the Chang'e 3, China's previous mission, was able to measure.""After combining the radar image with tomographic data and quantitative analysis, researchers found that the subsurface was made primarily of highly porous, granular material, embedded with boulders of different sizes.""According to CNN, this is likely due to the moon being frequently hit by meteors and other space debris during the early days of the solar system.""When an object strikes the moon, the impact ejects a wave of material. The cratered surface becomes the top layer over time, with layers of boulder and fine debris buried beneath."SOURCES: Science Advances, CNN, Space.comhttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/9/eaay6898https://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/26/world/change4-lunar-rover-moon-surface-scn/index.htmlhttps://www.space.com/china-change-4-moon-far-side-subsurface.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 03:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/02/3970162/3970162_01449DF6CE004C4592163FBFFC0AB776_200302_3970162_Chang_e_4_probe_reveals_what_s_underneath_the_fa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China lunar probe, Chang'e 4, China Chang'e 4, Yutu-2, China lunar rover, lunar rover, far side of the moon, ground penetrating radar]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970600</guid>
      <title>New luxury superyacht designed using ESA space mission techniques</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDutch shipyard Royal Huisman has designed the superyacht Sea Eagle II using the same engineering techniques typically reserved for space missions for the European Space Agency.The ship will be built in separate stages instead of the traditional approach in which ships are built from start to finish.The ship will be 81 meters long and will have three masted schooners, according to a news release from the ESA. Sea Eagle II will sport aluminum panels on its exterior. The panels will have holes and support structures added to them to cut down on construction time and accommodate features such as hatches for the yacht.According to a new release from European Space Agency dated February 27, the ship features a "desirable, luxurious interior."The superyacht is set to become the world's largest aluminum sailing ship once it is completed and delivered to its owners this spring. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The new superyacht was designed using the same engineering techniques typically used for space missions2. Dimensions of the superyacht3. The yacht's exterior will be made with aluminum panels4. The yacht's interior5. The superyacht sailing in the oceanVOICEOVER (in English): "Dutch shipyard Royal Huisman has designed the superyacht Sea Eagle II using the same engineering techniques typically reserved for space missions for the European Space Agency.""According to a news release from the ESA, the ship will be 81 meters long and will have three masted schooners.""Sea Eagle II will sport aluminum panels on its exterior." "The panels will have holes and support structures added to them to cut down on construction time and accommodate features such as hatches for the yacht.""According to the European Space Agency, the ship features a 'desirable, luxurious interior.'""The superyacht is set to become the world's largest aluminum sailing ship once it is completed and delivered to its owners this spring."SOURCES: New Atlas, European Space Agency, Royal Huisman https://newatlas.com/marine/aluminium-superyacht-space-mission-design-techniques/https://www.esa.int/ESA_Multimedia/Images/2020/02/Satellite_design_applied_to_superyachthttps://www.royalhuisman.com/category/news/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 03:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/03/3970600/3970600_E35A37ED305D405EB74A8DAB07EC6600_200303_3970600_New_luxury_superyacht_designed_using_ESA_space_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sea Eagle II, Sea Eagle II superyacht, Superyacht, Royal Huisman, luxurious superyacht, superyacht ESA, superyacht designed using space mission techniques]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971055</guid>
      <title>Symptoms of the novel coronavirus explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHere's a list of symptoms of the virus and precautions people can take in order to better protect themselves as the novel coronavirus continues to spread around the world. Initial symptoms of the coronavirus diseases, or Covid-19, include fever followed by a dry cough, according to BBC News. Patients suffering from Covid-19 could develop shortness of breath after a week. This may lead some to be hospitalized for further treatment.The BBC noted that symptoms are similar to those of common viruses such as the cold or the flu.The World Health Organization states that the incubation period for coronavirus diseases lasts up to 14 days. The incubation period may be longer and could last up to 24 days, BBC News reports, citing researchers. It's unclear how exactly the virus that causes Covid-19 spreads, though similar viruses are typically spread through droplets that are produced when a person who has contracted the virus sneezes or coughs.The United Kingdom's National Health Service advised the public to wash hands frequently with soap or use hand sanitizer, sneeze or cough into a tissue or into your sleeve and avoid touching the face with unwashed hands.In more severe cases, Covid-19 could lead to pneumonia, severe acute respiratory syndrome, organ failure or even death.The virus, which is officially known as severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2, or SARS-CoV-2, originated in China. It has since spread to 60 countries, with especially severe outbreaks in Italy, Iran and South Korea.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Novel coronavirus symptoms2. How it could spread 3. Precautions against the virus4. What the virus could lead toVOICEOVER (in English): "Initial symptoms of the coronavirus diseases, or Covid-19, include fever followed by a dry cough, according to BBC News. "Patients suffering from Covid-19 could develop shortness of breath after a week. This may lead some to be hospitalized for further treatment.""It's unclear how exactly the virus that causes Covid-19 spreads, though similar viruses are typically spread through droplets that are produced when a person who has contracted the virus sneezes or coughs.""The United Kingdom's National Health Service advised the public to wash hands frequently with soap or use hand sanitizer, sneeze or cough into a tissue or into your sleeve and avoid touching the face with unwashed hands.""In more severe cases, Covid-19 could lead to pneumonia, severe acute respiratory syndrome, organ failure or even death."SOURCES: BBC News, World Health Organization, United Kingdom National Health Servicehttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-51048366https://www.who.int/health-topics/coronavirushttps://www.who.int/docs/default-source/coronaviruse/situation-reports/20200301-sitrep-41-covid-19.pdf?sfvrsn=6768306d_2https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/coronavirus-covid-19/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 03:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/04/3971055/3971055_F7032F97A7034D9387994475293C0F3C_200304_3971055_Symptoms_of_the_novel_coronavirus_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Covid-19, coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, coronavirus precautions, coronavirus covid-19]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971042</guid>
      <title>DNA discovered in 75 million-year-old dinosaur fossils</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have discovered DNA inside 75 million-year-old dinosaur fossils, according to the National Science Review.According to the Science China Press writing on Phys.org, scientists from the U.S. and China made the discovery while investigating skull fragments of Hypacrosaurus nestlings. In addition to DNA, researchers also found proteins, chromosomes and cartilage cells among the fossils.According to the British Natural History Museum, these dinosaurs were herbivores and lived 70 million years ago in Canada and the USA during the Late Cretaceous period.Researchers suggest that their findings could mean that DNA can exist longer than currently thought and may, in fact, be preserved in fossils that are millions of years old. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hypacrosaurus nestling skull and nations involved in research2. Hypacrosaurus nestling skull fragments3. Findings in Hypacrosaurus nestling skull fragments 4. Depiction of Hypacrosaurus in natureVOICEOVER (in English): "New research published in the National Science Review details how researchers from China and the U.S. discovered DNA, and other organic materials inside 75 million-year-old dinosaur fossils." "Currently, DNA is thought to only last for around one million years.""According to the Science China Press writing on Phys.org, scientists made the discovery while investigating the skull fragments of Hypacrosaurus nestlings.""In addition to the DNA, researchers also found proteins, chromosomes and cartilage cells among the Hypacarosaurus fossils.""According to the British Natural History Museum, these dinosaurs were herbivores and lived 70 million years ago in Canada and the USA during the Late Cretaceous period." SOURCES: National Science Review, Science China Press (Phys.org), Natural History Muesumhttps://academic.oup.com/nsr/advance-article/doi/10.1093/nsr/nwz206/5762999https://phys.org/news/2020-02-cartilage-cells-chromosomes-dna-million-year-old.htmlhttps://www.nhm.ac.uk/discover/dino-directory/hypacrosaurus.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 03:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/04/3971042/3971042_FBE5D251602F4F7BAFE892562793A6F7_200304_3971042_DNA_discovered_in_75_million_year_old_dinosaur_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, science, dna, dinosaur bones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971619</guid>
      <title>NASA X-ray telescope detects biggest ever space explosion: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by X-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Largest space explosion ever observed in Ophiuchus cluster2. Explosion is the result of a supermassive black hole expelling matter and energy3. Black hole jets accelerate electrons to near light speed4. Data from X-ray and low frequency radio telescopes confirmed explosion5. The explosion creates a cavity that can fit 15 Milky Way Galaxies in a row6. The distance across the cavity is 1.5 million light yearsVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by X-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.""According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.""The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.""BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.""The study's lead author Simona Giacintucci at the Naval Research Laboratory is cited by MIT Technology Review as saying the cavity is so large that 15 Milky Way galaxies could fit inside its volume in a row.""According to co-author Professor Melanie Johnston-Hollitt at the Murchison Widefield Array, the gap is so vast that light traveling across its distance from one end will not reach the other for 1.5 million years."SOURCES: Arxiv.com, Chandra X-Ray Observatory, MIT Technology Review, BBChttps://arxiv.org/abs/2002.01291https://chandra.si.edu/photo/2020/ophiuchus/https://www.technologyreview.com/f/615300/astronomers-have-detected-the-biggest-explosion-the-universe/https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51669384***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 07:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/05/3971619/3971619_A73239D793D6424584B64D35965308E3_200305_3971619_NASA_X_ray_telescope_detects_biggest_ever_space__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space explosion, big bang, Ophiuchus cluster, Ophiuchus supercluster, galaxy, black hole, supermassive black hole, plasma, x-ray, telescope, telescopes, Chandra, NASA, U.S., space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971613</guid>
      <title>NASA X-ray telescope detects biggest ever space explosion: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by X-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.The study's lead author Simona Giacintucci at the Naval Research Laboratory is cited by MIT Technology Review as saying the cavity is so large that 15 Milky Way galaxies could fit inside its volume in a row.According to co-author Professor Melanie Johnston-Hollitt at the Murchison Widefield Array, the gap is so vast that light traveling across its distance from one end will not reach the other for 1.5 million years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Largest space explosion ever observed in Ophiuchus cluster2. Explosion is the result of a supermassive black hole expelling matter and energy3. Black hole jets accelerate electrons to near light speed4. Data from X-ray and low frequency radio telescopes confirmed explosion5. The explosion creates a cavity that can fit 15 Milky Way Galaxies in a row6. The distance across the cavity is 1.5 million light yearsVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by X-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.""According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.""The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.""BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.""The study's lead author Simona Giacintucci at the Naval Research Laboratory is cited by MIT Technology Review as saying the cavity is so large that 15 Milky Way galaxies could fit inside its volume in a row.""According to co-author Professor Melanie Johnston-Hollitt at the Murchison Widefield Array, the gap is so vast that light traveling across its distance from one end will not reach the other for 1.5 million years."SOURCES: Arxiv.com, Chandra X-Ray Observatory, MIT Technology Review, BBChttps://arxiv.org/abs/2002.01291https://chandra.si.edu/photo/2020/ophiuchus/https://www.technologyreview.com/f/615300/astronomers-have-detected-the-biggest-explosion-the-universe/https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51669384***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 07:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/05/3971613/3971613_4CDD77EB57884AA6A3466AA4D9B8BED7_200305_3971613_NASA_X_ray_telescope_detects_biggest_ever_space__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space explosion, big bang, Ophiuchus cluster, Ophiuchus supercluster, galaxy, black hole, supermassive black hole, plasma, x-ray, telescope, telescopes, Chandra, NASA, U.S., space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971533</guid>
      <title>NASA X-ray telescope detects biggest ever space explosion: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by X-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.The study's lead author Simona Giacintucci at the Naval Research Laboratory is cited by MIT Technology Review as saying the cavity is so large that 15 Milky Way galaxies could fit inside its volume in a row.According to co-author Professor Melanie Johnston-Hollitt at the Murchison Widefield Array, the gap is so vast that light traveling across its distance from one end will not reach the other for 1.5 million years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Largest space explosion ever observed in Ophiuchus cluster2. Explosion is the result of a supermassive black hole expelling matter and energy3. Black hole jets accelerate electrons to near light speed4. Data from X-ray and low frequency radio telescopes confirmed explosion5. The explosion creates a cavity that can fit 15 Milky Way Galaxies in a row6. The distance across the cavity is 1.5 million light yearsVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by X-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.""According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.""The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.""BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.""The study's lead author Simona Giacintucci at the Naval Research Laboratory is cited by MIT Technology Review as saying the cavity is so large that 15 Milky Way galaxies could fit inside its volume in a row.""According to co-author Professor Melanie Johnston-Hollitt at the Murchison Widefield Array, the gap is so vast that light traveling across its distance from one end will not reach the other for 1.5 million years."SOURCES: Arxiv.com, Chandra X-Ray Observatory, MIT Technology Review, BBChttps://arxiv.org/abs/2002.01291https://chandra.si.edu/photo/2020/ophiuchus/https://www.technologyreview.com/f/615300/astronomers-have-detected-the-biggest-explosion-the-universe/https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51669384***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 05:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/05/3971533/3971533_6C7D7A266BC54D48A61E6BAE4DD89A92_200305_3971533_NASA_X_ray_telescope_detects_biggest_ever_space__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space explosion, big bang, Ophiuchus cluster, Ophiuchus supercluster, galaxy, black hole, supermassive black hole, plasma, x-ray, telescope, telescopes, Chandra, NASA, U.S., space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971520</guid>
      <title>Galactic collision may have given rise to Milky Way's warped shape</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe European Space Agency's space observatory Gaia may have found an explanation for the warped shape of the Milky Way Galaxy, which is bent into an S shape. This warp rotates with the galaxy's stars instead of standing still.A study published in Nature Astronomy says that an ongoing collision with another galaxy, most likely the dwarf satellite galaxy Sagittarius, has disrupted the dish shape of our galaxy.The European Space Agency launched Gaia in 2013 to render a 3D map of the Milky Way.The agency says the survey will eventually take a spatial census of 1 billion stars in our galaxy, or 1 percent of its constituents. Citing the authors, the European Space Agency says that Gaia mapped out the motions, velocity and distance of our galaxy's stars. The researchers then worked backward to determine when and how collisions with Sagittarius deformed our galactic dish.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Milky Way Galaxy has an S-shaped dish or warp2. The warp could be the result of an ongoing collision with dwarf galaxy Sagittarius 3. Space probe Gaia's 3D mapping of the galaxy contributes to the studyVOICEOVER (in English): "The European Space Agency's space observatory Gaia may have found an explanation for the warped shape of the Milky Way Galaxy, which is bent into an S shape. This warp rotates with the galaxy's stars instead of standing still.""The European Space Agency launched Gaia in 2013 to render a 3D map of the Milky Way.""The agency says the survey will eventually take a spatial census of 1 billion stars in our galaxy, or 1 percent of its constituents." "A study published in Nature Astronomy says that an ongoing collision with another galaxy, most likely the dwarf satellite galaxy Sagittarius, has disrupted the dish shape of our galaxy.""Citing the authors, the European Space Agency says that Gaia mapped out the motions, velocity and distance of our galaxy's stars. The researchers then worked backward to determine when and how collisions with Sagittarius deformed our galactic dish."SOURCES: Nature Astronomy, European Space Agencyhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-020-1017-3http://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Space_Science/Gaia/Milky_Way_s_warp_caused_by_galactic_collision_Gaia_suggestshttps://sci.esa.int/web/gaia***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 05:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/05/3971520/3971520_6A96BAE5A62C4DC195DEED2B090E4851_200305_3971520_Galactic_collision_may_have_given_rise_to_Milky__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Milky Way Galaxy, Milky Way Galaxy's warp, warp, galactic collision, gaia, sagittarius, Sagittarius Dwarf Spheroidal Galaxy, dwarf galaxy, European Space Agency, esa, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971459</guid>
      <title>How airlines are disinfecting airplanes amid the novel coronavirus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs the novel coronavirus spreads globally, major airlines are taking preventative measures to ensure their airplanes are as clean as possible.Southwest Airlines told CNN Travel that their airlines' cleaning procedure includes disinfecting all hard surfaces inside the cabin as well as cleaning all seats and the carpet amid the outbreak of Covid-19.An American Airlines spokesperson told the broadcasting network that airplane lavatories and floors are being thoroughly cleaned while all visible trash on seat pockets is removed before every flight.A Qantas Airways spokesperson explained that their cabins, seats, galleys and washrooms are being cleaned and disinfected. The spokesperson also noted that their planes use HEPA filters as part of their air-conditioning systems. The airline says the filters "provide much cleaner air than other public spaces" such as trains or shopping centers.Delta Air Lines says it is using a technique called fogging, which involves spraying an EPA-registered disinfectant on all trans-Pacific flights landing in the U.S. The airline says it plans to expand fogging to more inbound international flights.Cathay Pacific is replacing all seat covers and disinfecting all surfaces and carpets as well as sterilizing water equipment and replacing air filters, CNN reports. The airline has also stopped providing hot towels, pillows, blankets, magazines and duty-free service on all flights to and from China.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cleaning procedure of Southwest Airlines2. Airline lavatories and floors being cleaned while visible trash is removed3. Cleaning procedure of Qantas Airways4. Plane being disinfected using the fogging techniqueVOICEOVER (in English): "Southwest Airlines told CNN Travel that their airlines' cleaning procedure includes disinfecting all hard surfaces inside the cabin as well as cleaning all seats and the carpet amid the outbreak of Covid-19.""An American Airlines spokesperson told the broadcasting network that airplane lavatories and floors are being thoroughly cleaned while all visible trash on seat pockets is removed before every flight.""A Qantas Airways spokesperson explained that their cabins, seats, galleys and washrooms are being cleaned and disinfected.""The spokesperson also noted that their planes use HEPA filters as part of their air-conditioning systems. The airline says the filters 'provide much cleaner air than other public spaces' such as trains or shopping centers.""Delta Air Lines says it is using a technique called fogging, which involves spraying an EPA-registered disinfectant on all trans-Pacific flights landing in the U.S.""The airline says it plans to expand fogging to more inbound international flights."SOURCES: CNN, Business Insider  https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/airplane-hygiene-coronavirus/index.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/coronavirus-airlines-disinfectant-clean-planes-healthcare-hospitals-2020-2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/05/3971459/3971459_37EE0F76A22149B39622A85353DF0C8E_200305_3971459_How_airlines_are_disinfecting_airplanes_amid_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Cleaning airlines, cleaning airplanes, sanitizing airplanes, cleaning inside airplanes, cleaning airplanes covid-19, sanitizing airplanes covid-19]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3972259</guid>
      <title>Futuristic new bridge unfolds like an umbrella</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have demonstrated a futuristic bridge-building technique that allows the structure to unfold like an umbrella to the length of its span. This new technique is cost-effective, time-saving and has less impact on the natural landscape, according to a news release from Vienna University of Technology.The Lafnitz Bridge in Austria was built vertically instead of horizontally with scaffolding, like traditional bridges.Using this technique, engineers erected two vertical concrete piers and attached steel girders on both sides. As the piers are then slowly lowered using hydraulic systems, the steel girders unfold.Once the bridge has opened up to reach a horizontal position, concrete is added to the structure.The 116-meter Lafnitz Bridge was "unfolded" over the Lafnitz River on February 27, 2020.Johann Kollegger, a professor at the Vienna University of Technology, explained in the news release that traditional bridges erected using scaffolding can take months to be completed.Using this new technique, the elements for the lowering method can be set up in two to three days while the lowering process itself takes roughly three hours.Kollegger noted that the technique could be used to build bridges in difficult terrain or "terrain that should be not disturbed," such as nature reserves.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the bridge is built2. How the structure is lowered3. The bridge 'unfolding' and concrete being added4. The completed bridgeVOICEOVER (in English): "The Lafnitz Bridge in Austria was built vertically instead of horizontally with scaffolding, like traditional bridges.""Using this technique, engineers erected two vertical concrete piers and attached steel girders on both sides.""As the piers are then slowly lowered using hydraulic systems, the steel girders unfold.""Once the bridge has opened up to reach a horizontal position, concrete is added to the structure.""The 116-meter Lafnitz Bridge was 'unfolded' over the Lafnitz River on February 27, 2020."SOURCES: Vienna University of Technology, New Atlas, Tech Xplore https://www.tuwien.at/en/tu-wien/news/news-articles/news/the-unfoldable-bridge/https://newatlas.com/architecture/unfolding-highway-bridge-engineering-tu-wien/https://techxplore.com/news/2020-03-unfoldable-bridge.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/06/3972259/3972259_4B0C3431F91742F7B2666C07C9A032DC_200306_3972259_Futuristic_new_bridge_unfolds_like_an_umbrella_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Unfoldable bridge, unfolding bridge, bridge unfolds like umbrella, innovative bridge design, vertical bridge, bridge building techniques, vienna bridge, Lafnitz bridge, vertical bridge austria, futuristic bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3972032</guid>
      <title>Scientists are building a wormhole tunnel analogue in quantum circuits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have proposed to build a functional wormhole tunnel by simulating quantum entangled black holes in a lab. Quanta Magazine reports the linked black holes are theoretically able to teleport quantum information via the tunnel.Black holes were thought to totally obliterate the objects they consume. However, the experiment will test a new idea in physics that evaporating black holes actually send information about subsumed objects back to the universe via Hawking radiation.Citing California Institute of Technology physicist Sepehr Nezami, the outlet reports the research team believes a black hole could be forced to disgorge intact information after it is entangled with another black hole on a quantum level.Stanford University's Adam Brown is cited as saying quantum circuitry could make a functional analog for entangled black holes. If the theory is correct, this circuitry would be able to instantly transmit and decrypt qubits, also known as quantum teleportation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Quantum entangled black hole may act as a conduit for quantum information2. New theory speculates that black hole preserves information via Hawking radiation 3. Experiment designed to test the theory by creating a wormhole analogue4. Quantum circuitry will functionally duplicate quantum entangled black holesVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have proposed to build a functional wormhole tunnel by simulating quantum entangled black holes in a lab. Quanta Magazine reports the linked black holes are theoretically able to teleport quantum information via the tunnel.""Black holes were thought to totally obliterate the objects they consume. However, the experiment will test a new idea in physics that evaporating black holes actually send information about subsumed objects back to the universe via Hawking radiation.""Citing California Institute of Technology physicist Sepehr Nezami, the outlet reports the research team believes a black hole could be forced to disgorge intact information after it is entangled with another black hole on a quantum level.""Stanford University's Adam Brown is cited as saying quantum circuitry could make a functional analog for entangled black holes. If the theory is correct, this circuitry would be able to instantly transmit and decrypt qubits, also known as quantum teleportation."SOURCES: Quanta Magazine https://www.quantamagazine.org/wormholes-reveal-a-way-to-manipulate-black-hole-information-in-the-lab-20200227/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/06/3972032/3972032_ED959055D5CE4693A9FCFD3EEE9E85D1_200306_3972032_Scientists_are_building_a_wormhole_tunnel_analog_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Quantum entangled black holes, black holes, quantum information, hawking radiation, wormhole, wormholes, quantum computing, quantum computers, quantum computer, black hole information paradox, caltech, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971925</guid>
      <title>1.5 billion-year-old Earth was all water, no continents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew evidence from Iowa State University and the University of Colorado suggests that 1.5 billion years ago, the planet was covered by a vast ocean and had no continents.Published in Nature Geoscience, the research examined more than 100 ancient samples of seafloor, located now in the outback of northwestern Australia. Its rocky scenery of craggy seafloor preserves a hydrothermal system dating back 3.2 billion years.Lead study author, Benjamin Johnson told Live Science that when the Earth was 1.5 billion years old, the ocean had high levels of isotope oxygen-18.Their computer models showed that continental landmasses leach oxygen-18 from the oceans, but in the ancient samples, he observed an abundance of it. So, in the absence of continents, the oceans would carry more oxygen-18, which implies a "Waterworld."The continents appeared later, as plate tectonics drove enormous, rocky landmasses upward to breach the sea surfaces. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The earth is shown as a Waterworld with no land2. The Australian outback is identified as a source of chemical clues3. The effects on Isotope oxygen-18 from continents4. Where the continents came fromVOICEOVER (in English): "New evidence from Iowa State University and the University of Colorado suggests that 1.5 billion years ago, the planet was covered by a vast ocean and had no continents.""Published in Nature Geoscience, the research examined more than 100 ancient samples of seafloor, located now in the outback of northwestern Australia. Its rocky scenery of craggy seafloor preserves a hydrothermal system dating back 3.2 billion years.""Lead study author, Benjamin Johnson told Live Science that when the Earth was 1.5 billion years old, the ocean had high levels of isotope oxygen-18.""Their computer models showed that continental landmasses leach oxygen-18 from the oceans, but in the ancient samples, he observed an abundance of it." "So, in the absence of continents, the oceans would carry more oxygen-18, which implies a 'Waterworld.'""The continents appeared later, as plate tectonics drove enormous, rocky landmasses upward to breach the sea surfaces."SOURCES: Live Science, Nature Geosciencehttps://www.livescience.com/waterworld-earth.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41561-020-0538-9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/06/3971925/3971925_7077049CF2CA421C8B3A4A09DE38EEC0_200306_3971925_1_5_billion_year_old_Earth_was_all_water__no_con_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Waterworld, earth was a Waterworld, continents, 1.5 billion-year-old Earth was a Waterworld, space, no land earth, blue planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973250</guid>
      <title>NASA to be unable to contact Voyager 2 for almost a year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANStarting early this month, Voyager 2 will stop receiving commands from NASA, the space agency announced in a news release on March 5.This is because the transmitter that sends commands to Voyager 2, the DSS43 radio antenna near Canberra, Australia, will undergo "critical upgrades" over the next 11 months.As Voyager 2 travels in space, the radio antenna won't be able to send commands to the space probe while it is being updated. The spacecraft is currently flying in a downward direction relative to our planet's orbital plane, which means it can only be in contact with the radio antenna site in Australia.During this time, the Voyager team will put the spacecraft into a state of inactivity, which will still allow the spacecraft to send back scientific data to the team during the next 11 months.NASA said in the news release that the radio antenna's transmitters and other parts need to be replaced and upgraded as they are 40 years old and are "increasingly unreliable."The DSS43 antenna is part of the U.S. space agency's deep space network, which is used to communicate and receive information from faraway spacecraft.NASA said the upgrades will also benefit future space missions such as the Artemis lunar missions and Mars 2020 rover mission.The upgrades on the DSS43 radio antenna are expected to be complete by January of 2021.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The DSS43 radio antenna near Canberra, Australia2. The radio antenna and the Voyager 2 spacecraft in space3. Voyager 2 sending data back to earth 4. Parts of the DSS43 radio antenna that will be upgradedVOICEOVER (in English): "Starting early this month, Voyager 2 will stop receiving commands from NASA, the space agency announced in a news release on March 5.""This is because the transmitter that sends commands to Voyager 2, the DSS43 radio antenna near Canberra, Australia, will undergo 'critical upgrades' over the next 11 months.""As Voyager 2 travels in space, the radio antenna won't be able to send commands to the space probe while it is being updated.""The spacecraft is currently flying in a downward direction relative to our planet's orbital plane, which means it can only be in contact with the radio antenna site in Australia.""During this time, the Voyager team will put the spacecraft into a state of inactivity, which will still allow the spacecraft to send back scientific data to the team during the next 11 months.""NASA said in the news release that the radio antenna's transmitters and other parts need to be replaced and upgraded as they are 40 years old and are 'increasingly unreliable.'""The DSS43 antenna is part of the U.S. space agency's deep space network, which is used to communicate and receive information from faraway spacecraft."SOURCES: New Atlas, NASA https://newatlas.com/space/voyager-2-communications-antenna-shutdown/https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7611***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 12:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/09/3973250/3973250_BC836B2BEFAB4BF68F860EDBF36D51E6_200309_3973250_NASA_to_be_unable_to_contact_Voyager_2_for_almos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, radio antennas, deep space antennas, deep space network, DSS43, DSS43 NASA, NASA, deep space, deep space satellites, space, space exploration, DSS43 radio antenna, deep space station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973135</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus quarantine hotel collapses in China, killing 10</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScores of people under coronavirus quarantine in Quanzhou, China were trapped over the weekend after the hotel they were in suddenly collapsed, reports the South China Morning Post. The collapsed Xinjia Express Hotel being used for Co-Vid 19 quarantine was 7 stories tall and 66 rooms, according to state-run newspaper The China Daily.According to the state-run Xinhua News, two supermarkets on the ground floor of the hotel were undergoing remodeling when the building collapsed around 7 p.m. on Saturday. The area's top housing official Zhang Yi told Xinhua News that he received a phone call from construction workers moments before the collapse reporting a damaged pillar.Citing local authorities, the South China Morning Post reports that 8 people escaped as the building collapsed, while 38 have been pulled from the rubble. Many remain unaccounted for. The South China Morning Post reports that more than 1,000 emergency responders were sent to the site of the collapse. The newspaper reports that those trapped include 58 people under quarantine and government medical workers. All guests had tested negative for the virus but had still been subject to a mandatory 14-day quarantine. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of hotel 2. Depiction of hotel groundfloor exterior3. Depiction of construction worker calling about damaged pillar on groundfloor4. Depiction of hotel collapse and number of those rescuedVOICEOVER (in English): "The collapsed Xinjia Express Hotel being used for Co-Vid 19 quarantine was 7 stories tall and 66 rooms, according to state-run newspaper The China Daily.  At least 10 people were killed.""According to the state-run Xinhua News, two supermarkets on the ground floor of the hotel were undergoing remodeling when the building collapsed around 7 p.m. on Saturday." "The area's top housing official Zhang Yi told Xinhua News that he received a phone call from construction workers moments before the collapse reporting a damaged pillar.""Citing authorities, the South China Morning Post reports that 8 people escaped as the building collapsed, while 38 have been pulled from the rubble. Many remain unaccounted for."SOURCES: China Daily, Xinhua News, South China Morning Post, Guardian, http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202003/08/WS5e649de7a31012821727d325_1.htmlhttp://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202003/09/WS5e659d49a31012821727d55a_1.htmlhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2020-03/08/c_138855560.htmhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3074167/investigators-probe-renovations-collapsed-coronavirus-hotelhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/07/china-coronavirus-quarantine-hotel-collapses-trapping-dozens***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 08:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/09/3973135/3973135_7C32CDBA179D4378A5B5424453454336_200309_3973135_Coronavirus_quarantine_hotel_collapses_in_China__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Covid-19 China hotel collapse, coronavirus quarantine hotel collapse, xinjia express hotel, quanzhou building collapse, hotel collapse china, structural failures, quarantine hotel china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973084</guid>
      <title>Study reveals how COVID-19 infects human cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from China have used cryo-electron microscopy to show how SARS-CoV-2 infects humans. The study published in Science says the virus targets a type of receptor found on human cells in the lungs, heart, kidneys and intestines.A previous study published in Science found the virus' spike protein has two receptor binding domains, or RBDs, facing downward and another facing upward. These allow the virus to bind with and invade human cells.According to the new study, the virus targets a human ACE2 receptor that has bonded with an amino acid transporter. This subtype of ACE2 structure has never been discovered before.The virus uses the spike protein's 'up' RBD to bind with the ACE2 structure, which enables the virus to enter and infect the cell. According to the researchers, their discovery may help in developing a cure or vaccine that prevents infection by targeting ACE2.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SARS-CoV-2 infects humans via cell receptors found in the lungs and other organs 2. The configuration of receptor binding domains in SARS-CoV-2 spike protein 3. The vulnerable receptor is a previously unknown subtype of ACE2 receptor4. Discovery of ACE2 receptor could aid in developing antivirals and vaccinesVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from China have used cryo-electron microscopy to show how SARS-CoV-2 infects humans. The study published in Science says the virus targets a type of receptor found on human cells in the lungs, heart, kidneys and intestines.""A previous study published in Science found the virus' spike protein has two receptor binding domains, or RBDs, facing downward and another facing upward. These allow the virus to bind with and invade human cells.""According to the new study, the virus targets a human ACE2 receptor that has bonded with an amino acid transporter. This subtype of ACE2 structure has never been discovered before.""The virus uses the spike protein's 'up' RBD to bind with the ACE2 structure, which enables the virus to enter and infect the cell. According to the researchers, their discovery may help in developing a cure or vaccine that prevents infection by targeting ACE2."SOURCES: Science, Drugtargetreview.comhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2020/03/03/science.abb2762.fullhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2020/02/19/science.abb2507https://www.drugtargetreview.com/news/56895/scientists-demonstrate-how-covid-19-infects-human-cells/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/09/3973084/3973084_785ED679A69D418182D3561577A04680_200309_3973084_Study_reveals_how_COVID_19_infects_human_cells_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, COVID-19, SARS-COV-19, coronavirus, spike protein, receptors, S1, S2, receptor binding domains, receptor binding domain, RBD, RBDs, ACE2 receptors, ACE2, receptor, receptors, human cells, protein structures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973611</guid>
      <title>NASA finds possible clue for life on early Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn a study published in Astrobiology, astrobiologists at Washington State University and Technische Universitat in Berlin, say NASA's Curiosity rover found organic compounds called thiophenes in soil samples that may have been produced by bacteria.The rover's instruments break down larger molecules and scientists can only examine chemical fragments. This means they cannot rule out a non-biological origin for the thiophenes, according to a press release from Washington State University.On Earth, thiophenes are found in coal, crude oil and white truffles.A thiophene molecule has four carbon atoms and a sulfur atom that make up a ring. Carbon and sulfur are essential elements to living organisms. The thiophene could be non-biological or bacterial in origin, but the evidence is not conclusive for either case.The study's authors say that bacteria may have existed when Mars was hotter and wetter three billion years ago. Some of those bacteria may have played a role in the sulfate reduction that transforms sulfur to thiophenes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Curiosity identifies organic compound thiophenes on Mars2. Thippenes may be bacterial in origin and found in coal, crude oil and truffles on Earth3. Thiopenes contain bioessential elements of carbon and sulfur 4. Bacteria that may have existed on Mars could have produced thiophenes VOICEOVER (in English): "In a study published in Astrobiology, astrobiologists at Washington State University and Technische Universitat in Berlin, say NASA's Curiosity rover found organic compounds called thiophenes in soil samples that may have been produced by bacteria.""The rover's instruments break down larger molecules and scientists can only examine chemical fragments. This means they cannot rule out a non-biological origin for the thiophenes, according to a press release from Washington State University.""On Earth, thiophenes are found in coal, crude oil and white truffles.""A thiophene molecule has four carbon atoms and a sulfur atom that make up a ring. Carbon and sulfur are essential elements to living organisms. The thiophene could be non-biological or bacterial in origin, but the evidence is not conclusive for either case.""The study's authors say that bacteria may have existed when Mars was hotter and wetter three billion years ago. Some of those bacteria may have played a role in the sulfate reduction that transforms sulfur to thiophenes." SOURCES: Astrobiology, Washington State University (Phys.org)http://astrobiology.com/2020/03/organic-molecules-discovered-by-curiosity-rover-consistent-with-early-life-on-mars.htmlhttps://phys.org/news/2020-03-molecules-curiosity-rover-early-life.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 10:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/10/3973611/3973611_35C01CCB21B34D35B66BC43318ED8171_200310_3973611_NASA_finds_possible_clue_for_life_on_early_Mars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Curiosity, rover, Mars rover, thiophenes, thiophene, organic compound, organic compounds, carbon, sulfur, bacteria, bacterial, Mars, life on Mars, Washington State University, Technische Universitat in Berlin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973523</guid>
      <title>Great Barrier Reef may enters 'critical time'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHot weather over the coming weeks could see the Great Barrier Reef enter a period of dangerous coral bleaching, reports Vice.com.Citing international marine experts, Phys.org reports that Australia's Great Barrier Reef might soon face another period of severe coral bleaching if the warmer than average March weather continues to heat the reef. The last time that happened large swathes of corals were wiped out.For scale, the reef is around the same size as Japan. Vice reports that between 2016 and 2017 half of all corals died in the Great Barrier Reef following a series of heatwaves.  According to National Geographic, 30 percent died in 2016, and a further 20 percent perished in 2017 due to heat stress.The coming weeks will be a "critical time" for the reef, explained David Wachenfield, Chief Scientist at the Great Barrier Reef Marine Park Authority (GBRMPA), in a weekly update on the reef's health posted to GBPRMPA YouTube channel. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Healthy coral reef.2. Coral reef after a bleaching period.3. Size of Great Barrier Reef compared to Japan.4. Damage caused by coral bleaching in 2016 and 2017.VOICEOVER (in English): "Citing international marine experts, Phys.org reports that Australia's Great Barrier Reef might soon face another period of severe coral bleaching if the warmer than average March weather continues to heat the reef." "The last time that happened large swathes of corals were wiped out.""For scale, the GBR is around the same size as Japan." "Vice reports that between 2016 and 2017 half of all corals died in the Great Barrier Reef following a series of heatwaves." "According to National Geographic, 30 percent died in 2016, and a further 20 percent perished in 2017 due to heat stress." SOURCES: Great Barrier Reef Marine Park Authority, Phys.org, Vice, National Geohttp://www.gbrmpa.gov.au/the-reef/reef-healthhttps://phys.org/news/2020-03-great-barrier-reef-crucial-period.htmlhttps://www.vice.com/en_us/article/y3mxmg/great-barrier-reef-coral-bleaching-2020https://www.nationalgeographic.com/magazine/2018/08/explore-atlas-great-barrier-reef-coral-bleaching-map-climate-change/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 07:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/10/3973523/3973523_0D5DEDA9356447B18344953E9B57939E_200310_3973523_Great_Barrier_Reef_may_enters__critical_time__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974050</guid>
      <title>How the coronavirus spread in the United States</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to Bloomberg, Patient Zero arrived at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport from Wuhan, China on January 15. During his time there he took public transportation at the airport.On January 19, he checked himself into a clinic after experiencing a fever and cough. He was admitted, tested for the virus and sent home to self-quarantine. Results of the test came back positive the next day and Patient Zero was then admitted into a special biocontainment ward at Providence Regional Medical Center in Everett, Washington. This unit was originally developed for the Ebola virus. By February 21, Patient Zero had fully recovered. However, an infected individual or individuals went undetected. Health experts researching the spread in Seattle believe that it was in the four-day window of time from January 15 to 19 that Patient Zero may have infected more people. Marc Lipsitch, an epidemiology professor at the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health, told Bloomberg that according to his estimates, for every dozen cases American officials caught, 20 to 25 went undetected. The lack of efficient testing kits and testing criteria also exacerbated the spread of the novel coronavirus. Early testing kits from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention were working well. However, by mid-February, testing results were coming back inconclusive due to manufacturing issues.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Patient Zero arriving at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport 2. Patient Zero checks himself into hospital is checked and alter admitted into a special isolation ward.3. Patient zero infects others4. Faulty tests and criteria lead to more undetected cases.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Bloomberg, Patient Zero arrived at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport from Wuhan, China on January 15. During his time there he took public transportation at the airport.""On January 19, he checked himself into a clinic after experiencing a fever and cough. He was admitted, tested for the virus and sent home to self-quarantine.""Results of the test came back positive the next day and Patient Zero was then admitted into a special biocontainment ward at Providence Regional Medical Center in Everett, Washington. This unit was originally developed for the Ebola virus. By February 21, Patient Zero had fully recovered." "However, an infected individual or individuals went undetected. Health experts researching the spread in Seattle believe that it was in the four-day window of time from January 15 to 19 that Patient Zero may have infected more people.""Marc Lipsitch, an epidemiology professor at the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health, told Bloomberg that according to his estimates, for every dozen cases American officials caught, 20 to 25 went undetected.""The lack of efficient testing kits and testing criteria also exacerbated the spread of the novel coronavirus. Early testing kits from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention were working well. However, by mid-February, testing results were coming back inconclusive due to manufacturing issues."SOURCES: Bloomberg, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Factcheck.orghttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2020-03-09/how-coronavirus-spread-from-patient-zero-in-seattlehttps://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2020/p0206-coronavirus-diagnostic-test-kits.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2020/t0212-cdc-telebriefing-transcript.htmlhttps://www.factcheck.org/2020/03/the-facts-on-coronavirus-testing/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 12:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/11/3974050/3974050_087E3AA7B76742A28FF800A594523001_200311_3974050_How_the_coronavirus_spread_in_the_United_States_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Coronavirus, covid19, covid, patient zero coronavirus, coronavirus in america, coronavirus in us, coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, coronavirus precautions, coronavirus covid-19,  seattle wuhan virus, seattle lockdown]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973902</guid>
      <title>Ancient settlement destroyed by comet, research suggests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANImpact from a comet around 12,800 years ago is believed to have wiped out a human settlement, according to new research published in Scientific Reports.  The study suggests that meltglass samples found at the Abu Hureyra site in Syria could be evidence that a comet destroyed the area.  The high-energy and intense heat needed to create the molten glass material could only have resulted from a cosmic impact, suggests study author and University of California Santa Barbara, Geology Professor James Kennet. He says those sorts of temperatures could melt a car in less than 60 seconds.The findings back a theory known as the Younger Dryas impact hypothesis. This suggests that debris from a disintegrating comet entering Earth's atmosphere struck areas in the Americas, the Middle East and Europe some 12,800 years ago.Kennet says that the settlement at Abu Hureyra would have been "abruptly destroyed" by such an event.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Research excavation area2. Research dig site where meltwater glass was discovered3. Depiction of comet in space and areas it is suggested to have struck4. Depiction of comet hitting ancient human settlementVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in the journal Scientific Reports suggests that meltglass samples found at the Abu Hureyra[a] site in Syria could be evidence that a comet destroyed one of humanity's earliest settlements 12,800 years." "The high-energy and intense heat needed to create the molten glass material could only have resulted from a cosmic impact, suggests study author and University of California Santa Barbara, Geology Professor James Kennet." "The findings back a theory known as the Younger Dryas impact hypothesis. This suggests that debris from a disintegrating comet entering Earth's atmosphere struck areas in the Americas, the Middle East and Europe some 12,800 years ago." "Kennet says that the settlement at Abu Hureyra would have been "abruptly destroyed" by such an event."SOURCES: University of California Santa Barbara, Scientific Reportshttps://www.news.ucsb.edu/2020/019823/fire-skyhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-020-60867-w***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 07:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/11/3973902/3973902_87E4A2AF29864A15ACE5AA77488B4C28_200311_3973902_Ancient_settlement_destroyed_by_comet__research__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Comet, asteroid, abu hureyra, ancient humans, comet ancient humanity, early human, extinction events, space, human history, science, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973835</guid>
      <title>Dubai plans to build sky transportation system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDubai's Roads & Transport Authority has announced it is working in collaboration with British company Beemcar to construct a driverless cable-car network that would operate above the city streets.According to CNN, each electric pod would have four individual seats. The pods are set to travel at 50 kilometers per hour and stand at 7.5 meters above the city streets, supported by carbon composite beams.According to Beemcar, the electric pod system would be able to transport roughly 20,000 passengers per hour along routes that are designed to cover the busiest areas of the city.Beemcar isn't the first foreign company to collaborate with Dubai in developing aerial transportation systems. American SkyTran and Belarusian company Skyway are also collaborating with the city's transportation authorities.These collaborations are part of the city's effort to reach its goal of making 25 percent of its urban transportation driverless by 2030.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dubai's collaboration with Beemcar to develop sky transportation system.2. Infrastructure of the sky pods 3. Sky pods transporting several individuals and riding through the city.4. Showing different skypods around the city.VOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: "Dubai's Roads & Transport Authority has announced it is working in collaboration with British company Beemcar to construct a driverless cable-car network that would operate above the city streets.""According to CNN, each electric pod would have four individual seats. The pods are set to travel at 50 kilometers per hour and stand at 7.5 meters above the city streets, supported by carbon composite beams.""According to Beemcar, the electric pod system would be able to transport roughly 20,000 passengers per hour along routes that are designed to cover the busiest areas of the city."***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/11/3973835/3973835_C69A521771F347818207BBBE230EB8DE_200311_3973835_Dubai_plans_to_build_sky_transportation_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dubai, skypod, dubai skytrain, dubai skypod, dubai beemcar, beemcar, sky transportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974721</guid>
      <title>'Iron rain' found on exoplanet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found evidence of molten iron rain driven by extreme heat on an exoplanet 640 lightyears from Earth, according to new research.Exoplanet WASP-76b is found in the Gemini constellation where its close orbit to a star causes extreme temperatures on one side of the planet, while the other side is cooler.According to Physics World, the conditions are hot enough to break down molecules into atoms on the side exposed to the star. On the darker side these can recombine into molecules.The exoplanet orbits the star differently to how Earth orbits the Sun. Earth rotates as it circles the sun. The exoplanet does not. The Guardian reports that, similar to Earth's moon, the exoplanet is "tidally locked". This means that only one side of the planet is continually exposed to the star, while the other is locked in darkness. It's these conditions that are believed to create the exoplanet's extreme weather conditions and iron rain.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of extreme weather conditions on exoplanet2. How the extreme weather causes iron rain3. How the exoplanet orbits its star4. Depiction of iron rain on exoplanetVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have found evidence of molten iron rain driven by extreme heat on an exoplanet 640 lightyears from Earth""Exoplanet WASP-76b is found in the Gemini constellation where its close orbit to a star causes extreme temperatures on one side of the planet, while the other side is cooler.""According to Physics World, the conditions are hot enough to break down molecules into atoms on the side exposed to the star. On the darker side these can recombine into molecules.""The exoplanet orbits the star differently to how Earth orbits the Sun. Earth rotates as it circles the sun. The exoplanet does not. "The Guardian reports that, similar to Earth's moon, the exoplanet is "tidally locked". "This means that only one side of the planet is continually exposed to the star, while the other is locked in darkness." "It's these conditions that are believed to create the exoplanet's extreme weather conditions and iron rain."SOURCES: PHYSICS WORLD, NATURE, GUARDIANhttps://physicsworld.com/a/iron-rain-on-exoplanet-is-driven-by-huge-extremes-in-temperature/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-2107-1.epdf?referrer_access_token=56ktVHef7TroJ1_LjHBMlNRgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0NYq1mnfS3gXQsKbxGmaZ59X7YPltXqnt97Uzw1n-RRTlSrEXcSK8L0EOVZSanIzY02IQtI3B5WgJ1xhOfhlA0oQgR0gmsenhpyUIdlTqgeeVKTrxHQA78eDyNNCh8pKOyRDIMj4Ba-OjO1zA7e0GA6oz2i4IPT2MhHOkmaP45Rk8sz4Q2P21_DCu-ZFU6Jl85mEqVPrE_jm4wVlKBDbXHIxeu04rXTFBahwCkze6fqwfVadDo2ogJXnmLDrtandJs%3D&tracking_referrer=physicsworld.comhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/mar/11/scientists-identify-rain-of-molten-iron-on-distant-exoplanet***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 07:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/13/3974721/3974721_26A718FA9CC9473E97CAF078C95BBAFE_200313_3974721__Iron_rain__found_on_exoplanet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Iron rain, wasp76b, pisces constellation, hot rain, space weather, space research, iron rain research, weird weather, extreme weather]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974635</guid>
      <title>Sea turtles are attracted to the smell of ocean plastics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew evidence suggests that sea turtles are drawn to the smell of plastic debris found in the ocean, according to a report published in Current Biology.The research team conducted experiments on 15 five-month-old captive loggerhead turtles.They placed each of the turtles into an isolated container where they would be exposed to the odor of four different items in random order: turtle food, clean plastic debris, deionized water, and plastic that was purposely exposed to a marine environment for five weeks so it would become coated with marine microbes.The turtles were given roughly one minute inside the container before being exposed to the odor of the items. The airborne particles were supplied into the container through a pipe and a fan outside of the isolated tank for two minutes. Researchers observed the turtles' behavior for four minutes after being exposed to the odors.Results showed that turtles were attracted by the scent of turtle food and bio-fouled plastic equally. When exposed to these two items, turtles kept their nares above the water three times longer than they did when exposed to clean plastics and deionized water.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Loggerhead turtle swimming towards ocean plastic2. Odors the loggerhead turtle is exposed to3. Odor particles are funneled into pool where turtle is being contained4. Turtle is attracted to ocean plastics and turtle foodVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report published in Current Biology, new evidence suggests that sea turtles are drawn to the smell of plastic debris found in the ocean." "The research team conducted experiments on 15 five-month-old captive loggerhead turtles.""They placed each of the turtles into an isolated container where they would be exposed to the odor of four different items in random order: turtle food, clean plastic debris, deionized water, and plastic that was purposely exposed to a marine environment for five weeks so it would become coated with marine microbes.""The turtles were given roughly one minute inside the container before being exposed to the odor of the items. The airborne particles were supplied into the container through a pipe and a fan outside of the isolated tank for two minutes. Researchers observed the turtles' behavior for four minutes after being exposed to the odors.""Results showed that turtles were attracted by the scent of turtle food and bio-fouled plastic equally. When exposed to these two items, turtles kept their nares above the water three times longer than they did when exposed to clean plastics and deionized water."SOURCES: Current Biology, BBC Newshttps://www.cell.com/action/showPdf?pii=S0960-9822%2820%2930115-9https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51804884***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 03:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/13/3974635/3974635_0A1CE5805EA94F6BAD6F8862CF946F43_200313_3974635_Sea_turtles_are_attracted_to_the_smell_of_ocean__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic pollution, pollution in the ocean, plastic in the ocean, turtles, marine turtle, turtles eat plastic, loggerhead turtle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975779</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How the coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2) infects human cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from China have used cryo-electron microscopy to show how the virus responsible for COVID-19 infects humans via a subtype of ACE2 receptor that has never been discovered before.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SARS-CoV-2 can bind with cellular receptors in the lungs and other organs.2. Goblet and ciliated lung cells are specifically targeted3. Viral spike protein's receptor binding domains 4. COVID-19 attacks a previously unknown type of ACE-2 receptor5. The virus' upward facing RBD crucial for infecting humans6. Virus take over  endoplasmic reticulum to replicate RNA, proteins7. Hijacked Golbi body assembles new viruses8. Stress from viral infection leads to cellular deathVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from China have used cryo-electron microscopy to show how SARS-CoV-2 infects humans. The study published in Science says the virus targets a type of receptor found on human cells in the lungs, heart, kidneys and intestines.""Citing Kingston University microbiologist Mark Fielder, Sky News reports that the virus seems to attack two types of lung cells: goblet cells that coat the respiratory tract with mucus, and ciliated cells that usually filter out pathogens.""A previous study published in Science found the virus' spike protein has two receptor binding domains, or RBDs, facing downward and another facing upward. These allow the virus to bind with and invade human cells.""According to the new study, the virus targets a human ACE2 receptor that has bonded with an amino acid transporter. This subtype of ACE2 structure has never been discovered before.""The virus uses the spike protein's 'up' RBD to penetrate the cell. The virus then dissolves its own protein shell and releases its RNA payload inside the cell, according to the British Society for Immunology.""A study in Frontiers in Microbiology says a coronavirus hijacks the cell's structure to reproduce. The viral RNA takes over the host cell's endoplasmic reticulum to replicate itself and to manufacture the protein parts to make new viruses.""According to the Society for Immunology, the hijacked cell's Golgi bodies then package viral RNA and proteins in a viral protein shell. This leads to the creation of new viruses that leave the infected cell via the membrane.""The study in Frontiers in Microbiology says coronavirus takeover imposes stress on the host cell. Cell death, or apoptosis, is the result when the infection overwhelms the host cell's ability to maintain homeostasis."SOURCES:Science, Sky News, Drugtargetreview.com, British Society for Immunology, Frontiers in Microbiology, the Russian Journal of Inorganic Chemistryhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2020/03/03/science.abb2762.fullhttps://news.sky.com/story/coronavirus-how-does-covid-19-attack-the-human-body-11947643https://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2020/02/19/science.abb2507https://www.drugtargetreview.com/news/56895/scientists-demonstrate-how-covid-19-infects-human-cells/https://www.immunology.org/public-information/bitesized-immunology/pathogens-and-disease/virus-replicationhttps://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fmicb.2014.00296/fullhttps://www.researchgate.net/publication/269040074_Advances_and_prospects_of_using_nanocrystalline_ceria_in_cancer_theranostics***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 08:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/16/3975779/3975779_D120857F7D294F8E8911414ACD25CEF9_200316_3975779_Explainer__How_the_coronavirus__SARS_CoV_2__infe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media,  COVID-19, SARS-COV-2, coronavirus, spike protein, receptors, S1, S2, receptor binding domains, receptor binding domain, RBD, RBDs, ACE2 receptors, ACE2, receptor, receptors, human cells, protein structures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975740</guid>
      <title>Vape additive creates toxic ketene gas: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMedical researchers from Ireland have linked vitamin E acetate to vaping illness. According to new research published in PANAS, the substance is commonly found in illegal THC-based vaping cartridges.The Royal College of Surgeons in Ireland's research team says in a news release that heating the normally harmless substance through vaping produces ketene, a highly toxic gas.The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention sounded the alarm on vaping illness after detecting a rash of lung injury cases that appear to be related to e-cigarette use that began in August 2019.The researchers say ketene can cause severe lung damage up to 24 hours after exposure. Citing doctors at the Mayo Clinic, the New York Times reports the lung injuries of vaping illness patients resembled those of industrial accident-related chemical burns.According to a report in the New England Journal of Medicine, vitamin E acetate was in the lung liquid samples taken from 48 out of 51 cases of vaping illness, or close to 94 percent.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Researchers identify vitamin E acetate as a probable cause of vaping illness2. Vaping device heats the substance, turning it into a ketene3. Ketene can cause severe lung injuries 4. The substance is found in lung liquid samples in 94 percent of vaping illness patientsVOICEOVER (in English): "Medical researchers from Ireland have linked vitamin E acetate to vaping illness. According to new research published in PANAS, the substance is commonly found in illegal THC-based vaping cartridges.""The Royal College of Surgeons in Ireland's research team says in a news release that heating the normally harmless substance through vaping produces ketene[a], a highly toxic gas.""The researchers say ketene can cause severe lung damage up to 24 hours after exposure. Citing doctors at the Mayo Clinic, the New York Times reports the lung injuries of vaping illness patients resembled those of industrial accident-related chemical burns.""According to a report in the New England Journal of Medicine, vitamin E acetate was in the lung liquid samples taken from 48 out of 51 cases of vaping illness, or close to 94 percent."SOURCES: PANAS, Royal College of Surgeons in Ireland (Medical Express), New York Times, CDChttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2020/03/09/1920925117.short?rss=1&utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+Pnas-RssFeedOfEarlyEditionArticles+%28Latest+Articles%29https://m.medicalxpress.com/news/2020-03-vaping-chemical-toxic-ketene-gas.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/02/health/vaping-illnesses.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/tobacco/basic_information/e-cigarettes/severe-lung-disease.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/16/3975740/3975740_4F46D80D35B14A8EBD42DAA5F019FA4F_200316_3975740_Vape_additive_creates_toxic_ketene_gas__study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, E-cigarettes, vaping, vape, vaping illness, ketene, toxic gas, lung injuries, evali, Royal College of Surgeons in Ireland, Ireland, CDC, health, US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975640</guid>
      <title>COVID-19 can survive on some surfaces for up to three days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research by American health officials and experts published in medRxiv shows that the novel coronavirus can survive in air particles for several hours and on some surfaces for up to three days.Researchers used a nebulizer machine to spread the coronavirus in the air and on several surfaces in a controlled environment. The device was used to emulate how the coronavirus would disperse if an infected individual coughed.  Results showed that the virus was still detectable in the air three hours after it was spread.It was also detectable on copper surfaces for up to four hours, on cardboard surfaces for up to 24 hours and on plastic and stainless steel surfaces for up to two to three days.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  A person spreads coronavirus particles in their bathroom2.  Researchers use a nebulizer to emulate the spread of coronavirus in a controlled environment3. Coronavirus particles survive for three hours in the air4. Visualization of how long coronavirus particles survive on different surfacesVOICEOVER (in English): "New research by American health officials and experts published in medRxiv shows that the novel coronavirus can survive in air particles for several hours and on some surfaces for up to three days.""Researchers used a nebulizer machine to spread the coronavirus in the air and on several surfaces in a controlled environment. The device was used to emulate how the coronavirus would disperse if an infected individual coughed. ""Results showed that the virus was still detectable in the air three hours after it was spread.""It was also detectable on copper surfaces for up to four hours, on cardboard surfaces for up to 24 hours and on plastic and stainless steel surfaces for up to two to three days."SOURCES: medRxiv, Medical Xpresshttps://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.09.20033217v1.full.pdfhttps://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-03-coronavirus-surfaces-days.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 02:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/16/3975640/3975640_0F4E3249DBB84E89BF11E1E8F84BDCC3_200316_3975640_COVID_19_can_survive_on_some_surfaces_for_up_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Covid-19, coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, coronavirus precautions, coronavirus covid-19]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976174</guid>
      <title>Self-sufficient home allows residents to grow vegetables indoors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn architectural firm based in Shanghai has unveiled a futuristic, zero-waste house that allows residents to power their own homes and grow their own produce in a living space of 150 square meters. Yang Design's Green Concept House features solar panels and wind turbines that would be used to provide power to the house. Spare energy from electricity consumption would then be used to convert water vapor from the air into water drops using condensation panels on the roof of the house.Circular incubators present throughout the green house would allow residents to grow plants and vegetables indoors. Water drops created from the condensation panels would be deposited to a circular pool which would regulate water flow to each circular incubator.This system would be connected via a smartphone app, allowing residents to monitor their in-home garden using the app even if they are away from home. The app would alert homeowners with an alarm if one of the plants is in need of specific care or send out a notification if a vegetable or a plant is ready to be picked.The architectural firm explained on its website that this futuristic design could create a new means of communication between separated individuals and allow them to bond over the vegetable garden as well as redefine the concept of agriculture.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Green Concept House 2. How the house would be powered3. How plants could be grown inside the house4. Resident using a smartphone app to monitor plant growth5. Resident harvesting the produceVOICEOVER (in English): "Shanghai-based Yang Design has unveiled a futuristic Green Concept House that has 150 square meters of living space.""Solar panels and wind turbines would be used to provide power to the house.""Spare energy from electricity consumption would then be used to convert water vapor from the air into water drops using condensation panels on the roof of the house.""Circular incubators present throughout the green house would allow residents to grow plants and vegetables indoors.""Water drops created from the condensation panels would be deposited to a circular pool which would regulate water flow to each circular incubator.""This system would be connected via a smartphone app, allowing residents to monitor their in-home garden using the app even if they are away from home.""The app would alert homeowners with an alarm if one of the plants is in need of specific care or send out a notification if a vegetable or a plant is ready to be picked."SOURCES:  Inhabitat, Yang Design, Arch Dailyhttps://inhabitat.com/a-zero-waste-self-sustaining-home-of-the-future/http://www.yang-design.com/museumhttps://www.archdaily.com/934277/green-house-yang-design***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 07:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/17/3976174/3976174_7815C8B1CE154E5D86384FD9EF943E93_200317_3976174_Self_sufficient_home_allows_residents_to_grow_ve_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Green concept house, yang design, yang design green concept house, e-Vege House, green house, futuristic houses, self-sustaining houses, self-sufficient houses, future homes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976675</guid>
      <title>Israel uses geolocation data to fight the coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIsrael plans to combat the coronavirus outbreak via the cyber-monitoring of its citizens, according to Reuters.The New York Times reports the country will monitor cell phones to track people with COVID-19 and those who have come into close contact with them. The Israeli government will comb through the geolocation data gathered from the country's telecommunications providers to pinpoint those affected.This will then be used to track the history of the infected person's movements and to identify potentially infected individuals. Once identified, those suspected of catching the virus will receive a message telling them to self isolate immediately.According to the Thomson Reuters Foundation, there are 324 cases of the virus in Israel, 41 in Palestine and none in the Gaza Strip.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of an infected man coughing in a busy street2. Depiction of technology used to track the infected man3. Depiction of other people being tracked nearby the infected man4. Depiction of someone near the infected man later receiving a message to isolate themselvesVOICEOVER (in English): "The New York Times reports Israel will monitor cell phones to track people with COVID-19 and those who have come into close contact with them.""The government will comb through the geolocation data gathered from the country's telecommunications providers to pinpoint those affected.""This will then be used to track the history of the infected person's movements and to identify potentially infected individuals."  "Once identified, those suspected of catching the virus will receive a message telling them to self isolate immediately."SOURCES: Reuters, New York Times, Thomson Reuters Foundation, https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-israel/israel-to-fast-track-cyber-monitoring-of-coronavirus-cases-idUSKBN2133SPhttps://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/16/world/middleeast/israel-coronavirus-cellphone-tracking.htmlhttps://news.trust.org/item/20200317094316-biskl/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 09:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/18/3976675/3976675_7552739E35DE42F1834031F04C59EEF9_200318_3976675_Israel_uses_geolocation_data_to_fight_the_corona_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19 Israel, geolocation, Mass surveillance, israel coronavirus, palestine coronavirus, shin bet, benjamin netanyahu]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976658</guid>
      <title>Experts explain what viruses are</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA virus is made of nucleic acids surrounded by a protein shell. There are many types of viruses; some like the coronavirus have RNA-based genetic material, while others contain a DNA-based genome. According to the National Human Genome Research Institute, viruses straddle the definition of being living and nonliving. This is because viruses can only move or reproduce by infecting living cells, according to a study published in PubMed Central.The PubMed study explains the human immune system can fight off viruses by deploying B-cells. These white blood cells produce antibodies that eradicate viruses before they get into cells.The British Society of Immunology reports that another way the immune system fights viruses is to send killer T-cells to search and destroy infected cells. Since the immune response is attacking the body itself, it also causes stress to the patient.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Virus are comprised of protein-coated RNA or DNA genetic material 2. Viruses replicate by infecting living organisms3. B-cells create antibodies that could neutralize viruses before cellular infection4. T-cells destroy cells that had been infected by virusesVOICEOVER (in English): "A virus is made of nucleic acids surrounded by a protein shell. There are many types of viruses; some like the coronavirus have RNA-based genetic material, while others contain a DNA-based genome.""According to the National Human Genome Research Institute, viruses straddle the definition of being living and nonliving. This is because viruses can only move or reproduce by infecting living cells, according to a study published in PubMed Central.""The PubMed study explains the human immune system can fight off viruses by deploying B-cells. These white blood cells produce antibodies that eradicate viruses before they get into cells.""The British Society of Immunology reports that another way the immune system fights viruses is to send killer T-cells to search and destroy infected cells. Since the immune response is attacking the body itself, it also causes stress to the patient."SOURCES: National Human Genome Research Institute, PubMed Central, USA Todayhttps://www.genome.gov/genetics-glossary/Virushttps://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5406846/https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/30886356https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/03/15/coronavirus-covid-19-pandemic-what-virus-viruses-alive/5038734002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 08:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/18/3976658/3976658_4273F70934A64392A1A41929C0576C8D_200318_3976658_Experts_explain_what_viruses_are_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, COVD-19, SARS-CoV-2, viruses, virus, infection, immune system, antibody, antibodies, t-cells, b-cells, white blood cell, white blood cells, immune response, virology, immunology, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976530</guid>
      <title>Microplastics alter fish respiratory, reproductive systems: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study from Duke University has found that microplastic fibers can cause damage to the respiratory and reproductive systems of the Japanese medaka fish.For the study, researchers placed 27 pairs of the fish in a water tank with large amounts of suspended microplastic fibers.On a weekly basis, scientists monitored egg production, weight and the amount of fiber that was ingested and excreted out by the medaka fish.After 21 days, researchers examined the tissue of the Japanese medaka fish and found that those exposed to larger amounts of microplastic fibers had developed fused membranes and increased mucus production in their gills. The microfibers had also caused damage to the epithelial cells lining the fish gills. Female fish exposed to the microfibers had been found to produce more eggs over this period of time.The study also found that microplastic fibers residing in fish guts may release harmful chemical coatings that could leak into the bloodstream of the fish.Melissa Chernick, a researcher involved with the study, explained in a Duke University news release from March 16 that if wild fish swimming in the ocean damage their gills, it would make the fish less competitive while looking for food and less able to guard against potential predators in the sea.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Japanese medaka fish and microplastic fibers2. How researchers conducted the study3. Effect of microfibers on the fish4. Microplastic fibers in fish gutsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study from Duke University has found that microplastic fibers can cause damage to the respiratory and reproductive systems of the Japanese medaka fish.""For the study, researchers placed 27 pairs of the fish in a water tank with large amounts of suspended microplastic fibers.""On a weekly basis, scientists monitored egg production, weight and the amount of fiber that was ingested and excreted out by the medaka fish.""After 21 days, researchers examined the tissue of the Japanese medaka fish and found that those exposed to larger amounts of microplastic fibers had developed fused membranes and increased mucus production in their gills." "The microfibers had also caused damage to the epithelial cells lining the fish gills.""Female fish exposed to the microfibers had been found to produce more eggs over this period of time.""The study also found that microplastic fibers residing in fish guts may release harmful chemical coatings that could leak into the bloodstream of the fish."SOURCES: PLoS ONE, Duke University https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0229962https://today.duke.edu/2020/03/microplastic-fibers-linked-respiratory-reproductive-changes-fish***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 03:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/18/3976530/3976530_4B739330575E4116AD72C0120E0E2270_200318_3976530_Microplastics_alter_fish_respiratory__reproducti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Japanese medaka fish, microplastic fibers, microplastic fibers in fish, Japanese medaka fish microplastic fibers, microplastics, microplastic pollution, microplastic particles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977247</guid>
      <title>How the novel coronavirus progresses from day to day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese scientists have identified a pattern of day-to-day symptoms typical of patients with coronavirus in a new study. The study, published in the journal JAMA, looked at 138 patients hospitalized with novel coronavirus-infected pneumonia at the Zhongnan Hospital of Wuhan University. Fever is typically the first symptom experienced by those infected with SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes coronavirus disease 2019, according to the study of patients in Wuhan. Some COVID-19 patients may also experience fatigue, muscle pain and a dry cough.By day five, this transitions into breathing difficulties, especially for the elderly or those with preexisting health conditions. The study found it took patients an average of seven days after running a fever before they were admitted to a hospital.By day eight, those with severe symptoms had developed acute respiratory distress syndrome, or ARDS, which can be fatal. This is when fluid builds up in the lungs.Patients with worsening symptoms are typically admitted to the intensive care unit by day 10. These patients are probably experiencing more abdominal pain and loss of appetite than those with milder symptoms.On average, it took patients with COVID-19 roughly two and a half weeks to recover from the illness and be discharged from the hospital.According to CNN, as of March 19 there were 215,000 coronavirus cases globally. The death toll has surpassed 8,000.Countries such as Argentina, Canada and Taiwan as well as the European Union have shut their borders in order to slow the spread of the disease.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Typical initial symptoms of SARS-CoV-22. The elderly with breathing difficulties3. Severe symptoms causes fluid to build up in the lungs4. A patient in the ICU VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the study of patients in Wuhan, fever is typically the first symptom experienced by those infected with SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes coronavirus disease 2019.""Some COVID-19 patients may also experience fatigue, muscle pain and a dry cough.""By day five, this transitions into breathing difficulties, especially for the elderly or those with preexisting health conditions.""The study found it took patients an average of seven days after running a fever before they were admitted to a hospital.""By day eight, those with severe symptoms had developed acute respiratory distress syndrome, or ARDS, which can be fatal.""This is when fluid builds up in the lungs.""Patients with worsening symptoms are typically admitted to the intensive care unit by day 10.""These patients are probably experiencing more abdominal pain and loss of appetite than those with milder symptoms."SOURCES: JAMA, Business Insider, CNN, Al Jazeera  https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2761044https://www.businessinsider.com/coronavirus-covid19-day-by-day-symptoms-patients-2020-2https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-19-20-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2020/03/coronavirus-travel-restrictions-border-shutdowns-country-200318091505922.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/19/3977247/3977247_BFD351368CCF4A04AB7854768AF704A6_200319_3977247_How_the_novel_coronavirus_progresses_from_day_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19, COVID-19 virus, COVID-19 pandemic, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, day to day symptoms coronavirus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977186</guid>
      <title>U.S. tests experimental COVID-19 vaccine on first volunteer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA U.S. volunteer became the first person to receive an experimental COVID-19 vaccine as part of the first phase of humans trial on March 16, the Associated Press reports.According to Kaiser Permanente, which is funded by the National Institutes of Health to conduct the project, the vaccine eschews dead or inert viruses and instead utilizes messenger RNA, or mRNA.A previous study in Molecular Theory suggests engineered mRNA could cause ribosomes in human cells to manufacture artificially designed proteins.According to Kaiser Permanente, their vaccine would make cells produce a protein that is found in the outer coating of SARS-CoV-2, which triggers an immune response.If a person who received the vaccine is later infected with COVID-19, their prior immune response may help their body mount a stronger reaction to the real virus infection.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Kaiser Permanente tests experimental COVID-19 vaccine on first volunteer2. Messenger RNA vaccine makes cells produce viral proteins3. Viral protein triggers immune response4. Prior immune response is then expected to strengthen immune reaction to COVID-19VOICEOVER (in English): "A U.S. volunteer became the first person to receive an experimental COVID-19 vaccine as part of the first phase of humans trial on March 16, the Associated Press reports.""According to Kaiser Permanente, which is funded by the National Institutes of Health to conduct the project, the vaccine eschews dead or inert viruses and instead utilizes messenger RNA, or mRNA.""A previous study in Molecular Theory suggests engineered mRNA could cause ribosomes in human cells to manufacture artificially designed proteins.""According to Kaiser Permanente, their vaccine would make cells produce a protein that is found in the outer coating of SARS-CoV-2, which triggers an immune response.""If a person who received the vaccine is later infected with COVID-19, their prior immune response may help their body mount a stronger reaction to the real virus infection."SOURCES: National Institutes of Health, Associated Press, Kaiser Permanente, Molecular Therapy, Live Sciencehttps://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/nih-clinical-trial-investigational-vaccine-covid-19-beginshttps://apnews.com/76b614811eef32955180c8260188bc24https://www.cell.com/molecular-therapy-family/molecular-therapy/fulltext/S1525-0016(19)30088-7?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS1525001619300887%3Fshowall%3Dtruehttps://www.livescience.com/first-person-coronavirus-vaccine-clinical-trial.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 09:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/19/3977186/3977186_1F37B29E9739419A9E1CE00AFD1BB504_200319_3977186_U_S__tests_experimental_COVID_19_vaccine_on_firs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media,Vaccine, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, wuhan virus, coronavirus, mRNA, messanger RNA, clinical trial, Kaiser Permanente, US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977646</guid>
      <title>Mercury's extreme temperatures may cause ice to form</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMercury's close orbit around the sun and extreme heat may have helped the planet to generate ice. Writing in the Astrophysical Journal Letters, scientists say solar wind may contribute to a chemical process that forms ice in Mercury's poles.While much of Mercury is very hot, the planet lacks an atmosphere to dissipate the heat. According to Space.com, this allows pockets of cold to exist in the shadows of polar craters, which preserve the ice on Mercury.In a news release from Georgia Institute of Technology, researchers say Mercury's soil contains hydroxyl [a]groups, or bonded hydrogen and oxygen. After solar winds bombard the substance to 400 degrees Celsius, the oxygen and hydrogen break free to form water.The scientists say that according to their model, some of the water molecules would break down into their constituent atoms, but the remainder would escape and land on Mercury's poles. This creates ice deposits in the craters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ice exists in Mercury's poles despite close orbit and high temperatures2. Permanent shadows likely preserve ice in Mercury's polar craters3. Solar wind causes hydroxyl groups in Mecurian soil and minerals to form water4. Escaped water that landed in polar regions becomes iceVOICEOVER (in English): "Mercury's close orbit around the sun and extreme heat may have helped the planet to generate ice. Writing in the Astrophysical Journal Letters, scientists say solar wind may contribute to a chemical process that forms ice in Mercury's poles.""While much of Mercury is very hot, the planet lacks an atmosphere to dissipate the heat. According to Space.com, this allows pockets of cold to exist in the shadows of polar craters, which preserve the ice on Mercury.""In a news release from Georgia Institute of Technology, researchers say Mercury's soil contains hydroxyl [b]groups, or bonded hydrogen and oxygen. After solar winds bombard the substance to 400 degrees Celsius, the oxygen and hydrogen break free to form water.""The scientists say that according to their model, some of the water molecules would break down into their constituent atoms, but the remainder would escape and land on Mercury's poles. This creates ice deposits in the craters."SOURCES: The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Georgia Institute of Technology, Space.comhttps://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-03/giot-m4c031320.phphttps://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-03/giot-m4c031320.phphttps://www.space.com/mercury-scorching-heat-leads-to-ice.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 09:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/20/3977646/3977646_AF22EA65110C427A83030C1778862EFA_200320_3977646_Mercury_s_extreme_temperatures_may_cause_ice_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Mercury, ice, solar wind, solar winds, charged particles, water, hydroxyl, hydrogen, oxygen, crater, craters, NASA, Messenger, Georgia Tech, Georgia Institute of Technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978580</guid>
      <title>Start-up tracking coronavirus via human waste</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMassachusetts-based Biobot Analytics have launched a probono program to test community sewers for COVID-19.According to Popular Mechanics, the virus can live in human waste. Biobot Analytics aim to track and trace COVID-19 by having communities use their devices to collect samples over a 24-hour period.The company will analyze the data collected and use it to report their findings to impacted areas. If it works, the company says on its website that it will give communities a dynamic map of the virus as it spreads to new areas.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sampling device on US street 2. Sampling device in US Sewer3. Sampling device in US Sewer4. Map of COVID-19 infectionsVOICEOVER (in English): "Massachusetts-based Biobot Analytics have launched a probono program to test community sewers for COVID-19.""According to Popular Mecahnics, the virus can live in human waste." "Biobot Analytics aim to track and trace COVID-19 by having communities use their devices to collect samples over a 24-hour period." "The company will analyze the data collected and use it to report their findings to impacted areas." "If it works, the company says on its website that it will give communities a dynamic map of the virus as it spreads to new areas."SOURCES: Biobot Analytics, Popular Mechanicshttps://www.biobot.io/covid19/https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/health/a31468624/covid-19-spread-sewer-poop/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 08:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/23/3978580/3978580_7CC43EE53DAA471F8EC08B1149C3328E_200323_3978580_Start_up_tracking_coronavirus_via_human_waste_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Biobot analytics, covid-19, sewer map covid-19, biobot coronavirus, science, start-up boston, covid-19 explainer, coronavirus pandemic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978524</guid>
      <title>Japan's shell-lobbing spacecraft takes measure of space rock's age</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLaunched in late 2012, Japan's spacecraft Hayabusa2 was sent to investigate asteroid Ryugu by lobbing a copper shell into the space rock. Japan's space agency JAXA published the probe's findings in the journal Science on March 19.According to JAXA, the Hayabusa is 0.6m across the front, 0.4m from prow to stern, and has four ion thrusters. The spacecraft is equipped with X- and Ka-band antennas for communication and its sensors include optics, LIDAR and spectrometers.According to the study, the Small Carry-on Impactor shell blasted a semicircular crater 14m wide and 0.6m deep, with the shock apparently absorbed by boulders. This confirms that Ruygu is indeed a rubble-pile, or boulders loosely held together by sandy materials.The impact experiment suggests the most ancient materials of the asteroid are up to 4.6 billion years old, but the substance coalesced with other asteroids' remains only 10 million years ago to form Ryugu.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hayabusa2 fires Small Carry-on Impactor at asteroid Ryugu 2. Spacecraft equipment and features3. Analysis of the impact crater 4. Experiment reveals Ryugu's composition and ageVOICEOVER (in English): "Launched in late 2012, Japan's spacecraft Hayabusa2 was sent to investigate asteroid Ryugu by lobbing a copper shell into the space rock. Japan's space agency JAXA published the probe's findings in the journal Science on March 19.""According to JAXA, the Hayabusa is 0.6m across the front, 0.4m from prow to stern, and has four ion thrusters. The spacecraft is equipped with X- and Ka-band antennas for communication and its sensors include optics, LIDAR and spectrometers.""According to the study, the Small Carry-on Impactor shell blasted a semicircular crater 14m wide and 0.6m deep, with the shock apparently absorbed by boulders. This confirms that Ruygu is indeed a rubble-pile, or boulders loosely held together by sandy materials.""The impact experiment suggests the most ancient materials of the asteroid are up to 4.6 billion years old, but the substance coalesced with other asteroids' remains only 10 million years ago to form Ryugu."SOURCES: Science, JAXA, Space.comhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2020/03/18/science.aaz1701http://www.hayabusa2.jaxa.jp/en/enjoy/material/factsheet/FactSheet_en_v2.31s.pdfhttp://www.hayabusa2.jaxa.jp/en/topics/20200318_nature/https://www.space.com/asteroid-ryugu-young-japan-hayabusa2-reveals.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 06:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/23/3978524/3978524_D3EF25847A4F47FFB60178F0384F67B4_200323_3978524_Japan_s_shell_lobbing_spacecraft_takes_measure_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Hayabusa2, Ryugu, asteroid, asteroids, small carry-on impactor, crater, impact experiment, Japan, Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency, JAXA, space, space exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978993</guid>
      <title>Equinox sunset aligns with Sphinx</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA former Egyptian antiquities minister has claimed that a recent image is evidence that the Sphinx was built to align with the equinox.According to Zahi Hawas, former Minister of Antiquities, the image is evidence of an astronomical and religious connection between the sphinx and the spring and autumn equinoxes. An equinox is a cosmic event when day and night are equal in length. Hawas' assertion goes against modern archaeological thinking.Research from 2018 suggests that its construction also may relate to the autumn equinox. According to Newsweek, the Great Pyramid of Giza almost fits with the four cardinal directions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the Sphinx during the equinox2. Depiction of the Sphinx and sun3. Great Pyramid of Giza4. Great Pyramid of Giza and four cardinal directionsVOICEOVER (in English): "An image posted by the Egyptian Ministry of Antiquities showing the sun setting over the Sphinx on the spring equinox may demonstrate that the statue was built to align with the celestial event." "According to Zahi Hawas, former Minister of Antiquities, the image is evidence of an astronomical and religious connection between the sphinx and the spring and autumn equinoxes. "An equinox is a cosmic event when day and night are equal in length. Hawas' assertion goes against modern archaeological thinking.""Research from 2018 suggests that its construction also may relate to the autumn equinox.""According to Newsweek, the Great Pyramid of Giza almost fits with the four cardinal directions."SOURCES: FACEBOOK / MINISTRY OF ANTIQUITIES, NEWSWEEK, ANCIENT ORIGINShttps://www.facebook.com/moantiquities/photos/a.979988385380145/2935261899852774/https://www.newsweek.com/pyramid-ancient-egypt-equinox-1493770https://www.ancient-origins.net/news-history-archaeology/sphinx-alignment-0013459***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 08:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/24/3978993/3978993_E1A809E597D242B8BB4283E6FC6BBA75_200324_3978993_Equinox_sunset_aligns_with_Sphinx_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Science, sphinx, egypt, ancient mysteries, egypt explained, sphinx equinox alignment, sphinx pyramids equinox, ancient civilizations, lost civilizations]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978914</guid>
      <title>Comet ATLAS may be the brightest in years: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANComet ATLAS, also known as C/2019 Y4, is growing brighter at a surprising rate as it hurtles toward the Sun. Space.com reports that as of March 17, the newly discovered comet's magnitude, a measure of its brightness, was +8.5, 600 times brighter than forecasts. It may well become the brightest comet in years.Comets are made of dust, frozen water, ammonia, methane and carbon dioxide. Citing Karl Battams of the U.S. Naval Research Laboratory, Space Weather Archive reports ATLAS is shedding huge amounts of gas and it may yet disintegrate before reaching the Sun.The comet ATLAS is named after the Asteroid Terrestrial-impact Last Alert System, a pair of observatories in Hawaii that first discovered the comet on Dec. 18, 2019.Space Weather Archive reports ATLAS began heating up two months before reaching the Perihelion, or the nearest approach to the Sun. Should it withstand the sun's heat, the comet will loop inside Mercury's orbit and become visible to the naked eye on Earth in April.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Comet ATLAS may become the brightest comet in years2. The comet could disintegrate before it reaches the Sun 3. ATLAS is discovered by the Asteroid Terrestrial-impact Last Alert System in Hawaii4. The predicted trajectory of comet ATLASVOICEOVER (in English): "Comet ATLAS, also known as C/2019 Y4, is growing brighter at a surprising rate as it hurtles toward the Sun. Space.com reports that as of March 17, the newly discovered comet's magnitude, a measure of its brightness, was +8.5, 600 times brighter than forecasts. It may well become the brightest comet in years.""Comets are made of dust, frozen water, ammonia, methane and carbon dioxide. Citing Karl Battams of the U.S. Naval Research Laboratory, Space Weather Archive reports ATLAS is shedding huge amounts of gas and it may yet disintegrate before reaching the Sun.""The comet ATLAS is named after the Asteroid Terrestrial-impact Last Alert System, a pair of observatories in Hawaii that first discovered the comet on Dec. 18, 2019.""Space Weather Archive reports ATLAS began heating up two months before reaching the Perihelion, or the nearest approach to the Sun. Should it withstand the sun's heat, the comet will loop inside Mercury's orbit and become visible to the naked eye on Earth in April."SOURCES: Space.com, NASA, Space Weather Archive,https://www.space.com/comet-atlas-may-be-brightenting.html?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=dlvr.ithttps://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/spitzer/news/spitzer20130723.htmlhttps://spaceweatherarchive.com/2020/03/16/comet-atlas-is-brightening-faster-than-expected/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 06:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/24/3978914/3978914_8EADF12A43524A2394DC1F1794C2CA7D_200324_3978914_Comet_ATLAS_may_be_the_brightest_in_years__repor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, ATLAS, comet, brightest, C/2019 Y4, Mercury, visible to the naked eye, solar winds, C/2019 Y4, U.S. Naval Research Laboratory, Asteroid Terrestrial-impact Last Alert System, Hawaii, Washington, astronomy, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979539</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus RNA can last up to 17 days on surfaces</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to the latest report by the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, RNA material from the coronavirus can last on some surfaces for longer than previous research has shown.Experts analyzed the interior of the Diamond Princess cruise ship, which was quarantined off Yokohama, Japan, and found RNA material from the coronavirus in the cabins of both symptomatic and asymptomatic passengers that had been infected with SARS-CoV-2 up to 17 days after they had left the cruise.This evidence was found prior to disinfection of the rooms.The CDC specified in their report that although RNA of the virus was present, it does not mean live virus was still on the surfaces. It is also unclear whether or not this RNA is infectious.Commenting on the report, the MIT Technology Review says proper disinfection of surfaces kills traces of the coronavirus on all surfaces.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. RNA of the coronavirus2. Residue of coronavirus found inside a cabin of Diamond Princess cruise3. Viruses dissolve4. Experts disinfect cabinVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the latest report by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, RNA material from the coronavirus can last on some surfaces for longer than previous research has shown.""Experts analyzed the interior of the Diamond Princess cruise ship, which was quarantined off Yokohama, Japan, and found RNA material from the coronavirus in the cabins of both symptomatic and asymptomatic passengers that had been infected with SARS-CoV-2 up to 17 days after they had left the cruise.""This evidence was found prior to disinfection of the rooms.""The CDC specified in their report that although RNA of the virus was present, it does not mean live virus was still on the surfaces. It is also unclear whether or not this RNA is infectious.""Commenting on the report, the MIT Technology Review says proper disinfection of surfaces kills traces of the coronavirus on all surfaces."SOURCES: Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, MIT Technology Review https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/69/wr/pdfs/mm6912e3-H.pdfhttps://www.technologyreview.com/s/615402/coronavirus-might-last-on-surfaces-for-a-lot-longer-than-we-thought/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 12:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/25/3979539/3979539_B7378493FE704C68A154E997B57D0367_200325_3979539_Coronavirus_RNA_can_last_up_to_17_days_on_surfac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, covid-19, coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, coronavirus precautions, coronavirus covid-19, diamond princess cruise, covid-19 diamond princess cruise]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979447</guid>
      <title>Ancient wormlike creature is possibly the common ancestor of most animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGeologists examining fossil impressions from South Australia have found evidence of the earliest relative of most animal life on Earth, a tiny, wormlike creature that lived 555 million years ago, according to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.Writing in a news release, scientists at the University of California, Riverside say laser scans suggest the Ikaria wariootia was about the size of a grain of rice, 7mm long and 2.5mm wide at the largest. They were wide in the head, narrow in the rear, and possessed bilateral symmetry. This suggests they had a mouth, anus and gut.The wormlike creatures are the oldest animals ever found to possess bilateral symmetry. This suggests they may be the first common ancestors to animals organized along the bilateral body plan, including dinosaurs, insects and humans.According to the news release, bilateral symmetry was a crucial evolutionary step that gave animals an efficient way to organize their body and to move purposefully.The ocean floor-dwelling creatures lived during the Ediacaran Period. Scientists say the worms likely possessed senses that allowed them to navigate the well-oxygenated sands and search for organic matter to consume.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Scientists identify Ikaria wariootia from fossil impressions2. The creature shows bilateral symmetry3. Ikaria wariootia is possibly the ancestor of all bilaterally symmetrical animals4. The creature is speculated to possess sensory organsVOICEOVER (in English): "Geologists examining fossil impressions from South Australia have found evidence of the earliest relative of most animal life on Earth, a tiny, wormlike creature that lived 555 million years ago, according to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.""Writing in a news release, scientists at the University of California, Riverside say laser scans suggest the Ikaria wariootia was about the size of a grain of rice, 7mm long and 2.5mm wide at the largest. They were wide in the head, narrow in the rear, and possessed bilateral symmetry. This suggests they had a mouth, anus and gut.""The wormlike creatures are the oldest animals ever found to possess bilateral symmetry. This suggests they may be the first common ancestors to animals organized along the bilateral body plan, including dinosaurs, insects and humans.""The ocean floor-dwelling creatures lived during the Ediacaran Period. Scientists say the worms likely possessed senses that allowed them to navigate the well-oxygenated sands and search for organic matter to consume."SOURCES: Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the U.S., University of California Riversidehttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2020/03/17/2001045117https://news.ucr.edu/articles/2020/03/23/ancestor-all-animals-identified-australian-fossils***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 09:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/25/3979447/3979447_2E560D30C81A451890C7CCD91D00AB6D_200325_3979447_Ancient_wormlike_creature_is_possibly_the_common_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ancient worm, accient worms, worms, bilateral symmetry, bilateral, Ediacaran Period, Edicaran biota, paleontology, University California, Riverside, UC Riverside, Australia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979850</guid>
      <title>Exhaust fumes from container ships influence cloud composition and reflect solar radiation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research suggests that exhaust fumes from container ships could be delaying the effects of climate change.According to the University of Washington, exhaust fumes from container ships have sulfate particles that attract water molecules. These transform into cloud droplets that can pack clouds and, in turn, reflect solar radiation before it warms the ocean. Researchers looked at satellite data from one of the busiest Atlantic shipping lanes from between 2003 and 2015. They calculated what the lane would've looked like with emissions and without. They say that the difference helps to clarify how much industrial pollution influences clouds.The University of Washington posits that without the cooling effect of these sulfate particles then the Earth may have already heated by 1.5 degrees Celsius. This is a change deemed to have significant societal impacts by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of container ship exhaust fumes2. Depiction of sulfate particles reflecting solar radiation3. Depiction of Earth with and without sulfate particles4. Depiction of Earth heating by 1.5 degrees CelsiusVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the University of Washington, exhaust fumes from container ships have sulfate particles that attract water molecules.""These transform into cloud droplets that can pack clouds and, in turn, reflect solar radiation before it warms the ocean." "Researchers looked at satellite data from one of the busiest Atlantic shipping lanes from between 2003 and 2015." "They calculated what the lane would've looked like with emissions and without. They say that the difference helps to clarify how much industrial pollution influences clouds.""The University of Washington posits that without the cooling effect of these sulfate particles the Earth may have already heated by 1.5 degrees Celsius." "This is a change deemed to have significant societal impacts by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change." SOURCES: University of Washingtonhttps://www.washington.edu/news/2020/03/24/ships-emissions-create-measurable-regional-change-in-clouds/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 08:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/26/3979850/3979850_1A852DA1CD5A40529A7D9F18E4ADE08E_200326_3979850_Exhaust_fumes_from_container_ships_influence_clo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Climate change, container shipping, global warming, delaying global warming, delaying climate change, impact of climate change, science, explainer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3980387</guid>
      <title>Trump's border wall could threaten jaguar recovery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. President Donald Trump's new plans to accelerate the construction of the border wall poses a great threat to biodiversity and the environment, and in particular the jaguar.On March 16, the Department of Homeland Security announced it will waive a number of environmental laws and regulations to accelerate the construction of border walls in Pima[a], Santa Cruz and Cochise[b] counties in Arizona. According to the Center for Biological Diversity, parts of the new border walls will run through remote natural environments and block jaguars from migrating between Mexico and the southwestern U.S.They will also isolate a small breeding population of northern jaguars in Sonora, Mexico  hindering repopulation efforts.The jaguar is the largest cat in the Americas and one of the four big cats of the Panthera genus, the others being the lion, tiger and leopard.Inhabitat reports other animals that will be negatively impacted by the new border walls are the Mexican gray wolf, the lesser long-nosed bat, the ocelot, the Sonoran pronghorn and the cactus ferruginous pygmy owl.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Areas where border wall will be built2. Areas where border walls will affect migration3. Area where breeding populations of jaguars exist4. Other animals affected by border wall constructionVOICEOVER (in English): "On March 16, the Department of Homeland Security announced it will waive a number of environmental laws and regulations to accelerate the construction of border walls in Pima, Santa Cruz and Cochise counties in Arizona. ""According to the Center for Biological Diversity, parts of the new border walls will run through remote natural environments and block jaguars from migrating between Mexico and the southwestern U.S.""They will also isolate a small breeding population of northern jaguars in Sonora, Mexico  hindering repopulation efforts.""Inhabitat reports other animals that will be negatively impacted by the new border walls are the Mexican gray wolf, the lesser long-nosed bat, the ocelot, the Sonoran pronghorn and the cactus ferruginous pygmy owl."SOURCES: Center for Biological Diversity, Department of Homeland Securityhttps://www.biologicaldiversity.org/programs/international/borderlands_and_boundary_waters/pdfs/A_Wall_in_the_Wild.pdfhttps://biologicaldiversity.org/w/news/press-releases/new-border-wall-segments-would-end-us-jaguar-recovery-2020-03-17/https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2020/03/16/2020-05349/determination-pursuant-to-section-102-of-the-illegal-immigration-reform-and-immigrant-responsibility***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 10:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/27/3980387/3980387_5B5FBD3818534578AE6D8B555CBA707F_200327_3980387_Trump_s_border_wall_could_threaten_jaguar_recove_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, President Trump, Trump border wall, US southern border wall, border wall wildlife, border wall animals, border wall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3980292</guid>
      <title>Montreal Protocol is stopping changes to Southern Hemisphere winds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe ozone layer's recovery is stopping changes in the atmospheric circulation systems of the Southern Hemisphere, according to new research.Writing in a study published in Nature, researchers say the Montreal Protocol is curbing ozone depletion, a phenomenon responsible for Antarctica's ozone hole. This hole has disrupted atmospheric circulation in the southern hemisphere, including shifting the mid-latitude jet stream poleward. The Montreal Protocol was signed in 1987 to phase out chlorofluorocarbons, or CFCs, from air conditioning, refrigerators and packaging. According to the study, the international accord's removal of CFC pollution has halted the jet stream's drift to the south.Writing in a news release, the University of Colorado Boulder says its researchers believe climate warming is driving the jet stream to the Southern Pole. Ozone layer recovery exerts an opposite effect that has paused the shift.According to the university, ozone depletion is also linked to the southward expansion of the Southern Hemisphere's tropical dry region, which affects rainfall in South America, East Africa and Australia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Effects of ozone depletion on Southern Hemisphere wind systems2. Montreal Protocol's phase out of CFC is reversing the growth of ozone hole3. Ozone layer recovery halted climate warming's effect in Southern Hemisphere winds4. Climate warming related wind changes would affect rainfall in multiple continentsVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers say the Montreal Protocol is curbing ozone depletion, a phenomenon responsible for Antarctica's ozone hole. This hole has disrupted atmospheric circulation in the southern hemisphere, including shifting the mid-latitude jet stream poleward. "The Montreal Protocol was signed in 1987 to phase out chlorofluorocarbons, or CFCs, from air conditioning, refrigerators and packaging. According to a new study published in Nature, the international accord's removal of CFC pollution has halted the jet stream's drift to the south.""Writing in a news release, the University of Colorado Boulder says its researchers believe climate warming is driving the jet stream to the Southern Pole. Ozone layer recovery exerts an opposite effect that has paused the shift.""According to the university, ozone depletion is also linked to the southward expansion of the Southern Hemisphere's tropical dry region, which affects rainfall in South America, East Africa and Australia." SOURCES: Nature, University of Colorado Boulder https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-2120-4https://cires.colorado.edu/news/international-ozone-treaty-stops-changes-southern-hemisphere-winds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 08:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/27/3980292/3980292_06DD2EBA7CF744178016E82AE52D8A2A_200327_3980292_Montreal_Protocol_is_stopping_changes_to_Souther_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Montreal Protocol, chlorofluorocarbons, CFC, jet stream, jet streams, mid latitude jet stream, Antarctica, Southern Pole, ozone hole, ozone layer, Southern Hemisphere, climate warming, environment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981313</guid>
      <title>Quasar black hole radiation may stop galaxies from creating stars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANQuasar black holes emit radiation so powerful that they can prevent star formation in the surrounding galaxy, according to a study in the Astrophysical Journal Supplementary Letters.Writing on behalf of co-author Nahum Arav, a Virginia Tech press release says quasar outflows rip through interstellar space to generate intense light and heat. The quasar radiation blasts away matter that is needed for birthing stars. The radiation emissions dubbed quasar winds blow hundreds of solar masses of material away each year. According to Science Alert, quasars spend billions of years in this violent state before maturing into more conventional black holes.According to the research team, it is a scientific puzzle that the universe does not have bigger galaxies or more numerous stars than it actually possesses. They say quasars at the core of elliptical galaxies could be part of the answer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Quasars emit powerful radiation capable of preventing star formation 2. Energy from quasar emissions generates tremendous heat and light3. Quasar radiation blows away matter needed for star formation4. Quasars limit the size of many galaxies and number of stars in the universeVOICEOVER (in English): "Quasars are supermassive black holes that emit potent radiation at the core of many galaxies. According to a study in the Astrophysical Journal Supplementary Letters, quasar outflows are so powerful that they prevent star formation in these galaxies.""Writing on behalf of co-author Nahum Arav, a Virginia Tech press release says quasar outflows rip through interstellar space to generate intense light and heat. The quasar radiation blasts away matter that is needed for birthing stars.""The radiation emissions dubbed quasar winds blow hundreds of solar masses of material away each year. According to Science Alert, quasars spend billions of years in this violent state before maturing into more conventional black holes.""According to the research team, it is a scientific puzzle that the universe does not have bigger galaxies or more numerous stars than it actually possesses. They say quasars at the core of elliptical galaxies could be part of the answer."SOURCES: The Astrophysical Journal Supplementary Letters, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Science Alerthttps://iopscience.iop.org/journal/0067-0049/page/Focus_on_HSTCOS_Observationshttps://vtnews.vt.edu/articles/2020/03/science-quasar_tsunamis_stars_blackholes.htmlhttps://www.sciencealert.com/quasars-can-trigger-tsunamis-that-tear-across-galaxies-and-snuff-out-star-formation***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 09:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/30/3981313/3981313_2E060829EDB5498CBD5D5C1C8AD0125D_200330_3981313_Quasar_black_hole_radiation_may_stop_galaxies_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Quasar, black hole, supermassive black hole, black hole radiation, quasar winds, prevent star formation, galaxy quenching, star formation quenching,  elliptical galaxies, astrophysics, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981264</guid>
      <title>Neanderthals hunted marine life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch published in the journal Science has found that Neanderthals living on the coast of Portugal ate a variety of seafood.This is contrary to the thinking that humans were unique in their ability to hunt for marine lifeCiting the research, the BBC reports that Neanderthals were found to have eaten sharks, dolphins, mussels, crabs, eels, sea bream, seals and some sea birds. Food from marine resources is thought to have made up half of the Neanderthal diet. The rest is said to consist of ancient cattle, horse, deer, goat and tortoise.It is believed that humans developed their creativity and cognition from eating the brain-enhancing fats of marine life.Research from earlier this year found evidence that suggested Neanderthals living in a cave in Italy used to dive for shellfish. It is thought that they used the shellfish not only for food, but for making tools as well.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Neanderthals eating fish2. Overview of Neanderthal seafood diet3. Overview of Neanderthal diet4. Depiction of Neanderthal diving for shellfishVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in the journal Science has found that Neanderthals living on the coast of Portugal ate a variety of seafood." "This is contrary to the thinking that humans were unique in their ability to hunt for marine life.""Citing the research, the BBC reports that Neanderthals were found to have eaten sharks, dolphins, mussels, crabs, eels, sea bream, seals and some sea birds." "Food from marine resources is thought to have made up half of the Neanderthal diet. The rest is said to consist of ancient cattle, horse, deer, goat and tortoise.""It is believed that humans developed their creativity and cognition from eating the brain-enhancing fats of marine life.""Research from earlier this year found evidence that suggested Neanderthals living in a cave in Italy used to dive for shellfish."It is thought that they used the shellfish not only for food, but for making tools as well."SOURCES: Science, BBChttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/367/6485/eaaz7943https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-52054653https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51128639***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 08:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/30/3981264/3981264_A21F4AE3E86A478493DCE49C34BC58D1_200330_3981264_Neanderthals_hunted_marine_life_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, neanderthal, neanderthal diet, neanderthal seafood, neanderthal swimming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981110</guid>
      <title>Loss of sense of smell and taste potential symptoms of coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a report from the American Academy of Otolaryngology-Head and Neck Surgery, anosmia, the loss of smell; hyposmia, a reduced sense of smell; and dysgeusia, the distortion of the sense of taste, should be added to the list of symptoms caused by the COVID-19 virus.In a newsletter on the topic, Claire Hopkins, President of the British Rhinological Society, and Nirmal Kumar, President of ENT UK, reported that more than two in three confirmed cases of coronavirus in Germany have anosmia.Similarly, in South Korea, 30 percent of patients who tested positive for the virus had anosmia as their main symptom.The report also mentions anecdotal evidence that a patient can be generally asymptomatic, only presenting anosmia, and still test positive for COVID-19. However, patients with just anosmia are often not tested or asked to self-isolate as this symptom is not yet recognized as a sign of coronavirus.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of loss of smell and taste2. Percentage of cases of anosmia in Germany3. Percentage of cases of anosmia in Korea4. Asymptomatic man with anosmia carrying COVID-195. Initial symptoms of COVID-196. Most vulnerable individualsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report from the American Academy of Otolaryngology-Head and Neck Surgery, anosmia, the loss of smell; hyposmia, a reduced sense of smell; and dysgeusia, the distortion of the sense of taste, should be added to the list of symptoms caused by the COVID-19 virus.""In a newsletter on the topic, Claire Hopkins, President of the British Rhinological Society, and Nirmal Kumar, President of ENT UK, reported that more than two in three confirmed cases of coronavirus in Germany have anosmia.""Similarly, in South Korea, 30 percent of patients who tested positive for the virus had anosmia as their main symptom.""The report also mentions anecdotal evidence that a patient can be generally asymptomatic, only presenting anosmia, and still test positive for COVID-19.""A previous a study of patients in Wuhan, China, where the COVID-19 virus outbreak originated, found fever is typically the first symptom of those infected with the virus. Some individuals may also experience fatigue, muscle pain and a dry cough.""By day five of infection, some patients begin to experience breathing difficulties, especially elderly individuals and people with preexisting health conditions."SOURCES: American Academy of Otolaryngology  Head and Neck Surgery, ENT UKhttps://www.entnet.org/content/aao-hns-anosmia-hyposmia-and-dysgeusia-symptoms-coronavirus-diseasehttps://www.entuk.org/sites/default/files/files/Loss%20of%20sense%20of%20smell%20as%20marker%20of%20COVID.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 01:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/30/3981110/3981110_4E980B0A8A2141EFAE777AD2C7A75ECB_200330_3981110_Loss_of_sense_of_smell_and_taste_potential_sympt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19, COVID-19 virus, COVID-19 pandemic, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, day to day symptoms coronavirus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981631</guid>
      <title>Explainer: Why the COVID-19 coronavirus was not made in a lab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe novel coronavirus did not originate from a research laboratory, according to a study published in Nature Medicine. Researchers say the novel coronavirus was not made in a lab, after comparing its RNA sequence to SARS, MERS and other coronaviruses including the HKU1, which is known to cause mild symptoms in humans. Citing the authors, Live Science reports the study focuses on the novel coronavirus's spike protein.The protein consists of receptor binding domains, also known as RBDs, and a cleavage site.The RBD hooks on to an ACE2 receptor on the surface of human cells, then the cleavage site opens the receptor for the virus to enter.The spike protein design is deemed so effective that it could only have resulted from natural selection and not human engineering.When scientists simulated the virus in computer models, they found computers to underate COVID-19's infectiousness by a significant margin.Study co-author Kristian Andersen of Scripps Research was cited as saying if scientists designed the virus, they would not have chosen the spike protein mutations that seemed ineffective.Additionally, biological weapons were usually created from deadly viruses, but SARS-CoV-2's close relatives are bat and pangolin viruses that are largely innocuous.The virus is speculated to have spread from bats to pangolins to humans. According to the researchers, they are working to determine at what point SARS-CoV-2 developed the cleavage site mutations that increased its infectiousness.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study claims COVID-19 did not originate from a laboratory2. Researchers compared SARS-CoV-2 RNA sequence to other coronaviruses3. Novel coronavirus possess specific mutations to its spike proteins4. These spike proteins enable the virus to target ACE2 receptors to infect humans5. Computer models underestimate the effectiveness of coronavirus mutations6. Biological weapons are not likely to be based on previously innocuous virusesVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers say the novel coronavirus was not made in a lab, after comparing its RNA sequence to SARS, MERS and other coronaviruses including the HKU1, which is known to cause mild symptoms in humans. The study is published in Nature Medicine.""Citing the authors, Live Science reports the study focuses on the novel coronavirus's spike protein." "The protein consists of receptor binding domains, also known as RBDs, and a cleavage site.""The RBD hooks on to an ACE2 receptor on the surface of human cells, then the cleavage site opens the receptor for the virus to enter.""The spike protein design is deemed so effective that it could only have resulted from natural selection and not human engineering.""When scientists simulated the virus in computer models, they found computers to underate COVID-19's infectiousness by a significant margin.""Study co-author Kristian Andersen of Scripps Research was cited as saying if scientists designed the virus, they would not have chosen the spike protein mutations that seemed ineffective.""Additionally, biological weapons were usually created from deadly viruses, but SARS-CoV-2's close relatives are bat and pangolin viruses that are largely innocuous.""The virus is speculated to have spread from bats to pangolins to humans. According to the researchers, they are working to determine at what point SARS-CoV-2 developed the cleavage site mutations that increased its infectiousness."SOURCES: Nature Medicine, Live Sciencehttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0820-9https://www.livescience.com/coronavirus-not-human-made-in-lab.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 07:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/03/31/3981631/3981631_88CA00D780DD4C76ABA87AAD9E58BF01_200331_3981631_Explainer__Why_the_COVID_19_coronavirus_was_not__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, not a biological weapon, laboratory construct, RNA, RNA sequencing, spike protein, receptor binding domains, cleavage site, receptor binding domain, RBD, ACE2, receptors, receptor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
