<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3838673</guid>
      <title>UN unveils new measures to combat Ebola crisis in DR Congo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Ebola epidemic has already killed 1,200 people in the Democratic Republic of Congo and is currently at risk of spreading to nearby countries, according to the World Health Organization.According to the U.S. based Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Ebola typically affects humans and nonhuman primates. The infection is spread through viruses within the Ebola virus group.The virus is transferred to humans through contact with the fluids of dead wild animals, such as bats, according to the World Health Organization. Ebola is then transmitted among humans through direct contact with contaminated body fluids.Symptoms of the virus include fever, headache, sore throat rashes and, in severe cases,  internal or external bleeding.According to the WHO website, the UN is adapting a new strategy to identify and treat people as soon as possible. They are also said to be providing access to vaccinations.The 2018 Democratic Republic of Congo outbreak is the second largest Ebola epidemic in history and, according to Forbes, is the country's tenth outbreak since 1976.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Ebola virus and countries where the disease could spread to2. How the virus is typically spread 3. How the virus is transmitted to humans4. Symptoms of the virus5. The UN's new strategy of combating the Ebola epidemic in DR CongoVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the World Health Organization, the ebola epidemic has already killed 1,200 people in the Democratic Republic of Congo and is currently at risk of spreading to nearby countries.""According to the U.S. based Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, ebola typically affects humans and nonhuman primates. The infection is spread by viruses within the Ebola virus group.""According to the World Health Organization, the virus is transferred to humans through contact with the fluids of dead wild animals, such as bats." "Ebola is then transmitted among humans through direct contact with contaminated body fluids.""Symptoms of the virus include fever, headache, sore throat rashes and, in severe cases,  internal or external bleeding.""According to the WHO website, the UN is adapting a new strategy to identify and treat people as soon as possible. They are also said to be providing access to vaccinations."SOURCES: Forbes, World Health Organization, AFP, Voice of America, The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention,  https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2019/05/28/an-ebola-outbreak-rages-in-democratic-republic-of-congo/#2a58e9b97665https://www.who.int/news-room/detail/23-05-2019-united-nations-strengthens-ebola-response-in-democratic-republic-of-the-congohttps://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/ebola-virus-diseasehttps://www.africanews.com/2019/05/28/dr-congo-strengthened-effort-against-ebola-is-paying-off-but-insecurity-still-major-constraint-un-health-agency/https://www.voanews.com/a/un-strengthens-measures-to-combat-ebola-epidemic-in-dr-congo/4932346.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/vhf/ebola/about.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/03/3838673/3838673_C6BF6523288A438BB07E3E93F24770FE_190603_3838673_UN_unveils_new_measures_to_combat_Ebola_crisis_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, bola virus, virus, viral outbreak, Congo, West Africa, ebola outbreak, congo ebola outbreak, ebola outbreak news, ebola outbreak congo, health, infectious diseases, disease, illness, healthcare]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838607</guid>
      <title>New exoplanet found in star's 'Neptunian Desert' region</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers have discovered a Neptune-like exoplanet called NGTS-4b in the Neptunian Desert region of a star, according to a study published in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society. This is the first time this type of exoplanet has been found in a star's Neptunian Desert region, CNN reports. Neptunian Desert refers to the area close to stars where no planets similar to Neptune's scale can be found. Stars send out strong radiation to this area. This causes planets to lose their gaseous atmosphere. They usually evaporate, leaving behind a rocky core.According to the new research, NGTS-4b was spotted using a ground telescope called Next Generation Transit Survey.The exoplanet, nicknamed, "The Forbidden Planet," is three times the size of Earth and has a radius that is only 20 percent smaller than Neptune. The exoplanet has temperatures of up to 1,000 degrees Celsius.Space.com reports the new exoplanet orbits a star named NGTS-4, which is around 920 light years away from Earth. The exoplanet completes orbits of the star every 1.3 days, according to a University of Warwick press release.Astronomers believe the exoplanet could have moved into the Neptunian Desert region at some point in the past one million years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where the exoplanet was found2. Describing what usually happens to planets in the Neptunian Desert3. The size of the planet in comparison to Earth and Neptune, and how hot it gets on the planet4. The exoplanet orbiting a star, and its distance from EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers have discovered a Neptune-like exoplanet called NGTS-4b in the Neptunian Desert region of a star.""This refers to the area close to stars where no planets similar to Neptune's scale can be found.""CNN reports, this is the first time this type of exoplanet has been found in a star's Neptunian Desert region.""Stars send out strong radiation to this area. This causes planets to lose their gaseous atmosphere. They usually evaporate, leaving behind a rocky core.""The exoplanet, nicknamed, 'The Forbidden Planet,' is three times the size of Earth and has a radius that is only 20 percent smaller than Neptune.""The exoplanet has temperatures of up to 1,000 degrees Celsius.""Space.com reports the new exoplanet orbits a star named NGTS-4, which is around 920 light years away from Earth.""According to a University of Warwick press release, the exoplanet completes orbits of the star every 1.3 days."SOURCES: Space.com, University of Warwick, Oxford Academic, CNN, Phys.org, https://www.space.com/forbidden-planet-ndgts4b-neptunian-desert.htmlhttps://warwick.ac.uk/newsandevents/pressreleases/the_forbidden_planethttps://academic.oup.com/mnras/article/486/4/5094/5475662https://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/29/world/forbidden-planet-exoplanet-discovery-trnd-scn/index.htmlhttps://phys.org/news/2019-05-forbidden-planet-neptunian.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/03/3838607/3838607_5195B2D7B02A48D3A8DA35643CDC39B1_190603_3838607_New_exoplanet_found_in_star_s__Neptunian_Desert__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space, space exploration, astronomy, neptune, neptunian desert, forbidden planet, neptune forbidden planet, exoplanet, NGTS-4b, NGTS-4, Next-Generation Transit Survey telescope]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842453</guid>
      <title>Liquid water may have erupted from Pluto's icy volcanoes, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study suggests that scientists may have found proof of liquid water being spewed out of Pluto's volcanoes. Ammonia was found on Pluto's surface, according to a study published in Science Advances. This has led scientists to believe that the dwarf planet's volcanoes may have recently erupted with liquid water.Scientists found evidence of ammonia in areas where tectonic activity had previously taken place. They discovered this by analyzing data from NASA's New Horizons probe which flew by Pluto in 2015.According to the researchers, ammonia was mixed in with water from Pluto's underground ocean. Subsequently, liquid water erupted through cracks and vents.Scientists are calling this cryovolcanism, as reported by Space.com. Lead author of the study Cristina Dalle Ore, told the website that radioactive heat from Pluto's ores causes the planet's interior to be warmer than its surface. This allows the ammonia to be liquid despite Pluto's frigid temperatures.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pluto in space, an inset of ammonia, a Plutonian volcano and a drop of water2. The surface of Pluto, and the NASA spacecraft flying over Pluto3. Pluto's underground ocean, and liquid water appearing on Pluto's surface4. Cross section of Pluto depicting the warm interior and the cold exteriorVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in Science Advances, ammonia was found on Pluto's surface. "This has led scientists to believe that the dwarf planet's volcanoes may have recently erupted with liquid water.""Scientists found evidence of ammonia in areas where tectonic activity had previously taken place." "They discovered this by analyzing data from NASA's New Horizons probe which flew by Pluto in 2015.""According to the researchers, ammonia was mixed in with water from Pluto's underground ocean. Subsequently, liquid water erupted through cracks and vents.""Space.com reports that scientists are calling this cryovolcanism.""Lead author of the study Cristina Dalle Ore, told the website that radioactive heat from Pluto's ores causes the planet's interior to be warmer than its surface. "This allows the ammonia to be liquid despite Pluto's frigid temperatures."SOURCES: Space.com, Science Advances, Science News, https://www.space.com/active-pluto-ammonia-buried-liquid-ocean.htmlhttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/5/5/eaav5731https://www.sciencenews.org/article/ice-volcanoes-pluto-may-have-spewed-organic-rich-water***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/10/3842453/3842453_A613DA7869E94ADE889B4B6CA22A024E_190610_3842453_Liquid_water_may_have_erupted_from_Pluto_s_icy_v_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space, space exploration, pluto, pluto volcano, volcanoes on pluto, ice volcanoes on pluto, pluto ice volcano, icy pluto, dwarf planet, liquid water pluto]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843149</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong leader to push through with extradition plan despite protests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHong Kong Chief Executive Carrie Lam announced on Monday that she has no plans to withdraw a controversial plan to allow extradition to mainland China, despite mass protests against it.According to The New York Times, the Hong Kong government has proposed an extradition bill that will allow case-based transfers of suspected criminals to territories it does not have agreements with, including Taiwan, Macau, and China.The administration wants to pass the bill before July, to allow for the extradition of a Hong Kong man wanted for murdering his girlfriend in Taiwan.The Guardian reports that opponents of the bill say it is being pushed by the Chinese government, setting off fears that Beijing will be able to use it to extradite political activists, dissidents, and other opponents in the city.On Sunday, over a million people marched the streets of Hong Kong to oppose the extradition plan. The mostly peaceful protest turned violent after midnight, after police with batons and pepper spray clashed with demonstrators attempting to occupy areas around the Legislative Council complex.Despite the opposition, the government has no plans to change the bill's wording or withdraw it from legislation.Lam has reasoned that it is necessary to prevent Hong Kong from turning into a fugitive haven, and claims there are human rights safeguards in the bill that meet international standards, and are in place to protect the city's unique freedoms.According to the Guardian, China's Foreign Affairs Ministry said it supports Hong Kong in passing the bill. In a Monday editorial, state-owned China Daily defended the extradition plan and blamed "foreign forces" for creating chaos in Hong Kong.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hong Kong extradition bill 2. Fears over Beijing using extradition bill to target and suppress political opponents3. Protesters marching to oppose extradition bill4. Hong Kong government has no plans to withdraw bill or change wordingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to The New York Times, the Hong Kong government has proposed an extradition bill that will allow case-based transfers of suspected criminals to territories it does not have agreements with, including Taiwan, Macau, and mainland China.""The Guardian reports that opponents of the bill say it is being pushed by the Chinese government, setting off fears that Beijing will be able to use it to extradite political activists, dissidents, and other opponents in the city.""On Sunday, over a million people marched the streets of Hong Kong to oppose the extradition plan.""The mostly peaceful protest turned violent after midnight, after police with batons and pepper spray clashed with demonstrators attempting to occupy areas around the Legislative Council complex.""Despite the opposition, the government has no plans to change the bill's wording or withdraw it from legislation.""Chief Executive Carrie Lam has reasoned that it is necessary to prevent Hong Kong from turning into a fugitive haven, and claims there are human rights safeguards in the bill that meet international standards, and are in place to protect the city's unique freedoms."SOURCES: New York Times, BBC, The Guardianhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/10/world/asia/hong-kong-carrie-lam-extradition.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-48577907https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-47810723https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jun/10/hong-kong-protests-china-state-media-foreign-forces-extradition-bill***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 18:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/12/3843149/3843149_1E7C81D23D4E45D098591FC4650B739C_190612_3843149_Hong_Kong_leader_to_push_through_with_extraditio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, HK mass protest, Hong Kong mass protest, China extradition, China extradition bill, China extradition law, HK extradition, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843145</guid>
      <title>NASA to open International Space Station to tourists by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA will be opening the International Space Station to commercial ventures, including space tourism.According to the BBC, starting in 2020, there will be two private space missions per year, each for stays of up to 30 days.Travelers will be ferried to the ISS by two companies hired by NASA  SpaceX using its Crew Dragon capsule, and Boeing with the Starliner it's currently building.These companies would choose the clients and be responsible for determining crew composition, and making sure the private astronauts meet the medical and training requirements for spaceflight.The L.A. Times reports that apart from a $58 million roundtrip ticket, tourists will need to pay $35,000 for each day spent at the station. Use of the station's toilets and life support system costs $11,250 per day, while the daily charge for crew supplies such as food, air, and medical supplies is $22,500.The AFP reports the International Space Station isn't owned entirely by NASA, having been built starting in 1998 with Russia. The U.S. though, paid for and controls most of the orbiter's modules.While NASA had previously banned commercial use of the station, the Russian space agency has long embraced space tourism. In 2001, U.S. businessman Dennis Tito paid Russia $20 million to be the first space tourist on the ISS.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two private space missions a year to the ISS, each trip up to 30 days2. Travelers ferried to space by SpaceX and Boeing3. Private companies responsible for choosing clients, crew4. Cost of trip to the ISSVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, NASA will be opening the International Space Station to commercial ventures, including space tourism.""Starting 2020, there will be two private space missions per year, each for stays of up to 30 days.""Travelers will be ferried to the ISS by two companies hired by NASA  SpaceX using its Crew Dragon capsule, and Boeing with the Starliner it's currently building.""These companies would choose the clients and be responsible for determining crew composition, and making sure the private astronauts meet the medical and training requirements for spaceflight.""The L.A. Times reports that apart from a $58 million roundtrip ticket, tourists will need to pay $35,000 for each day spent at the station.""Use of the station's toilets and life support system costs $11,250 per day, while the daily charge for crew supplies such as food, air, and medical supplies is $22,500."SOURCES: BBC, AFP, L.A. Times, New York Timeshttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-48560874https://news.yahoo.com/nasa-open-international-space-station-tourists-2020-152434058.htmlhttps://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-nasa-international-space-station-visitors-20190607-story.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/07/science/space-station-nasa.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 18:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/12/3843145/3843145_75E28BFAF97B4590BF51B084B7CDAC85_190612_3843145_NASA_to_open_International_Space_Station_to_tour_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, ISS, international space station, space tourism, space tourists, space station, private astronaut, private space trip]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842859</guid>
      <title>Turning plastic into usable fuel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRenewlogy, a private waste management company, has found a way to turn plastic into fuel.The company is able to process around 10 tons of plastic waste on a daily basis to convert into fuel, according to Renewlogy's website.Plastic waste is shredded into smaller pieces and then put into a oxygen-free reactor. The machine is then heated up. This causes the carbon molecules present in the plastic to break down into smaller molecules, essentially turning plastic into usable fuel.Renewlogy explained on their website that gases created from the process would be captured and recycled to prevent any toxic gas emissions.According to the company, the byproduct of the carbon molecules are then converted into naphtha, which is commonly used to create virgin plastic, diesel fuel, and other petrochemical products. The company claims that less than 10 percent of plastic has ever been recycled.According to Renewlogy's website, plastic production is forecasted to double in the next decade.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Plastic waste and a bottle of gasoline2. Plastic waste being turned into smaller bits of plastic and being put into the oxygen-free reactor3. The process of how the reactor breaks down the plastic4. What the byproduct of the plastic waste can be converted intoVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Renewlogy's website, the company is able to process around 10 tons of plastic waste on a daily basis to convert into fuel.""Plastic waste is shredded into smaller pieces and then put into a oxygen-free reactor.""The machine is then heated up. This causes the carbon molecules present in the plastic to break down into smaller molecules, essentially turning plastic into usable fuel.""According to the company, the byproduct of the carbon molecules are then converted into naphtha, which is commonly used to create virgin plastic, diesel fuel, and other petrochemical products."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Renewlogy, Ted Talk https://inhabitat.com/renewlogy-turns-low-grade-plastic-into-usable-fuels/https://renewlogy.com/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lR0Hv5CFY9Q***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 09:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/11/3842859/3842859_61AB758137C44128B4091D3BAE4A392A_190611_3842859_Turning_plastic_into_usable_fuel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, renewlogy, usable fuel, turning plastic into fuel, plastic fuel, recycling plastic, recycling plastic to fuel, plastic waste recycling]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842626</guid>
      <title>Total solar eclipse to occur on July 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBloomberg reports that according to NASA, the total solar eclipse on July 2 will start off  the coast of New Zealand, and reach its peak 1,000 kilometers north of Easter Island, lasting four minutes and 33 seconds.A total eclipse occurs when the sun, moon, and Earth are in a direct line. It's only visible from a small area  those who see it are in the center of the moon's shadow when it hits Earth.Parts of Chile and Argentina will be in the path of totality, but only for a brief window of time.The Independent reports that viewers in San Juan, Argentina can expect to see 36 seconds of totality, while those in La Silla, Chile may be able to view it for one minute 53 seconds.According to Bloomberg, a partial eclipse will be visible in Brazil, Ecuador, Uruguay, and Paraguay if weather permits.Chile's Elqui Valley is one of the few spots on land to view the total eclipse from, and over a quarter of a million visitors are expected on the days surrounding the eclipse.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location and length of July 2 total solar eclipse2. What happens during a total solar eclipse3. Areas in the path of totality4. Areas where partial solar eclipse is visibleVOICEOVER (in English): "Bloomberg reports that according to NASA, the total solar eclipse on July 2 will start off  the coast of New Zealand, and reach its peak 1,000 kilometers north of Easter Island, lasting four minutes and 33 seconds."A total eclipse occurs when the sun, moon, and Earth are in a direct line. It's only visible from a small area  those who see it are in the center of the moon's shadow when it hits Earth.""Parts of Chile and Argentina will be in the path of totality, but only for a brief window of time.""The Independent reports that viewers in San Juan, Argentina can expect to see 36 seconds of totality, while those in La Silla, Chile may be able to view it for one minute 53 seconds.""According to Bloomberg, a partial eclipse will be visible in Brazil, Ecuador, Uruguay, and Paraguay if weather permits."SOURCES: NASA, Bloomberg, The Independent, Unitariumhttps://www.nasa.gov/audience/forstudents/5-8/features/nasa-knows/what-is-an-eclipse-58https://eclipse.gsfc.nasa.gov/solar.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-28/how-to-see-july-2020-total-solar-eclipse-in-chile-guided-tourshttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/when-is-total-solar-eclipse-2019-where-how-to-see-space-moon-earth-time-a8933456.htmlhttp://time.unitarium.com/events/eclipse/072019/city.html?city=Coquimbo-Chile&cix=72***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 03:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/11/3842626/3842626_F03E333754D547A0926040B82C0F9C3A_190611_3842626_Total_solar_eclipse_to_occur_on_July_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, solar eclipse, eclipse, total solar eclipse, chile eclipse, july 2 eclipse, 2019 total solar eclipse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843598</guid>
      <title>Facebook planning giant Texan solar farm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook is partnering up with Longroad Energy, a renewable energy developer, to build a massive solar farm in Texas. Called The Prospero Solar project, the Associated Press reports, the farm will occupy 18 square kilometers. This is more than five times the size of New York City's Central Park.According to Engadget, the solar farm will have a capacity of 379 megawatts. This is part of Facebook's plan to use renewable energy to power its data centers. Facebook's data centers are used to store images, videos and other user information.Engadget reports that Facebook is already using renewable energy for 75 percent of its business, as of last year. According to Facebook Sustainability, the company intends to become 100 percent energy efficient by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Facebook icon and a solar farm2. The size of the solar farm and an energy icon3. Facebook's data centers4. What the company's data center storesVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook is partnering up with Longroad Energy, a renewable energy developer, to build a massive solar farm in Texas.""Called The Prospero Solar project, the Associated Press reports, the farm will occupy 18 square kilometers. ""This is more than five times the size of New York City's Central Park.""According to Engadget, the solar farm will have a capacity of 379 megawatts.""This is part of Facebook's plan to use renewable energy to power its data centers.""Facebook's data centers are used to store images, videos and other user information."SOURCES: The Associated Press via The New York Times, Engadget, Fast Company, Facebook sustainability, https://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2019/06/11/us/ap-us-facebook-solar-farms.htmlhttps://www.engadget.com/2019/05/31/facebook-solar-farm-texas-renewable-energy/https://www.fastcompany.com/90356697/facebook-is-investing-hundreds-of-millions-in-a-gigantic-new-solar-farmhttps://sustainability.fb.com/sustainability-in-numbers/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 13:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/12/3843598/3843598_40A6C7FC90564A9898E03959DA026835_190612_3843598_Facebook_planning_giant_Texan_solar_farm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, facebook solar farm, solar farm, renewable energy, Facebook data centers, Facebook solar project, facebook solar farm texas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843573</guid>
      <title>Bees build nests from plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from Argentina's National Agricultural Technology Institute shows that solitary bees are making nests out of plastic packaging.Scientists set up 63 trap nests around crop fields for the wild bees between 2017 and 2018. Three of the nests were used by bees.Citing the study, ScienceAlert reports that two were built from mud and petals, while the third one had three cells made from plastic.The first two cells were created out of thin, light blue plastic. The third was crafted from a thicker, white plastic. The researchers found that the bees had created them by cutting the materials into different shapes and then stacking them on one another.The first cell contained a dead larva. The second one seemed to have had a bee grow into adulthood while the third cell was incomplete.In a Spanish-language press release translated using Google Translate, lead author of the study Mariana Allasiano said the research would demonstrate the adaptive flexibility that certain species of bees would have in the face of changes in environmental conditions.The research was published in the April 2019 issue of the French journal, Apidologie.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Crop field full of trap nests2. The three nests that were found3. Types of plastic used4. How the cells were built and what was found in the cellsVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from Argentina's National Agricultural Technology Institute shows that solitary bees are making nests out of plastic packaging." "Scientists set up 63 trap nests around crop fields for the wild bees between 2017 and 2018. Three of the nests were used by bees.""Citing the study, ScienceAlert reports that two were built from mud and petals, while the third one had three cells made from plastic.""The first two cells were created out of thin, light blue plastic. The third was crafted from a thicker, white plastic.""The researchers found that the bees had created them by cutting the materials into different shapes and then stacking them on one another.""The first cell contained a dead larva. The second one seemed to have had a bee grow into adulthood while the third cell was incomplete."SOURCES: Apidologie, National Geographic, Inhabitat, Science Alert,  National Agricultural Technology Institute,  https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs13592-019-00635-6https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2019/06/wild-bees-building-homes-from-plastic/https://inhabitat.com/wild-bees-are-building-nests-with-plastic/https://www.sciencealert.com/wild-bees-have-been-found-building-nests-entirely-out-of-plastic-for-the-first-timehttps://inta.gob.ar/noticias/abejas-reutilizadoras-primera-evidencia-mundial-de-un-nido-de-abeja-construido-con-plastico ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/12/3843573/3843573_760E93A87B0343B28151DEA4D1355364_190612_3843573_Bees_build_nests_from_plastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, bees, wild bees, plastic, plastic waste, plastic waste solution, argentina, solitary bees, plastic bee nest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843564</guid>
      <title>Canada plans to ban single-use plastics by 2021</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCanadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau announced on Monday that Canada will ban single-use plastics as early as 2021.While the specific products to be outlawed have yet to be decided, CNN reports that bags, straws, cutlery, and stirring sticks may be included.According to DW, Trudeau said plastic producers will be held responsible for the full life cycle of their products, and that manufacturers and the companies using the products will need to provide recycling plans.The government would also work with the companies to establish targets on waste.The BBC reports that currently, less than 10 percent of plastics are recycled in Canada.Each year, the country throws away 3 million tonnes of plastic waste, which end up in landfills and incinerators, litter beaches and parks, and pollute bodies of water.According to the Canadian government, over a million birds and 100,000 sea mammals are injured or die globally each year when they mistake plastic for food.Trudeau claims that banning single-use plastic will not only reduce pollution and protect the environment, but also create 42,000 jobs in the recycling and recovery industries.Canada's anti-plastic crusade comes after the EU and the United Kingdom passed similar bans in late March and May, respectively. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Canada ban on single-use plastics by 20212. Plastic producers to be held responsible for their products3. Plastic waste in Canada4. Effect of plastic pollution on marine animals5. Canada plastic ban to create 42,000 jobsVOICEOVER (in English): "Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau announced on Monday that Canada will ban single-use plastics as early as 2021.""While the specific products to be outlawed have yet to be decided, CNN reports that bags, straws, cutlery, and stirring sticks may be included.""According to DW, Trudeau said plastic producers will be held responsible for the full life cycle of their products, and that manufacturers and the companies using the products will need to provide recycling plans.""The government would also work with the companies to establish targets on waste.""The BBC reports that currently, less than 10 percent of plastics are recycled in Canada.""Each year, the country throws away 3 million tonnes of plastic waste, which end up in landfills and incinerators, litter beaches and parks, and pollute bodies of water.""According to the Canadian government, over a million birds and 100,000 sea mammals are injured or die globally each year when they mistake plastic for food.""Trudeau claims that banning single-use plastic will not only reduce pollution and protect the environment, but also create 42,000 jobs in the recycling and recovery industries."SOURCES: CTV, DW, BBC, New York Times, CNNhttps://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/canada-moving-on-single-use-plastics-ban-but-will-determine-products-later-1.4459274https://www.dw.com/en/canada-to-start-single-use-plastic-ban-in-2021/a-49130499https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-48477087https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/10/world/canada/single-use-plastic-ban.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/10/americas/canada-single-use-plastics-intl-hnk/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/12/3843564/3843564_6D792EFEC62A44BC83C94150F15C3780_190612_3843564_Canada_plans_to_ban_single_use_plastics_by_2021_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic ban, single use plastics, plastics ban, plastic pollution, canada plastic ban, canada single use plastics, plastic waste, harmful plastic waste, Canada plastic ban 2021]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843261</guid>
      <title>Gulf of Mexico's 'dead zone' may be the biggest on record</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Gulf of Mexico could have a dead zone almost 8,000 square miles in size due to this year's record-breaking rainfall in the American Midwest, according to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.Citing scientists' predictions, the NOAA says the dead zone could be one of the largest on record. Dead zones, also referred to as hypoxic zones, have low-oxygen levels that are deadly to marine life.These occur as nutrients present in fertilizers, such as nitrogen and phosphorus, are washed into rivers due to annual rainfall. Nutrients present in the river water runoff then cause algae to grow in ocean water, as fresh water doesn't mix with the ocean's due to its density.Louisiana State University ocean ecologist, Nancy Rabalais, told National Geographic that animals such as shrimp and fish will swim away from hypoxic zones when oxygen levels drop below two parts per million.Farmers are starting to adopt practices such as making less use of fertilizers and using more cover crops to decrease nutrient runoff, as reported by National Geographic.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dead zone in the Gulf of Mexico2. Low-oxygen dead zone in the Gulf of Mexico3. How dead zones occur4. What causes algal bloom on ocean water5. Shrimp and fish swimming away from dead zonesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Gulf of Mexico could have a dead zone almost 8,000 square miles in size, due to this year's record-breaking rainfall in the American Midwest.""Citing scientists' predictions, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration or NOAA, says the dead zone could be one of the largest on record.""The NOAA explains on its website that dead zones, also referred to as hypoxic zones, have low-oxygen levels that are deadly to marine life.""These occur as nutrients present in fertilizers, such as nitrogen and phosphorus, are washed into rivers due to annual rainfall.""Nutrients present in the river water runoff then cause algae to grow in ocean water, as fresh water doesn't mix with the ocean's due to its density.""Nancy Rabalais, an ocean ecologist at Louisiana State University told National  Geographic that animals such as shrimp and fish will swim away from hypoxic zones when oxygen levels drop below two parts per million."SOURCES: National Geographic, CNN, University of Michigan, The Washington Post, University of Waterloo, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2019/06/massive-dead-zone-predicted-to-be-one-of-largest-gulf-of-mexico/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/10/health/gulf-dead-zone-study-climate-scn/index.htmlhttps://uwaterloo.ca/news/news/gulf-mexico-dead-zone-not-expected-shrink-anytime-soonhttps://www.noaa.gov/media-release/noaa-forecasts-very-large-dead-zone-for-gulf-of-mexico***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 04:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/12/3843261/3843261_D4B1BF6AD15B4EBC9D9A8A61AF40AC14_190612_3843261_Gulf_of_Mexico_s__dead_zone__may_be_the_biggest__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dead zone, gulf of mexico, gulf of mexico dead zone, hypoxic zone, midwest rainfall, mississippi river, dead zone nutrient runoff]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843925</guid>
      <title>Ancient nomads linked to modern populations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study sheds light on how ancient human migration in Northeastern Siberia is linked to human populations today.  In a new paper published in the journal Nature, scientists studied the population history of Siberia by analyzing DNA from the remains of 34 ancient individuals from sites in northeastern Siberia, northern East Asia, and southwestern Finland that date back 31,600 to 600 years. They then compared them with DNA of ancient and modern humans from Eurasia and North America. Results show the first human groups to arrive in the region were the Ancient North Siberians which are now extinct. Later on, two more migratory waves came from East Asia, the third of which was a group named Neo-Siberians. Modern Siberians can trace their ancestry back to this group.  Scientists also discovered a new group of humans they named Ancient North Siberians by extracting DNA from teeth that belonged to two unrelated children whose remains were found near Siberia's Yana River at a location called the Yana Rhinoceros Horn Site. They believed these would have ties with early native North Americans, however, they appear to be unrelated.DNA collections indicate native North Americans came as a result of mixing between East Asians and a population distantly linked to Ancient Northern Siberians which occurred roughly 20,000 years ago.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Areas where ancient human DNA was extracted2. Migratory waves that populated Siberia3. DNA extracted from human teeth; new human species discovered4. Ancient humans linked to native North AmericansVOICEOVER (in English): "In a new paper published in the journal Nature, scientists studied the population history of Siberia by analyzing DNA from the remains of 34 ancient individuals from sites in northeastern Siberia, northern East Asia, and southwestern Finland that date back 31,600 to 600 years.""They then compared them with DNA of ancient and modern humans from Eurasia and North America.""Results show the first human groups to arrive in the region were the Ancient North Siberians which are now extinct." "Later on, two more migratory waves came from East Asia, the third of which was a group named Neo-Siberians. Modern Siberians can trace their ancestry back to this group." "Scientists also discovered a new group of humans they've named Ancient North Siberians by extracting DNA from teeth that belonged to two unrelated children whose remains were found near Siberia's Yana River at a location called the Yana Rhinoceros Horn Site." "They believed these would have ties with early native North Americans, however, they appear to be unrelated.""DNA collections indicate native North Americans came as a result of bonding between East Asians and a population distantly linked to Ancient Northern Siberians which occurred roughly 20,000 years ago."  SOURCES: Nature, Science News, The Guardian, Live Science, University of Cambridgehttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1279-zhttps://www.sciencenews.org/article/dna-reveals-ancient-siberians-set-stage-first-americans?tgt=nrhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jun/05/ancient-siberia-was-home-to-previously-unknown-humans-say-scientistshttps://www.livescience.com/65654-dna-ice-age-teeth-siberia.htmlhttps://www.cam.ac.uk/research/news/dna-from-31000-year-old-milk-teeth-leads-to-discovery-of-new-group-of-ancient-siberians***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 07:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/13/3843925/3843925_505A7DD53BA84C39BEB72B0AE2F2D924_190613_3843925_Ancient_nomads_linked_to_modern_populations_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ancient North Siberians, siberia, human species, ancient humans, migration, new human species, Yana Rhinoceros Horn Site, Yana River]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844734</guid>
      <title>US believes Iran behind oil tanker explosions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. government reckons Iran is responsible for two suspected oil tanker attacks in the Gulf of Oman this week, the BBC reports.On Thursday, two oil tankers were sailing through international waters south east of the Strait of Hormuz when a fire broke out onboard. This was followed by an explosion.The Front Altair was carrying 75,000 tons of naptha and was heading from the United Arab Emirates to Taiwan, BBC News reports.The second oil tanker, the Kokuka Courageous, was believed to be carrying around 25,000 tons of methanol. The ship was travelling from Saudi Arabia to Singapore.According to Reuters, U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo told reporters that the U.S. believes Iran was behind the attacks. "This assessment is based on intelligence, the weapons used, the level of expertise needed to execute the operation, recent similar Iranian attacks on shipping, and the fact that no proxy group operating in the area has the resources and proficiency to act with such a high degree of sophistication," Pompeo said, according to Reuters.A statement by the Iranian mission to the United Nations, said:  "Iran categorically rejects the U.S. unfounded claim with regard to 13 June oil tanker incidents, and condemns it in the strongest possible terms."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The two oil tankers and where the incident took place2.  What the vessels were carrying and where they were heading3. The ships on a map and an explosion bubble around them4. What might have caused the explosions VOICEOVER (in English): "On Thursday, two oil tankers were sailing through international waters south east of the Strait of Hormuz when a fire broke out onboard. This was followed by an explosion.""BBC News reports the Front Altair was carrying 75,000 tons of naptha and was heading from the United Arab Emirates to Taiwan.""The second oil tanker, the Kokuka Courageous, was believed to be carrying around 25,000 tones of methanol. The ship was travelling from Saudi Arabia to Singapore.""Citing Iran's state news agency Irna, the BBC reports that the first incident occurred on the Front Altair when it was 46 kilometers off the Iranian port of Jask." "The second took place an hour later, when the Kokuka Courageous caught fire around 51 kilometers off Jask.""The president of Kokuka Sangyo, the Japanese company that owns Kokuka Courageous, said he believes the ship was hit by a shell. "Managers of the vessel added that the ship was damaged "as a result of a suspected attack."""According to the Guardian, Taiwan's state oil refiner CPC Corporation suspects that the Front Altair was hit in a torpedo attack. The CPC was chartering the tanker."SOURCES: BBC News, The Guardian, CBS News, CNN, Reuters, https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-48627014https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-48630374https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jun/13/oil-tankers-blasts-reports-gulf-of-oman-us-navyhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/oil-tanker-attack-gulf-of-oman-fire-iran-likely-responsible-pompeo-says-today-2019-06-13-live-updates/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/13/middleeast/sea-of-oman-tanker-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-tanker/tanker-attacks-in-gulf-of-oman-fuel-security-oil-supply-fears-idUSKCN1TE0OI***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/14/3844734/3844734_68ED130F183E44E685D5684D1EC810B2_190614_3844734_US_believes_Iran_behind_oil_tanker_explosions_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Gulf of Oman, Gulf of Oman explosions, Gulf of Oman tanker, Oman, Middle East, Strait of Hormuz, iran]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844432</guid>
      <title>NASA to explore a mysterious, metallic asteroid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA is readying for a mission that will launch in 2022 to explore the metal asteroid Psyche. Scientists think Psyche may once have been a Mars-sized planet that had its outer crust blasted off billions of years ago by violent asteroid collisions, according to NASA's website.Psyche is located in the main asteroid belt in our solar system between Mars and Jupiter. Researchers believe Psyche is composed mostly of iron and nickel, similar to Earth's core.Psyche will carry scientific instruments including a magnetometer to measure the asteroid's magnetic field and a spectrometer to detect what exactly the ancient asteroid is made out of, according to NASA.A multispectral imager will take high-resolution images of Psyche to distinguish between metals and silicates.The probe will be launched in August 2022 and is expected to reach the asteroid by Jan. 31, 2026.Through this mission, scientists hope to gain a better understanding of how our solar system was formed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New Psyche spacecraft and the asteroid2. What caused the asteroid to lose its outer crust3. What the asteroid is made out of 4. Scientific instruments analyzing the ancient asteroid5. The spacecraft about to reach the asteroidVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA is readying for a mission that will launch in 2022 to explore the metal asteroid Psyche." "According to NASA's website, scientists think Psyche may once have been a Mars-sized planet that had its outer crust blasted off billions of years ago by violent asteroid collisions.""Psyche is located in the main asteroid belt in our solar system between Mars and Jupiter.""Researchers believe Psyche is composed mostly of iron and nickel, similar to Earth's core.""According to NASA, Psyche will carry scientific instruments including a magnetometer to measure the asteroid's magnetic field and a spectrometer to detect what exactly the ancient asteroid is made out of.""A multispectral imager will take high-resolution images of Psyche to distinguish between metals and silicates.""The probe will be launched in August 2022 and is expected to reach the asteroid by Jan. 31, 2026.""Through this mission, scientists hope to gain a better understanding of how our solar system was formed."SOURCES: NASA, Live Sciencehttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7419https://www.nasa.gov/psychehttps://www.livescience.com/65703-asteroid-psyche-probe-iron-mission.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 07:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/14/3844432/3844432_521E9C48C55F4C58A39060D6839ADA91_190614_3844432_NASA_to_explore_a_mysterious__metallic_asteroid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, nasa, space exploration, asteroid Psyche, nasa spacecraft, nasa psyche, nasa psyche project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844369</guid>
      <title>Paris details green Eiffel Tower area revamp</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe city of Paris has announced plans to revamp the area around the Eiffel Tower and turn it into a pedestrian-friendly garden.The 72 million euro project was designed by London-based Gustafson Porter + Bowman, according to the Guardian.The plans include, transforming the area's Trocadro Gardens[h][i][j] into a green amphitheater space for tourists.According to French television network France 24, the Pont d'Iena[k][l] bridge would be turned into a green walkway where pedestrians could walk or cycle across it. The bridge will also connect with gardens on opposite sides of the River Seine[m][n].Private vehicles would be restricted, with only public and emergency transport allowed onto the bridge.The second phase of construction, on the opposite side of the tower, will commence after the 2024 Olympics and is expected to be finished in 2030.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The area around the Eiffel Tower2. The Trocadro Gardens being turned into an amphitheater3. The Pont d'Iena bridge transforming into a walkway, with limited transportation allowed on4. The bridge connecting to gardens on the opposite sides of the RiverVOICEOVER (in English): "The city of Paris has announced plans to revamp the area around the Eiffel Tower and turn it into a pedestrian-friendly garden.""According to the Guardian, the 72 million euro project was designed by London-based Gustafson Porter + Bowman.""The plans include, transforming the area's Trocadro Gardens[o][p][q] into a green amphitheater space for tourists.""According to French television network France 24, the Pont d'Iena[r][s] bridge would be turned into a green walkway where pedestrians could walk or cycle across it.""Private vehicles would be restricted, with only public and emergency transport allowed onto the bridge.""The bridge will also connect with gardens on opposite sides of the River Seine[t][u]."SOURCES: The Guardian, Reuters, France 24, The Local France, Gustafson Porter + Bowman press release,https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jun/07/eiffel-tower-revamp-to-turn-roads-into-garden-in-heart-of-parishttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-paris-skyline/changes-to-the-paris-skyline-non-merci-idUSKCN1SZ28Rhttps://www.france24.com/en/20190522-paris-hidalgo-create-green-corridor-giant-garden-between-trocadero-eiffel-towerhttps://www.thelocal.fr/20190522/the-72-million-plan-to-create-largest-garden-in-paris-around-the-eiffel-towerhttps://static1.squarespace.com/static/573b1a59b654f91cddb061f5/t/5ce417e13e089b00011038ea/1558452205457/Press+Note_Winner_Gustafson+Porter+%2B+Bowman.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 06:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/14/3844369/3844369_B70C4F513FBA474681C389454A884434_190614_3844369_Paris_details_green_Eiffel_Tower_area_revamp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, eiffel tower, paris eiffel tower, eiffel tower garden, garden renovation france, garden renovation eiffel tower, eiffel tower renovation, eiffel tower revamped, paris garden eiffel tower]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3845899</guid>
      <title>F-35 fighter jets suffering from multiple issues, report finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmerican F-35 fighter jets currently have 13 deficiencies including loss of flight control in certain cases, according to documents acquired by Defense News.The documents reveal that after completing certain unspecified maneuvers, pilots of the F-35B and F-35C fighter jets were not always able to completely control the pitch, yaw and roll of their aircraft.Citing the documents, Defense News reports the two fighter jets are also compelled to limit their airspeed in order to avoid structural damage to the stealth coating.If a tire suddenly blows out on the F-35A and F-35B fighter jets, this could potentially destroy its hydraulic brake lines.F-35C jets may have a green glow appear on their helmet mounted display at times, making it challenging to land on aircraft carriers, according to Defense News.Other issues include the F-35 erroneously reporting that a battery has failed under cold weather conditions and sudden cabin pressure spikes which can cause extreme pain in the ear.Mat Winter, the U.S. Defense Department's F-35 program executive, told Defence News that nine out of the 13 problems are likely to be corrected or receive a downgrade in its status before the government decides to move on with full-rate production at the end of this year.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The F35 B fighter jet in the sky2. What could cause damage to the F35 B and F35 C fighter jets 3. The F-35B fighter jet trying to land when its tire blows out4. Other issues found with the F-35 fighter jetsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to documents acquired by Defense News, American F-35 fighter jets currently have 13 deficiencies including loss of flight control in certain cases.""The documents reveal that after completing certain unspecified maneuvers, pilots of the F-35B and F-35C fighter jets were not always able to completely control the pitch, yaw and roll of their aircraft.""Citing the documents, Defense News reports the two fighter jets are also compelled to limit their airspeed in order to avoid structural damage to the stealth coating.""If a tire suddenly blows out on the F-35A and F-35B fighter jets, this could potentially destroy its hydraulic brake lines.""According to Defense News, F-35C jets may have a green glow appear on their helmet mounted display at times, making it challenging to land on aircraft carriers.""Other issues include the F-35 erroneously reporting that a battery has failed under cold weather conditions and sudden cabin pressure spikes which can cause extreme pain in the ear."SOURCES: Defense News, Business Insider,https://www.defensenews.com/air/2019/06/12/the-pentagon-is-battling-the-clock-to-fix-serious-unreported-f-35-problems/https://www.businessinsider.com/f-35-still-struggling-with-more-than-dozen-big-problems-2019-6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 09:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/17/3845899/3845899_EEA95CE498B341208524333C0C1CC154_190617_3845899_F_35_fighter_jets_suffering_from_multiple_issues_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pentagon, F-35, F-35 problems, f35 problems 2019, f 35 fighter jet problems, F-35 program, F-35B, F-35C, F-35 flaws,  F-35 design flaws, pentagon F-35]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3845883</guid>
      <title>Magnetic field may be keeping Milky Way's black hole at bay</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA magnetic field at the center of our galaxy may be keeping a supermassive black hole at bay.According to their website, NASA believes they now know why the supermassive black hole at the center of our galaxy is suspiciously dormant in comparison to others in different galaxies.New research from NASA's Stratospheric Observatory for Infrared Astronomy, or SOFIA, is helping scientists understand the difference between a highly active black hole and a relatively inactive one.The results from SOFIA and its far-infrared camera, or HAWC+, have given them large amounts of data about the magnetic field at the center of the Milky Way and its role in making the Sagittarius A* black hole so tranquil.NASA stated that like most black holes if the magnetic field funnels the gas directly into it, the black hole is active because of its mass consumption of gas. However, the new observations using HAWC+ reveals that the magnetic field at the center of the Milky Way channels the gas so it flows into an orbit around the black hole, making the black hole calmer because it's not ingesting any gas that would ultimately create new stars.Principal investigator and lead author of the study Darren Dowell said, "the spiral shape of the magnetic field channels the gas into an orbit around the black holethis could explain why our black hole is quiet while others are active."According to NASA, the new observations using HAWC+ helps understand how the material in the atmosphere of a supermassive black hole interacts with its host, and also to help to answer the long-established question of why the black hole in the center of our Milky Way is fainter in comparison to those in other galaxies.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. An active and inactive black hole2. Details of NASA's SOFIA plane and camera3. Magnetic field behavior4. Blackholes emitting lightVOICEOVER (in English): "According to their website, NASA believe they now know why the supermassive black hole at the center of our galaxy is suspiciously dormant in comparison to others in different galaxies.""New research from NASA's Stratospheric Observatory for Infrared Astronomy, or SOFIA, is helping scientists understand the difference between a highly active black hole and a relatively inactive one.""The results from SOFIA and its far-infrared camera, or HAWC+, have given them large amounts of data about the magnetic field at the center of the Milky Way and its role in making the Sagittarius A* black hole so tranquil.""NASA stated that like most black holes, if the magnetic field funnels the gas directly into it, the black hole is active because of its mass consumption of gas." "However, the new observations using HAWC+ reveals that the magnetic field at the center of the Milky Way channels the gas so it flows into an orbit around the black hole, making the black hole calmer because it's not ingesting any gas that would ultimately create new stars."SOURCES: SOFIA SCIENCE CENTER, NASA, METROhttps://www.sofia.usra.edu/science/instruments/hawchttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/magnetic-field-may-be-keeping-milky-way-s-black-hole-quiethttps://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/chandra/multimedia/black-hole-SagittariusA.htmlhttps://metro.co.uk/2019/06/13/nasa-reveals-monster-black-hole-centre-milky-way-isnt-feeding-everything-around-9939608/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 08:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/17/3845883/3845883_27E183CDC94F4B3F8BB69BF284BF663C_190617_3845883_Magnetic_field_may_be_keeping_Milky_Way_s_black__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, TomoNews, Satire, NASA, massive black hole, Milkyway galaxy, magnetic field, supermassive black hole stopped, SOFIA, HAWC+, black hole magnetic field, magnetic field black hole, supermassive black hole, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846563</guid>
      <title>Gunman opens fire outside Dallas federal building</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA masked gunman was fatally shot on Monday after opening fire on a federal building in Dallas.Citing witnesses, the Dallas Morning News reports that gunman Brian Clyde parked his car at a street corner in front of the Earle Cabell Federal Building in Dallas.He then ran and began shooting at the building at 8:40 a.m.The publication reports that security personnel on the first floor pushed people to the ground as Clyde fired shots outside.The 22-year-old former army soldier was shot while exchanging gunfire with federal officers who responded to the incident. He died at the scene.Police inspected Clyde's 2003 Nissan Altima and found a suspicious device, which they detonated using controlled explosions.Authorities say they are looking into a motive for the attack and are actively looking into Clyde's social media presence.His Facebook page was taken down Monday afternoon, but online posts included rants about the U.S. government and photos of ammunition, according to CBS DFW.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman shooting outside Dallas federal building2. Security personnel pushed people to the ground inside building3. Gunman killed during shootout with police4. Police detonate suspicious device in gunman's carVOICEOVER (in English): "The Dallas Morning News reports that according to witnesses, gunman Brian Clyde parked his car at a street corner in front of the Earle Cabell Federal Building in Dallas.""He then ran and began shooting at the building at 8:40 a.m.""The publication reports that security personnel on the first floor pushed people to the ground as Clyde fired shots outside.""The 22-year-old former army soldier was shot while exchanging gunfire with federal officers who responded to the incident. He died at the scene.""Police inspected Clyde's 2003 Nissan Altima, and found a suspicious device, which they then detonated using controlled explosions."SOURCES: Dallas News, Corpus Christi Caller Timeshttps://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/06/17/shots-fired-federal-courthouse-downtown-dallashttps://www.caller.com/story/news/crime/2019/06/17/brian-isaack-clyde-killed-dallas-shooting-went-del-mar-college/1479981001/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 10:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/18/3846563/3846563_FB7073885D474C28AE0C1F73818F7D2A_190618_3846563_Gunman_opens_fire_outside_Dallas_federal_buildin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dallas court shooting, dallas courthouse shooting, dallas shooting, dallas federal building shooting, dallas federal building, earle cabell building, brian clyde, army veteran]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847160</guid>
      <title>Ghost nets explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe International Union for Conservation of Nature, or IUCN, describes ghost nets as a silent menace threatening the world's marine species. Here's what makes them so bad. According to the Olive Ridley Project, ghost nets are commercial fishing nets that have been abandoned, lost or discarded at sea.They are made from a strong plastic and can remain in the water for a long time.Ghost nets float with ocean currents and trap plastic and other debris, as well as fish and crustaceans  a process known as ghost fishing.Fish caught in the nets often act as bait, luring larger predators like turtles, sharks and dolphins, who eventually become entangled themselves.When a drifting net becomes too heavy due to its catch, it may eventually sink to the seabed, where smaller ocean dwellers feed on the entangled creatures.This, along with natural decomposition, reduces the weight of the net so that it floats back up to the surface, where it then restarts its destructive cycle.In addition to this, ghost nets can also cause damage by smothering reefs and introducing invasive species and parasites into coral reef habitats.The United Nations Environment Programme estimates that over 600 to 800,000 metric tonnes of ghost gear enters the ocean annually. Some are lost during storms, and some dumped deliberately.Nick Mallos, director of the Trash Free Seas Program at Ocean Conservancy, says ghost nets are the most deadly form of marine litter.Efforts being made to lessen their impact include clearing drifting nets and promoting the use of biodegradable fishing gear. But there is no quick-fix solution, and certain practices, such as illegal fishing, remain a block to progress.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of ghost nets 2. Depiction of ghost fishing3. Destructive cycle of ghost fishing4. Ghost nets smother reefs, introduce invasive species to coral habitatsVOICEOVER (in English): "Ghost nets are commercial fishing nets that have been abandoned, lost or discarded at sea.""They are made from a strong plastic and can remain in the water for a long time.""Ghost nets float with ocean currents and trap plastic and other debris, as well as fish and crustaceans  a process known as ghost fishing.""Fish caught in the nets often act as bait, luring larger predators like turtles, sharks and dolphins, who eventually become entangled themselves.""When a drifting net becomes too heavy due to its catch, it may eventually sink to the seabed, where smaller ocean dwellers feed on the entangled creatures.""This, along with natural decomposition, reduces the weight of the net so that it floats back up to the surface, where it then restarts its destructive cycle.""In addition to this, ghost nets can also cause damage by smothering reefs and introducing invasive species and parasites into coral reef habitats."SOURCES: Olive Ridley Project, IUCN, United Nations Environment Programme, Hawaii News Nowhttps://oliveridleyproject.org/what-are-ghost-netshttps://www.iucn.org/content/ghost-nets-silent-killers-oceanshttps://www.unenvironment.org/news-and-stories/story/how-banish-ghosts-dead-fishing-gear-our-seashttps://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2019/06/15/volunteers-spend-hours-removing-pound-ghost-net-oahu-beach/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/19/3847160/3847160_5AF9CFB922CE4CBEADC25DCF054E1204_190619_3847160_Ghost_nets_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ghost net, ghost nets, ghost fishing, silent killer, fishing nets, marine animals, commercial fishing, marine life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847057</guid>
      <title>Domino's to use driverless vehicles to deliver pizza</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDomino's is teaming up with Nuro, a robotics company, to use automated vehicles to make pizza deliveries in Houston, Texas starting later this year.According to a press release by Domino's, the unmanned car is called R2. It will be used to make deliveries to a selected number of customers who place their orders online.Customers would be able to track the driverless vehicle on Domino's app. Once the pizza is delivered, customers would be able to unlock the self-driving pizza delivery pod via a PIN code provided by the company. This isn't the first time Domino been testing out autonomous vehicle technology.According to the Houston Chronicle, the company had previously tested out self-driving cars, drones and even rovers in an effort to make automated pizza delivery a reality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Domino's logo and the self-driving pizza delivery vehicle2. The unmanned vehicle on the road and a laptop with a Domino's icon3. Customers being able to track the pizza as it is being delivered4. Customer unlocking the driverless pizza delivery vehicle to retrieve her pizzaVOICEOVER (in English): "Domino's is teaming up with Nuro, a robotics company, to use automated vehicles to make pizza deliveries in Houston, Texas starting later this year.""According to a press release by Domino's, the unmanned car is called R2. It will be used to make deliveries to a selected number of customers who place their orders online.""Customers would be able to track the driverless vehicle on Domino's app.""Once the pizza is delivered, customers would be able to unlock the self-driving pizza delivery pod via a PIN code provided by the company."SOURCES: Domino's press release, Houston Chronicle, https://dominos.gcs-web.com/news-releases/news-release-details/dominosr-and-nuro-partner-bring-autonomous-pizza-delivery?field_nir_news_date_value%5Bmin%5D=2019https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/06/17/dominos-will-start-delivering-pizzas-via-an-autonomous-robot-this-fall/?noredirect=onhttps://www.chron.com/business/article/Domino-s-brings-self-driving-pizza-delivery-pilot-14004694.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 09:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/19/3847057/3847057_401133BA491149278F7FE3363376CA42_190619_3847057_Domino_s_to_use_driverless_vehicles_to_deliver_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dominos technology, Domino's pizza, Domino's pizza self driving car, dominos technology, high tech delivery car, self driving vehicles 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846859</guid>
      <title>Cryptocurrency mining could be contributing to climate change, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the Technical University of Munich has found that the amount of computing power needed to mine bitcoin produces roughly the same amount of carbon emissions as a major city like Las Vegas.Bitcoin miners have to solve many complex mathematical problems to generate bitcoins, according to the study. This process requires large amounts of electrical power, in turn increasing carbon emissions.The scientists determined that the virtual currency consumed about 46 Terawatt hours of energy as of November 2018. This is equivalent to around 5,650,411 tonnes of coal."They wanted to find out where the cryptocurrency miners were located, how much energy was consumed and how much carbon emissions were produced as a result.The study found that 68 percent of bitcoin mining takes place in Asia, with 17 percent taking place in Europe and 15 percent in North America. Researchers estimate that mining cryptocurrency creates more than 22 million tons of carbon emissions per year.This is roughly equivalent to the amount of carbon emissions produced by developing nations such as Sri Lanka or major world cities such as Vienna or Las Vegas.In a Technical University of Munich press release, lead author of the study and TUM PhD candidate, Christian Stoll explained that there were bigger factors contributing to climate change.He added, "However, the carbon footprint is big enough to make it worth discussing the possibility of regulating cryptocurrency mining in regions where power generation is especially carbon-intensive."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Electric power icon, bitcoin and carbon emissions 2. The process of how bitcoin miners generate bitcoins3. How much energy bitcoin mining is found to have consumed4. Where the mining takes place and the amount of carbon emissions it creates VOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the Technical University of Munich has found that the amount of computing power needed to mine bitcoin produces roughly the same amount of carbon emissions as a major city like Las Vegas.""According to the study, Bitcoin miners have to solve many complex mathematical problems to generate bitcoins.""This process requires large amounts of electrical power, in turn increasing carbon emissions.""The scientists determined that the virtual currency consumed about 46 Terawatt hours of energy as of November 2018. This is equivalent to around 5,650,411 tonnes of coal.""They wanted to find out where the cryptocurrency miners were located, how much energy was consumed and how much carbon emissions were produced as a result.""The study found that 68 percent of bitcoin mining takes place in Asia, with 17 percent taking place in Europe and 15 percent in North America.""Researchers estimate that mining cryptocurrency creates more than 22 million tons of carbon emissions per year.""This is roughly equivalent to the amount of carbon emissions produced by developing nations such as Sri Lanka or major world cities such as Vienna or Las Vegas."SOURCES: Newshub, Joule, CBS News, Science Daily, Technical University of Munich press release, https://www.newshub.co.nz/home/money/2019/06/bitcoin-as-bad-for-climate-change-as-a-large-city-study.htmlhttps://www.cell.com/joule/fulltext/S2542-4351(19)30255-7https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bitcoin-emits-as-much-carbon-as-las-vegas-researchers-say/https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/06/190613104533.htmhttps://www.tum.de/nc/en/about-tum/news/press-releases/details/35499/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 04:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/19/3846859/3846859_7726D8916A264D76A7C631DE5FB82188_190619_3846859_Cryptocurrency_mining_could_be_contributing_to_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cryptocurrency, money transfer, virtual currency, bitcoin climate change, climate change, bitcoin mining, bitcoin climate impact]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846813</guid>
      <title>U.S. to deploy 1,000 additional troops to the Middle East</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Pentagon is set to send 1,000 additional soldiers to the Middle East amid rising tensions with Iran, CNN reports.In a statement from the U.S. Department of Defense, Acting Secretary of Defense Patrick Shanahan announced that the troops would address "air, naval, and ground-based threats in the Middle East."The announcement comes after two oil tankers were attacked in the Gulf of Oman last week. The U.S. suspects Iran was responsible, claims that Tehran denies.Shanahan said, "The recent Iranian attacks validate the reliable, credible intelligence we have received on hostile behavior by Iranian forces and their proxy groups that threaten United States personnel and interests across the region."The deployment would include troops for additional surveillance and intelligence gathering, The Associated Press reports, citing U.S. officials.The move is part of a military package shown to U.S. leaders last month that includes Patriot missile batteries, aircraft and ships, according to the Associated Press.Shanahan downplayed the announcement and said "the United States does not seek conflict with Iran." He explained the action was taken to protect U.S. military personnel and interests in the region.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of the Middle East, US troops and Iran's flag2. An F-35C, Aircraft carrier USS Carl Vinson and soldier on ground3. The two oil tankers that were attacked in the Gulf of Oman4. RQ-4 Global Hawk surveillance aircraft5. Patriot missile batteries, an F-35C and a US Navy shipVOICEOVER (in English): "The Pentagon is set to send 1,000 additional soldiers to the Middle East amid rising tensions with Iran.""In a statement from the U.S. Department of Defense, Acting Secretary of Defense Patrick Shanahan announced that the troops would address quote 'air, naval, and ground-based threats in the Middle East.'""The announcement comes after two oil tankers were attacked in the Gulf of Oman last week. The U.S. suspects Iran was responsible, claims Tehran denies.""Citing U.S. officials, the Associated Press reports that the deployment would include troops for additional surveillance and intelligence gathering.""According to the Associated Press, the move is part of a military package shown to U.S. leaders last month that includes Patriot missile batteries, aircraft and ships."SOURCES: CNN, The Guardian, Reuters, U.S. Department of Defense, The Associated Presshttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/17/politics/us-additional-troops-iran-tensions/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/17/us-to-send-1000-additional-troops-to-the-middle-east-citing-hostile-behaviorhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-attacks-usa-pentagon/u-s-to-send-1000-additional-troops-to-the-middle-east-idUSKCN1TI2UOhttps://dod.defense.gov/News/News-Releases/News-Release-View/Article/1879076/statement-from-acting-secretary-of-defense-patrick-shanahan-on-additional-force/source/GovDelivery/https://www.apnews.com/cc0ae3b3f2aa4eba849a37ecac5f5774***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/19/3846813/3846813_079523D24FF245BBB1979333BF042F5F_190619_3846813_U_S__to_deploy_1_000_additional_troops_to_the_Mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, USA, Iran, Middle East, US forces, US military, iran vs usa, usa middle east, usa vs middle east]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846803</guid>
      <title>Malfunctioning fire switch on Boeing Dreamliners spark safety concerns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA crucial fire-fighting system on Boeing's fleet of 787 Dreamliners was found to have the potential to malfunction, sparking fears among airline pilots.The Guardian reports that Boeing warned airlines using the 787 Dreamliner that the switch used to extinguish engine fires has failed in a 'small number' of instances.According to Boeing's airline alert, long-term heating can cause the fire switch to remain locked so it can't be used to release the two extinguishers in each engine.Boeing claims the risk of fires is low. But a pilot told The Observer that should the switch malfunction during an engine fire, there's no manual override to deploy the extinguishers, and therefore no way of putting the fire out.The Federal Aviation Administration admitted the malfunction is a risk to the flying public, but decided not to ground the fleet. Instead, it issued an airworthiness directive and required airlines to inspect the switches every 30 days.According to the Observer, the pilot community says Boeing's attitude to the risk is upsetting, especially in light of recent issues with the 737 Max. The FAA has declined to comment on the pilots' concerns, saying only that it invited feedback from the airline industry back when its directive was proposed in February.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Switch used to extinguish engine fires on Boeing Dreamliners2. Long-term heating can cause fire switch to remain locked3. No manual override to deploy fire extinguishers if switch malfunctions4. FAA did not ground Dreamliner fleetVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that Boeing warned airlines using the 787 Dreamliner that the switch used to extinguish engine fires has failed in a 'small number' of instances.""According to Boeing's airline alert, long-term heating can cause the fire switch to remain locked so it can't be used to release the two extinguishers in each engine.""Boeing claims the risk of fires is low. But a pilot told The Observer that should the switch malfunction during an engine fire, there's no manual override to deploy the extinguishers, and therefore no way of putting the fire out.""The Federal Aviation Administration admitted the malfunction is a risk to the flying public, but decided not to ground the fleet. Instead, it issued an airworthiness directive and required airlines to inspect the switches every 30 days."SOURCES: The Guardian, Times of Israel, Federal Aviation Administrationhttps://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/jun/15/boeing-dreamliner-b787-safety-fearshttps://www.timesofisrael.com/pilots-fear-for-fire-safety-of-dreamliner-planes-also-used-by-el-al-report/http://rgl.faa.gov/Regulatory_and_Guidance_Library/rgad.nsf/0/6e06edef7054f6ca8625839a005059d5/$FILE/2019-02-03.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 03:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/19/3846803/3846803_46511BF60FA945C7AE32C44FD778F1B6_190619_3846803_Malfunctioning_fire_switch_on_Boeing_Dreamliners_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Boeing, Boeing 787, B787, Dreamliner, Boeing Dreamliner, Boeing safety, Boeing safety, Boeing safety fears, FAA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846786</guid>
      <title>NASA to use "starshade" technology in search for new worlds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has announced plans to use starshade technology to search for new planets beyond our solar system.Two spacecraft would be used in a future starshade mission, according to the space agency's website.One would be a space telescope that would look for planets while the other probe would be carrying the starshade.NASA said the starshade technology would be used to block starlight. This would allow the telescope to get a clear view of any new orbiting planets in space.The spacecraft carrying the starshade would fly 40,000 kilometers in front of the planet-hunting telescope.NASA explained that this technology would only work if the two spacecraft stay are aligned to within one meter of each other. If there is a greater distance between the two, this would allow light from star to seep into the space telescope's view.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The new starshade technology and the solar system2. The space telescope and the probe carrying the starshade3. How the starshade would work in space4. The starshade and the space telescope floating in spaceVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has announced plans to use so-called starshade technology to search for new planets beyond our solar system.""According to the space agency's website, two spacecraft would be used in a future starshade mission.""One would be a space telescope that would look for planets while the other probe would be carrying the starshade.""NASA said the starshade technology would be used to block starlight. This would allow the telescope to get a clear view of any new orbiting planets in space.""The spacecraft carrying the starshade would fly 40,000 kilometers in front of the planet-hunting telescope.""However, this technology would only work if the two spacecraft stay are aligned to within one meter of each other. If there is a greater distance between the two, this would allow light from star to seep into the space telescope's view."SOURCES: Space.com, NASA, https://www.space.com/starshade-exoplanet-formation-flying-tech.htmlhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7420***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 02:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/19/3846786/3846786_E8E14E8BD57A43849D9227E55431150B_190619_3846786_NASA_to_use__starshade__technology_in_search_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, nasa, space, exoplanet, starshade, nasa starshade, nasa starshade project, starshade technology, nasa alien planet discovery, future starshade mission, starshade nasa, WFIRST, coronagraph]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847646</guid>
      <title>Facebook to launch Libra cryptocurrency in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook is coming out with a controversial new Bitcoin-style cryptocurrency.Facebook on Tuesday announced plans to launch its own cryptocurrency in 2020. The digital currency, called Libra, is backed by a reserve of financial assets, making it less volatile than other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin.The social giant won't have direct control over Libra. Instead, it will be serviced by the Libra Association, an independent nonprofit headquartered in Switzerland. Its founding members include companies like Uber, Visa, MasterCard, and PayPal, among others.""The association's main functions are to validate transactions on the Libra blockchain, and manage the reserve the digital currency is tied to.A digital wallet for the new cryptocurrency, called Calibra, is also being launched, and will be available on Messenger, WhatsApp, and as a standalone app.Calibra will allow users to send Libra to anyone with a smartphone, and in the future may be used to pay for purchases on the app or to various vendors for day-to-day transactions.According to Facebook, the Libra blockchain is pseudonymous, allowing users to hold more than one address not linked to their real-world identity.It claims financial data on Libra transactions will be kept separate from user ad profiles, and that Calibra account information will not be used to improve ad targeting on Facebook-owned platforms.With Facebook's track record thus far, it's understandable that more than a few are wary of this new venture. CNBC reports that Democratic Rep. Maxine Waters said in a statement that the company is "continuing its unchecked expansion and extending its reach into the lives of its users."Citing a lack of regulatory framework for cryptocurrency, she has requested the company pause work on Libra until Congress and regulators can examine the issues and take action.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Facebook cryptocurrency Libra backed by reserve of assets2. Libra governed by non-profit organization3. Calibra digital wallet 4. Libra blockchain pseudonymousVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook on Tuesday announced plans to launch its own cryptocurrency in 2020. The digital currency, called Libra, is backed by a reserve of financial assets, making it less volatile than other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin.""The social giant won't have direct control over Libra. Instead, it will be serviced by the Libra Association, an independent nonprofit headquartered in Switzerland. Its founding members include companies like Uber, Visa, MasterCard, and PayPal, among others.""The association's main functions are to validate transactions on the Libra blockchain, and manage the reserve the digital currency is tied to.""A digital wallet for the new cryptocurrency, called Calibra, is also being launched, and will be available on Messenger, WhatsApp, and as a standalone app.""Calibra will allow users to send Libra to anyone with a smartphone, and in the future may be used to pay for purchases on the app or to various vendors for day-to-day transactions.""According to Facebook, the Libra blockchain is pseudonymous, allowing users to hold more than one address not linked to their real-world identity.""It claims financial data on Libra transactions will be kept separate from user ad profiles, and that Calibra account information will not be used to improve ad targeting on Facebook-owned platforms."SOURCES: Facebook, The Guardian, CNBChttps://libra.org/en-US/white-paper/#introducing-librahttps://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jun/18/what-is-libra-facebook-new-cryptocurrencyhttps://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/18/rep-maxine-waters-facebook-should-stop-work-on-libra-cryptocurrency.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 09:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/20/3847646/3847646_2769C3E696954E67819A867BCD987804_190620_3847646_Facebook_to_launch_Libra_cryptocurrency_in_2020_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, libra, facebook libra, cryptocurrency, facebook cryptocurrency, facebook digital currency, libra cryptocurrency, calibra, calibra digital wallet, facebook calibra, bitcoin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847464</guid>
      <title>Uber unveils first looks at flying taxi, Uber Air</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOn Tuesday the ridesharing company for the first time offered a look at the inside of its aviation product, Uber Air.On its website, Uber says Uber Air is envisioned as a zero-emission electric air vehicle service, available at the push of a button and created by the company in a bid to ease road congestion.According to the Verge, the interior was designed in partnership with French aerospace company Safran.Four passenger seats are turned outwards to the window in rows of two. Behind the second row is room for storing passenger luggage.The craft is illuminated in blue light and, according to Forbes, it has seats upholstered in aerospace-grade 'ultra leather,' a tough, low-friction material for passengers to easily slide in and out of.According to Forbes, initially, the designers had envisioned a cabin more fitting to the customer's needs with charging points, cupholders, and digital screens. But Ian Scoley, a vice president at Safran's design studio, told Forbes: 'We realized for an 8-minute flight, that's all irrelevant.' Uber states on its website that it aims to demonstrate flights in 2020 and for the service to become commercially available in 2023.Dallas and Los Angeles will be the first places to offer this service commercially, with Melbourne being the first city outside of the U.S. to host trails.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Uber Air vehicle benefits explained using pullouts2. Uber Air interior shown and explained3. Designers discussing Uber Air design process 4. Uber Air flies over cityVOICEOVER (in English): "On Tuesday the ridesharing company for the first time offered a look at the inside of its aviation product, Uber Air.""On its website Uber says Uber Air is envisioned as a zero-emission electric air vehicle service, available at the push of a button and created by the company in a bid to ease road congestion.""According to the Verge, the interior was designed in partnership with French aerospace company Safran." "Four passenger seats are turned outwards to the window in rows of two. Behind the second row is room for storing passenger luggage.""The craft is illuminated in blue light and, according to Forbes, it has seats upholstered in aerospace-grade 'ultra leather,' a tough, low-friction material for passengers to easily slide in and out of.""According to Forbes, initially the designers had envisioned a cabin more fitting to the customer's needs with charging points, cupholders and digital screens. But Ian Scoley, a vice president at Safran's design studio, told Forbes: 'We realized for an 8-minute flight, that's all irrelevant.'" "Uber states on its website that it aims to demonstrate flights in 2020 and for the service to become commercially available in 2023.""Dallas and Los Angeles will be the first places to offer this service commercially, with Melbourne being the first city outside of the U.S. to host trails." SOURCES: FORBES, THE VERGE, UBER, THE GUARDIAN   https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2019/06/11/uber-air-taxis-cabin-design/#1e64cdd81b56https://www.theverge.com/2019/6/11/18661129/uber-air-taxi-cabin-interior-elevate-helicopterhttps://www.uber.com/tw/zh-tw/elevate/vision/https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jun/12/uber-air-announces-melbourne-as-trial-city-for-flying-taxi-service***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 05:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/20/3847464/3847464_A65EB85212D84EE0A2E840D957BEB8DE_190620_3847464_Uber_unveils_first_looks_at_flying_taxi__Uber_Ai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Uber, Uber Air, Uber Air taxi, Uber Air vehicle, zero emissions, Safran, Uber driver, Safran aerospace, public transportation, aviation, electric vehicle, road congestion, traffic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848400</guid>
      <title>New undersea cable to go through the Arctic Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFinland-based Fiber optic infrastructure company Cinia and Russian telecommunications operator MegaFon have joined hands to build a fiber optic cable across the Arctic Ocean.The Arctic Fiber project is planned to be launched in three phases.As per Submarine Cable Networks, there would be a fiber optic cable line between Nome and Prudhoe Bay in Alaska in Phase 1. During Phase 2, the cable would be extended west into Asia, down to China and Japan. In Phase 3, the cable would be branched into the Lowest Northwest Passage into Canada and onto the United Kingdom.According to IEEE Spectrum, the cables would reduce latency between European, Asian and North American users.The magazine notes that there are other undersea cables stretching across the northern Atlantic to Europe, then through the Mediterranean. They cut across the Indian Ocean and go up through the South China Sea before finally spanning the Pacific to the U.S. west coast.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cinia logo and MegaFon logo and underwater cable2. The map of the fiber optic cable lines3. What the cables would be used for4. Other underwater cables around the worldVOICEOVER (in English): "Finland-based Fiber optic infrastructure company Cinia and Russian telecommunications operator MegaFon have joined hands to build a fiber optic cable across the Arctic Ocean.""The Arctic Fiber project is planned to be launched in three phases.""As per Submarine Cable Networks, there would be a fiber optic cable line between Nome and Prudhoe Bay in Alaska in Phase 1.""During Phase 2, the cable would be extended west into Asia, down to China and Japan.""In Phase 3, the cable would be branched into the Lowest Northwest Passage into Canada and onto the United Kingdom.""According to IEEE Spectrum, the cables would reduce latency between European, Asian and North American users.""The magazine notes that there are other undersea cables stretching across the northern Atlantic to Europe, then through the Mediterranean.They cut across the Indian Ocean and go up through the South China Sea before finally spanning the Pacific to the U.S. west coast."SOURCES:IEEE Spectrum, The Register, Submarine Cable Networkshttps://spectrum.ieee.org/tech-talk/telecom/internet/melting-sea-ice-opens-the-floodgate-for-a-new-fiber-optic-cable-routehttps://www.theregister.co.uk/2019/06/07/cinia_and_megafon_plan_a_submarine_cable_across_the_arctic_sea/https://www.submarinenetworks.com/systems/asia-europe-africa/arctic-fiber***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 12:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/21/3848400/3848400_13D82C73C66145CF84B25BB1BADA6E5A_190621_3848400_New_undersea_cable_to_go_through_the_Arctic_Sea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, arctic ice melting, arctic ice melting news, climate change, arctic cables, arctic cable route, Arctic Connect Cable, arctic sea, arctic undersea cable, arctic fiber project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848397</guid>
      <title>Honeybee colonies on the decline: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA nationwide U.S. survey has found that bee colonies are dying off due to harsh winters.The report by Bee Informed Partnership, a non-profit group led by the University of Maryland, surveyed around 4,700 beekeepers managing around 320,000 bee colonies during the 2018 to 2019 winter season.Researchers found that beekeepers lost an estimated 37.7 percent of honeybee colonies in the past year alone.This is the highest number of winter losses recorded by the non-profit group for honey bees ever since they started 13 years ago.Entomologists from the group told the Guardian that parasites such as varroa mites could be causing an increase in colony losses due to the viruses they carry.Adding that, pesticides used to remove the mites seem to be becoming less effective.Beekeepers have been making efforts to split healthy bee colonies in order to duplicate them, according to the newspaper.Other problems beekeepers need to deal with include bees dying off due to disease, pesticide use and habitat loss.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ten bee colonies out of which four disappear due to the cold weather2. The percentage of honey bee colonies lost in the past year3. Varroa mites causing a decline to the bee colonies4. Two bee colonies being split into fourVOICEOVER (in English): "A nationwide U.S. survey has found that bee colonies are dying off due to harsh winters.""The report by Bee Informed Partnership, a non-profit group led by the University of Maryland, surveyed around 4,700 beekeepers managing around 320,000 bee colonies during the 2018 to 2019 winter season.""Researchers found that beekeepers lost an estimated 37.7 percent of honeybee colonies in the past year alone.""This is the highest number of winter losses recorded by the non-profit group for honey bees ever since they started 13 years ago.""Entomologists from the group told the Guardian that parasites such as varroa mites could be causing an increase in colony losses due to the viruses they carry.""Adding that, pesticides used to remove the mites seem to be becoming less effective.""According to the newspaper, beekeepers have been making efforts to split healthy bee colonies in order to duplicate them."SOURCES:  The Guardian, Bee Informed Partnership, National Public Radiohttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/jun/19/us-beekeepers-lost-40-of-honeybee-colonies-over-past-year-survey-findshttps://beeinformed.org/https://beeinformed.org/results/2018-2019/https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2019/06/19/733761393/more-bad-buzz-for-bees-record-numbers-of-honey-bee-colonies-died-last-winter***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/21/3848397/3848397_016130C1A2E5472D8B04002782C6037F_190621_3848397_Honeybee_colonies_on_the_decline__Report_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Colony Collapse Disorder, honey bees, bees, honeybee colonies, bee population decline, honey bee population decline]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848224</guid>
      <title>Poor posture due to smartphone use leads to 'horn bone' growth in skull</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from Australia has found that excess usage of smartphones causes a horn-like bone spur to grow at the back of the skull.These bones spurs, also known as enthesophytes, are abnormal bony projections that can form at the attachment of a tendon or ligament.The University of the Sunshine Coast study found that the bone spurs were 10 to 30 millimeters thick.Scientists sampled more than 1200 people between the ages of 18 to 30 and found that around 41 percent of the participants had developed a bony lump at the back of their skull.Further testing such as MRI scans and blood tests were performed. These confirmed that the bone spurs were not a result of genetic factors or inflammation.Enthesophytes are typically seen in older people with poor posture and are the bones response to stress, according to the study.Researchers explained that in this case the abnormal growth forms due to long-term pressure on the skeleton, as the head shifts forwards while we use smartphones for extended periods.According to the study, the bone deformation could cause chronic pain. Carrying the head forward also causes other problems such as neck stiffness and headaches.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A smartphone causing a horn bone to grow at the back of the skull2. The amount of participants found to have the bone3. Hunched back elderly person 4. A person using a smartphone which causes the bone growthVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from Australia has found that excess usage of smartphones causes a horn-like bone spur to grow at the back of the skull.""These bones spurs, also known as enthesophytes, are abnormal bony projections that can form at the attachment of a tendon or ligament." "The University of the Sunshine Coast study found that the bones were 10 to 30 millimeters thick.""Scientists sampled more than 1200 people between the ages of 18 to 30 and found that around 41 percent of the participants had developed a bony lump at the back of their skull.""Further testing such as MRI scans and blood tests were performed. These confirmed that the bone spurs were not a result of genetic factors or inflammation.""According to the study, enthesophytes are typically seen in older people with poor posture.""Researchers explained that in this case the bone growth forms due to long-term pressure on the skeleton, as the head shifts forwards while we use smartphones for extended periods."SOURCES: The West Australian, Journal of Anatomy, University of the Sunshine Coasthttps://thewest.com.au/news/health/researchers-reveal-technology-is-proving-a-pain-in-the-neck-ng-b881234805zhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/joa.12466?utm_source=miragenews&utm_medium=miragenews&utm_campaign=news&https://www.usc.edu.au/explore/usc-news-exchange/news-archive/2019/june/tech-use-causing-horn-like-bone-growth-in-young-people***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 09:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/21/3848224/3848224_0EF12BC32E5648E5AF7E3F31AF6DB7E0_190621_3848224_Poor_posture_due_to_smartphone_use_leads_to__hor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, australia, smartphones, tablets ,smartphone usage, smartphone usage  effects, bad effects of smartphone,  technology effects on skull, horn-like growths, human evolution, skull deformation, human skeleton]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849739</guid>
      <title>Hawaii skydiving plane crash leaves 11 dead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA skydiving plane crashed in Hawaii over the weekend leaving behind no survivors, reports the Honolulu Star Advertiser. The incident is said to be one of the worst civilian disasters in Hawaiian history.The aircraft was a Beechcraft BE65-A90 and was operated by the Oahu Parachute Center, according to the Honolulu Star Advertiser.The crash took place near Dillingham Airfield in Honolulu at 6:30 P.M. on Friday soon after takeoff, according to Hawaii News Now.The television station cites witness Steven Tickemyer as saying that the aircraft dived down before the crash and was engulfed in flames as soon as it hit the airfield's fence line.Honolulu Police told the Star Advertiser that the victims included three men aged 27, 28 and 29, two women aged 26 and 27, plus six other men whose ages weren't revealed.Authorities are still investigating the cause of the plane crash, reports Hawaii News Now. In a tweet, Honolulu Mayor Kirk Caldwell said: "I am closely following the tragic developments out of Dillingham Airfield this evening. At this time our thoughts and prayers are with the family and friends of the victims."Elsewhere, Hawaii News Now reports friends and family of the victims have started laying flowers at the site of the crash to mourn the dead.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The plane and a parachute icon2.  Where the accident took place and the plane taking off3. The plane diving down and an explosion bubble appears4. Victims of the plane crashVOICEOVER (in English): "A skydiving plane has crashed in Hawaii, leaving behind no survivors. This is said to be one of the worst civilian disasters in Hawaiian history.""According to the Honolulu Star Advertiser, the aircraft was a Beechcraft BE65-A90 and was operated by the Oahu Parachute Center.""According to Hawaii News Now, the crash took place near Dillingham Airfield in Honolulu at 6:30 P.M. on Friday soon after takeoff." "The television station cites witness Steven Tickemyer as saying that the aircraft dived down before the crash and was engulfed in flames as soon as it hit the airfield's fence line.""Honolulu Police told the Star Advertiser that the victims included three men aged 27, 28 and 29, two women aged 26 and 27, plus six other men whose ages weren't revealed.""Hawaii News Now reports that authorities are still investigating the cause of the plane crash."SOURCES: Star Advertiser, Go Fund Me, Khon 2,  Hawaii News Now, https://www.staradvertiser.com/2019/06/23/hawaii-news/mourners-search-for-answers-as-the-death-toll-from-fridays-fiery-plane-crash-rises/?HSA=2a28a3f6e35429d38eac149fa265d410ed22dfadhttps://www.gofundme.com/f/casey-williamson-funeral-costshttps://www.khon2.com/news/local-news/friends-family-identify-two-victims-from-deadly-crash/2093677397https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2019/06/22/authorities-responding-reports-possible-plane-crash-north-shore/ ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 13:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/24/3849739/3849739_1CABAC4B0BBC494690C70E9E82068836_190624_3849739_Hawaii_skydiving_plane_crash_leaves_11_dead_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hawaii, hawaii skydiving crash, hawaii plane crash, honolulu plane crash, skydiving, skydiving accident, skydiving victims, skydiving plane crash, skydiving accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849510</guid>
      <title>China deploys J-10 fighter jets to Woody Island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMilitary aircraft have recently been spotted on a Chinese-controlled island in the contested South China Sea, in the first known deployment of fighter jets there since 2017.CNN reports that a satellite image from ImageSat International shows China has deployed four Chengdu J-10 fighter jets to Woody Island in the Paracels.Analysts told CNN that both the placement of the jets out in the open, and the equipment accompanying them indicate they were on the disputed island for up to 10 days.The planes were also not carrying external fuel tanks, suggesting they were to be refueled on Woody Island.According to a former operations director at the U.S. Pacific Command's Joint Intelligence Center, the deployment is a statement that China can extend their air power reach over the region.With the J-10 aircraft's combat range of up to 500 miles or 750 kilometers, this puts the South China Sea and other vital shipping lanes well within reach.Former Australian Air Force officer and current Griffiths Institute fellow Peter Layton speculated that it could also be early training deployment to get the J-10s ready for an ADIZ declaration.An ADIZ or air defense identification zone would require aircraft flying over the disputed waters to first notify Beijing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China deploys 4 J-10 fighter jets to Woody Island2. Fighter jets refueled on the island3. J-10 combat reach in South China Sea4. Beijing air defense identification zone in South China SeaVOICEOVER (in English): "CNN reports that a satellite image from ImageSat International shows China has deployed four Chengdu J-10 fighter jets to Woody Island in the Paracels.""Analysts told CNN that both the placement of the jets out in the open, and the equipment accompanying them indicate they were on the disputed island for up to 10 days.""The planes were also not carrying external fuel tanks, suggesting they were to be refueled on Woody Island.""According to a former operations director at the U.S. Pacific Command's Joint Intelligence Center, the deployment is a statement that China can extend their air power reach over the region.""With the J-10 aircraft's combat range of up to 500 miles or 750 kilometers, this puts the South China Sea and other vital shipping lanes well within reach.""Former Australian Air Force officer and current Griffiths Institute fellow Peter Layton speculated that it could also be early training deployment to get the J-10s ready for an ADIZ declaration."An ADIZ or air defense identification zone would require aircraft flying over the disputed waters to first notify Beijing."SOURCES: CNNhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/20/asia/china-fighters-satellite-image-woody-island-intl-hnk/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 07:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/24/3849510/3849510_79587D16D3374579A40764F5C4E31DA6_190624_3849510_China_deploys_J_10_fighter_jets_to_Woody_Island_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, South China Sea, Woody Island, China fighter jets, J10 fighter jet, artificial islands, Paracels, Paracel Islands, China, china military aircraft, China military]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849375</guid>
      <title>Heathrow airport expansion plans unveiled</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHeathrow Airport has unveiled a proposal to expand its airport, including plans to open a new runway by 2026.This would be the London airport's third runway. The new runway will be 3,500 meters long and would be located in the north-west area of the airport.According to architectural designs released by Heathrow Airport Expansion Consultation website, the proposed runway would be turned into a bridge as it passes over the M25, a motorway around London.According to the BBC, expansion plans include building one single site for cars to park at. The new site would be built at the northern part of the airport on an unspecified date.By 2050, the airport also plans to unveil a new terminal that would integrate indoor and outdoor spaces. Additional plans include creating a low carbon-emissions zone and reducing noise pollution in the area.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The new runway2. Runway over M253. New airport parking lot4. New airport terminal VOICEOVER (in English): "Heathrow Airport has unveiled a proposal to expand its airport, including plans to open a new runway by 2026.""This would be the London airport's third runway.""The new runway will be 3,500 meters long and would be located in the north-west area of the airport.""According to architectural designs released by the airport, the proposed runway would be turned into a bridge as it passes over the M25, a motorway around London.""According to the BBC, expansion plans include building one single site for cars to park at. The new site would be built at the northern part of the airport on an unspecified date.""By 2050, the airport also plans to unveil a new terminal that would integrate indoor and outdoor spaces."SOURCES: CNN, The Guardian, Heathrow Consultation, BBC Newshttps://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/heathrow-airport-expansion-plans-revealed-intl-scli-gbr/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/jun/18/heathrow-third-runway-expansion-plans-revealedhttps://aec.heathrowconsultation.com/topics/overview-airport-masterplans-2022-2050/https://www.bbc.com/news/business-48668001***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 02:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/24/3849375/3849375_B96AD6BCDA0D4A0183F0F91D407671F6_190624_3849375_Heathrow_airport_expansion_plans_unveiled_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Heathrow airport, London heathrow airport, london heathrow airport expansion, london heathrow airport expansion project, Heathrow airport third runway, heathrow airport new terminal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849368</guid>
      <title>Iran shoots down U.S. military drone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIran shot down a U.S. military surveillance drone over the Strait of Hormuz on Thursday.This is the first time Iran has directly attacked the U.S. military, The Associated Press reports.Iran says the U.S. Navy RQ-4A Global Hawk was flying over its territorial airspace while the U.S. says the plane was flying in international airspace.Both countries released coordinates of where the military drone was flying during the incident, CNN reports.Iranian Foreign Minister Javad Zarif tweeted a timeline of the incident. He said the U.S. aircraft took off at 00:14 and was targeted at 04:05 as it violated Iranian airspace.A Khordad-3 medium range air defense missile was used to shoot down the American military drone, according to Iran's Tasnim News Agency.Iran's Revolutionary Guard commander General Hossein Salami said the country had shot down the drone to send a warning to the U.S, according to CNN.As soon as the incident took place. U.S. President Donald Trump tweeted, "Iran made a very big mistake!""We do not have any intention for war with any country, but we are fully ready for war," said Salami, the Associated Press reports, citing a televised press address.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The U.S. surveillance drone in the sky, where it was shot down and the U.S. and the U.S. flag and Iranian flag2. The drone in the sky and coordinates from Iran and the U.S. of where the drone was 3. The timeline of the incident4. The missile that was used to shoot down the American drone.VOICEOVER (in English): " Iran shot down a U.S. military surveillance drone over the Strait of Hormuz on Thursday.""The Associated Press reports this is the first time Iran has directly attacked the U.S. military.""Iran says the U.S. Navy RQ-4A Global Hawk was flying over its territorial airspace while the U.S. says the plane was flying in international airspace.""CNN reports that both countries released coordinates of where the military drone was flying during the incident.""Iranian Foreign Minister Javad Zarif tweeted a timeline of the incident.""He said the U.S. aircraft took off at 00:14 and was targeted at 04:05 as it violated Iranian airspace.""According to Iran's Tasnim News Agency, a Khordad-3 medium range air defense missile was used to shoot down the American military drone. ""Iran's Revolutionary Guard commander General Hossein Salami said the country had shot down the drone to send a warning to the U.S, according to CNN."SOURCES: CNN, The Associated Press, The New York Times, Tasnim News Agencyhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/20/middleeast/iran-drone-claim-hnk-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.apnews.com/e4316eb989d5499c9828350de8524963https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/20/world/middleeast/iran-us-drone.htmlhttps://www.tasnimnews.com/en/news/2019/06/20/2036513/irgc-shoots-down-us-drone-in-iran-s-airspace***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 02:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/24/3849368/3849368_098F4BC7D1C845FB98C360C91E84431B_190624_3849368_Iran_shoots_down_U_S__military_drone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  iran vs usa, Middle East, Strait of Hormuz, iran, USA, usa middle east, usa vs middle east, us iran drone,  iran shoot down us drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850320</guid>
      <title>Ocean Cleanup device redeployed to trap plastic in Great Pacific Garbage Patch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA floating device designed to trap plastic trash in the ocean has been upgraded in a second attempt to clean up the Great Pacific Garbage Patch.According to Ocean Cleanup, an upgraded design dubbed System 001/B is currently being redeployed to the patch.New features include the attachment of inflatable buoys in the opening, which will tow the system forward, propelling it using the force of the wind.Should the buoys fail, an alternative is to attach a parachute-like sea anchor that will turn the system around and bring the speed close to the speed of the water.The screen has been brought forward in order to eliminate the rail connection that caused the boom fracture, and the heavy stabilizing frames removed to ease the load on the pipe. The size of the barrier has also been reduced by a factor of three, in order to speed up procurement, assembly, and towing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ocean Cleanup System 0012. Great Pacific Garbage Patch3. System 001 towed to Great Pacific Garbage Patch4. System 001 unable to retain collected plastic5. Floating boom broke apart under constant wind and waves6. Inflatable buoys on System 001/B7. Parachute sea-anchor on System 001/B8. Other changes made on System 001/BVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that the Ocean Cleanup project's system 001 is a floating 600-meter long U-shaped barrier that is meant to collect plastic debris in the ocean.""The project's main goal is to clean up the Great Pacific Garbage Patch, a massive island of garbage in the Pacific Ocean between California and Hawaii.""Last September, System 001 was towed from San Francisco to the Patch, but problems arose during its first cleanup attempt.""While the system managed to catch plastic waste, it struggled to maintain sufficient speeds and was unable to retain the collected trash.""The floating boom also broke apart under constant wind and waves, reports the Guardian.""According to Ocean Cleanup, an upgraded design dubbed System 001/B is currently being redeployed to the patch.""New features include the attachment of inflatable buoys in the opening, which will tow the system forward, propelling it using the force of the wind.""Should the buoys fail to speed it up, an alternative option is to attach a parachute-like sea anchor that will turn the system around and bring the speed close to the speed of the water.""The screen has been brought forward in order to eliminate the rail connection that caused the boom fracture, and the heavy stabilizing frames removed to ease the load on the pipe.""The size of the barrier has also been reduced by a factor of three, in order to speed up procurement, assembly, and towing."SOURCES: Ocean Cleanup, The Guardianhttps://theoceancleanup.com/updates/system-design-upgrades-completed-to-be-relaunched-in-june/https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/jun/23/great-pacific-garbage-patch-floating-plastic-trap-deployed-again***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/25/3850320/3850320_7237896453704E7DA0BBCF0614318164_190625_3850320_Ocean_Cleanup_device_redeployed_to_trap_plastic__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, great pacific garbage patch, pacific garbage patch, ocean cleanup, plastic pollution, ocean plastic, ocean garbage, pacific ocean cleanup, pacific ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850239</guid>
      <title>One dead as two fighter jets collide in Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo military jets collided in northeastern Germany on Monday while on a mission for the German air force, Deutsche Welle reports.The two aircraft crashed before 2:00 P.M. local time in northeastern Germany near Lake Mueritz, which is north of Berlin.Three Eurofighter jets took off from Laage Air Base, according to Germany's public international broadcaster, Deutsche Welle .The trio was part of the German military's Tactical Air Force Wing 73, which specializes in air defense.The two pilots ejected from their fighter jets and launched their parachutes. One of the pilots was found alive, hanging on a tree canopy. The other pilot was found dead, with human remains being found in the area by the police.Part of the plane wreckage was found in the surrounding area of Malchow, Deutsche Welle reports.The German broadcaster cites reports as saying that the wreckage had caused fires that were extinguished.In a statement, Germany's Minister of Defence Ursula von der Leyen said that they would launch an investigation into the incident.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two fighter jets and where the incident took place in Germany2. Three fighter jets taking off and in the sky together3. The pilots ejecting themselves from the fighter jets4. The plane wreckageVOICEOVER (in English): "Two military jets collided in northeastern Germany on Monday while on a mission for the German air force.""The two aircraft crashed before 2:00 P.M. local time in northeastern Germany near Lake Mueritz, which is north of Berlin.""According to Germany's public international broadcaster, Deutsche Welle, three Eurofighter jets took off from Laage Air Base. The trio was part of the German military's Tactical Air Force Wing 73, which specializes in air defense.""The two pilots ejected from their fighter jets and launched their parachutes.""One of the pilots was found alive, hanging on a tree canopy." "The other pilot was found dead, with human remains being found in the area by the police.""Deutsche Welle reports part of the plane wreckage was found in the surrounding area of Malchow.""The German broadcaster cites reports as saying that the wreckage had caused fires that were extinguished."SOURCES: Deutsche Welle, BBC News, CNN, ABC News via The Associated Press https://www.dw.com/en/pilot-dies-after-eurofighters-collide-in-northern-germany/a-49332147https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-48746559https://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/24/europe/eurofighter-jets-crash-germany-grm-intl/index.htmlhttps://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/reports-fighter-jets-collide-northeastern-germany-63906308***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 12:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/25/3850239/3850239_76CD094593C64EC0931978D9D3A0EBF4_190625_3850239_One_dead_as_two_fighter_jets_collide_in_Germany_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, german air force, germany, fighter jets, eurofighters, german military jets, Laage Air Base, germany military, Eurofighter jets, plane wreckage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850224</guid>
      <title>London's wooden skyscraper explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPLP Architecture and Cambridge University's Department of Architecture unveiled a proposal in 2016 to build London's first wooden skyscraper.The building would be made out of timber and includes mid-rise terraces.The 300-meter tall building is planned to be constructed in central London alongside the Barbican housing estate, according to the architecture firm's website.The skyscraper could house up to 1,000 new residential homes in a 1 million square feet space. The wooden structure would also be made to meet fire regulations set in place for existing concrete and steel buildings.If everything goes according to plan, the building would become the second tallest building in London after The Shard, Inhabitat reports.Researchers explained in a University of Cambridge news release that wooden structures could potentially have multiple benefits such as wood being a renewable source, cost reduction and making the building more lightweight.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The wooden structure2. What the building is made out of and what it includes3. Where the building would be made4. The wooden London skyscraper and The ShardVOICEOVER (in English): "PLP Architecture and Cambridge University's Department of Architecture unveiled a proposal in 2016 to build London's first wooden skyscraper.""The building would be made out of timber and includes mid-rise terraces.""According to the architecture firm's website, the 300-meter tall building is planned to be constructed in central London alongside the Barbican housing estate.""The skyscraper could house up to 1,000 new residential homes in a 1 million square feet space.""The wooden structure would also be made to meet fire regulations set in place for existing concrete and steel buildings.""If everything goes according to plan, the building would become the second tallest building in London after The Shard, Inhabitat reports."SOURCES: PLP Architecture, Dezeen, Urban Next, Inhabitat, University of Cambridge, http://www.plparchitecture.com/oakwood-timber-tower.htmlhttps://www.dezeen.com/2016/04/08/plp-architecture-cambridge-university-london-first-wooden-skyscraper-barbican/https://urbannext.net/oakwood-timber-tower/https://inhabitat.com/worlds-tallest-timber-skyscraper-proposed-for-london/https://www.cam.ac.uk/research/news/timber-skyscrapers-could-transform-londons-skyline***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 11:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/25/3850224/3850224_C476221610014C9C90308A0A617F558C_190625_3850224_London_s_wooden_skyscraper_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, London skyscraper, wooden skyscraper london, timber building london,  tallest timber building london, skyscrapers, tall skyscrapers, unique skyscrapers, timber structures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850032</guid>
      <title>Plans for Tokyo's wooden skyscraper in explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapanese company Sumitomo Forestry has announced plans to build the tallest wooden skyscraper in the world in the city of Tokyo by 2041.The skyscraper would be 350-meters tall and will mark the company's 350th anniversary.The hybrid structure would be made from 90 percent wood and 10 percent steel, according to a press release by the company.The building would use around 185,000 cubic meters of wood. This would allow the structure to remove approximately 100,000 tons of carbon dioxide from the air as well as encourage reforestation.The exterior of the building will be made out of a braced tube structure which would be able to protect the structure in case of an emergency.According to Inhabitat, the building will be covered in greenery and will allow sunlight to enter its interior.Once complete, the structure will be the tallest building in Japan as well as the tallest wooden tower in the world.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The skyscraper2. What the skyscraper would be made out of3. What the exterior of the building will be made out of4. Greenery on the skyscraperVOICEOVER (in English): "Japanese company Sumitomo Forestry announced in February 2018 plans to build the world's tallest wooden skyscraper in Tokyo by 2041.""The building would be 350-meters tall and will mark the company's 350th anniversary.""According to a press release by the company, the hybrid structure would be made from 90 percent wood and 10 percent steel.""The building would use around 185,000 cubic meters of wood." "The company claims this would allow the structure to remove approximately 100,000 tons of carbon dioxide from the air as well as encourage reforestation.""The exterior of the building will be made out of a braced tube structure which would be able to protect the structure in case of an emergency.""According to Inhabitat, the building will be covered in greenery and will allow sunlight to enter its interior."SOURCES:  Arch Daily, Building Design + Construction, Inhabitat, Design Boom, Sumitomo Forestry Companyhttps://www.archdaily.com/889142/japan-plans-for-supertall-wooden-skyscraper-in-tokyo-by-2041https://www.bdcnetwork.com/japanese-company-announces-plans-world%E2%80%99s-tallest-wooden-skyscraperhttps://inhabitat.com/japanese-builder-unveils-plans-for-worlds-tallest-timber-skyscraper-in-tokyo/https://www.designboom.com/architecture/tokyo-plans-worlds-tallest-wooden-skyscraper-2041/http://sfc.jp/english/news/pdf/20180214_e_01.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 07:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/25/3850032/3850032_3AD68F7D9FF447AF85782C44D25DB712_190625_3850032_Plans_for_Tokyo_s_wooden_skyscraper_in_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, tallest wooden skyscraper, skyscraper construction, wooden skyscraper, wooden skyscraper japan, tokyo wooden skyscraper, japanese skyscrapers, timber skyscraper, timber structures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850619</guid>
      <title>Massive freshwater reservoir discovered beneath Atlantic Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have discovered a massive freshwater aquifer hidden beneath the Atlantic.According to a study published in Scientific Reports, Columbia University scientists used an electromagnetic receiver to survey offshore groundwater deposits below the Atlantic Ocean.The results reveal a reservoir of freshwater stretching from the coast of New Jersey to Massachusetts, extending out about 50 miles to the edge of the continental shelf. The reservoir begins some 600 feet below the ocean floor, and bottoms out at 1,200 feet.Researchers theorize that toward the end of the last ice age some 15 to 20,000 years ago, the world's water was locked in ice. Much of what is now the underwater U.S. continental shelf was exposed due to lower sea levels.When the ice melted, sediments formed river deltas over the shelf which trapped freshwater in scattered pockets. Sea levels then rose later on.The aquifer is not stagnant, and is likely fed by subterranean runoff from the land. It is also freshest near the shore, and becomes saltier farther out, suggesting that it gradually mixes with ocean water over time.Because of this, the water would first need to be desalinated before people can use it.While there's no need to dip into this reservoir at the moment, there may be other existing aquifers that could potentially represent a resource in drier regions like southern California, Australia, the Middle East, or sub-Saharan Africa.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Electromagnetic waves used to survey offshore groundwater2. Location and size of freshwater reservoir under Atlantic Ocean3. How freshwater reservoir came about4. Water freshest near the shore, becomes saltier farther outVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in Scientific Reports, Columbia University scientists used an electromagnetic receiver to survey offshore groundwater deposits below the Atlantic Ocean.""The results reveal a reservoir of freshwater stretching from the coast of New Jersey to Massachusetts, extending out about 50 miles to the edge of the continental shelf.""The reservoir begins some 600 feet below the ocean floor, and bottoms out at 1,200 feet.""Researchers theorize that toward the end of the last ice age some 15 to 20,000 years ago, the world's water was locked in ice. Much of what is now the underwater U.S. continental shelf was exposed due to lower sea levels.""When the ice melted, sediments formed river deltas over the shelf which trapped freshwater in scattered pockets. Sea levels then rose later on.""The aquifer is not stagnant, and is likely fed by subterranean runoff from the land.""It is also freshest near the shore, and becomes saltier farther out, suggesting that it gradually mixes with ocean water over time."SOURCES: Scientific Reports, Columbia Universityhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-019-44611-7https://blogs.ei.columbia.edu/2019/06/20/undersea-freshwater-aquifer-northeast/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 08:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/26/3850619/3850619_7B7383C543AB456583D643B5A70AB746_190626_3850619_Massive_freshwater_reservoir_discovered_beneath__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, freshwater reservoir, freshwater store, atlantic freshwater, atlantic freshwater reservoir, aquifer, atlantic aquifer, freshwater under the ocean, atlantic ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851372</guid>
      <title>80-story wooden skyscraper planned for Chicago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArchitectural firm Perkins and Will, along with engineers Thronton Tomasetti and the University of Cambridge conceptualized a wooden skyscraper to be built along the Chicago River in 2017.Called the River Beech Tower, the 80-story high tower would be part of the Chicago's River Beech project.The team would only use real and commercially available timber materials for construction, according to the firm's website.The structure would consist of a diagrid system on its exterior. This would take advantage of the timber's natural axial strength, reports ArchDaily.The building would include 300 residential apartments as well as various skyparks that would feature in its interior for visitors and residents. According to Travel and Leisure, visitors and residents would also have access to green spaces located throughout the building.The River Beech Project will consist of ten other buildings, a green space as well as a river walk, according to Travel and Leisure.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The skyscraper and the Chicago River2. What the building is made out of 3. The building's unique exterior4. The build would feature a skypark VOICEOVER (in English): "Architectural firm Perkins and Will, along with engineers Thronton Tomasetti and the University of Cambridge have conceptualized a wooden skyscraper to be built along the Chicago River.""Called the River Beech Tower, the 80-story high tower would be part of the Chicago's River Beech project.""According to the firm's website, the team would only use real and commercially available timber materials for construction.""ArchDaily reports the structure would consist of a diagrid system on its exterior. This would take advantage of the timber's natural axial strength.""The building would include 300 residential apartments as well as various skyparks that would feature in its interior for visitors and residents.""According to Travel and Leisure, visitors and residents would also have access to green spaces located throughout the building."SOURCES: Travel and Leisure, Research Perkins + Will, Perkins + Will, Curbed, Arch Daily, Design Boomhttps://www.travelandleisure.com/culture-design/architecture-design/chicago-river-beech-tower-tallest-wooden-skyscraperhttp://research.perkinswill.com/articles/curbed-proposed-80-story-wooden-skyscraper-may-be-a-preview-of-tall-timber-future/?utm_medium=website&utm_source=archdaily.comhttps://perkinswill.com/work/river-beech-towerhttps://www.curbed.com/2017/10/9/16449494/tall-timber-building-skyscraper/comment/447612033https://www.archdaily.com/796649/the-tallest-timber-tower-yet-perkins-plus-wills-concept-proposal-for-river-beech-towerhttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/perkins-will-river-beech-tower-timber-skyscraper-chicago-11-08-2017/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 12:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/27/3851372/3851372_FCAAD5EF7355466C87F19020BC30320A_190627_3851372_80_story_wooden_skyscraper_planned_for_Chicago_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, architecture, wooden structures, wooden buildings, wooden skyscraper, wooden skyscraper chicago, skyscrapers, tall skyscrapers, unique skyscrapers, timber structures, eco-friendly buildings]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851067</guid>
      <title>South America to get Solar Eclipse in July</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA total solar eclipse is set to take place on Tuesday, July 2, across South America.A total solar eclipse occurs when the moon covers part of the sun facing Earth, according to NASA.According to Space.com, the eclipse will start at the east-northeast of Wellington, New Zealand and make its way across the Southern Pacific Ocean. The eclipse will appear over central Chile, and is expected to last for 2 minutes and 36 seconds. It will continue east-southeast through to central Argentina and Uruguay.A partial solar eclipse will also appear over other South American countries such as Panama, Costa Rica, and part of Nicaragua.This year's solar eclipse will be 70 percent longer than the solar eclipse that took place across the continental U.S. in 2019, reports Astronomy.com.A total solar eclipse usually occurs around every 18 months, according to NASA.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A total solar eclipse 2. How a total solar eclipse takes place3. Where next week's total solar eclipse will be able to be viewed4. Countries that would be able to view a partial solar eclipseVOICEOVER (in English): "A total solar eclipse is set to take place on Tuesday, July 2, across South America.""According to NASA, a total solar eclipse occurs when the moon covers part of the sun facing Earth." "According to Space.com, the eclipse will start at the east-northeast of Wellington, New Zealand and makes it way across the Southern Pacific Ocean.""The eclipse will appear over central Chile, and is expected to last for 2 minutes and 36 seconds. It will continue east-southeast through to central Argentina and Uruguay.""A partial solar eclipse will also appear over other South American countries such as Panama, Costa Rica, and part of Nicaragua."SOURCES: Space.com, Astronomy magazine, Vox, NASA, https://www.space.com/one-week-until-total-solar-eclipse-2019.htmlhttp://astronomy.com/news/observing/2019/01/our-guide-to-the-2019-eclipse-in-south-americahttps://www.vox.com/science-and-health/2019/6/25/18715409/eclipse-solar-2019-chile-argentina-south-america-live-streamhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2017/the-moon-is-front-and-center-during-a-total-solar-eclipsehttps://svs.gsfc.nasa.gov/4711***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 05:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/27/3851067/3851067_E10AB990A1294BF4BB707651C31054F9_190627_3851067_South_America_to_get_Solar_Eclipse_in_July_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, south america, solar eclipse, solar eclipse in south america, solar eclipse explained, south america eclipse, solar eclipse, eclipse, total solar eclipse, july 2 eclipse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851811</guid>
      <title>Hubble Space Telescope finds charged soccer-shaped molecules in space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Hubble Space Telescope have identified electrically-charged molecules in space that are shaped like soccer balls. According to NASA, Buckminsterfullerene or Buckyballs, are molecules made of 60 carbon atoms arranged in a hollow sphere, in the rough shape of a soccer ball.Buckyballs, which are also called C60, has been found on Earth in some rare cases, in rocks and minerals or in soot created from high-temperature combustion.Though Buckyballs have been seen in space before, scientists using the Hubble Space Telescope recently discovered for the first time ionized C60 within the interstellar medium or ISM.The C60 becomes ionized when ultraviolet light from stars strips off an electron from the molecule, giving it a positive charge.The ISM is the diffuse matter and radiation that exists in between solar systems, which was previously considered too harsh an environment to sustain complex carbon-based molecules.Though most of it contains helium and hydrogen, it contains many other compounds that have not been identified.Researchers say they will continue searching the universe to see where else they can locate C60+. The Epoch Times reports that at the moment, observations seem to be pointing to a widespread presence in the Milky Way.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of C60 molecule2. Ionized C60 discovered in the interstellar medium3. How C60 becomes ionized4. Depiction of interstellar mediumVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA, Buckminsterfullerene or Buckyballs, are molecules made of 60 carbon atoms arranged in a hollow sphere, in the rough shape of a soccer ball.""Buckyballs, which are also called C60, has been found on Earth in some rare cases, in rocks and minerals or in soot created from high-temperature combustion.""Though Buckyballs have been seen in space before, scientists using the Hubble Space Telescope recently discovered for the first time ionized C60 within the interstellar medium or ISM.""The C60 becomes ionized when ultraviolet light from stars strips off an electron from the molecule, giving it a positive charge.""The ISM is the diffuse matter and radiation that exists in between solar systems, which was previously considered too harsh an environment to sustain complex carbon-based molecules.""Though most of it contains helium and hydrogen, it contains many other compounds that have not been identified."SOURCES: CNN, NASA Goddard Space Flight Center (via EurekAlert)https://edition.cnn.com/2019/06/25/world/hubble-soccer-balls-in-space-scn-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-06/nsfc-hft062519.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/28/3851811/3851811_F1660A322F934273980FF0231BC2DA5B_190628_3851811_Hubble_Space_Telescope_finds_charged_soccer_shap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space soccer balls, buckyballs, space buckyballs, buckminsterfullerene, C60, hubble space telescope, hubble telescope, tiny electric soccer balls, carbon molecules, interstellar medium, ISM]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851790</guid>
      <title>Scientists use 3D-printed molds to grow human hair</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have discovered a new way to grow human hair in the lab using 3D-printed molds.According to a Columbia University news release, researchers used 3D-printing to create a plastic mold with long, thin extensions half a millimeter wide, and designed to mimic the natural microenvironment of human hair cells.Once human skin is engineered to grow around the mold, hair follicle cells are seeded in and topped by keratin-producing cells.They are then fed a cocktail of growth factors that stimulates hair growth. This includes JAK inhibitors, which were found to reawaken resting hair follicles in mice when applied on the skin.Researchers had previously discovered a pathway called JAK-STAT in the stem cells of resting hair follicles that keeps them in a dormant state. By controlling pathway activity, JAK inhibitors can trigger follicle growth.According to the Columbia researchers, human hair follicles appeared after three weeks and started creating hair.The technique will be especially useful for hair restoration surgery, which currently relies on the redistribution of follicles from one part of the body to another.Using this new method, scientists can create "a grid of hairs that are patterned correctly and engineered so they can be transplanted back into that same patient's scalp."Hair follicles grown this way could allow for an unlimited supply, with no need for donor hair grafts.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 3D-printed mold that mimics natural microenvironment of human hair cells 2. Human skin grown on mold, hair follicle cells seeded in skin3. JAK-STAT pathway in follicle cells and JAK inhibitors4. Engineered hair follicles used in hair restoration surgeryVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a Columbia University news release, researchers used 3D-printing to create a plastic mold with long, thin extensions half a millimeter wide, and designed to mimic the natural microenvironment of human hair cells.""Once human skin is engineered to grow around the mold, hair follicle cells are seeded in and topped by keratin-producing cells.""They are then fed a cocktail of growth factors that stimulates hair growth. This includes JAK inhibitors, which were found to reawaken resting hair follicles in mice when applied on the skin.""Researchers had previously discovered a pathway called JAK-STAT in the stem cells of resting hair follicles that keeps them in a dormant state. By controlling pathway activity, JAK inhibitors can trigger follicle growth.""According to the Columbia researchers, human hair follicles appeared after three weeks and started creating hair.""The technique will be especially useful for hair restoration surgery, which currently relies on the redistribution of follicles from one part of the body to another.""Using this new method, scientists can create 'a grid of hairs that are patterned correctly and engineered so they can be transplanted back into that same patient's scalp.'"SOURCES: Columbia University Irving Medical Centerhttps://www.cuimc.columbia.edu/news/studies-uncover-new-approaches-combat-hair-loss-men-and-women***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/28/3851790/3851790_B0C45AB7550D41C5B51F624EDF225BEB_190628_3851790_Scientists_use_3D_printed_molds_to_grow_human_ha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 3D printing, 3D printed mold, 3D printed hair farm, hair farm, hair mold, hair loss, baldness cure, baldness breakthrough]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851770</guid>
      <title>Hybrid wooden skyscraper planned for Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArchitecture firm Perkins and Will announced plans in May 2019 to build the tallest hybrid wooden skyscraper in the world in Vancouver.The building will be called Canada Earth Tower and is expected to be built in the city's Central Broadway Corridor in collaboration with private developer Delta Land Development, which has yet to submit a formal rezoning application.Bruce Langereis, president of Delta Land Development, told online newspaper the Daily Hive that the building's exterior, structural columns and floor plates would be made out of cross-laminated timber, a material that can be manufactured with a fire-resistance of 30, 60 and 90 minutes, according to industry site GreenSpec. The building would also include a concrete core with an elevator and an emergency staircase.The skyscraper could rise up to 40 stories high and include approximately 200 residential apartments in a 339,300 square feet space, according to ArchDaily. Sections of the tower would also include an outdoor garden for residents.A horse-shaped complex would lie at the bottom of the building. Developers plan to transform the space into a place for retail stores, restaurants and offices.The building would include other green designs such as energy-efficient air and water pumps, natural ventilation and insulated roofs, the Daily Hive reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Canada Earth Tower2. Skyscraper's exterior, elevator and emergency staircase3. Building's height and footprint4. Horse-shaped complex at the bottom of the towerVOICEOVER (in English): "Architecture firm Perkins and Will announced plans in May 2019 to build the tallest hybrid wooden skyscraper in the world in Vancouver.""Called Canada Earth Tower, the building is expected to be built in the city's Central Broadway Corridor in collaboration with private developer Delta Land Development, which has yet to submit a formal rezoning application.""Bruce Langereis, president of Delta Land Development, told online newspaper the Daily Hive that the building's exterior, structural columns and floor plates would be made out of cross-laminated timber, a material that can be manufactured with a fire-resistance of 30, 60 and 90 minutes, according to industry site GreenSpec." "The building would also include a concrete core with an elevator and an emergency staircase.""According to ArchDaily, the skyscraper could rise up to 40 stories high and include approximately 200 residential apartments in a 339,300 square feet space.""Sections of the tower would also include an outdoor garden for residents.""A horse-shaped complex would lie at the bottom of the building. Developers plan to transform the space into a place for retail stores, restaurants and offices."SOURCES: ArchDaily, Archinect, Daily Hive, DesignBoom, GreenSpechttps://www.archdaily.com/916559/perkins-plus-will-design-the-worlds-tallest-wooden-skyscraper-for-vancouverhttps://archinect.com/news/article/150135111/world-s-tallest-wooden-skyscraper-may-grow-in-vancouverhttps://dailyhive.com/vancouver/1745-west-8th-avenue-vancouver-canada-earth-towerhttps://dailyhive.com/vancouver/broadway-corridor-plan-vancouverhttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/perkins-will-canada-earth-tower-wood-05-16-19/http://www.greenspec.co.uk/building-design/crosslam-timber-fire-resistance-and-rating/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/28/3851770/3851770_C04E7C089D6C432DBFF6E6DA01ACBA48_190628_3851770_Hybrid_wooden_skyscraper_planned_for_Canada_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, skyscraper, wooden skyscraper, hybrid timber tower, hybrid timber tower vancouver, world's tallest hybrid timber tower, wooden skyscraper canada, timber skyscraper, timber structures, Canada Earth Tower]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851607</guid>
      <title>China hacked eight different service providers: Reuters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHackers from China's Ministry of State Security were found breaking into eight different computer service providers around the world, according to a Reuters report.This was an attempt to steal commercial secrets from the service providers' clients, Reuters reports, citing sources familiar with the case.Hewlett Packard Enterprise, IBM, Fujitsu, Tata Consultancy Services, NTT Data, Dimensions Data, Computer Sciences Corporation and DXC Technology were all victims of Chinese cyber attacks.According to the Reuters report, the global hacking campaign is known as "Cloud Hopper," and is believed to have been going on for years. The report says Chinese hacking group APT 10 or Advanced Persistent Threat 10, carried out the attacks for the Chinese Ministry of State Security.Reuters reports that they did this by sending out a phishing email to trick company employees into downloading malware or giving out their passwords. Once gaining access to clientele networks, hackers identified commercially sensitive data to encrypt and exfiltrate.In a statement to Reuters, China denied the accusations and said: "The Chinese government has never in any form participated in or supported any person to carry out the theft of commercial secrets."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A Chinese Ministry of State Security logo and eight computers all being connected2. A computer, a calendar and the Chinese Ministry of State Security logo3. How the cyber attacks were carried out4. Data being exfiltrated from a computer VOICEOVER (in English): "In a detailed report by Reuters, hackers from China's Ministry of State Security were said to be breaking into eight different computer service providers around the world.""Citing sources familiar with the case, Reuters reports, this was an attempt to steal commercial secrets from the service providers' clients.""The report says the global hacking campaign is known as 'Cloud Hopper,' and is believed to have been going on for years.""According to Reuters, Chinese hacking group APT 10 or Advanced Persistent Threat 10, carried out the attacks for the Chinese Ministry of State Security.""They are said to have done this by sending out a phishing email to trick company employees into downloading malware or giving out their passwords.""Once access to networks was acquired, hackers identified commercially sensitive data to encrypt and exfiltrate."SOURCES: Reuters, https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-cyber-cloudhopper-companies-exc/exclusive-china-hacked-eight-major-computer-services-firms-in-years-long-attack-idUSKCN1TR1D4?utm_source=reddit.comhttps://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/china-cyber-cloudhopper/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 04:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/28/3851607/3851607_6465CCB7964D4E84B51904C6E1AFE700_190628_3851607_China_hacked_eight_different_service_providers___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, hacking, chinese cyber attacks, chinese cyber espionage, technology service providers, Cloud Hopper, cyber espionage,  chinese hackers, Cloud Hopper attacks, APT 10]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3853292</guid>
      <title>Scientist pinpoint mysterious space radio waves</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAustralian scientists have for the first time pinpointed the precise location of a mysterious burst of radio waves that originated in another galaxy.According to a release by the Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization or CSIRO, researchers in a world's first have identified the exact location of a great one-off rupture of cosmic radio waves.New Atlas reported that fast radio bursts are one of the most perplexing mysteries of the space age. So what in the galaxy are they and why haven't their origins been located before?Fast radio bursts, or FRBs, are millisecond-long signals which are known to repeat. However, most are single burst, making them extremely challenging to localize. They come from all corners of the universe and were discovered in 2007, with 85 of them since detected. Nobody has been able to understand where they're coming from or what's causing them, until now.An Australian led team of astronomers have now located the galaxy from where one of these FRB waves originated, some 3.6 billion light-years away. The discovery was made using CSIRO's new Australian Square Kilometre Array Pathfinder, a radio telescope in Western Australia.CSIRO lead author Keith Bannister said, "This is the big breakthrough that the field has been waiting for since astronomers discovered fast radio bursts in 2007.So, how has this new technology allowed them to localize the radio signal?The Australian Square Kilometre Array Pathfinder is a design of multiple dish antennas. The burst had to travel a different distance to contact each dish, thus reaching them all at a somewhat different time, allowing for pinpoint accuracy.Adam Deller of Swinburne University of Technology said, "From these tiny time differences  just a fraction of a billionth of a second  we identified the burst's home galaxy and even its exact starting point, 13,000 light years out from the galaxy's center in the galactic suburbs."The cause of the burst remains unknown.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A fast radio burst is emitted from deep space2. Scientist try to identify the source3. ASKAP antennas absorb radio wave information4. ASKAP antennas identify the location of the burstVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a release by the Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization or CSIRO, researchers in a world's first have identified the exact location of a great one-off rupture of cosmic radio waves.""Fast radio bursts, or FRBs, are millisecond-long signals which are known to repeat. However, most are single bursts, making them extremely challenging to localize. They come from all corners of the universe and were discovered in 2007, with 85 of them since detected. Nobody has been able to understand where they're coming from or what's causing them  until now.""An Australian led team of astronomers have now located the galaxy from where one of these FRB waves originated, some 3.6 billion light-years away. The discovery was made using CSIRO's new Australian Square Kilometre Array Pathfinder, a radio telescope in Western Australia.""The Australian Square Kilometre Array Pathfinder is a design of multiple dish antennas. The burst had to travel a different distance to contact each dish, thus reaching them all at a somewhat different time, allowing for pinpoint accuracy."SOURCES: SOURCES: CSIRO, SCIENCEhttps://www.csiro.au/en/News/News-releases/2019/Astronomers-make-history-in-a-split-secondhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2019/06/26/science.aaw5903***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 13:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/07/01/3853292/3853292_7D47765348574249BC8802922D47627E_190701_3853292_Scientist_pinpoint_mysterious_space_radio_waves_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, TomoNews, Satire, space, Australia, CSIRO, ASKAP, astronomers have determined the precise location of a powerful one-off burst of cosmic radio waves, FRBs, fast radio bursts, radio waves, galaxy, galaxies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3853091</guid>
      <title>Eric Holder shot Nipsey Hussle after 'snitch' accusation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to NBC News, an unsealed grand jury transcript said that rapper Nipsey Hussle was shot on March 31 after making a comment about someone being an informant.Hussle was murdered outside of his clothing store in Los Angeles during a personal dispute with alleged killer Eric Holder.According to witness testimony from Herman Douglas, Hussle allegedly said, "man, you know, they got some paperwork on you."Deputy District Attorney John McKinney said the remarks led Holder to leave, return and then fire shots from two weapons, a semi-automatic handgun, and a revolver.Douglas testified that "paperwork" meant police or court documents recording Holder as a snitch. Holder was driven to the scene by a woman he was dating. The woman testified in court saying that she was amazed to see the rapper and got out of the car to ask for a picture, it was at this point she heard Holder turn the accusation onto Hussle.After the heated exchange, the woman said that she and Holder drove off and that's when Holder pulled out a gun and demanded she stop and wait at a certain location. She said that Holder got out of the car, didn't explain himself and then after a short while jumped back into the vehicle. She continued saying that she was confused but that Holder threatened to slap her if she did not drive off quickly.Holder has pleaded not guilty. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hussle and Holder having confrontation2. Holder returns with two guns3. A woman drives Holder away and then stops4. Holder gets out with a gun and then returnsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NBC News, an unsealed grand jury transcript said that rapper Nipsey Hussle was shot on March 31 after making a comment about someone being an informant." "Hussle was murdered outside of his clothing store in Los Angeles during a personal dispute with alleged killer Eric Holder.""According to witness testimony from Herman Douglas, Hussle allegedly said, "man, you know, they got some paperwork on you.'""Deputy District Attorney John McKinney said the remarks led Holder to leave, return and then fire shots from two weapons, a semi-automatic handgun and a revolver.""Holder was driven to the scene by a woman he was dating. The woman testified in court saying that she was amazed to see the rapper and got out of the car to ask for a picture, it was at this point she heard Holder turn the accusation onto Hussle.""After the heated exchange, the woman said that she and Holder drove off and that's when Holder pulled out a gun and demanded she stop and wait at a certain location." "She said that Holder got out of the car, didn't explain himself and then after a short while jumped back into the vehicle. She continued saying that she was confused but that Holder threatened to slap her if she did not drive off quickly."SOURCES: NBC Newshttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/judge-rules-unseal-grand-jury-transcript-nipsey-hussle-murder-case-n1023341***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/07/01/3853091/3853091_2F103C21497A482C894B98153E8B9A0C_190701_3853091_Eric_Holder_shot_Nipsey_Hussle_after__snitch__ac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Nipsey Hussle, Nipsey Hussle shooting, Eric Holder, Nipsey Hussle rapper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3852984</guid>
      <title>NASA announces Dragonfly mission to explore Titan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA is sending a nuclear-powered drone to explore the unique and richly organic Titan moon.NASA announced on Thursday that it will be sending a multi-rotor vehicle called Dragonfly on a mission to Titan, Saturn's largest moon.Dragonfly will launch in 2026 and land on the satellite eight years later, in 2034.The rotorcraft, which has eight rotors and flies like a drone, will spend at least two and a half years making two dozen short flights to explore Titan.According to the New York Times, it will be equipped with a nuclear battery that is charged in between flights.Part of the mission is to study whether Titan is or once was host to life. Its nitrogen-based atmosphere is similar to Earth's, albeit four times denser. Instead of water, lakes, rivers, and seas are filled with liquid methane.While the surface is composed of rock-hard ice, a liquid water reservoir exists beneath the crust.Dragonfly will have cameras on board to stream images taken during flight. It will also carry scientific instruments including spectrometers to study the moon's composition, meteorology sensors, and seismometers. Drills in the landing skids will take surface samples to be analyzed onboard.Dragonfly is not the first spacecraft to touch down on Saturn's largest moon. Europe's Huygens probe landed on Titan in 2005, after traveling to the Saturn system with NASA's Cassini spacecraft. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dragonfly drone launched to Titan2. Dragonfly flying over Titan surface3. Environment on Titan4. Other instruments on DragonflyVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA announced on Thursday that it will be sending a multi-rotor vehicle called Dragonfly on a mission to Saturn's largest moon Titan.""Dragonfly will launch in 2026 and land on the satellite eight years later, in 2034.""The rotorcraft, which has eight rotors and flies like a drone, will spend at least two and a half years making two dozen short flights to explore Titan.""According to the New York Times, it will be equipped with a nuclear battery that is charged in between flights.""Part of the mission is to study whether Titan is or once was host to life. Its nitrogen-based atmosphere is similar to Earth's, albeit four times denser. Instead of water, lakes, rivers, and seas are filled with liquid methane.""While the surface is composed of rock-hard ice, a liquid water reservoir exists beneath the crust.""Dragonfly will have cameras on board to stream images taken during flight. It will also carry scientific instruments including spectrometers to study the moon's composition, meteorology sensors, and seismometers.""Drills in the landing skids will take surface samples to be analyzed onboard."SOURCES: NASA, New York Timeshttps://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasas-dragonfly-will-fly-around-titan-looking-for-origins-signs-of-life/https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/27/science/nasa-titan-dragonfly-caesar.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 03:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/07/01/3852984/3852984_B1DD278AF8AB40068F7BAB39920B0CB0_190701_3852984_NASA_announces_Dragonfly_mission_to_explore_Tita_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dragonfly, nasa dragonfly, dragonfly mission, titan, titan moon, saturn moon, saturn system, life on titan, nasa mission, nasa new frontiers, new frontiers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3852967</guid>
      <title>How to view a solar eclipse in a safe way</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast and Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAhead of next week's total eclipse across South America, astronomers from the American Astronomical Society are warning the public that staring directly at an eclipse can cause permanent damage to the eyes.The American Astronomical Society's website says eclipse glasses or handheld solar filters that compliant with ISO 12312-2 international safety standards must be used when looking at a partially eclipsed sun.This is because the concentrated solar rays from the sun are strong enough to cause significant damage to the retina and could even lead to blindness.Unfiltered cameras, telescopes or regular sunglasses must be not be used when viewing an eclipse. Old solar filters must be discarded if they are scratched, punctured, torn or damaged in any way.The solar filter can only be removed when the moon has completely covered the sun in a total eclipse.Alternate viewing methods include viewing the eclipse via a pinhole projection. This is when you cut a pinhole onto a piece of paper or cardboard and use it to project light onto another piece of paper to view the eclipse.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A partial eclipse, the impact of an eclipse on one's eyes, eclipse glasses and one handheld solar filter2. Inset of the sun and the eyes becoming damaged3. Unfiltered cameras, telescopes, sunglasses and old solar filters4. Total solar eclipse5. Pinhole projection to view the eclipse6. How a total solar eclipse occurs7. Where next week's total solar eclipse will be able to be viewedVOICEOVER (in English): "Ahead of next week's total eclipse across South America, astronomers from the American Astronomical Society are warning the public that staring directly at an eclipse can cause permanent damage to the eyes.""The American Astronomical Society's website says eclipse glasses or handheld solar filters that compliant with ISO 12312-2 international safety standards must be used when looking at a partially eclipsed sun.""This is because the concentrated solar rays from the sun are strong enough to cause significant damage to the retina and could even lead to blindness.""Unfiltered cameras, telescopes or regular sunglasses must be not be used when viewing an eclipse.""Old solar filters must be discarded if they are scratched, punctured, torn or damaged in any way.""The solar filter can only be removed when the moon has completely covered the sun in a total eclipse.""Alternate viewing methods include viewing the eclipse via a pinhole projection.""This is when you cut a pinhole onto a piece of paper or cardboard and use it to project light onto another piece of paper to view the eclipse.""A total solar eclipse occurs when the moon covers part of the sun facing earth." "Space.com reports next week's solar eclipse will start at the east-northeast of Wellington, New Zealand and make its way across the Southern Pacific Ocean.""The eclipse will appear over central Chile and is expected to last for 2 minutes and 36 seconds. It will continue east-southeast through to central Argentina and Uruguay.""Its path will be 11,000 kilometers in width."SOURCES: Space.com, NASA, American Astronomical Society, https://www.space.com/solar-eclipse-glasses-reuse-safety.htmlhttps://www.space.com/one-week-until-total-solar-eclipse-2019.htmlhttps://www.space.com/35555-total-solar-eclipse-safety-tips.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/content/eye-safety-during-a-total-solar-eclipsehttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2017/the-moon-is-front-and-center-during-a-total-solar-eclipsehttps://eclipse.aas.org/eye-safety/eyewear-viewershttps://eclipse.aas.org/eye-safety/safe-viewing***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 02:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/07/01/3852967/3852967_BA36040AAF844EF38D3F2015FD9C861B_190701_3852967_How_to_view_a_solar_eclipse_in_a_safe_way_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, south america, solar eclipse, solar eclipse explained, south america eclipse, solar eclipse eyewear]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
