<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 19:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>4046221</guid>
      <title>Megaripples below Louisiana proof of tsunami caused by asteroid that killed dinosaurs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe theory that the asteroid which made all non-avian dinosaurs extinct also sent a mile-high tsunami crashing into North America has been further confirmed by the discovery of fossilised 'megaripples,' according to a new study published in the Earth and Planetary Science Letters journal.Occurring 66 million years ago, the flow of huge waves may have continued for days as they reflected back on themselves multiple times within the Gulf of Mexico, according to the study.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid heading towards Earth 66 million years ago2. Asteroid hits Earth forming Chicxulub crater and creating massive tsunami3. Mile-high tsunami spreads into North America, sweeping Tyrannosaurus Rex into sea4. Earth freezes over5. Cross section of modern day Earth showing megaripples in sediment below Louisiana 6. Location of megaripples in relation to original impact of asteroidVOICEOVER (in English): "The theory that the asteroid which made all non-avian dinosaurs extinct also sent a mile-high tsunami crashing into North America has been further confirmed by the discovery of fossilised 'megaripples,' according to a new study published in the Earth and Planetary Science Letters journal.""Occurring 66 million years ago, the flow of huge waves may have continued for days as they reflected back on themselves multiple times within the Gulf of Mexico, according to the study.""According to Science Alert, the effects of the tsunami would have imposed devastation for thousands of miles, forcing sea life onto land and land life into the sea. However, atmospheric changes were primarily responsible for wiping out up to 75 percent of species on the planet at the time.""The asteroid hit with the power of 10 billion atomic bombs, according to previous research by the Jackson School of Geosciences, and initially this turned the planet into a fiery hellscape. However, when sulfur-bearing minerals from the impact site were released into the atmosphere, they began reflecting sunlight away from the planet, causing catastrophic global cooling.""The latest addition to this picture of Earth in the moments just after the apocalyptic impact comes via gigantic ripples below its surface. They were engraved by the tsunami in sediments 1,500 meters or 5,000 feet below what is now central Louisiana.""These megaripples show average wavelengths of 600 meters or 1,968 feet, and average wave heights of 16 meters or 52 feet, making them the largest ripples documented on Earth, according to the study."SOURCES: Earth and Planetary Science Letters journal, Jackson School of Geosciences, Science Alert, Science Magazinehttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0012821X21003186?via%3Dihubhttps://www.jsg.utexas.edu/news/2019/09/rocks-at-asteroid-impact-site-record-first-day-of-dinosaur-extinction/https://www.sciencealert.com/tsunami-megaripples-from-the-dinosaur-killing-asteroid-impact-discovered-in-louisianahttps://www.sciencealert.com/catastrophic-new-details-from-the-day-the-dinosaurs-died-uncovered-in-fossilshttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2021/07/giant-tsunami-dino-killing-asteroid-impact-revealed-fossilized-megaripples?utm_campaign=SciMag&utm_source=Social&utm_medium=Reddit***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 10:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/16/4046221/4046221_2D2D18B7FB88482788DBDDC501E769AC_210716_4046221_Megaripples_below_Louisiana_proof_of_tsunami_cau_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, asteroid, dinosaurs, T-Rex, megaripples]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046214</guid>
      <title>The plan to build tropical sauna islands in Helsinki's frozen sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew Atlas reports, citing architecture firm Carlo Ratti Associati, that Helsinki has named the Helsinki Hot Heart project as the winner of its Helsinki Energy Challenge.If the project does go ahead, it will be built in the ocean next to the city and will consist of an archipelago of ten artificial islands built on top of huge water basins.Each basin will measure 225 meters in diameter and hold up to ten million cubic meters of water.Energy drawn from wind, sunlight and other renewable sources will power heat pumps that will heat water and pump it into the huge water basins.The tanks will act like a big thermal battery, storing the hot water until it's pumped into the city's heat-distribution network, as required.Additionally, thanks to all the heat being produced, four of the large islands will serve as recreational parks, with pools and tropical forests installed.The idea is that these will be encased within a transparent dome and LED lighting, allowing locals to enjoy warm parks in the middle of winter.The idea was inspired by the Finnish ideal that everyone has the right to relax and enjoy nature.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Zoom from global to local, show project's location off city shoreline2. Show aerial side view of project, zoom on one basin, show size and depth3. Wind turbine, solar panel, with cables feeding electricity to ocean heat pumps4. Ocean heat pumps pump hot sea water to project's giant water basins, from basins to city heat grid5. Side aerial view of project, highlight four dome-covered parks, zoom, remove roof to reveal forest and hot pools6. People enjoying hot, steaming tropical park, hot steaming pools and beachesVOICEOVER (in English): "New Atlas reports, citing architecture firm Carlo Ratti Associati, that Helsinki has named the Helsinki Hot Heart project as the winner of its Helsinki Energy Challenge.""If the project does go ahead, it will be built in the ocean next to the city and will consist of an archipelago of ten artificial islands built on top of huge water basins.""Each basin will measure 225 meters in diameter and hold up to ten million cubic meters of water.""Energy drawn from wind, sunlight and other renewable sources will power heat pumps that will heat water and pump it into the huge water basins.""The tanks will act like a big thermal battery, storing the hot water until it's pumped into the city's heat-distribution network, as required.""Additionally, thanks to all the heat being produced, four of the large islands will serve as recreational parks, with pools and tropical forests installed.""The idea is that these will be encased within a transparent dome and LED lighting, allowing locals to enjoy warm parks in the middle of winter.""The idea was inspired by the Finnish ideal that everyone has the right to relax and enjoy nature."SOURCES: New Atlas, Inhabitat, The Architects' Journal, CarloRatti.comhttps://newatlas.com/architecture/carlo-ratti-associati-hot-heart-helsinki/https://inhabitat.com/a-tropical-forest-will-soon-grow-in-helsinki-and-provide-all-the-citys-heat/https://www.architectsjournal.co.uk/epic-games/carlo-rattihttps://carloratti.com/project/hot-heart/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 05:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/16/4046214/4046214_2C0492C8604E40EFAD07FEA4CB35F9A6_210716_4046214_The_plan_to_build_tropical_sauna_islands_in_Hels_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Helsinki, hot, heart, water, warm, energy, environment, sustainable, wind, solar, sun, power, electricity, sustainable, fins, finland, nordic, winter, spa, sauna, heating, cost, heat battery, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046241</guid>
      <title>Italy covers melting glacier with reflective sheets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe BBC reports that conservation workers have been covering the Presena Glacier in northern Italy with huge cloth sheets every year since 2008. They put the sheets on at the end of the ski season and take them off again in September, ready for the cooler temperatures and winter snowfalls. These sheets are made from a special reflective material called a "geotextile," which reflects the sun's rays to help prevent the snow underneath from melting. The conservationists say about 70 percent of the snow can be saved over the summer by using the protective sheets. Each sheet is five meters wide and 70 meters long, and they are sewn together and weighted in place so they don't blow away. In total they cover around 120,000 square meters of the glacier. Covering this much of the glacier is no easy task and can take between a month and six weeks for the team to complete. The volume of the Presena Glacier has shrunk by more than a third since 1993. The glacier has also been plagued by algae that turns its white snow pink. The algae also absorbs sunlight and increases the risk of ice melting.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Workers pulling white cloth sheets over glacier outcrops2. Specially adapted snowmobile transports big roll of geotextile up glacier3. Special snowmobile on top of glacier, reversing to unroll big roll of geotextile4. Workers pulling large sheets over glacier, stitching sheets together with machine5. Show large section neatly covered, zoom out to show whole central part of glacier covered6. Scientist sampling pink algae on glacier, zoom out to show pink patches on glacierVOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports that conservation workers have been covering the Presena Glacier in northern Italy with huge cloth sheets every year since 2008.""They put the sheets on at the end of the ski season and take them off again in September, ready for the cooler temperatures and winter snowfalls.""These sheets are made from a special reflective material called a "geotextile," which reflects the sun's rays to help prevent the snow underneath from melting.""The conservationists say about 70 percent of the snow can be saved over the summer by using the protective sheets.""Each sheet is five meters wide and 70 meters long, and they are sewn together and weighted in place so they don't blow away. In total they cover around 120,000 square meters of the glacier.""Covering this much of the glacier is no easy task and can take between a month and six weeks for the team to complete.""The volume of the Presena Glacier has shrunk by more than a third since 1993.""The glacier has also been plagued by algae that turns its white snow pink. The algae also absorbs sunlight and increases the risk of ice melting."SOURCES: Reuters, BBChttps://www.reuters.com/business/environment/italy-covers-shrinking-glacier-save-it-summer-heat-2021-07-01/https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsround/57735433***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 10:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/19/4046241/4046241_8AB423D2B7154E4BB7BE9C5F729E2EA7_210719_4046241_Italy_covers_melting_glacier_with_reflective_she_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Presena, glacier, ice, snow, melt, melting, reflective, sheet, geotextile, protect, italy, environment, conservation, conservationist, green, global, warming, climate, change, glaciologist, glaciology, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046258</guid>
      <title>Amazon went from 'carbon sink' to carbon polluter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Guardian reports that scientists have recently confirmed that the Amazon rainforest is now emitting more carbon dioxide than it is able to absorb, and its emissions amount to a billion tonnes of carbon dioxide a year. The giant forest had previously been a carbon sink, absorbing the airborne carbon that is driving the climate crisis. Sadly, the Amazon is now causing the acceleration of the climate crisis, researchers said. Most of the emissions are caused by fires, many deliberately set to clear land for beef and soy production. But even without fires, hotter temperatures and droughts mean the southeastern Amazon has become a source of CO2, rather than a sink. The scientists said the discovery that part of the Amazon was emitting carbon even without fires was particularly worrying. They said it was most likely the result of each year's deforestation and fires making adjacent forests more susceptible the next year. The trees produce much of the region's rain, so fewer trees means more severe droughts and heatwaves, which cause more tree deaths and fires.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dead trees and leaves releasing CO2, young tree sucking up CO22. CO2 rising from amazon jungle, 33% of it getting absorbed back into jungle3. Heating planet sequence, CO2 rising from jungle, add fires, more CO2 less absorption4. CO2 rising from jungle, jungle getting hotter, heat wave, drier, more CO2 released5. Green, wet jungle, half gets deforested, causing remaining half to dry out6. Continue to show remaining half drying out, heat waves, dying treesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that scientists have recently confirmed that the Amazon rainforest is now emitting more carbon dioxide than it is able to absorb, and its emissions amount to a billion tonnes of carbon dioxide a year.""The giant forest had previously been a carbon sink, absorbing the airborne carbon that is driving the climate crisis. Sadly, the Amazon is now causing the acceleration of the climate crisis, researchers said.""Most of the emissions are caused by fires, many deliberately set to clear land for beef and soy production. But even without fires, hotter temperatures and droughts mean the southeastern Amazon has become a source of CO2, rather than a sink.""The scientists said the discovery that part of the Amazon was emitting carbon even without fires was particularly worrying. They said it was most likely the result of each year's deforestation and fires making adjacent forests more susceptible the next year.""The trees produce much of the region's rain, so fewer trees means more severe droughts and heatwaves, which cause more tree deaths and fires."SOURCES: The Guardian, Washington Post, Inhabitathttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/jul/14/amazon-rainforest-now-emitting-more-co2-than-it-absorbshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2021/07/16/amazon-rainforest-climate-carbon/https://inhabitat.com/the-amazon-rainforest-now-emits-more-carbon-than-it-absorbs/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-021-03629-6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 04:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/20/4046258/4046258_13678F484B3E4D1FB2574B6C6E85D350_210720_4046258_Amazon_went_from__carbon_sink__to_carbon_pollute_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Carbon, sink, amazon, jungle, rainforest, rain, forest, brazil, emit, emission, emitting, absorb, absorption, carbon dioxide, co2, greenhouse, gas, climate, change, crisis, global, warming, fire, fires, deforestation, clearing, drought, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046269</guid>
      <title>Israeli spyware used by Saudi murderers, regimes worldwide</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Washington Post reports that 37 smartphones owned by people connected with murdered Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi were targeted by "military-grade spyware" created by an Israeli company. The Post says these smartphones were on a list of more than 50,000 numbers that are concentrated in countries known to engage in surveillance of their citizens. These countries' governments are known to be clients of the Israeli company, NSO Group, whose Pegasus spyware is ostensibly licensed to track terrorists and major criminals. Many of the numbers on the list were in the Middle East, but the greatest number was in Mexico. The targeted individuals include top military and political officials, as well as journalists and human rights activists. The spyware can easily bypass strong passwords and encryption and can attack phones without any warning to users. It can also read anything on a device that the user can, while also stealing photos, recordings, location records, communications, passwords, call logs and social media posts.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Saudi agents surveilling Kashoggi via PC monitors, hacking his phone2. Show on map how spyware was sold by Israel to Saudis and rest of world3. NSO's two bosses exchange disk for briefcase full of money4. Map view of spyware sales show 50K phones infected, zoom to Mexico where 15K infected5. Icons of types of people targeted, generals, politicians, journalists - Saudis bypassing password on Kashoggi's phone as they remotely hack it6. Saudis remotely hacking Kashoggi phone, copying folders of photos from phone to their PCsVOICEOVER (in English): "The Washington Post reports that 37 smartphones owned by people connected with murdered Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi were targeted by 'military-grade spyware' created by an Israeli company.""The Post says these smartphones were on a list of more than 50,000 numbers that are concentrated in countries known to engage in surveillance of their citizens.""These countries' governments are known to be clients of the Israeli company, NSO Group, whose Pegasus spyware is ostensibly licensed to track terrorists and major criminals.""Many of the numbers on the list were in the Middle East, but the greatest number was in Mexico.""The targeted individuals include top military and political officials, as well as journalists and human rights activists.""The spyware can easily bypass strong passwords and encryption and can attack phones without any warning to users.""It can also read anything on a device that the user can, while also stealing photos, recordings, location records, communications, passwords, call logs and social media posts."SOURCES: Washington Post, The Guardian, CNN, Al Jazeerahttps://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/interactive/2021/nso-spyware-pegasus-cellphones/https://edition.cnn.com/2021/07/18/politics/israeli-spyware-phone-list-hack-investigation/index.htmlhttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/7/18/malware-targets-journalists-activists-and-lawyers-media-reportshttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/sep/12/israel-planted-spying-devices-near-white-house-says-reporthttps://ifamericansknew.org/us_ints/sp-foxvideo.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/21/4046269/4046269_87343E2C4EC6429EBBE31DE57CECE95D_210721_4046269_Israeli_spyware_used_by_Saudi_murderers__regimes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Washington Post, spy, espionage, phone, hack, attack, smartphones, murder, Saudi, arabia, journalist, Jamal, Khashoggi, military-grade, spyware, Israeli company, israel, nso group, pegasus, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046290</guid>
      <title>U.S. and allies accuse China of serious ransomware crimes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCNN reports that the U.S. and its foreign allies accused China of supporting widespread criminality in cyberspace on Monday, July 19. The U.S. says the crimes that China helped support include a massive hack of Microsoft's email system and other ransomware attacks against U.S. companies. In a coordinated announcement, the White House and governments in Europe and Asia accused China's Ministry of State Security of using "criminal contract hackers" to conduct a range of destabilizing activities around the world for personal profit. White House officials said they were surprised by the extent of Chinese involvement in hiring criminal networks to invade and extort money around the world. One official said at least one American company had been targeted for a large ransom by hackers working in association with the Chinese intelligence service. While the public announcement represents a dramatic escalation in the increasingly urgent attempt by the Biden administration to stave off further breaches, Biden stopped short of applying new punishment against Beijing. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flags of U.S. and allies point fingers at flag of China2. Biden makes announcement to explain hacking charges3. Biden's monitor shows how China-based hackers attacked Microsoft servers4. Monitor shows how initial infected servers in turn infected other hardware5. Monitor shows spread of spyware into U.S. server infrastructure6. IT manager working at workstation, suddenly confronted with system lockout and ransomware demandVOICEOVER (in English): "CNN reports that the U.S. and its foreign allies accused China of supporting widespread criminality in cyberspace on Monday, July 19.""The U.S. says the crimes that China helped support include a massive hack of Microsoft's email system and other ransomware attacks against U.S. companies.""In a coordinated announcement, the White House and governments in Europe and Asia accused China's Ministry of State Security of using "criminal contract hackers" to conduct a range of destabilizing activities around the world for personal profit.""White House officials said they were surprised by the extent of Chinese involvement in hiring criminal networks to invade and extort money around the world.""One official said at least one American company had been targeted for a large ransom by hackers working in association with the Chinese intelligence service.""While the public announcement represents a dramatic escalation in the increasingly urgent attempt by the Biden administration to stave off further breaches, Biden stopped short of applying new punishment against Beijing."SOURCES: CNN, Associated Presshttps://edition.cnn.com/2021/07/19/politics/us-china-cyber-offensive/index.htmlhttps://apnews.com/article/microsoft-exchange-hack-biden-china-d533f5361cbc3374fdea58d3fb059f35***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 05:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/22/4046290/4046290_B673C01A76944B3F859358B967A91460_210722_4046290_U_S__and_allies_accuse_China_of_serious_ransomwa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ransomware, attack, hack, spyware, spy, espionage, profit, cyber, biden, white house, official, administration, criminal, hacking, U.S., us, china, beijing, russia, extortion, ransome, criminality, cyberspace, microsoft, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046304</guid>
      <title>China's new hovering train is faster than a jet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANReuters reports that China unveiled a maglev train capable of a top speed of 600 kilometers per hour, or 370 miles per hour, on Tuesday, July 21. That maximum speed would make the train, which was self-developed by China and manufactured in the coastal city of Qingdao, the fastest ground vehicle in the world. Using electro-magnetic force, the maglev train "levitates" above the track with no contact between itself and the rail. This means that the train hovers on magnetic fields created by huge currents of electricity. China has been using the technology for almost two decades on a very limited scale. Shanghai has a short maglev line running from one of its airports to town. While there are currently no inter-city maglev lines in China that could make good use of the higher speeds, cities like Shanghai and Chengdu have started to conduct research. At 600 kilometers per hour, it would only take two-and-a-half hours to travel from Beijing to Shanghai by train  a journey of more than 1,000 kilometers, or 620 miles. Such a journey would take three hours by plane or five-and-a-half hours by high-speed rail.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New maglev train going 600kph on elevated track, racing past cars on highway2. First part of sequence illustrating functioning of wraparound electromagnetic system3. Second part of sequence, focusing on magnets in T-shaped track4. Third part of sequence, focusing on overall interaction between track and train electromagnets5. Mechanical animation showing function from above, cutaway, magnetic interchange6. Show named route on map, with train racing against passenger jet and winningVOICEOVER (in English): "Reuters reports that China unveiled a maglev train capable of a top speed of 600 kilometers per hour, or 370 miles per hour, on Tuesday, July 21.""That maximum speed would make the train, which was self-developed by China and manufactured in the coastal city of Qingdao, the fastest ground vehicle in the world.""Using electro-magnetic force, the maglev train "levitates" above the track with no contact between itself and the rail.""This means that the train hovers on magnetic fields created by huge currents of electricity.""China has been using the technology for almost two decades on a very limited scale. Shanghai has a short maglev line running from one of its airports to town.""While there are currently no inter-city maglev lines in China that could make good use of the higher speeds, cities like Shanghai and Chengdu have started to conduct research.""At 600 kilometers per hour, it would only take two-and-a-half hours to travel from Beijing to Shanghai by train  a journey of more than 1,000 kilometers, or 620 miles.""Such a journey would take three hours by plane or five-and-a-half hours by high-speed rail."SOURCES: Reuters, CBC, Nikkei Asiahttps://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-unveils-600-kph-maglev-train-state-media-2021-07-20/https://www.cbc.ca/news/science/china-fastest-train-1.6110819https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Transportation/China-unveils-600-kph-superfast-maglev-train***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 06:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/23/4046304/4046304_62E546DBC3C94AEB85549A6EC8A75166_210723_4046304_China_s_new_hovering_train_is_faster_than_a_jet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Maglev, magnetic, levitation, levitate, china, qingdao, train, rail, track, 370, miles, per, hour, 600, kilometers, fastest, train, in, world, electromagnet, electromagnetic, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046341</guid>
      <title>China can simultaneously imprison more than one million in Xinjiang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has built the capacity to simultaneously imprison at least 1.01 million people in Xinjiang. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Detention center areas marked on map of Xinjiang2. Detention center areas one-third the size of Manhattan3. Detention center cell dimensions4. Potential for overcrowding in cells5. Repurposing of hospital to become detention center 6. Construction of detention center with graph of construction growth between 2016 and 20217. Detention center capacity vs. U.S. prison capacity 8. Corridor inside center with yellow lines9. Classroom inside center10. Inside factory within center11. Physical intimidation and abuse within centerVOICEOVER (in English): "China has built the capacity to simultaneously imprison at least 1.01 million people in Xinjiang, according to Buzzfeed News analysis. This may suggest previous estimates of around a million Uyghur and other ethnic minority Muslims being detained over the last five years are too low."  "Three hundred and forty-seven facilities have been identified as being built since 2016, and as of April 2021 these facilities covered an area of more than 206 million square feet, or around 19.2 million square meters  enough to cover a third of Manhattan.""Within the facilities, government documents from 2010 and 2013 indicate cells are designed to hold between eight and 16 people, allowing between 5 and 7 square meters per person.""Those specifications, combined with the total area allocated for detention centers, are how the estimated capacity of more than one million people was arrived at. However, previous accounts of overcrowding, plus the existence of 100 detention facilities built before 2016 and not included in the report, could indicate a still larger capacity.""According to the Buzzfeed News report, the coordinated campaign to imprison Muslims in Xinjiang began in 2016, initially with schools, hospitals and other public buildings repurposed to become detention centers.""This process solidified into something more sophisticated in the following years as more and more purpose-built facilities were constructed, peaking between 2017 and 2019.""As of April 2021, Buzzfeed News estimates this amount of detention space provides the capacity to imprison one in 25 of the population of Xinjiang, a relative detention capacity seven times higher than that of the United States, the country with the highest official prison population in the world."SOURCES: Buzzfeed News, Australian Strategic Policy Institute, Reuters, Global China: Assessing China's Growing Role in the World, Atalayar, BBC, Time Magazinehttps://www.brookings.edu/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/FP_20200914_china_oppression_xinjiang_millward_peterson.pdfhttps://atalayar.com/en/content/being-muslim-china-not-dangerous-being-uyghurhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-22278037https://time.com/3099950/china-muslim-hui-xinjiang-uighur-islam/https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/meghara/china-camps-prisons-xinjiang-muslims-sizehttps://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/meghara/inside-xinjiang-detention-camphttps://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/alison_killing/xinjiang-camps-china-factories-forced-laborhttps://cdn.xjdp.aspi.org.au/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/25125443/documenting-xinjiangs-detention-system.cleaned.pdfhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang/china-says-most-people-in-xinjiang-camps-have-returned-to-society-idUSKCN1UP15F***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/26/4046341/4046341_9AA9A95154EF4998A6C670AF2CFC2B6D_210726_4046341_China_can_simultaneously_imprison_more_than_one__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Xinjiang, Uyghur Muslims, CCP, China, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046339</guid>
      <title>Dubai says freak rain was caused by cloud-seeding drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Independent reports that the United Arab Emirates has been abuzz with excitement over very unusual torrential rain that fell in the desert country for a few days around Monday, July 19.On Twitter, the UAE's weather bureau hinted that much of this unseasonal downpour is due to its multi-million-dollar cloud seeding efforts. One of the ways in which the UAE seeds clouds, is by using electricity-inducing drones. The drones were developed by the UAE and researchers from the University of Reading in England. They get catapulted into the air and cruise through the sky, gathering weather data and giving a nudge to clouds in the form of an electrical charge. The idea is that the electrical charge helps clump water droplets and other particles together to make new and bigger clouds that actually have a chance to generate much-needed precipitation. This is important since the UAE typically receives only four inches, or 10 centimeters, of rain per year. The idea is to make the droplets inside the clouds big enough so that when they fall out of the cloud, they survive down to the surface.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Zoom from global to UAE on global map, adding inset image of the Dubai skyline2. Show torrential rain coming down around desert roads of UAE, streams of floodwater3. Show special weather drone being launched and flying over UAE desert4. Drone flying in clouds, pulsing electrical charge, electrical charge helping droplets clump together5. Droplets clump together more and more, forming big water drop6. Zoom out to show many drops forming inside cloud, then falling out of cloudVOICEOVER (in English): "The Independent reports that the United Arab Emirates has been abuzz with excitement over very unusual torrential rain that fell in the desert country for a few days around Monday, July 19.""On Twitter, the UAE's weather bureau hinted that much of this unseasonal downpour is due to its multi-million-dollar cloud seeding efforts.""One of the ways in which the UAE seeds clouds, is by using electricity-inducing drones. The drones were developed by the UAE and researchers from the University of Reading in England.""They get catapulted into the air and cruise through the sky, gathering weather data and giving a nudge to clouds in the form of an electrical charge.""The idea is that the electrical charge helps clump water droplets and other particles together to make new and bigger clouds that actually have a chance to generate much-needed precipitation.""This is important since the UAE typically receives only four inches, or 10 centimeters, of rain per year.""The idea is to make the droplets inside the clouds big enough so that when they fall out of the cloud, they survive down to the surface."SOURCES: The Independent, USA Today, Newsweek, IFLScience.comhttps://www.independent.co.uk/climate-change/news/dubai-fake-rain-heat-b1887596.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2021/07/21/cloud-seeding-uae-artificial-rain-drones-electricity/8040330002/https://www.newsweek.com/dubai-creates-fake-rain-using-drones-battle-122-degree-heat-1611887https://www.iflscience.com/environment/fake-rain-the-uae-thanks-cloud-seeding-for-its-recent-rain-downpours/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 13:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/26/4046339/4046339_A3BE3D5246674E3392EEDFAD96018759_210726_4046339_Dubai_says_freak_rain_was_caused_by_cloud_seedin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[United arab emirates, uae, cloud, seeding, rainmaking, rainmaker, rain, rainfall, boost, droplet, drop, precipitation, drone, electrical, charge, pulse, torrential, torrent, flood, floodwater, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046333</guid>
      <title>China can simultaneously imprison more than one million in Xinjiang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has built the capacity to simultaneously imprison at least 1.01 million people in Xinjiang. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Detention center areas marked on map of Xinjiang2. Detention center areas one-third the size of Manhattan3. Detention center cell dimensions4. Potential for overcrowding in cells5. Repurposing of hospital to become detention center 6. Construction of detention center with graph of construction growth between 2016 and 20217. Detention center capacity vs. U.S. prison capacity 8. Corridor inside center with yellow lines9. Classroom inside center10. Inside factory within center11. Physical intimidation and abuse within centerVOICEOVER (in English): "China has built the capacity to simultaneously imprison at least 1.01 million people in Xinjiang, according to Buzzfeed News analysis. This may suggest previous estimates of around a million Uyghur and other ethnic minority Muslims being detained over the last five years are too low."  "Three hundred and forty-seven facilities have been identified as being built since 2016, and as of April 2021 these facilities covered an area of more than 206 million square feet, or around 19.2 million square meters  enough to cover a third of Manhattan.""Within the facilities, government documents from 2010 and 2013 indicate cells are designed to hold between eight and 16 people, allowing between 5 and 7 square meters per person.""Those specifications, combined with the total area allocated for detention centers, are how the estimated capacity of more than one million people was arrived at. However, previous accounts of overcrowding, plus the existence of 100 detention facilities built before 2016 and not included in the report, could indicate a still larger capacity.""According to the Buzzfeed News report, the coordinated campaign to imprison Muslims in Xinjiang began in 2016, initially with schools, hospitals and other public buildings repurposed to become detention centers.""This process solidified into something more sophisticated in the following years as more and more purpose-built facilities were constructed, peaking between 2017 and 2019.""As of April 2021, Buzzfeed News estimates this amount of detention space provides the capacity to imprison one in 25 of the population of Xinjiang, a relative detention capacity seven times higher than that of the United States, the country with the highest official prison population in the world."SOURCES: Buzzfeed News, Australian Strategic Policy Institute, Reuters, Global China: Assessing China's Growing Role in the World, Atalayar, BBC, Time Magazinehttps://www.brookings.edu/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/FP_20200914_china_oppression_xinjiang_millward_peterson.pdfhttps://atalayar.com/en/content/being-muslim-china-not-dangerous-being-uyghurhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-22278037https://time.com/3099950/china-muslim-hui-xinjiang-uighur-islam/https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/meghara/china-camps-prisons-xinjiang-muslims-sizehttps://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/meghara/inside-xinjiang-detention-camphttps://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/alison_killing/xinjiang-camps-china-factories-forced-laborhttps://cdn.xjdp.aspi.org.au/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/25125443/documenting-xinjiangs-detention-system.cleaned.pdfhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang/china-says-most-people-in-xinjiang-camps-have-returned-to-society-idUSKCN1UP15F***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 12:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/26/4046333/4046333_83A77501358142FEB072088DAB84F854_210726_4046333_China_can_simultaneously_imprison_more_than_one__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Xinjiang, Uyghur Muslims, CCP, China, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046349</guid>
      <title>Scientists shocked by size of Mars' liquid core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe BBC reports that NASA scientists have studied data from the seismology sensors on its InSight probe and now know what the internal structure of Mars looks like. The probe has been sensing small quakes on the planet since early 2019. Its readings reveal that Mars' crust is between 24 and 72 kilometers thick, which is thinner than expected. But the key finding is the size of the planet's liquid and metallic core. Its radius of 1,830 kilometers is wider than expected. This means that the mantle between the core and the crust is thinner than previously thought. And that means it's highly unlikely this mantle can achieve the pressures where the mineral bridgmanite becomes stable. On Earth, this stiff mineral blankets the core, slowing convection and the loss of heat. On early Mars, its absence would have led to rapid cooling. This initially would have permitted strong convection in the metal core, which drove a global magnetic field. But because of rapid cooling, this has now switched off and today Mars has no global magnetic field.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. InSight probe's crane lifting instrument from probe and putting it down on surface of Mars2. Show Mars as sphere, with probe on top, then show Mars cut open to show insides3. Highlight crust, then inner core, liquid metal, add measuring line on core's radius4. Highlight mantle, add red measuring line, cluster of bridgmanite forming, then deforming5. Show Earth cut open to show layers, bridgmanite layer highlighted, inset box shows molecular structure6. Mars' cutaway, currents rotating in liquid core, magnetic field active, cooling of core stops currents, magnetic field disappearsVOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports that NASA scientists have studied data from the seismology sensors on its InSight probe and now know what the internal structure of Mars looks like.""The probe has been sensing small quakes on the planet since early 2019. Its readings reveal that Mars' crust is between 24 and 72 kilometers thick, which is thinner than expected.""But the key finding is the size of the planet's liquid and metallic core. Its radius of 1,830 kilometers is wider than expected.""This means that the mantle between the core and the crust is thinner than previously thought. And that means it's highly unlikely this mantle can achieve the pressures where the mineral bridgmanite becomes stable.""On Earth, this stiff mineral blankets the core, slowing convection and the loss of heat. On early Mars, its absence would have led to rapid cooling.""This initially would have permitted strong convection in the metal core, which drove a global magnetic field. But because of rapid cooling, this has now switched off and today Mars has no global magnetic field."SOURCES: BBC, NASA, National Geographichttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-57935742https://mars.nasa.gov/insight/https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/nasa-insight-spacecraft-reveals-first-peek-inside-mars-center***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/27/4046349/4046349_9677B9694E2D46EFA92579D3A44C937C_210727_4046349_Scientists_shocked_by_size_of_Mars__liquid_core_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Seismology, seismic, seismologist, wave, study, quake, mars, martian, tremor, insight, probe, nasa, lander, magnetosphere, magnetic, field, radiation, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046364</guid>
      <title>U.S. sends large F-22 force to counter China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCNN reports that the U.S. Air Force is sending an unusually large force of F-22 stealth fighters to the western Pacific this month. Approximately 25 F-22s will be joined by 10 F-15 fighters and support planes, as part of an exercise that is meant to send a strong message to China, amid growing tensions about China's actions around Taiwan and in the South China Sea. The exercise is designed to spread U.S. combat planes out among airfields across the region, to increase their chances of surviving enemy missile strikes. Much of the U.S.'s air power in the western Pacific is concentrated in two large military installations on Okinawa and Guam. A strike on those bases could cripple the U.S. military's ability to hit back if too much U.S. air power was concentrated there. The new exercise will see crews practicing from smaller, less developed airfields on Guam and islands like Tinian. The new strategy would increase the number of targets enemy missiles would need to destroy and give U.S. air power a better chance of being able to fight back.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map zoom from global US to Marianas, showing planes moving to Marianas2. Chinese warship sailing on ocean, zoom in to show officer exiting to balcony3. Same officer looks up to see 26 F-22s and 10 F-15s fly low overhead4. Show Kadena and Guam bases on map, zoom to Kadena showing many planes close together5. Zoom out to show regional map, showing jet icons leaving 2 bases to spread out to smaller airstrips over region6. Map icon view of Chinese cruise missiles approaching US airstrips, jets, most intercepted but some hit, F-22 icons move toward China, followed by B-2s and carriersVOICEOVER (in English): "CNN reports that the U.S. Air Force is sending an unusually large force of F-22 stealth fighters to the western Pacific this month.""Approximately 25 F-22s will be joined by 10 F-15 fighters and support planes, as part of an exercise that is meant to send a strong message to China, amid growing tensions about China's actions around Taiwan and in the South China Sea.""The exercise is designed to spread U.S. combat planes out among airfields across the region, to increase their chances of surviving enemy missile strikes.""Much of the U.S.'s air power in the western Pacific is concentrated in two large military installations on Okinawa and Guam.""A strike on those bases could cripple the U.S. military's ability to hit back if too much U.S. air power was concentrated there.""The new exercise will see crews practicing from smaller, less developed airfields on Guam and islands like Tinian.""The new strategy would increase the number of targets enemy missiles would need to destroy and give U.S. air power a better chance of being able to fight back."SOURCES: CNN, Forbes, UPIhttps://edition.cnn.com/2021/07/15/asia/us-air-force-f-22-guam-tinian-exercise-intl-hnk-ml/index.htmlhttps://www.forbes.com/sites/davidaxe/2021/07/20/the-us-air-force-is-sending-dozens-of-f-22-stealth-fighters-to-practice-for-war-with-china/?sh=498b851afaf9https://www.upi.com/Defense-News/2021/07/16/f22-usaf-guam-marianas-exercise-China/6291626457191/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 05:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/28/4046364/4046364_DEA4370FF9F04A3FAF0F416BCF20D389_210728_4046364_U_S__sends_large_F_22_force_to_counter_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Pentagon, usaf, us air force, us, china, deploy, frontline, front line, deployment, f-22, f-15, c-130, tinian, guam, marianas, islands, afb, base, warning, fifth, generation, fighter, jet, stealth, tensions, taiwan, south china sea, wwiii, world war 3, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046379</guid>
      <title>Amazon's Bezos offers NASA billions to get Musk's contract</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBBC reports that Jeff Bezos is offering NASA a discount of more than $2 billion for the agency to give his space company a lucrative human lunar landing system contract that his rival Elon Musk's SpaceX won in April this year. In Bezos' original proposal for the lunar landing system, his Blue Origin company would team up with other companies to build three vehicles, called elements. These three elements would be launched separately and link up in Earth orbit. This is where the Transfer Element would be used to transport the whole package to the moon. Once in position over the moon, the other two elements would detach, using the Descent Element's thrusters to slow them down so they could fall to the moon's surface. The Descent Element would also protect the astronaut-carrying Ascent Element from flying rocks, although this would mean that the astronauts would have to climb down a long ladder to get to the surface. Once it's time to return, the Ascent Element would fire its own rockets to blast back into moon orbit, where it would meet up again with the Transfer Element.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bezos stands before NASA panel, offers truckload of money 2. falls on knees - Descent Element docks with Transfer Element in Earth orbit3. Ascent Element docks with other elements, Transfer Element's rocket fires, moving package4. Over moon, Ascent and Descent element detach, Descent E fires rockets to slow and drop5. Ascent and Descent Elements land as one unit, DE rockets firing, rocks shooting out, Astronauts 6. working around lander unit, then show AE firing rockets, leaving DE behind on moonVOICEOVER (in English): "BBC reports that Jeff Bezos is offering NASA a discount of more than $2 billion for the agency to give his space company a lucrative human lunar landing system contract that his rival Elon Musk's SpaceX won in April this year.""In Bezos' original proposal for the lunar landing system, his Blue Origin company would team up with other companies to build three vehicles, called elements.""These three elements would be launched separately and link up in Earth orbit.""This is where the Transfer Element would be used to transport the whole package to the moon.""Once in position over the moon, the other two elements would detach, using the Descent Element's thrusters to slow them down so they could fall to the moon's surface.""The Descent Element would also protect the astronaut-carrying Ascent Element from flying rocks, although this would mean that the astronauts would have to climb down a long ladder to get to the surface.""Once it's time to return, the Ascent Element would fire its own rockets to blast back into moon orbit, where it would meet up again with the Transfer Element."SOURCES: BBC, Reuters, The Vergehttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-57978465https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/science/bezos-offers-nasa-2-billion-exchange-moon-mission-contract-2021-07-26/https://www.theverge.com/2021/7/26/22594038/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-nasa-lunar-lander-2-billion***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 05:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/29/4046379/4046379_4179354B69004E05B6CDC82827D10E68_210729_4046379_Amazon_s_Bezos_offers_NASA_billions_to_get_Musk__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Jeff, bezos, blue, origin, space, lunar, human, landing, system, hls, contract, spacex, nasa, moon, mission, astronaut, billion, dollars, national, team, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046412</guid>
      <title>Satellites show China is building many more nuke silos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe New York Times reports that analysts have found a second new missile base in China, only days after another new base was found. Identified via satellite imagery, the new missile base in China's Xinjiang region may eventually include 110 silos, according to a report by the Federation of American Scientists, or FAS. It is the second apparent silo field uncovered this month by researchers, adding to 120 silos that appear to be under construction in the neighboring province of Gansu. For decades, China has operated around 20 silos for its liquid-fueled ICBMs, called the DF-5. Now, it appears to be building 10 times more, possibly for housing its newest ICBM, the DF-41, according to the FAS report. The New York Times says the new silos are clearly being built to be discovered. The most recent silo field is in the eastern part of the Xinjiang region, not far from one of China's notorious Uyghur "re-education" camps in the city of Hami. The road network linking the different silo construction sites also makes the area look suspiciously like a massive nuclear base on satellite images.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Globe rotation and zoom to show Xinjiang province on map2. Show satellite images that gradually zoom in on new missile site3. Zoom in on lid of missile silo, lid opens, missile launches4. Compare two DF-5 type missiles to new DF-41 missile5. Follow missile as it flies, see-through view of multiple warheads in nose6. Follow one warhead as it falls to a city and explodeVOICEOVER (in English): "The New York Times reports that analysts have found a second new missile base in China, only days after another new base was found.""Identified via satellite imagery, the new missile base in China's Xinjiang region may eventually include 110 silos, according to a report by the Federation of American Scientists, or FAS.""It is the second apparent silo field uncovered this month by researchers, adding to 120 silos that appear to be under construction in the neighboring province of Gansu.""For decades, China has operated around 20 silos for its liquid-fueled ICBMs, called the DF-5.""Now, it appears to be building 10 times more, possibly for housing its newest ICBM, the DF-41, according to the FAS report.'"The New York Times says the new silos are clearly being built to be discovered.""The most recent silo field is in the eastern part of the Xinjiang region, not far from one of China's notorious Uyghur "re-education" camps in the city of Hami.""The road network linking the different silo construction sites also makes the area look suspiciously like a massive nuclear base on satellite images."SOURCES: New York Times, ABC News, Insider.comhttps://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/26/us/politics/china-nuclear-weapons.htmlhttps://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/us-warns-china-building-nuclear-missile-silos-79160762https://www.insider.com/china-constructing-massive-nuclear-base-silos-xinjiang-2021-7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/30/4046412/4046412_3823D78AFF194776BE7A5C7233065B1B_210730_4046412_Satellites_show_China_is_building_many_more_nuke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, xinjiang, nuclear, missile, base, silo, df-5, df-41, chinese, xi jinping, satellite, image, federation of scientists, US, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046408</guid>
      <title>Satellites show China is building many more nuke silos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe New York Times reports that analysts have found a second new missile base in China, only days after another new base was found. Identified via satellite imagery, the new missile base in China's Xinjiang region may eventually include 110 silos, according to a report by the Federation of American Scientists, or FAS. It is the second apparent silo field uncovered this month by researchers, adding to 120 silos that appear to be under construction in the neighboring province of Gansu. For decades, China has operated around 20 silos for its liquid-fueled ICBMs, called the DF-5. Now, it appears to be building 10 times more, possibly for housing its newest ICBM, the DF-41, according to the FAS report. The New York Times says the new silos are clearly being built to be discovered. The most recent silo field is in the eastern part of the Xinjiang region, not far from one of China's notorious Uyghur "re-education" camps in the city of Hami. The road network linking the different silo construction sites also makes the area look suspiciously like a massive nuclear base on satellite images.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Globe rotation and zoom to show Xinjiang province on map2. Show satellite images that gradually zoom in on new missile site3. Zoom in on lid of missile silo, lid opens, missile launches4. Compare two DF-5 type missiles to new DF-41 missile5. Follow missile as it flies, see-through view of multiple warheads in nose6. Follow one warhead as it falls to a city and explodeVOICEOVER (in English): "The New York Times reports that analysts have found a second new missile base in China, only days after another new base was found.""Identified via satellite imagery, the new missile base in China's Xinjiang region may eventually include 110 silos, according to a report by the Federation of American Scientists, or FAS.""It is the second apparent silo field uncovered this month by researchers, adding to 120 silos that appear to be under construction in the neighboring province of Gansu.""For decades, China has operated around 20 silos for its liquid-fueled ICBMs, called the DF-5.""Now, it appears to be building 10 times more, possibly for housing its newest ICBM, the DF-41, according to the FAS report.'"The New York Times says the new silos are clearly being built to be discovered.""The most recent silo field is in the eastern part of the Xinjiang region, not far from one of China's notorious Uyghur "re-education" camps in the city of Hami.""The road network linking the different silo construction sites also makes the area look suspiciously like a massive nuclear base on satellite images."SOURCES: New York Times, ABC News, Insider.comhttps://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/26/us/politics/china-nuclear-weapons.htmlhttps://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/us-warns-china-building-nuclear-missile-silos-79160762https://www.insider.com/china-constructing-massive-nuclear-base-silos-xinjiang-2021-7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/30/4046408/4046408_1971D71C5BDC44F38776D76ED164DE0E_210730_4046408_Satellites_show_China_is_building_many_more_nuke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, xinjiang, nuclear, missile, base, silo, df-5, df-41, chinese, xi jinping, satellite, image, federation of scientists, US, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4046397</guid>
      <title>Google co-founder Larry Page seeing out pandemic in Fiji</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLarry Page, the co-founder of Google, has spent much of the COVID-19 pandemic on tropical islands in Fiji, entering the country via a government system that allows wealthy individuals to avoid COVID-19 travel restrictions, according to Business Insider.Page has stayed mostly on Tavarua island, to the west of the main Fijian island, according to two different people who have seen him there in the past year, cited by Insider.Fiji has closed its borders to tourists and business passengers during the pandemic. However, it has made an exception for 'for yachts and pleasure craft wanting to explore our islands,' in the form of what it calls "Blue Lanes."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Inside Larry Page's Yacht as it sails next to Tavarua island, Fiji2. Map view of Yacht arriving at Tavarua3. 'Blue Lane Approved' burgee flag flown on deck of yacht4. Diagram of steps super-rich can take to enter Fiji5. Larry Page's private jet flying into Fiji with COVID medical supplies6. Medical supplies unpacked on Fijian runwayVOICEOVER (in English): "Larry Page, the co-founder of Google, has spent much of the COVID-19 pandemic on tropical islands in Fiji, entering the country via a government system that allows wealthy individuals to avoid COVID-19 travel restrictions, according to Business Insider.""Page has stayed mostly on Tavarua island, to the west of the main Fijian island, according to two different people who have seen him there in the past year, cited by Insider.""Fiji has closed its borders to tourists and business passengers during the pandemic. However, it has made an exception for 'for yachts and pleasure craft wanting to explore our islands,' in the form of what it calls 'Blue Lanes.'""Under the system of Blue Lanes, yacht owners can enter the country with minimal restrictions, including a negative COVID test. They must quarantine for 14 days, but this includes time spent travelling on their vessels.""Page's time in Fiji has been largely unreported, however a donation of COVID medical supplies he made to the country was briefly made public by a journalist at Fijian Broadcasting Company News.""Citing a person familiar with the story, Business Insider reports that Fijian health authorities asked the network to take the information down, saying it should not be public."SOURCES: New York Post, Business Insider, Tourism Fiji, Fijian Broadcasting Company Newshttps://nypost.com/2021/07/23/google-co-founder-larry-page-reportedly-hiding-out-in-fiji/https://www.businessinsider.com/larry-page-google-bought-fiji-island-pandemic-hiding-tavarua-namotu-2021-7https://www.fiji.travel/articles/sail-fijis-blue-laneshttps://www.fiji.travel/COVID-19/CORONAVIRUS-COVID-19-INFORMATION-FIJIhttps://twitter.com/Naikasof/status/1406146066332884992***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 05:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/21/07/30/4046397/4046397_4CAE99E54305485989175A7A4A5A9787_210730_4046397_Google_co_founder_Larry_Page_seeing_out_pandemic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Larry Page, Google, co-founder, Fiji, Tavarua, Blue Lane, rich, wealthy, elite, billionaire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
