<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 19:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3914865</guid>
      <title>Researchers track Otzi the Iceman's last journey using moss</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrozen plant species buried with Otzi the Iceman has allowed scientists to trace the unusual route he took before his death.Otzi the Iceman was a hunter who died in the Alps 5,300 years ago. His mummified body was discovered near the Italy-Austria border in 1991.According to Science News, he was believed to have died due to freezing temperatures in the Italian Alps. But the discovery of an arrowhead in his left shoulder has led scientists to believe he was deliberately killed.A new study from the University of Glasgow examined fragments of frozen vegetation buried alongside or inside Otzi, which includes 75 different species of mosses and liverworts.Only 30% of the species are local, others were likely transported via Otzi's clothing or inside his gut.According to New Scientist, researchers found a type of bog moss in Otzi's colon that is used to staunch wounds, and may have been used to treat a gash on his palm.His intestines also contained the moss Neckera complanata and traces of pollen.Both moss species are found in low-elevation woodlands, while Otzi was found 3,200 meters above sea level.This suggests the Iceman travelled from the forests below and went through Schnalstal valley on his final ascent.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Otzi the iceman's mummified remains2. How Otzi may have died3. Moss and liverworts found in and near Otzi's remains4. Types of moss and pollen found in Otzi's intestines5. Otzi's route up the alps based on examination of plants' originVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Science News, he was believed to have died due to freezing temperatures in the Italian Alps. But the discovery of an arrowhead in his left shoulder has led scientists to believe he was deliberately killed.""A new study from the University of Glasgow examined fragments of frozen vegetation buried alongside or inside Otzi, which includes 75 different species of mosses and liverworts.""Only 30% of the species are local, others were likely transported via Otzi's clothing or inside his gut.""According to New Scientist, researchers found a type of bog moss in Otzi's colon that is used to staunch wounds, and may have been used to treat a gash on his palm.""His intestines also contained the moss Neckera complanata and traces of pollen.""Both moss species are found in low-elevation woodlands, while Otzi was found 3,200 meters above sea level.""This suggests the Iceman travelled from the forests below and went through Schnalstal valley on his final ascent."SOURCES: PLOS One, New Scientist, National Geographic, New York Timeshttps://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0223752https://www.newscientist.com/article/2221809-otzi-the-icemans-last-journey-revealed-by-moss-found-in-his-stomach/https://www.nationalgeographic.com/history/2019/10/scientists-reconstruct-otzi-iceman-final-climb/https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/26/world/europe/bolzano-italy-iceman-south-tyrol-museum-of-archaeology.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 11:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/01/3914865/3914865_351939B289C74245AAD2C551B08DAE95_191101_3914865_Researchers_track_Otzi_the_Iceman_s_last_journey_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Otzi, iceman, Otzi the iceman, mummy, prehistoric, prehistoric man, Italy, Alps, Alpine mountains, archeology, archaeobotany, bryophytes, moss, bog moss, liverworts, copper age, chalcolithic, ancient murder, cold case, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3914730</guid>
      <title>NASA planning orbiter mission to Pluto</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has commissioned Southwest Research Institute to study the possibility and the cost of a long-term Pluto orbiter mission.NASA and Southwest Research Institute aim to send an unmanned spacecraft to study Pluto and two other Kuiper Belt Objects for a total of two years, according to a press release from the research institute. For the mission, the institute will work to develop a new spacecraft with a new payload design.According to the press release, the spacecraft would have a larger payload than the New Horizons space probe and carry more advanced instruments.The press release didn't detail which exact instruments the space probe could potentially carry.The institute previously lead NASA's New Horizon mission, in which the New Horizon space probe was able to fly past Pluto and its five moons and reach Kuiper Belt Object (KBO) 2014 MU69, also known as Ultima Thule, the farthest object visited till date.The spacecraft captured high-resolution images of Pluto but wasn't able to enter Pluto's orbit as it was traveling fast at 50,700 kilometers per hour, according to Phys.org. Researchers will deliver their results to the National Academy Planetary Decadal Study in 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA logo, Southwest Research Institute logo and Pluto2. Silhouette of an unmanned spacecraft and what it would study 3. How the spacecraft would differ from the New Horizons space probe4. NASA's previous New Horizons missionVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has commissioned Southwest Research Institute to study the possibility and the cost of a long-term Pluto orbiter mission.""According to a press release from the research institute, NASA and Southwest Research Institute aim to send an unmanned spacecraft to study Pluto and two other Kuiper Belt Objects for a total of two years." "For the mission, the institute will work to develop a new spacecraft with a new payload design.""According to the press release, the spacecraft would have a larger payload than the New Horizons space probe and carry more advanced instruments.""The press release didn't detail which exact instruments the space probe could potentially carry.""The institute previously lead NASA's New Horizon mission, in which the New Horizon space probe was able to fly past Pluto and its five moons and reach Kuiper Belt Object (KBO) 2014 MU69, also known as Ultima Thule, the farthest object visited till date."SOURCES: New Atlas, Southwest Research Institute, Phys.orghttps://newatlas.com/space/nasa-commissions-plan-for-pluto-orbital-mission/https://www.swri.org/press-release/pluto-orbiter-mission-decadal-survey-studyhttps://www.swri.org/press-release/swri-pluto-orbiter-kuiper-belt-charon-gravity-assisthttps://phys.org/news/2019-10-horizons-team-pieces-images-pluto.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 09:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/01/3914730/3914730_F3FCBF6CDFFE4F92A38E213E77D3B06E_191101_3914730_NASA_planning_orbiter_mission_to_Pluto_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Pluto, Pluto orbital mission, mission to pluto, NASA, NASA mission to Pluto, pluto mission, pluto mission nasa, Southwest Research Institute, orbital mission to Pluto, dwarf planet, Pluto system orbital tour, Pluto orbit, pluto orbiter mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3914722</guid>
      <title>New study suggests exposure to sunlight could alter gut microbiome in humans.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANExposure to ultraviolet rays may increase biodiversity of the gut microbiome in humans.Canadian researchers find that being under the sun could enrich gut flora and that a novel skin-gut axis may exist, according to a study published in Frontiers in Microbiology on October 24. The researchers say that 21 women volunteers were subjected to three full body exposures to UV rays over one week.Blood samples were tested for vitamin D levels and stool samples were tested for the biodiversity of their gut bacteria.Frontiers Science News reports that half of the participants who regularly took vitamin D supplements experienced no changes to their gut microbiome.However, women who did not take supplements saw increases to vitamin D levels, and their gut microbiome became as diverse as the supplemented group.The researchers state that multiple sclerosis and inflammatory bowel diseases are associated with the lack of sunlight, vitamin D, and unhealthy gut microbiota.The study indicates that there is a direct link between those factors, but it does not identify the causal mechanism.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. UV light exposure changes gut microbiome2. Research methodology3. Results in volunteers with and without regular vitamin D intake4. Implications on health of the studyVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Frontiers in Microbiology, Frontiers Science News, New Atlas, https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fmicb.2019.02410/full?utm_source=fweb&utm_medium=nblog&utm_campaign=ba-sci-fmicb-uvb-microbiomehttps://blog.frontiersin.org/2019/10/24/where-the-sun-doesnt-shine-skin-uv-exposure-reflected-in-poop/https://newatlas.com/health-wellbeing/uvb-sunlight-skin-gut-microbiome-vitamin-d-autoimmune/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 09:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/01/3914722/3914722_C79925914CBC4664948D596E10EA2953_191101_3914722_New_study_suggests_exposure_to_sunlight_could_al_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, gut microbiome, gut microbiota, uv light, ultraviolet, sunlight, vitamin, vitamin d, Inflammatory bowel disease, multiple sclerosis, skin gut axis, skin gut pathway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3914574</guid>
      <title>At least 45,000 Android devices infected with unremovable malware</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at cybersecurity firms Malwarebytes and Symantec have uncovered an Android trojan called xHelper that is able to reinstall itself even after users have uninstalled it.According to Symantec, the malware has already infected more than 45,000 devices, mainly in the U.S., India and Russia, over the last six months.Malwarebytes explained in a blogpost that the malware is installed through web redirects that take users to web pages that host unofficial Android apps. These unofficial apps include code that installs the xHelper trojan onto a users' phone once these apps have been downloaded.The malware shows users popup ads and notification spam, though it doesn't seem to carry out any sketchy operations, according to Malwarebytes.The ads and notifications lead users to Google's Play Store where they are asked to download more apps  a method by which authors of the xHelper trojan earn money each time these apps are installed.Even if users restore their Android phones back to factory settings or manually uninstall the malware, the xHelper trojan is able to reinstall itself.Symantec advised users to take precautions and not download apps from unfamiliar sites and to only install apps from trusted sources.The company also advised users to pay close attention to permissions the app is seeking, backup important data frequently and install a suitable mobile security app to protect their device.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Malware being downloaded onto an Android phone2. How the malware is installed3. Malware shows users popup ads and notification spam4. Malware is able to reinstall itself onto Android phones even if users restore their phone back to factory settings or manually uninstall the malware VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at cybersecurity firms Malwarebytes and Symantec have uncovered an Android trojan called xHelper that is able to reinstall itself even after users have uninstalled it.""According to Symantec, the malware has already infected more than 45,000 devices, mainly in the U.S., India and Russia, over the last six months.""Malwarebytes explained in a blogpost that the malware is installed through web redirects that take users to web pages that host unofficial Android apps.""These unofficial apps include code that installs the xHelper trojan onto a users' phone once these apps have been downloaded.""The malware shows users popup ads and notification spam, though it doesn't seem to carry out any sketchy operations, according to Malwarebytes.""The ads and notifications lead users to Google's Play Store where they are asked to download more apps  a method by which authors of the xHelper trojan earn money each time these apps are installed.""Even if users restore their Android phones back to factory settings or manually uninstall the malware, the xHelper trojan is able to reinstall itself.""According to ZDNet, some users have said even after disabling the 'Install apps from unknown sources' option after manually uninstalling the app, their device was reinfected with the malware in a matter of minutes."  SOURCES: ZDNet, Malwarebytes LABS, Symantechttps://www.zdnet.com/article/new-unremovable-xhelper-malware-has-infected-45000-android-devices/https://blog.malwarebytes.com/android/2019/08/mobile-menace-monday-android-trojan-raises-xhelper/https://www.symantec.com/blogs/threat-intelligence/xhelper-android-malware***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 04:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/01/3914574/3914574_E2B4C0C500E74368AB07A26FFCCFAA79_191101_3914574_At_least_45_000_Android_devices_infected_with_un_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, xHelper malware, xHelper malware infects android devices, xHelper android malware, xHelper virus, xHelper app, android apps,  android apps 2019, android phones, Android malware,third-party apps, third-party android apps, suspicious android apps, unremovable malware]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3914568</guid>
      <title>At least 45,000 Android devices infected with unremovable malware</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at cybersecurity firms Malwarebytes and Symantec have uncovered an Android trojan called xHelper that is able to reinstall itself even after users have uninstalled it.According to Symantec, the malware has already infected more than 45,000 devices, mainly in the U.S., India and Russia, over the last six months.Malwarebytes explained in a blogpost that the malware is installed through web redirects that take users to web pages that host unofficial Android apps. These unofficial apps include code that installs the xHelper trojan onto a users' phone once these apps have been downloaded.The malware shows users popup ads and notification spam, though it doesn't seem to carry out any sketchy operations, according to Malwarebytes.The ads and notifications lead users to Google's Play Store where they are asked to download more apps  a method by which authors of the xHelper trojan earn money each time these apps are installed.Even if users restore their Android phones back to factory settings or manually uninstall the malware, the xHelper trojan is able to reinstall itself.Some users have said even after disabling the "Install apps from unknown sources" option after manually uninstalling the app, their device was reinfected with the malware in a matter of minutes, according to ZDNet.   Symantec advised users to take precautions and not download apps from unfamiliar sites and to only install apps from trusted sources.The company also advised users to pay close attention to permissions the app is seeking, backup important data frequently and install a suitable mobile security app to protect their device.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Malware being downloaded onto an Android phone2. How the malware is installed3. Malware shows users popup ads and notification spam4. Malware is able to reinstall itself onto Android phones even if users restore their phone back to factory settings or manually uninstall the malware VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at cybersecurity firms Malwarebytes and Symantec have uncovered an Android trojan called xHelper that is able to reinstall itself even after users have uninstalled it.""According to Symantec, the malware has already infected more than 45,000 devices, mainly in the U.S., India and Russia, over the last six months.""Malwarebytes explained in a blogpost that the malware is installed through web redirects that take users to web pages that host unofficial Android apps.""These unofficial apps include code that installs the xHelper trojan onto a users' phone once these apps have been downloaded.""The malware shows users popup ads and notification spam, though it doesn't seem to carry out any sketchy operations, according to Malwarebytes.""The ads and notifications lead users to Google's Play Store where they are asked to download more apps  a method by which authors of the xHelper trojan earn money each time these apps are installed.""Even if users restore their Android phones back to factory settings or manually uninstall the malware, the xHelper trojan is able to reinstall itself.""According to ZDNet, some users have said even after disabling the 'Install apps from unknown sources' option after manually uninstalling the app, their device was reinfected with the malware in a matter of minutes."  SOURCES: ZDNet, Malwarebytes LABS, Symantechttps://www.zdnet.com/article/new-unremovable-xhelper-malware-has-infected-45000-android-devices/https://blog.malwarebytes.com/android/2019/08/mobile-menace-monday-android-trojan-raises-xhelper/https://www.symantec.com/blogs/threat-intelligence/xhelper-android-malware***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/01/3914568/3914568_747F232C3A604F11BF0C6CF6F3B6AD55_191101_3914568_At_least_45_000_Android_devices_infected_with_un_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, xHelper malware, xHelper malware infects android devices, xHelper android malware, xHelper virus, xHelper app, android apps,  android apps 2019, android phones, Android malware,third-party apps, third-party android apps, suspicious android apps, unremovable malware]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916143</guid>
      <title>Studies suggest measles may give the body "immune amnesia" by destroying immune memory cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found that measles is a lot more devastating to the immune system than previously thought.According to the WHO, measles is a highly contagious airborne disease caused by a virus in the paramyxoviridae family.Symptoms of a measles infection usually include a cough, fever, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash erupts on the face and neck after several days, and spreads to the rest of the body over the next three to four days.The Guardian reports that the body has two key lines of immune response in dealing with viruses. Memory B-cells remember previous infections the body has had before and protects against them. Naive B-cells, meanwhile, defend against new infections.A study published in the journal Science Immunology found that measles wipes out a substantial number of memory cells reduces the diversity of the naive b-cells.This causes 'immune amnesia', where the immune system to forget how to respond to infections, leaving the body vulnerable to other diseases.Another study published in Science looked at antibodies in the blood of unvaccinated children in the Netherlands before and after a measles infection. They found that the measles destroyed 11 to 78% of the children's antibody memory bank.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Measles virus2. Measles symptoms3. The body's main lines of immune response, naive and memory b-cells4. Measles virus destroys memory cells and suppresses diversity of naive cells5. Two studies investigate the effect of measles on children's antibodies 6. Measles infection resets immune system to baby-like state7. Vaccination against measlesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the WHO, measles is a highly contagious airborne disease caused by a virus in the paramyxoviridae family.""Symptoms of a measles infection usually include a cough, fever, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash erupts on the face and neck after several days, and spreads to the rest of the body over the next three to four days.""The Guardian reports that the body has two key lines of immune response in dealing with viruses. Memory B-cells remember previous infections the body has had before and protects against them.""Naive B-cells, meanwhile, defend against new infections.""A study published in the journal Science Immunology found that measles wipes out a substantial number of memory cells reduces the diversity of the naive b-cells.""This causes 'immune amnesia', where the immune system to forget how to respond to infections, leaving the body vulnerable to other diseases.""Another study published in Science looked at antibodies in the blood of unvaccinated children in the Netherlands before and after a measles infection.""They found that the measles destroyed 11 to 78% of the children's antibody memory bank.""According to the BBC, babies are born with limited antibodies that become more varied as they grow older." "Measles resets the immune system to an immature, baby-like state, with only a narrow range of antibodies to work with, and a limited ability to fight off new infections."A way to avoid this is by getting the MMR vaccine, which eliminates the risk of catching a measles infection. Revaccination also helps with those whose immune system memories have already been ravaged by the disease.SOURCES: Science, Science Immunology, Reuters, BBC, WHOhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/366/6465/599https://immunology.sciencemag.org/content/4/41/eaay6125https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-measles-immunity-idUSKBN1XA2E4?utm_source=34553&utm_medium=partnerhttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-50251259https://www.who.int/ith/diseases/measles/en/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 15:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/04/3916143/3916143_EEFCB47A91824E9B841763204726131A_191104_3916143_Studies_suggest_measles_may_give_the_body__immun_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Measles, measles infection, autoimmune system, immune system, immunity, immunity amnesia, b-cells, memory cells, memory b-cells, lymphocytes, b lymphocytes, VirScan, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3915932</guid>
      <title>China dumped 27 percent more waste into the ocean in 2018</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina discarded 200.7 million cubic meters of waste into its coastal waters in 2018.In a briefing on October 29, China's environmental ministry said that this is a 27 percent increase from 2017 and the highest level in at least a decade. The bulk of the waste was dumped into the delta regions of the Yangtze and Pearl rivers.China is discarding large amounts of trash into its ocean waters in an attempt to clean up its rivers, Reuters reports, citing environmental groups. According to the ministry, the country found an average of 24 kilograms of floating waste for every 1,000 square meters of surface water, almost 90 percent of the waste was plastic. Plastic waste was also found below surface water and on the seabed.China said it plans to designate 30 percent of its coastal waters to be completely off-limits for development as part of the country's "ecological red line" scheme.China is also moving its steel and petrochemical industries to its coastline in order to protect its rivers at the same time, according to Reuters.Huo Chuanlin, from China's environmental ministry, explained in the briefing that they were working to improve on the issue of wastewater from rivers entering into oceans.Huo added that China cannot be blamed for the global ocean plastic pollution crisis, even though the nation is the biggest manufacturer and exporter of plastic products around the world.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. An increase of trash found in China's coastal waters2. Why China could be dumping waste into its coastal waters3. Where trash was found in the ocean4. China's plan to designate portions of its coastal waters as off-limits for development VOICEOVER (in English): "China discarded 200.7 million cubic meters of waste into its coastal waters in 2018." "In a briefing on October 29, China's environmental ministry said that this is a 27 percent increase from 2017 and the highest level in at least a decade.""The bulk of the waste was dumped into the delta regions of the Yangtze and Pearl rivers.""Citing environmental groups, Reuters reports that China is discarding large amounts of trash into its ocean waters in an attempt to clean up its rivers.""According to the ministry, the country found an average of 24 kilograms of floating waste for every 1,000 square meters of surface water, almost 90 percent of the waste was plastic.""Plastic waste was also found below surface water and on the seabed.""China said it plans to designate 30 percent of its coastal waters to be completely off-limits for development as part of the country's 'ecological red line' scheme."SOURCES: Reuters, Ministry of Ecology and Environment the People's Republic of China, https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-pollution-oceans-idUSKBN1X80FLhttp://english.mee.gov.cn/News_service/news_release/201901/t20190130_691493.shtmlhttp://english.mee.gov.cn/News_service/media_news/201910/t20191030_739838.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 08:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/04/3915932/3915932_003DCD274B2347178583D56954F95DC0_191104_3915932_China_dumped_27_percent_more_waste_into_the_ocea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China plastic pollution, china coastal waters plastic waste, china coastal waters, chinese rivers plastic, ocean polluting crises, china plastic, china marine plastic pollution, china plastic ocean pollution, plastic pollution, plastic waste, plastic waste in oceans, ocean plastic pollution, plastic waste in the ocean, plastic polluting the oceans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3915797</guid>
      <title>A quarter of all pigs could die from swine fever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMark Schipp, vice president of the World Organization for Animal Health, stated in a press conference on October 31 that roughly a quarter of the pig population worldwide is expected to die off as a result of the spread of African swine fever. African swine fever is spread through bites by infectious ticks, contact through infected animals, contact with objects containing the virus, or by ingesting the meat of infected animals. The disease is spread by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family.Symptoms of the disease include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen, legs as well as diarrhea.The disease can be fatal for pigs, though it isn't transmissible to humans.There is currently no approved vaccine to prevent the spread of the disease, according to the World Organization for Animal Health.The swine fever outbreak has already claimed as many as 100 million pigs in China, the Guardian reports. This has resulted in rising pork prices around the world, mainly due to increasing demand from China.European pork prices have reached a six-year high, while the U.S. has managed to double its sale of pork to China.The African swine fever virus has already been identified in 50 countries around the world, including Poland, Russia, South Korea and the Philippines.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A quarter of pigs worldwide are expected to die due to African Swine fever2. How African swine fever is typically spread3. Virus that spreads the disease4. Symptoms of African swine fever5. The disease can be fatal for pigs but isn't transmissible to humans6. There is currently no approved vaccine for African swine fever7. How many pigs the disease has claimed in China8. Pork prices rising around the world 9. Countries around the world hit by the virusVOICEOVER (in English): "Mark Schipp, vice president of the World Organization for Animal Health, stated in a press conference on October 31 that roughly a quarter of the pig population worldwide is expected to die off as a result of the spread of African swine fever.""African swine fever is spread through bites by infectious ticks, contact through infected animals, contact with objects containing the virus, or by ingesting the meat of infected animals.""The disease is spread by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family.""Symptoms of the disease include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen, legs as well as diarrhea.""The disease can be fatal for pigs, though it isn't transmissible to humans.""According to the World Organization for Animal Health, there is currently no approved vaccine to prevent the spread of the disease.""The Guardian reports the swine fever outbreak has already claimed as many as 100 million pigs in China." "This has resulted in rising pork prices around the world, mainly due to increasing demand from China.""The African swine fever virus has already been identified in 50 countries around the world, including Poland, Russia, South Korea and the Philippines."SOURCES: The Guardian,  European Food Safety Authority, World Organization for Animal Healthhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/31/quarter-of-worlds-pig-population-to-die-of-african-swine-feverhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/sep/17/south-korea-confirms-african-swine-fever-outbreakhttps://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/topics/topic/african-swine-feverhttps://www.oie.int/fileadmin/Home/eng/Animal_Health_in_the_World/docs/pdf/Disease_cards/ASF/Report_29_Current_situation_of_ASF.pdfhttps://www.oie.int/en/animal-health-in-the-world/animal-diseases/african-swine-fever/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 04:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/04/3915797/3915797_C9D3BB5E302F4AE0A6677680AD38AC8E_191104_3915797_A_quarter_of_all_pigs_could_die_from_swine_fever_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, African swine fever, swine fever news, african swine fever outbreak, african swine flu china, african swine fever outbreak, swine fever symptoms in pigs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3915788</guid>
      <title>A quarter of all pigs could die from swine fever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMark Schipp, vice president of the World Organization for Animal Health, stated in a press conference on October 31 that roughly a quarter of the pig population worldwide is expected to die off as a result of the spread of African swine fever. African swine fever is spread through bites by infectious ticks, contact through infected animals, contact with objects containing the virus, or by ingesting the meat of infected animals. The disease is spread by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family.Symptoms of the disease include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen, legs as well as diarrhea.The disease can be fatal for pigs, though it isn't transmissible to humans.There is currently no approved vaccine to prevent the spread of the disease, according to the World Organization for Animal Health.The swine fever outbreak has already claimed as many as 100 million pigs in China, the Guardian reports. This has resulted in rising pork prices around the world, mainly due to increasing demand from China.European pork prices have reached a six-year high, while the U.S. has managed to double its sale of pork to China.The African swine fever virus has already been identified in 50 countries around the world, including Poland, Russia, South Korea and the Philippines.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A quarter of pigs worldwide are expected to die due to African Swine fever2. How African swine fever is typically spread3. Virus that spreads the disease4. Symptoms of African swine fever5. The disease can be fatal for pigs but isn't transmissible to humans6. There is currently no approved vaccine for African swine fever7. How many pigs the disease has claimed in China8. Pork prices rising around the world due to increasing demands 9. Countries around the world currently hit by the virusVOICEOVER (in English): "Mark Schipp, vice president of the World Organization for Animal Health, stated in a press conference on October 31 that roughly a quarter of the pig population worldwide is expected to die off as a result of the spread of African swine fever.""African swine fever is spread through bites by infectious ticks, contact through infected animals, contact with objects containing the virus, or by ingesting the meat of infected animals.""The disease is spread by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family.""Symptoms of the disease include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen, legs as well as diarrhea.""The disease can be fatal for pigs, though it isn't transmissible to humans.""According to the World Organization for Animal Health, there is currently no approved vaccine to prevent the spread of the disease.""The Guardian reports the swine fever outbreak has already claimed as many as 100 million pigs in China." "This has resulted in rising pork prices around the world, mainly due to increasing demand from China.""The African swine fever virus has already been identified in 50 countries around the world, including Poland, Russia, South Korea and the Philippines."SOURCES: The Guardian,  European Food Safety Authority, World Organization for Animal Healthhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/31/quarter-of-worlds-pig-population-to-die-of-african-swine-feverhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/sep/17/south-korea-confirms-african-swine-fever-outbreakhttps://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/topics/topic/african-swine-feverhttps://www.oie.int/fileadmin/Home/eng/Animal_Health_in_the_World/docs/pdf/Disease_cards/ASF/Report_29_Current_situation_of_ASF.pdfhttps://www.oie.int/en/animal-health-in-the-world/animal-diseases/african-swine-fever/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 04:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/04/3915788/3915788_834D5A4D6E4A48E18C563E0FD507B602_191104_3915788_A_quarter_of_all_pigs_could_die_from_swine_fever_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, African swine fever, swine fever news, african swine fever outbreak, african swine flu china, african swine fever outbreak, swine fever symptoms in pigs, what is african swine fever]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916557</guid>
      <title>New Delhi starts car rationing to clean up toxic air</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew Delhi is set to combat toxic smog in the city by banning cars with odd and even number plates on alternating days starting from November 4 to November 15. Those who ignore the order will be fined 4,000 rupees, or roughly US$56, BBC News reports. According to Reuters, the air quality index which measures levels of PM2.5 in areas across New Delhi has surpassed 900. This has far exceeded the 500 mark which is deemed as "severe" by the World Health Organization.The World Health Organization states that continual exposure to PM2.5 particles increases a person's risk of developing cardiovascular diseases, respiratory diseases and even lung cancer.Factors such as farmers from nearby states burning their crop stubble before winter to clear their fields, and industrial and construction emissions all contribute to worsening pollution levels in New Delhi during wintertime, according to Reuters. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How New Delhi plans to combat air pollution2. Air quality index in New Delhi3. Schools and construction work in the city has been halted4. Factors causing toxic smog in New Delhi 5. Why the pollutants linger in the atmosphere instead of dissipating into the airVOICEOVER (in English): "New Delhi is set to combat toxic smog in the city by banning cars with odd and even number plates on alternating days starting from November 4 to November 15.""BBC News reports those who ignore the order will be fined 4,000 rupees, or roughly US$56.""According to Reuters, the air quality index which measures levels of PM2.5 in areas across New Delhi has surpassed 900. This has far exceeded the 500 mark which is deemed as 'severe' by the World Health Organization." "Authorities in New Delhi have ordered schools to be closed until November 5 and have also ordered all construction work to be halted until further notice.""According to Reuters, factors such as farmers from nearby states burning their crop stubble before winter to clear their fields, and industrial and construction emissions all contribute to worsening pollution levels in New Delhi during wintertime.""The issue is exacerbated as people celebrate the Hindu new year Diwali, usually at the end of October or early November, and set off fireworks.""The pollutants linger in the atmosphere and accumulate instead of dissipating due to the wind changing direction after the monsoon season and colder air from the Himalayas.""Instead of stronger winds blowing from the east and clearing the air, softer winds blow from the northwest and move the pollutants towards New Delhi and other north Indian cities.""During the same time, cold air from the Himalayan mountains descends to New Delhi and other north Indian cities, essentially trapping the toxic pollutants in the cold air."SOURCES: Reuters, BBC News, The Guardian, WHO, AirVisual   https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-pollution/indian-capital-banishes-some-cars-in-hope-of-clearing-the-air-idUSKBN1XE0DShttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-pollution/indias-smog-bound-capital-suffers-most-hazardous-air-so-far-this-year-idUSKBN1XD08Fhttps://graphics.reuters.com/INDIA-POLLUTION/010080TH1L8/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-50285343https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsround/50291016https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/03/flights-diverted-in-delhi-as-toxic-smog-hits-worst-levels-of-2019https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/ambient-%28outdoor%29-air-quality-and-healthhttps://www.airvisual.com/world-most-polluted-cities***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 11:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/05/3916557/3916557_49F91AF6520748DCBB3FE1118BB74F36_191105_3916557_New_Delhi_starts_car_rationing_to_clean_up_toxic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, India pollution, india pollution problem, india pollution control, india pollution city, india pollution solutions, new delhi, new delhi pollution, pollution in delhi, new delhi pollution 2019, new delhi smog, india air pollution, toxic smog delhi]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916486</guid>
      <title>Researchers discovered fossilized Megalodon tooth after diving expedition in a flooded cavern in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers found at least 13 prehistoric shark teeth during a diving expedition in the Xoc cenote, a flooded cave in the Mexican city of Merida.Mexico City daily Excelsior reported that morphological analysis suggests one of the teeth belonged to a megalodon, a species of giant sharks that lived from about 23 million to 2.5 million years ago.Megalodons were biggest sharks known to have existed in the world.A megalodon could grow to as large as 18 meters long and its open jaws were 1.8 meters wide, dwarfing the great white shark, according to National Geographic.The researchers told Excelsior they found other teeth belonging to the sawshark and mako shark genuses likely originating in the same geological epochs as the megalodon tooth.Excelsior reported that the Xoc cenote is Merida's third largest flooded cavern and researchers are mapping the cave system. "Xoc" means shark in the Mayan language. A 'cenote' is a natural sinkhole.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Megalodon tooth found on cave walls2. Megalodon description and size comparison3. Sawshark and Mako shark teeth discovered4. Xoc cenote being mappedVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Excelsior, Maritime Herald, National Geographichttps://www.excelsior.com.mx/nacional/hallan-dientes-del-tiburon-mas-grande-del-mundo-en-yucatan/1344995https://www.maritimeherald.com/2019/10-31-trending-news-teeth-of-the-worlds-largest-prehistoric-shark-found-in-yucatan-mexico/https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/02/megalodon-extinct-great-white-shark/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 10:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/05/3916486/3916486_38EF36A283B545F7ABB0FC3410633269_191105_3916486_Researchers_discovered_fossilized_Megalodon_toot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Megalodon, tooth, prehistoric shark, Xoc cenote, cenote, flooded cave, cave, cavern, cavers, divers, sawshark, mako shark, fossils, paleontology, archeology, anthropology, Merida, Mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916808</guid>
      <title>Smugglers used power tools to breach Trump's new border wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to the Washington Post, the new border wall President Trump is building features steel and concrete bollards up to 30 feet tall, and concrete foundation that deters tunneling.U.S. Customs and Border Protection tweeted on October 24 that it has built 75 miles of Trump's new border wall and aims to finish 450 miles by 2020. The Post reports that although Trump called the wall "virtually impenetrable," smugglers have been able to cut through with cordless power saws costing as little as US$100.They go through the resulting gap one at a time and often move the damaged bollards back in place for future crossings.U.S. officials confirmed that there have been multiple breaches, but added that smugglers targeted sections of the wall not yet equipped with electronic vibration sensors.The BBC reports that when it is completed, Trump's border wall will feature steel barriers, all weather roads, cameras, and other technology.According to the Washington Post, the wall has cost US$10 billion so far.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Construction of border wall 2. Smugglers cut through new border wall with power saw3. Vibration sensors being installed to deter cutting4. The wall system and construction locationsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Washington Post, the new border wall system U.S. President Trump is building features steel and concrete bollards up to 30 feet tall, and concrete foundation that defeats tunneling.""U.S. Customs and Border Protection tweeted on October 24 that it has built 75 miles of Trump's new border wall and aims to finish 450 miles by 2020.""The Post reports that although Trump called the wall 'virtually impenetrable,' smugglers have been able to cut through with cordless power saws costing as little as US$100.""They go through the resulting gap one at a time and often move the damaged bollards back in place for future crossings.""U.S. officials confirmed that there have been multiple breaches, but added that smugglers targeted sections of the wall not yet equipped with electronic vibration sensors.""The BBC reports that when it is completed, Trump's border wall will feature steel barriers, all weather roads, cameras, and other technology.""According to the Washington Post, the wall has cost US$10 billion so far."SOURCES: The Washington Post, BBC Newshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/national/smugglers-are-sawing-through-new-sections-of-trumps-border-wall/2019/11/01/25bf8ce0-fa72-11e9-ac8c-8eced29ca6ef_story.html?fbclid=IwAR2Iu4kwbsuNdWtp0V8Q-u9MYiT5kHn00x22y2NF0XbrxRWtDZUTJ42CZSkhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46824649***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 03:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/06/3916808/3916808_065E08B9F44640589A642AF2EF52AC79_191106_3916808_Smugglers_used_power_tools_to_breach_Trump_s_new_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Donald Trump, Trump, new border wall, new wall, border wall, wall, power tool, reciprocating saw, smugglers, US-Mexico border, impenetrable, US, politics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917534</guid>
      <title>Scientists around the world have declared a climate emergency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMore than 11,000 scientists around the world have signed a declaration stating planet Earth is facing a climate emergency, according to a new study published in the journal BioScience.These scientists have outlined six crucial steps for us to take in order to tackle climate change.After analyzing 40 years of climate data, researchers stated that global surface temperature, sea levels, ocean acidity and ocean heat content are all steadily on the rise.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Scientists, globe and declaration2. Replace fossil fuels with clean renewables3. Cut down emissions of pollutants4. Restore ecosystems5. Eat plant-based food instead of animal-based products6. Build a carbon-based economy that focuses on the environment instead of GDP growth7. Stabilize global populationVOICEOVER (in English): "More than 11,000 scientists around the world have signed a declaration stating planet Earth is facing a climate emergency, according to a new study published in the journal BioScience.""These scientists have outlined six crucial steps for us to take in order to tackle climate change.""For the first step, the scientists say that we must replace fossil fuels with clean renewables.""Next, we must cut down emissions of methane, hydrofluorocarbons and other climate pollutants. Scientists say this could reduce short-term warming trend by over 50 percent in the next few decades.""Thirdly, the scientists stated that restoring and protecting ecosystems such as forests and grasslands, would not only benefit organisms that live in these ecosystems but also naturally isolate and take in more carbon dioxide pollutants in the atmosphere.""For the fourth step, the study says we must eat more plant-based food and reduce our consumption of animal-based products. This would reduce methane emissions from animals such as cattle and free up land for growing vegetables instead of livestock.""Next, the study says we need a carbon-free economy that focuses on our biosphere and environment instead of focusing on hitting economic goals related to GDP growth and the pursuit of wealth.""Lastly, scientists say we need to stabilize the global population to ensure social and economic justice for everyone living on this planet."SOURCES: New Atlas, Bioscience, University of Sydney, The Guardian, Washington Post https://newatlas.com/environment/climate-emergency-six-step-plan/https://academic.oup.com/bioscience/advance-article/doi/10.1093/biosci/biz088/5610806https://sydney.edu.au/news-opinion/news/2019/11/06/world-scientists-declare-climate-emergency.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/nov/05/climate-crisis-11000-scientists-warn-of-untold-sufferinghttps://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2019/11/05/more-than-scientists-around-world-declare-climate-emergency/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 09:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/07/3917534/3917534_54B74BADFB5C4150934984A497BCE456_191107_3917534_Scientists_around_the_world_have_declared_a_clim_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, explainer, illustration, graphic, climate change, climate emergency, climate crisis, scientists declare climate emergency, world scientists declare climate emergency, climate emergency declaration, world scientists climate change, climate catastrophe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917497</guid>
      <title>Voyagers' readings yield new clues about the solar system's structure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe latest data sent from Voyager 2 brought new insight and questions about the boundary region where the sun's influence ends and interstellar space begins.According to NASA, the sun's energetic influence projects a bubble around the solar system called the heliosphere, Reuters says.NASA reports that as Voyager 2 crossed the border region, or the heliopause, it registered an unexpectedly sharp difference in magnetic particles and plasma density.Comparing the data from Voyager 1, researchers found the heliopause is thinner and less changeable by solar cycles than thought previously, the New York Times reports.The New York Times reports that the sun creates the heliosphere bubble by blowing solar wind, or charged particles that are mostly hydrogen.University of Iowa Professor Don Gurnett told the New York Times that solar winds clash with interstellar winds in the bubble's outer region, which could explain why a sharp boundary was formed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Voyagers' trajectory out of solar system2. Voyager 1 readings on the heliopause3. Sun creates solar wind4. The heliosphere bubble and boundaryVOICEOVER (in English): "The latest data sent from Voyager 2 brought new insight and questions about the boundary region where the sun's influence ends and interstellar space begins.""According to NASA, the sun's energetic influence projects a bubble around the solar system called the heliosphere, Reuters says.""NASA reports that as Voyager 2 crossed the border region, or the heliopause, it registered an unexpectedly sharp difference in magnetic particles and plasma density.""Comparing the data from Voyager 1, researchers found the heliopause is thinner and less changeable by solar cycles than thought previously, the New York Times reports.""The New York Times reports that the sun creates the heliosphere bubble by blowing solar wind, or charged particles that are mostly hydrogen."University of Iowa Professor Don Gurnett told the New York Times that solar winds clash with interstellar winds in the bubble's outer region, which could explain why a sharp boundary was formed."SOURCES: Reuters, BBC News, The New York Times, Guardian, Space.comhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-exploration-voyager/nasa-probe-provides-insight-on-solar-systems-border-with-interstellar-space-idUSKBN1XE1PMhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50289353https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/04/science/voyager-2-interstellar-solar-wind.htmlhttps://www.space.com/nasa-voyager-2-interstellar-space-mysteries.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 08:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/07/3917497/3917497_0ABB2C3BE5794795B76A1680993F1BB8_191107_3917497_Voyagers__readings_yield_new_clues_about_the_sol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Voyagers, Voyager 1, Voyager 2, sun, solar system, heliosphere, heliopause, NASA, US, solar wind, solar winds, interstellar wind winds, interstellar, outer space, space TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917341</guid>
      <title>App developers had improper access to user data on Facebook</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook says roughly 100 app developers had improper access to user data from video streaming apps and social media management apps through admins that authorized the apps' access to Facebook groups.According to a news release from the company, at least 11 apps accessed names and profile pictures of group members in the past 60 days even though Facebook says it made changes in April 2018 to prevent app developers from accessing this information.The company explained that following the changes, group members had to opt-in in order to allow apps to access their information.Facebook says it has since removed this access for those app developers even though the social media giant says it didn't find any evidence of the apps abusing their access to user information.The company didn't mention how many users were affected by the breach.Facebook has been working to restrict developer access to user data since March 2018, following the Cambridge Analytica scandal in which the consulting firm gained access to user data from 87 million Facebook users, CNBC reports. As a result, the company suspended tens of thousands of apps in September.The social media giant was also ordered to pay a US$5 billion fine to the Federal Trade Commission over its privacy policies.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How app developers are able to access user data2. Apps collecting user information even if the user hasn't given them the permission to do so  3. Facebook says it has removed the access for app developers4. Facebook working to restrict developer access to user dataVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook says roughly 100 app developers had improper access to user data from video streaming apps and social media management apps through admins that authorized the apps' access to Facebook groups.""According to a news release from the company, at least 11 apps accessed names and profile pictures of group members in the past 60 days even though Facebook says it made changes in April 2018 to prevent app developers from accessing this information.""The company explained that following the changes, group members had to opt-in in order to allow apps to access their information.""Facebook says it has since removed this access for those app developers even though the social media giant says it didn't find any evidence of the apps abusing their access to user information.""CNBC reports Facebook has been working to restrict developer access to user data since March 2018, following the Cambridge Analytica scandal in which the consulting firm gained access to user data from 87 million Facebook users."SOURCES: CNBC, CNN, Facebookhttps://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/05/facebook-says-100-developers-may-have-improperly-accessed-user-data.htmlhttps://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/24/facebook-to-pay-5-billion-for-privacy-lapses-ftc-announces.htmlhttps://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/20/facebook-suspended-tens-of-thousands-of-apps-after-cambridge-analytica.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/05/tech/facebook-apps-user-data/index.htmlhttps://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/2019/11/05/changes-groups-api-access/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 03:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/07/3917341/3917341_5F34985EF9F846DBA9E197A599509A92_191107_3917341_App_developers_had_improper_access_to_user_data__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Facebook, facebook privacy, facebook scandals, facebook user data scandal, facebook privacy concerns, facebook data breach, facebook user data breach, facebook software developers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3918393</guid>
      <title>U.S. Air Force researching space solar energy system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Air Force wants to develop a system that generates solar energy in space, converts it to radio frequencies, and then beams it to forward operating bases.Colonel Eric Felt told Stars and Stripes, "energy is a strategic enabler and potential vulnerability for our nation."Remote outposts that rely on fuel for energy need to be supplied by convoys and protective escorts, which the enemy could target.The air force states that harnessing solar energy in space offers advantages such as providing power around the clock in all weather conditions.The project developers also said another application of the system is to supply energy to remote communities.According to Stars and Stripes, the system is envisioned as a constellation of satellites with ten thousand square meters of solar panels.The solar energy system would steer its beams at specific locations electrically, rather than having to turn mechanical arrays.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Space solar power system generates power then beams it to earth2. System to reduce need of fuel convoys at forward operating bases3. Advantages of space solar energy 4. Intended capabilities and design of conceptVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Air Force wants to develop a system that generates solar energy in space, converts it to radio frequencies, and then beams it to forward operating bases.""Colonel Eric Felt told Stars and Stripes, 'energy is a strategic enabler and potential vulnerability for our nation.'""Remote outposts that rely on fuel for energy need to be supplied by convoys and protective escorts, which the enemy could target.""The air force states that harnessing solar energy in space offers advantages such as providing power around the clock in all weather conditions.""The project developers also said another application of the system is to supply energy to remote communities.""According to Stars and Stripes, the system is envisioned as a constellation of satellites with ten thousand square meters of solar panels.""The solar energy system would steer its beams at specific locations electrically, rather than having to turn mechanical arrays."SOURCES: Stars and Stripes, U.S. Air Forcehttps://www.stripes.com/news/air-force/air-force-research-laboratory-looks-to-beam-solar-energy-from-space-1.605809https://www.robins.af.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/1998062/us-air-force-research-laboratory-developing-space-solar-power-beaming/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 02:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/09/3918393/3918393_2C3181039C3548C0A4C08DFFF777843C_191109_3918393_U_S__Air_Force_researching_space_solar_energy_sy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Space-based solar power, space, solar power, solar energy, SSPIDR, Space Solar Power Incremental Demonstration and Research, US, air force, Northrop Grumman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919213</guid>
      <title>Scientists identify first new HIV strain in two decades</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA joint study by Abbott Laboratories and the University of Missouri has identified a new subtype of the HIV strain for the first time in 19 years.A press release from Abbott Laboratories explains that three different samples of the HIV virus were obtained from the Democratic Republic of Congo, one in 1983, one in 1990 and a third one in 2001.Scientists weren't able to test the third sample because technologies at the time prevented the researchers from doing so. Now, scientists have developed next-generation sequencing technology to allow them to build a complete genome sequence from the third HIV sample.After analyzing the HIV virus, the researchers have identified it as the HIV-1 Group M subtype L.In the news release, one of the authors of the study, Mary Rodgers, principal scientist at Abbott Laboratories, said that identifying new viruses is like "searching for a needle in a haystack."Rodgers added that the new sequencing technology was like a "magnet" that allowed them to find the needle.According to CNN, current HIV treatments are able to fight different types of virus strains. It is believed to be able to fight this newly identified HIV strain as well.The study concluded by saying that additional strains of HIV could be spreading around in the Democratic Republic of Congo or elsewhere.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New subtype of the HIV strain and a calendar icon2. Three different HIV strains and flag of the Democratic Republic of Congo3. Genome sequence of the new HIV strain4. New HIV virus identified as the HIV-1 Group M subtype L5. Current HIV treatments and the newly identified HIV strain VOICEOVER (in English): "A joint study by Abbott Laboratories and the University of Missouri has identified a new subtype of the HIV strain for the first time in 19 years.""A press release from Abbott Laboratories explains that three different samples of the HIV virus were obtained from the Democratic Republic of Congo, one in 1983, one in 1990 and a third one in 2001.""Scientists weren't able to test the third sample because technologies at the time prevented the researchers from doing so.""Now, scientists have developed next-generation sequencing technology to allow them to build a complete genome sequence from the third HIV sample.""After analyzing the HIV virus, the researchers have identified it as the HIV-1 Group M subtype L."SOURCES: HIV sequence database, CNN, Scientific American, Abbot Libraries, Journal of Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndromes https://www.hiv.lanl.gov/content/sequence/HelpDocs/subtypes-more.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/06/health/hiv-new-strain-discovered/index.htmlhttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/first-new-hiv-strain-in-19-years-identified/https://abbott.mediaroom.com/2019-11-06-Abbott-Announces-Discovery-of-New-Strain-of-HIV-Keeping-Global-Health-Community-a-Step-Ahead-of-the-Virushttps://journals.lww.com/jaids/Abstract/publishahead/Complete_genome_sequence_of_CG_0018a_01.96307.aspx***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/11/3919213/3919213_687BC7FF1CF449C7BA682409637C9744_191111_3919213_Scientists_identify_first_new_HIV_strain_in_two__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, HIV, HIV strain, new HIV strain, new HIV strain discovered,  HIV virus, HIV strains, hiv strains and subtypes, evolution of HIV, scientists detect new strain of HIV]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920013</guid>
      <title>Clownfish have ultraviolet light vision: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA joint study from the University of Queensland and the University of Maryland has found that a particular species of clownfish called the Amphiprion akindynos is able to see ultraviolet light.Sara Stieb, a researcher involved with the study, explained in a University of Queensland news release that these fish live close to the water's surface, where UV light is able to easily penetrate through water.The study says that part of these fish's eyes have photoreceptors that are able to detect both ultraviolet light and violet light. With UV light vision, the fish can identify their kind as white stripes on a clownfish reflect ultraviolet light.This unique ability allows clownfish to communicate with one another over short distances as bigger fish aren't able to see UV light.The fish also uses ultraviolet light to find food it typically eats such as zooplankton. These appear as darker dots as they absorb UV light, making it easier for clownfish to locate them.Stieb said that the fact that these fish have this special ability makes sense because of their environment and what they consume.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Amphiprion akindynos clownfish species is able to see ultraviolet light2. UV light penetrating through water 3. Why this fish is able to detect UV light4. Clownfish reflecting UV light5. Clownfish communicating with one another6. Clownfish using UV light vision to find foodVOICEOVER (in English): "A joint study from the University of Queensland and the University of Maryland has found that a particular species of clownfish called the Amphiprion akindynos is able to see ultraviolet light.""Sara Stieb, a researcher involved with the study, explained in a University of Queensland news release that these fish live close to the water's surface, where UV light is able to easily penetrate through water.""The study says that part of these fish's eyes have photoreceptors that are able to detect both ultraviolet light and violet light.""With UV light vision, the fish can identify their kind as white stripes on a clownfish reflect ultraviolet light.""This unique ability allows clownfish to communicate with one another over short distances as bigger fish aren't able to see UV light.""The fish also uses ultraviolet light to find food it typically eats such as zooplankton.""These appear as darker dots as they absorb UV light, making it easier for clownfish to locate them."SOURCES: Science Daily, Scientific Reports, University of Queenslandhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/11/191111084931.htmhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-019-52297-0https://stories.uq.edu.au/news/2019/finding-nemos-cousins/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/12/3920013/3920013_838C22E808FB47648239213451B7FC10_191112_3920013_Clownfish_have_ultraviolet_light_vision__Study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Clownfish, finding nemo fish, clownfish UV light, clownfish can see UV light, fish sees UV light, ultraviolet light fish, Amphiprion akindynos, Amphiprion akindynos UV light, anemonefish]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919994</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protester shot by cop at point-blank range</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPolice in Hong Kong fired three live rounds during a city-wide strike, hitting at least one pro-democracy protester.RTHK reports that around 7:15 a.m. on Monday, masked protesters throwing debris onto an intersection in Hong Kong's Sai Wan Ho were confronted by a traffic policeman.In a live video posted by Cupid News, a protester in a white hoodie is seen approaching the officer, who reaches for his service pistol.The officer initially pointed his gun at the man at point-blank range, before putting him in a headlock.When another protester approached, the policeman turned his gun on him and fired a round into his torso from a distance of less than half a meter.Two more people, one in black and one in gray, came forward to grapple with the officer, who then fired two more shots. In the video, the protester in black can be seen falling to the ground.Riot police soon arrived to help subdue a large crowd of angry people. They had begun demanding an explanation for the shooting, and were pepper sprayed in return.According to the Hong Kong Free Press, an anonymous source told Ming Pao that two people had been shot, and that the first one, identified only as a 21-year-old man, was injured in the kidney and liver, with his renal vein crushed.He had needed cardiopulmonary resuscitation after his heart stopped once, and CNN reports that he remains in critical condition according to the Hong Kong Hospital Authority.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hong Kong traffic police confronting protesters2. Officer fires one shot at protester's torso3. Officer fires two more shots4. Angry crowd pepper sprayed by riot policeVOICEOVER (in English): "RTHK reports that around 7:15 a.m. on Monday, masked protesters throwing debris onto an intersection in Hong Kong's Sai Wan Ho were confronted by a traffic policeman.""In a live video posted by Cupid News, a protester in a white hoodie is seen approaching the officer, who reaches for his service pistol.""The officer initially pointed his gun at the man at point-blank range, before putting him in a headlock.""When another protester approached, the policeman turned his gun on him and fired a round into his torso from a distance of less than half a meter.""Two more people, one in black and one in gray, came forward to grapple with the officer, who then fired two more shots. In the video, the protester in black can be seen falling to the ground.""Riot police soon arrived to help subdue a large crowd of angry people. They had begun demanding an explanation for the shooting, and were pepper sprayed in return.""According to the Hong Kong Free Press, an anonymous source told Ming Pao that two people had been shot, and that the first one, identified only as a 21-year-old man, was injured in the kidney and liver, with his renal vein crushed."SOURCES: Hong Kong Free Press, RTHKhttps://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/11/11/breaking-hong-kong-police-shoot-protester-live-round-sai-wan-ho/https://news.rthk.hk/rthk/en/component/k2/1491211-20191111.htm?fbclid=IwAR3ZnJqPjh_qbpqHI3Nvx06jnmJLIm6EUXh-RlFYQpWotSqoLivP5QqFfL0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 12:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/12/3919994/3919994_0EC7A3D3D4EF4EFB9CACC95DEF46F685_191112_3919994_Hong_Kong_protester_shot_by_cop_at_point_blank_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, HK protest, Hong Kong protester, HK protester shot, Hong Kong police, HK police, Hong Kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919978</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk plans offshore spaceports for SpaceX Starships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpaceX is developing Starships, reusable rocket systems that will be used for fast traveling and space exploration.According to SpaceX, Starship's first stage booster named Super Heavy features 37 Raptor engines that will make Starships the most powerful launch systems ever built.Super Heavy is designed to separate from Starship and land itself while the spacecraft continues on its trajectory with its six Raptor thrusters.The Super Heavy booster and Starship will both be capable of reentry and reuse.SpaceX CEO Elon Musk told Space.com that the design utilizes 301 stainless steel because it is cost effective and resilient to the heat of atmospheric reentry.SpaceX claims that Starships will be fast enough to go between anywhere on Earth in less than an hour.Musk tweeted in June that a Starship will carry one hundred passengers in its cabin and up to a thousand when using its cargo hold.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Starship lifts off from spaceport in New York2. Super Heavy separates from Starship3. Atmospheric re-entry4. Starship lands in TokyoVOICEOVER (in English): "SpaceX is developing Starships, reusable rocket systems that will be used for fast traveling and space exploration.""According to SpaceX, Starship's first stage booster named Super Heavy features 37 Raptor engines that will make Starships the most powerful launch systems ever built.""Super Heavy is designed to separate from Starship and land itself while the spacecraft continues on its trajectory with its six Raptor thrusters.""The Super Heavy booster and Starship will both be capable of reentry and reuse.""SpaceX CEO Elon Musk told Space.com that the design utilizes 301 stainless steel because it is cost effective and resilient to the heat of atmospheric reentry.""SpaceX claims that Starships will be fast enough to go between anywhere on Earth in less than an hour.""Musk tweeted in June that a Starship will carry one hundred passengers in its cabin and up to a thousand when using its cargo hold."SOURCES: SpaceX, Space.com, Business Insiderhttps://www.spacex.com/starshiphttps://www.space.com/elon-musk-unveils-spacex-starship-2019-update.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/elon-musk-big-falcon-rocket-like-disney-space-mountain-2019-6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 12:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/12/3919978/3919978_51376FC161F94927BA66A47E007E4696_191112_3919978_Elon_Musk_plans_offshore_spaceports_for_SpaceX_S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Elon Musk, Musk, SpaceX, Starship, spaceport, offshore space port, super heavy, orbital vehicle, space, big falcon rocket, bfr]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919911</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk plans offshore spaceports for SpaceX Starships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpaceX is developing Starships, reusable rocket systems that will be used for fast traveling and space exploration.According to SpaceX, Starship's first stage booster named Super Heavy features 37 Raptor engines that will make Starships the most powerful launch systems ever built.Super Heavy is designed to separate from Starship and land itself while the spacecraft continues on its trajectory with its six Raptor thrusters.The Super Heavy booster and Starship will both be capable of reentry and reuse.SpaceX CEO Elon Musk told Space.com that the design utilizes 301 stainless steel because it is cost effective and resilient to the heat of atmospheric reentry.SpaceX claims that Starships will be fast enough to go between anywhere on Earth in less than an hour.Musk tweeted in June that a Starship will carry one hundred passengers in its cabin and up to a thousand when using its cargo hold.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Starship lifts off from spaceport in New York2. Super Heavy separates from Starship3. Atmospheric re-entry4. Starship lands in TokyoVOICEOVER (in English): "SpaceX is developing Starships, reusable rocket systems that will be used for fast traveling and space exploration.""According to SpaceX, Starship's first stage booster named Super Heavy features 37 Raptor engines that will make Starships the most powerful launch systems ever built.""Super Heavy is designed to separate from Starship and land itself while the spacecraft continues on its trajectory with its six Raptor thrusters.""The Super Heavy booster and Starship will both be capable of reentry and reuse.""SpaceX CEO Elon Musk told Space.com that the design utilizes 301 stainless steel because it is cost effective and resilient to the heat of atmospheric reentry.""SpaceX claims that Starships will be fast enough to go between anywhere on Earth in less than an hour.""Musk tweeted in June that a Starship will carry one hundred passengers in its cabin and up to a thousand when using its cargo hold."SOURCES: SpaceX, Space.com, Business Insiderhttps://www.spacex.com/starshiphttps://www.space.com/elon-musk-unveils-spacex-starship-2019-update.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/elon-musk-big-falcon-rocket-like-disney-space-mountain-2019-6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 10:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/12/3919911/3919911_28373734A6744301893ACCD3E6E56056_191112_3919911_Elon_Musk_plans_offshore_spaceports_for_SpaceX_S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Elon Musk, Musk, SpaceX, Starship, spaceport, offshore space port, super heavy, orbital vehicle, space, big falcon rocket, bfr]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920492</guid>
      <title>Baby fish found consuming plastic in larval fish nurseries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study led by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration's Pacific Islands Fisheries Science Center has found prey-size plastics present in larval fish nurseries in surface slicks off the west coast of the island of Hawaii.According to a news release from the NOAA, surface slicks are created when waves converge near coastlines and form ribbons of smooth water. These contain large amounts of plankton for larval fish that live in the surface slicks.The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, found seven times more plastic present in the surface slicks than larval fish.Researchers also found that plastics were 126 times more concentrated in the slicks than surface water off the coast of the same island.Scientists involved in the study dissected hundreds of larval fish from the surface slicks and found that pelagic fish species, including swordfish and mahi-mahi, and larval fish, such as triggerfish, all contained tiny pieces of plastic in their stomachs.This is the first time these fish species have been found consuming plastic just days after being spawned.Jamison Gove, a researcher from the NOAA who was involved with the study, stated in the agency's news release that it is alarming that larval fish are surrounded by plastic waste and are consuming plastic at such a vulnerable stage in their life.Scientists are unsure of the impact of plastic ingestion on larval fish. The study says that plastic could affect their development or even reduce their rate of survival.Previous studies had found that plastic ingestion in adult fish causes gut blockage, malnutrition and accumulation of plastic toxins.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Plastics found in larval fish nurseries in surface slicks2. How surface slicks are formed3. The amount of plastic found in the larval fish nurseries4. Different fish found containing pieces of plastic in their stomachVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study led by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration's Pacific Islands Fisheries Science Center has found prey-size plastics present in larval fish nurseries in surface slicks off the west coast of the island of Hawaii.""According to a news release from the NOAA, surface slicks are created when waves converge near coastlines and form ribbons of smooth water. These contain large amounts of plankton for larval fish that live in the surface slicks.""The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, found seven times more plastic present in the surface slicks than larval fish.""Researchers also found that plastics were 126 times more concentrated in the slicks than surface water off the coast of the same island.""Scientists involved in the study dissected hundreds of larval fish from the surface slicks and found that pelagic fish species, including swordfish and mahi-mahi, and larval fish, such as triggerfish, all contained tiny pieces of plastic in their stomachs.""This is the first time these fish species have been found consuming plastic just days after being spawned."SOURCES: Science Daily, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, NOAAhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/11/191111150636.htmhttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2019/11/05/1907496116https://www.staradvertiser.com/2019/11/11/breaking-news/even-baby-fish-are-eating-plastics-hawaii-study-finds/https://www.fisheries.noaa.gov/feature-story/prey-size-plastics-are-invading-larval-fish-nurseries***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 12:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/13/3920492/3920492_5058071023024374BC29FD34562706B2_191113_3920492_Baby_fish_found_consuming_plastic_in_larval_fish_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Larval fish nurseries, plastic in larval fish nurseries, pre-size plastic, fish nursery habitat plastic, hawaii fish nurseries, hawaii island, plastic pollution, plastic waste, plastic contamination, plastic in ocean, surface slicks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920482</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters clash with police at universities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOngoing protests have been taking place in Hong Kong for 24 consecutive weeks.Around midday on November 12, protesters in black clothing as well as office workers took to the streets and occupied an intersection in the city's business district, Central. The police fired tear gas in the afternoon and detained roughly 12 people, CNN reports. According to the Hong Kong Free Press, separate protests took place at a campus of the Chinese University of Hong Kong on the same day. Masked protesters in black had put up barricades on the university campus to prevent the police from entering in the morning.This led to a clash between the protesters and the police in the afternoon as activists threw bricks and petrol bombs at the officers while the officers fired tear gas and projectiles into the campus.According to CNN, this caused an empty car to catch on fire.Protesters also dropped bricks from a footbridge at Hong Kong Polytechnic University while other protesters threw chairs and traffic cones at passing traffic from another footbridge near the University of Hong Kong.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Office workers and protesters in black clothing protesting on the streets on Hong Kong2. Police firing tear gas3. Separate protests taking place at the Chinese University of Hong Kong4. Police and protesters clashing at the university5. Empty car caught on fire6. Protesters dropping bricks from a footbridge at Hong Kong Polytechnic University7. Other protesters throwing chairs and traffic cones at passing traffic from another footbridgeVOICEOVER (in English): "Around midday on November 12, protesters in black clothing as well as office workers took to the streets and occupied an intersection in the city's business district, Central.""CNN reports the police fired tear gas in the afternoon and detained roughly 12 people.""According to the Hong Kong Free Press, separate protests took place at a campus of the Chinese University of Hong Kong on the same day.""Masked protesters in black had put up barricades on the university campus to prevent the police from entering in the morning." "This led to a clash between the protesters and the police in the afternoon as activists threw bricks and petrol bombs at the officers while the officers fired tear gas and projectiles into the campus.""According to CNN, this caused an empty car to catch on fire.""Protesters also dropped bricks from a footbridge at Hong Kong Polytechnic University, while other protesters throw chairs and traffic cones at passing traffic from another footbridge near the University of Hong Kong."SOURCES: CNN, South China Morning Post, Hong Kong Free Press, BBC News https://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/11/asia/hong-kong-protests-dramatic-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3037453/hong-kong-protests-city-braces-third-straight-day-travelhttps://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/11/12/hong-kong-police-protesters-battle-night-cuhk-campus-university-head-among-tear-gassed/https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/11/12/cuhk-turns-battleground-protesters-police-clashes-rage-across-hong-kong-universities/https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-50384360***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 12:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/13/3920482/3920482_F4F00D6D889448E98E02150CD306613E_191113_3920482_Hong_Kong_protesters_clash_with_police_at_univer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, China extradition protests, Hong Kong protest 2019, Chinese University of Hong Kong, Chinese University of Hong Kong protests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920248</guid>
      <title>Design unveiled for new Sydney international airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBritish architectural firm Zaha Hadid Architects and Sydney-based Cox Architecture have won a competition to build the new Western Sydney International Airport.According to the British architectural firm's website, the airport draws inspiration from landscape surrounding the area and the region's cultural heritage.The new airport will make use of a sustainable design to allow sunlight to enter its interior. The airport's eco-friendly design will also include natural ventilation and water recycling to increase energy efficiency.The airport will be built in four stages. The project's initial stage is expected to be completed in 2026.The airport will be able to accommodate 10 million annual passengers after the first stage is complete, according to Zaha Hadid Architects. The number of passengers will increase to up to 82 million once the entire project is complete in 2060.Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison told ABC News Australia that the airport is set to become the largest gateway to Australia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Western Sydney International Airport2. What the airport draws inspiration from3. Sustainable features of the airport4. How the airport will be built5. The airport's interiorVOICEOVER (in English): "British architectural firm Zaha Hadid Architects and Sydney-based Cox Architecture have won a competition to build the new Western Sydney International Airport.""According to the British architectural firm's website, the airport draws inspiration from landscape surrounding the area and the region's cultural heritage.""The new airport will make use of a sustainable design to allow sunlight to enter its interior." "The airport's eco-friendly design will also include natural ventilation and water recycling in order to be energy efficient.""The airport will be built in four stages. The project's initial stage is expected to be completed in 2026." "According to Zaha Hadid Architects, the airport will be able to accommodate 10 million annual passengers after the first stage is complete.""The number of passengers will increase to up to 82 million once the entire project is complete in 2060."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Zaha Hadid Architects, Cox Architecture, ABC News Australia https://inhabitat.com/architects-reveal-winning-design-for-western-sydney-airport/https://www.zaha-hadid.com/architecture/western-sydney-international-airport/https://www.coxarchitecture.com.au/featuredhttps://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-10-29/western-sydney-airport-designs-revealed/11646956***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 05:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/13/3920248/3920248_7A8307B83B8743B68B7F29FC1242E660_191113_3920248_Design_unveiled_for_new_Sydney_international_air_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Architecture, Western Sydney Airport, Sydney Airport, Zaha Hadid architecture, Cox architecture, western sydney airport design, western sydney airport construction, new western sydney airport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920775</guid>
      <title>'Smart Forest City' design unveiled for Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANItalian architectural firm Stefano Boeri Architetti has unveiled design plans for a "Smart Forest City" in Cancun.The site would consist of 400 hectares of green space and feature public parks and private gardens, according to the architectural firm's website. The Smart Forest City would contain green roofs and more than 200,000 trees that would be able to absorb approximately 116.000 tons of carbon dioxide.The company explained that the area would be surrounded by a ring of solar panels and agricultural fields to provide renewable energy and food for the city. The development's agricultural fields would be irrigated by a water channel connected to an underwater maritime pipe.The site would use electric and semi-automatic vehicles instead of traditional vehicles for both residents and visitors.Visitors to the forest city would be required to leave their traditional vehicles at the city's outer edge.According to Stefano Boeri Architetti, the development would house an advanced research center for international organizations and companies that are interested in our planet's sustainability issues.The proposed plan would reforest the area and build the Smart Forest City instead of a shopping district.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 'Smart Forest City'2. Parks in the city3. Green roofs and trees absorbing carbon dioxide 4. Solar panels, agricultural fields and a water channel5. Electric vehicles instead of traditional vehiclesVOICEOVER (in English): "Italian architectural firm Stefano Boeri Architetti has unveiled design plans for a 'Smart Forest City' in Cancun.""According to the architectural firm's website, the site would consist of 400 hectares of green space and feature public parks and private gardens.""The Smart Forest City would contain green roofs and more than 200,000 trees that would be able to absorb approximately 116.000 tons of carbon dioxide.""The company explained that the area would be surrounded by a ring of solar panels and agricultural fields to provide renewable energy and food for the city.""The development's agricultural fields would be irrigated by a water channel connected to an underwater maritime pipe." "The site would use electric and semi-automatic vehicles instead of traditional vehicles for both residents and visitors.""Visitors to the forest city would be required to leave their traditional vehicles at the city's outer edge."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Stefano Boeri Architetti, Arch Daily, DesignBoomhttps://inhabitat.com/first-smart-forest-city-in-mexico-will-be-100-food-and-energy-self-sufficient/https://www.stefanoboeriarchitetti.net/en/project/smart-forest-city-cancun/https://www.archdaily.com/927312/first-smart-forest-city-in-mexico-designed-by-stefano-boeri-architettihttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/stefano-boeri-smart-forest-city-cancun-mexico-10-30-2019/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 05:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/14/3920775/3920775_FB98700145164219BBCEF41B2EC9C50C_191114_3920775__Smart_Forest_City__design_unveiled_for_Mexico_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Forest city, smart forest city, mexican smart forest city, smart forest city cancun, cancun mexico, cancun forest city, green forest city, forest city mexico, mexico green space, Stefano Boeri Architetti]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920699</guid>
      <title>Air Protein creates artificial meat from carbon dioxide</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAir Protein says it has launched a meat substitute made of chemical compounds and other elements harvested from the air in a press release on Tuesday.CNet reports that the faux meat utilizes carbon dioxide, oxygen and nitrogen.According to Air Protein, a proprietary technology converts the elements into a protein that contains the same amino acids found in animal meat.The technology is developed from NASA's concept that recycles carbon dioxide from astronauts with microbes called hydrogenotrophs, which convert the gas into edible protein.The company says the process is a sustainable food production alternative that helps to reduce the use of agricultural chemicals and stress on arable land.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Air Protein's ingredients2. Compounds and elements are synthesized to protein3. NASA's closed carbon loop concept4. Air Protein claims its product is a sustainable food production alternativeVOICEOVER (in English): "Air Protein says it has launched a meat substitute made of chemical compounds and other elements harvested from the air in a press release on Tuesday.""CNet reports that the faux meat utilizes carbon dioxide, oxygen and nitrogen.""According to Air Protein, a proprietary technology converts the elements into a protein that contains the same amino acids found in animal meat.""The technology is developed from NASA's concept that recycles carbon dioxide from astronauts with microbes called hydrogenotrophs, which convert the gas into edible protein.""The company says the process is a sustainable food production alternative that helps to reduce the use of agricultural chemicals and stress on arable land."SOURCES: Air Protein, CNEThttps://www.airprotein.com/press-releasehttps://www.airprotein.com/sciencehttps://www.cnet.com/news/air-protein-launches-air-based-meat/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 02:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/14/3920699/3920699_C2E1AA14F7FB475C92EA6D23A2AAA5A9_191114_3920699_Air_Protein_creates_artificial_meat_from_carbon__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Air protein, Kiverdi, substitute meat, imitation meat, faux meat, vegetarian, vegetarianism, air based meat, sustainability]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3921235</guid>
      <title>Proposed Nanjing skyscraper would be world's tallest LEED-Gold certified building</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S.-based architectural firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill has won a competition to design Nanjing's newest skyscraper, the South HeXi Yuzui Financial District Tower.The tower's design plans were inspired by the Yangtze River, according to the project website. The 500-meter-tall building will be able to reflect light, just like the Chinese river, while its exterior will be made up of efficient glass to reduce the amount of solar heat that enters the building.The architectural firm states that the building will incorporate eco-friendly features such as multiple green spaces and harvest rainwater from its sky gardens.The structure aims to become one of the tallest buildings to achieve LEED-Gold certification when completed in 2025.The tower will include an open-air observatory with a 360 view of the city.In addition to the supertall skyscraper, the company will also design other smaller office towers and residential towers as part of a larger development in the district.The new financial district will have access to the riverfront, public transportation, public parks and other facilities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The new tower2. What the tower is inspired by 3.  What the tower is made out of4. Eco-friendly features of the tower5. The view of the cityVOICEOVER (in English): "U.S.-based architectural firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill has won a competition to design Nanjing's newest skyscraper, the South HeXi Yuzui Financial District Tower.""According to the project website, the tower's design plans were inspired by the Yangtze River.""The 500-meter-tall building will be able to reflect light, just like the Chinese river, while its exterior will be made up of efficient glass to reduce the amount of solar heat that enters the building.""The architectural firm states that the building will incorporate eco-friendly features such as multiple green spaces and harvest rainwater from its sky gardens.""The structure aims to become one of the tallest buildings to achieve LEED-Gold certification when completed in 2025.""The tower will include an open-air observatory with a 360 view of the city."SOURCES: New Atlas, Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill Architecture, Arch Daily, Architect Magazine https://newatlas.com/architecture/south-hexi-yuzui-financial-district-tower/http://smithgill.com/work/south_hexi_yuzui/https://www.archdaily.com/928340/as-plus-gg-releases-design-for-new-financial-district-in-chinahttps://www.architectmagazine.com/project-gallery/south-hexi-yuzui-financial-district-and-tower_o***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 02:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/15/3921235/3921235_FA72AE9C9FA24AAF9622BB22D1E52683_191115_3921235_Proposed_Nanjing_skyscraper_would_be_world_s_tal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Skyscrapers, China skyscraper, supertall skyscrapers, supertall skyscrapers in China, Nanjing skyscrapers, Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill Architecture, South HeXi Yuzui Financial District Tower]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3922851</guid>
      <title>Silver carp linked to decline of native fish in the Mississippi River: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has linked invasive species of Asian carp to a decline of native sport fish in the Mississippi River and some of its tributaries.According to a study published in the journal Biological Invasions, there are four types of Asian carp  grass, bighead, silver and black carp  in this river system.The study focused on the silver carp because the species is more abundant in the Upper Mississippi, where the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers has been collecting data on fish for two decades.Asian carp were originally introduced to help clear out algae and weeds in sewage ponds and fish farms in the 1960s and 1970s. They escaped, entered the Mississippi River and started migrating north.The study suggests that this may have led to a decline of native sport fish such as the yellow perch, bluegill and white and black crappie during early life stages due to a dearth of plankton, which both silver carp and sport fish compete for.While analyzing fish data between 1994 to 2013, researchers found that the number of sport fish had declined by roughly 30 percent in infested areas of the Mississippi and Illinois rivers.Meanwhile, the study found that the number of native sport fish had increased by approximately 35 percent in sections of the Mississippi River farther upstream where the Asian carp had not arrived.Researchers considered other factors such as flooding, water temperatures and sediment pollution, though none of them were found to have had a significant impact on native sport fish population.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Silver carp linked to decline of native sport fish in the Mississippi River system2. Four types of Asian carp3. Silver carp4. Why the Asian carp were originally introduced5. How these fish entered the Mississippi River6. Percentage of native sport fish that have declined in infested parts of the riverVOICEOVER (in English): "New research has linked invasive species of Asian carp  in particular the silver carp  to a decline of native sport fish in the Mississippi River and some of its tributaries.""According to a study published in the journal Biological Invasions, there are four types of Asian carp  grass, bighead, silver and black carp  in this river system.""The study focused on the silver carp because the species is more abundant in the Upper Mississippi, where the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers has been collecting data on fish for two decades.""Asian carp were originally introduced to help clear out algae and weeds in sewage ponds and fish farms in the 1960s and 1970s.""They escaped, entered the Mississippi River and started migrating north.""The study suggests that this may have led to a decline of native sport fish such as the yellow perch, bluegill and white and black crappie during early life stages due to a dearth of plankton, which both silver carp and sport fish compete for.""While analyzing fish data between 1994 to 2013, researchers found that the number of sport fish had declined by roughly 30 percent in infested areas of the Mississippi and Illinois rivers."SOURCES: Associated Press, Biological Invasions https://apnews.com/3e21b700a5b540308d4ccc6ba5e719bbhttps://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10530-019-02124-4***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/18/3922851/3922851_B512601973F1428F9A227A2D38B7B2AD_191118_3922851_Silver_carp_linked_to_decline_of_native_fish_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Asian carp, silver carp, silver carp invasion, silver carp invasive species, invasive species mississippi river, silver carp mississippi river, mississippi river]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3922846</guid>
      <title>NASA to search for fossils on Martian crater</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA plans to send its Mars 2020 rover to search for signs of ancient life on Mars' Jezero Crater.In a news release, the space agency pointed to a recent study published in the journal Icarus which identified mineral deposits called carbonates along the crater's inner rim. The study says that a lake was at the site of the Martian crater more than 3.5 billion years ago.NASA says its Mars 2020 rover will collect rock core samples from the Martian surface, noting that carbonates on the crater could be preserving signs of past life.Scientists say these mineral deposits could also reveal how the red planet evolved from having liquid water and a thicker atmosphere to a cold, dry desert. Carbonate minerals are formed as carbon dioxide and water interact with one another.NASA also pointed to another study which found hydrated silica, minerals that are also capable of preserving ancient life, on the edge of the Jezero Crater. This could be an ideal location for the Mars 2020 rover to search for buried microbial fossils, especially if the minerals are located at the crater's bottom layer.NASA's Mars 2020 rover will be launched from Cape Canaveral, Florida in 2020.The Mars 2020 mission is part of a larger project by NASA that includes lunar missions in order to prepare humans to eventually explore the red planet.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA Mars 2020 rover, Mars and Jerezo Crater2. The rover collecting rock samples 3. How Mars evolved 4. How carbonate minerals are formed5. Rover searching for buried microbial fossilsVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA plans to send its Mars 2020 rover to search for signs of ancient life on Mars' Jezero Crater.""In a news release, the space agency pointed to a recent study published in the journal Icarus which identified mineral deposits called carbonates along the crater's inner rim." "The study says that a lake was at the site of the Martian crater more than 3.5 billion years ago.""NASA says its Mars 2020 rover will collect rock core samples from the Martian surface, noting that carbonates on the crater could be preserving signs of past life.""Scientists say these mineral deposits could also reveal how the red planet evolved from having liquid water and a thicker atmosphere to a cold, dry desert. Carbonate minerals are formed as carbon dioxide and water interact with one another.""NASA also pointed to another study which found hydrated silica, minerals that are also capable of preserving ancient life, on the edge of the Jezero Crater.""This could be an ideal location for the Mars 2020 rover to search for buried microbial fossils, especially if the minerals are located at the crater's bottom layer."SOURCES: Icarus, Geophysical Research Letters, NASA, CNet, https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0019103518306067?via%3Dihubhttps://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1029/2019GL085584?af=Rhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7539https://www.cnet.com/news/nasa-will-hunt-for-fossils-on-mars/https://www.cnet.com/news/see-nasa-mars-2020-rover-stand-on-its-own-legs-for-the-first-time/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/18/3922846/3922846_283B16DF3E6F40C2AFC38FB5DD7BBB4A_191118_3922846_NASA_to_search_for_fossils_on_Martian_crater_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, space exploration, Mars, Mars mission, NASA Mars mission, Mars 2020, NASA Mars rover 2020, NASA Mars 2020, red planet, mission to mars, mars mission nasa, Jezero crater, Jezero crater Mars, NASA mars fossils]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3922762</guid>
      <title>China tests submarine launched missile in Bohai Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has test launched a new submarine launched ballistic missile named the JL-3.The country's Defense Ministry told the Global Times in a conference on June 27 that the UFO sightings earlier that month was the result of a test launch conducted in the Bohai Sea.According to the Global Times, the missile was observed by Chinese netizens in Shandong, Shanxi, Hebei and Henan.Jane's 360 reported that the trajectory was consistent with a flight path toward the desert areas in the west that China uses for missile tests.The National Interest reports that the JL-3 features a multiple warhead design capable of carrying China's hydrogen bombs.An unnamed source told the South China Morning Post that the finished JL-3 will achieve a range of 9,000 kilometers.According to the National Interest, the completed missile will be able to reach Washington D.C. when fired by a submarine.The South China Moring Post reported that the missile has a shorter range than the US Trident II because China has not made significant breakthroughs in submarine design.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Launch of JL-3 missile 2. Missile flight paths and sightings3. Multiple warhead capability4. Range of JL-3 threatens the USVOICEOVER (in English): "China has test launched a new submarine launched ballistic missile named the JL-3.""China's Defense Ministry told the Global Times in a conference on June 27 that the UFO sightings earlier that month was the result of a test launch conducted in the Bohai Sea.""According to the Global Times, the missile was observed by Chinese netizens in Shandong, Shanxi, Hebei and Henan.""Jane's 360 reported that the trajectory was consistent with a flight path toward the desert areas in the west that China uses for missile tests.""The National Interest reports that the JL-3 features a multiple warhead design capable of carrying China's hydrogen bombs.""An unnamed source told the South China Morning Post that the finished JL-3 will achieve a range of 9,000 kilometers.""According to the National Interest, the completed missile will be able to reach Washington D.C. when fired by a submarine."SOURCES: Global Times, Jane's 360, South China Morning Posthttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1156030.shtmlhttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1152808.shtmlhttps://www.janes.com/article/89001/china-conducts-probable-test-launch-of-jl-3-slbmhttps://freebeacon.com/national-security/china-tests-new-sub-launched-strategic-missile/https://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/2178983/china-makes-big-progress-nuclear-strike-range-new-submarine***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 09:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/18/3922762/3922762_C75F53BBCAF7451CAA27B018CE25EDB4_191118_3922762_China_tests_submarine_launched_missile_in_Bohai__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, ballistic missile, submarine, flight test, missile test, nuclear weapons, JL-3, Giant Wave 3, ICBM, SLBM, Bohai Sea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923416</guid>
      <title>Thousands of Disney+ accounts stolen by hackers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHackers started targeting Disney's new streaming service just hours after it was launched on November 12.Hackers were able to gain access to users' Disney+ accounts and lock them out of all of their devices that had access to the service, according to an investigation by ZDNet.They were also able to change the email address and password of the user's streaming service account, essentially taking over the account.The report suggests that hackers may have stolen user credentials through keylogging or via malware designed to steal data. In some cases, hackers may have used emails and passwords leaked from other websites to gain access to the Disney+ accounts.The ZDNet report suggested Disney+ could provide multi-factor authentication for a more secure login to prevent hackers from gaining easy access to user accounts through previously used passwords.The report also advised users to set unique passwords for each online account.The streaming service is currently available in the U.S., Canada and the Netherlands.Thousands of Disney+ accounts were found for sale on hacking forums online, with prices ranging from US$3 to US$11. An authentic Disney+ account costs US$7 per month.The report even found free Disney+ accounts online that are available to be shared with others in the hacking forum.According to ZDNet, Disney has yet to respond to requests for comments on the streaming service's security issues.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Disney+ being targeted by hackers2. Hackers locking users out of their account3. How hackers could have used user credentials to access Disney+ accounts4. How Disney+ could provide better security5. How users can better protect themselves from such hacksVOICEOVER (in English): "Hackers started targeting Disney's new streaming service just hours after it was launched on November 12.""According to an investigation by ZDNet, hackers were able to gain access to users' Disney+ accounts and lock them out of all of their devices that had access to the service.""They were also able to change the email address and password of the user's streaming service account, essentially taking over the account.""The report suggests that hackers may have stolen user credentials through keylogging or via malware designed to steal data.""In some cases, hackers may have used emails and passwords leaked from other websites to gain access to the Disney+ accounts.""The ZDNet report suggested Disney+ could provide multi-factor authentication for a more secure login to prevent hackers from gaining easy access to user accounts through previously used passwords.""The report also advised users to set unique passwords for each online account."SOURCES: ZDNet, BBC News, https://www.zdnet.com/article/thousands-of-hacked-disney-accounts-are-already-for-sale-on-hacking-forums/https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-50461171***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 14:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/19/3923416/3923416_CECD92D3B1EE47BDA878A6F360711005_191119_3923416_Thousands_of_Disney__accounts_stolen_by_hackers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Disney, Disney+, Disney+ hacked, Disney+ hacked accounts, Disney+ video streaming service hacked, Disney+ glitches, Disney customers hacked,  Disney+ technical glitches]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923409</guid>
      <title>Iran restricts internet access amid gasoline protests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIran started restricting access to the internet on Friday, November 15, with nearly all access to the internet being restricted by Saturday, November 16, according to a report from NetBlocks, an organization that monitors worldwide internet access.The organization says Iran now only has five percent of ordinary levels of connectivity to the internet. This comes amid protests against the government's plan to hike gasoline prices.The Iranian government plans to increase prices for rationed gasoline by 50 percent, the New York Times reports. Those who purchase gasoline that exceeds the ration limit will face a 300 percent increase in fuel prices.According to the NetBlocks report, some of Iran's largest mobile network operators including MCI, RIghtel and IranCell, all fell silent around 6:00 p.m. on Saturday.Authorities must work with internet service providers and mobile data providers to shut down all internet connections, reports Wired.Alp Toker, director of NetBlocks, told Wired these telecoms would also need to overcome protections in a network system which are meant to make the system resilient in case of accidental outages or bugs. Toker noted that Iran's initial internet slowdowns may have been due to these very protections in the leadup to the now almost complete internet shutdown.The clampdown on internet service is believed to be designed to limit the number of people attending protests and to hinder media coverage, according to NetBlocks. Apps such as WhatsApp and Instagram have also been blocked.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Laptop with its internet connection being restricted2. Three Iranian mobile network operators falling silent around the same time3. How Iranian authorities could have worked to shut down all internet connections4. Why Iran is restricting access to the internetVOICEOVER (in English): "Iran started restricting access to the internet on Friday, November 15, with nearly all access to the internet being restricted by Saturday, November 16, according to a report from NetBlocks, an organization that monitors worldwide internet access."The organization says Iran now only has five percent of ordinary levels of connectivity to the internet.""This comes amid protests against the government's plan to hike gasoline prices." "According to the NetBlocks report, some of Iran's largest mobile network operators including MCI, RIghtel and IranCell, all fell silent around 6:00 p.m. on Saturday.""Wired reports that authorities must work with internet service providers and mobile data providers to shut down all internet connections.""Alp Toker, director of NetBlocks, told Wired these telecoms would also need to overcome protections in a network system which are meant to make the system resilient in case of accidental outages or bugs.""Toker noted that Iran's initial internet slowdowns may have been due to these very protections in the leadup to the now almost complete internet shutdown.""According to NetBlocks, the clampdown on internet service is believed to be designed to limit the number of people attending protests and to hinder media coverage.""Apps such as WhatsApp and Instagram have also been blocked."SOURCES: TechCrunch, NetBlocks, Wired, New York Times, Associated Press https://techcrunch.com/2019/11/17/iran-shuts-down-countrys-internet-in-the-wake-of-fuel-protests/https://netblocks.org/reports/internet-disrupted-in-iran-amid-fuel-protests-in-multiple-cities-pA25L18bhttps://www.wired.com/story/iran-internet-shutoff/https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/17/world/middleeast/iran-protest-rouhani.htmlhttps://apnews.com/2062e5a7e6b3447d9af1b42141661f01***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 14:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/19/3923409/3923409_90851E77C30244BFB16F57E05B3104CB_191119_3923409_Iran_restricts_internet_access_amid_gasoline_pro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Iran, Iran protests, iran protests internet, iran shuts down internet, iran shuts down internet fuel protests, iran gasoline, iran internet, Iran blocks internet access]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923209</guid>
      <title>NASA finds Neptune's moons engaged in dance-like movement</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThalassa and Naiad appear to be locked in an intricate 'dance of avoidance' that keep their respective orbits stable, according to NASA.  Thalassa and Naiad are described as small and tic tac and shaped, with computations of their mass and size showing the density of ice water.Thalassa circles Neptune every seven hours and thirty minutes, while Naiad completes the circuit every seven hours, but on an orbit tilted by five degrees relative to Thalassa.Viewed from Thalassa, Naiad appear to dance in a wave like pattern, passing twice from above and twice from below.NASA researchers said this behavior between celestial bodies is called a resonance, but the specific pattern of these moons have never been seen before.According to researchers, Neptune disrupted its original satellite system when it captured its giant moon, Triton.The disruption caused Naiad to veer into a tilted orbit before it settled into the ballet-like resonance with Thalassa.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Neptune and its moons2. Thalassa and Naiad orbits3. Naiad's orbital trajectory in relation to Thalassa4. Theory of strange orbits forming after disruption to systemVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA, Thalassa and Naiad appear to be locked in an intricate 'dance of avoidance' that keep their respective orbits stable.""Thalassa circles Neptune every seven hours and thirty minutes, while Naiad completes the circuit every seven hours, but on an orbit tilted by five degrees relative to Thalassa.""Viewed from Thalassa, Naiad appear to dance in a wave like pattern, passing twice from above and twice from below.""NASA researchers said this behavior between celestial bodies is called a resonance, but the specific pattern of these moons have never been seen before.""According to researchers, Neptune disrupted its original satellite system when it captured its giant moon, Triton.""The disruption caused Naiad to veer into a tilted orbit before it settled into the ballet-like resonance with Thalassa."SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?release=2019-227***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 08:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/19/3923209/3923209_D4EB89392E804E8EBFE4C64B94AF71CE_191119_3923209_NASA_finds_Neptune_s_moons_engaged_in_dance_like_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Neptune, Thalassa, Naiad, moons, dance of avoidance, dance, resonance, space, NASA, JPL, astronomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924242</guid>
      <title>New skyscraper proposed for Chicago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmerican architectural firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill has unveiled updated design plans to build a 1,422-foot tall skyscraper in Chicago.The top of the tower will curve inwards.The skyscraper is part of a larger project that includes an overhaul of nearby buildings as well as the iconic Tribune Tower.The structure will include commercial spaces as well as parking at the bottom, Dezeen reports. The building's upper part will include a hotel, rental apartments and condominiums.Upon completion, the skyscraper would become Chicago's second tallest building, surpassing Trump International Hotel & Tower, which stands at 1,380 feet.Developers of the project are still waiting for zoning approval, reports the Chicago Tribune. The designers of the skyscraper updated their initial plans as residents of the area raised concerns about traffic and security near the Chicago River.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The new skyscraper2. The tower is part of a larger project to overhaul surrounding buildings in the area3. Spaces the building will include4. The tower would become Chicago's second tallest building when completedVOICEOVER (in English): "American architectural firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill has unveiled updated design plans to build a 1,422-foot tall skyscraper in Chicago.""The top of the tower will curve inwards.""The skyscraper is part of a larger project that includes an overhaul of nearby buildings as well as the iconic Tribune Tower.""Dezeen reports the structure will include commercial spaces as well as parking at the bottom.""The building's upper part will include a hotel, rental apartments and condominiums.""Upon completion, the skyscraper would become Chicago's second tallest building, surpassing Trump International Hotel & Tower, which stands at 1,380 feet."SOURCES: Chicago Tribune, Dezeen, Archinecthttps://www.chicagotribune.com/columns/ryan-ori/ct-biz-tribune-tower-supertall-building-ryan-ori-20191113-hgszckgnvrflrfn4xfqo5pytqq-story.htmlhttps://www.dezeen.com/2018/04/27/chicago-second-tallest-skyscraper-planned-beside-tribune-tower-redevelopment/https://archinect.com/news/article/150170212/adrian-smith-gordon-gill-unveil-modest-changes-for-chicago-s-second-tallest-tower***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 08:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/21/3924242/3924242_058A161DE96B4DBC86BBCE2B6ABA2F48_191121_3924242_New_skyscraper_proposed_for_Chicago_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Chicago, chicago skyscrapers, the second tallest skyscraper in chicago, chicago skyscrapers new, chicago architecture, new skyscrapers, Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924020</guid>
      <title>Airbus' VSR700 unmanned aerial vehicle conducts first flight in France</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA prototype of the Airbus Helicopters' VSR700 Unmanned Aerial System successfully performed its first test flight at a drone testing center in southern France on November 8.A press release from Airbus stated that the aircraft performed multiple takeoffs and landings, with its longest flight lasting roughly 10 minutes.On its website, the company says that the VSR700 has a maximum speed of 185 kilometers per hour. The aerial vehicle was tethered with 30-meter cables while conducting the test flight.The company says the aircraft will eventually be cleared to fly without a cable.Airbus said aerial vehicle was based on the Helicopteres Guimbal's Cabri G2 and will be able to operate on ships with other helicopters.The VSR700 will feature an advanced flight control system, a payload bay in place of a cockpit and a specialized set of avionics. The company explained that the aircraft will also be capable of carrying multiple full size naval sensors as it has an endurance of eight hours with full payload.Airbus had previously conducted a test flight of another version of the same aerial vehicle, called the VSR700 Optionally Piloted Vehicle, in 2017.The VSR700 Unmanned Aerial System will perform test flights with French company the Naval Group for the French Navy in 2021.The aircraft is being pitched for the French Navy's airborne drone system program scheduled for 2028, according to Naval News. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Airbus Helicopters' VSR700 taking off2. The aircraft in flight and then landing3. The aerial vehicle is based on the Helicopteres Guimbal's Cabri G24. The aircraft operating on a ship5. Features of the VSR700 Unmanned Aerial SystemVOICEOVER (in English): "A prototype of the Airbus Helicopters' VSR700 Unmanned Aerial System successfully performed its first test flight at a drone testing center in southern France on November 8.""A press release from Airbus stated that the aircraft performed multiple takeoffs and landings, with its longest flight lasting roughly 10 minutes.""On its website, the company says that the VSR700 has a maximum speed of 185 kilometers per hour.""The aerial vehicle was tethered with 30-meter cables while conducting the test flight.""Airbus said aerial vehicle was based on the Helicopteres Guimbal's Cabri G2 and will be able to operate on ships with other helicopters.""The VSR700 will feature an advanced flight control system, a payload bay in place of a cockpit and a specialized set of avionics.""The company explained that the aircraft will also be capable of carrying multiple full size naval sensors as it has an endurance of eight hours with full payload."SOURCES: Airbus, New Atlas, Naval News, Defense World, Flight Global  https://www.airbus.com/newsroom/press-releases/en/2019/11/vsr700-prototype-performs-first-flight.htmlhttps://www.airbus.com/helicopters/UAS/VSR700.htmlhttps://newatlas.com/military/airbus-vsr700-drone-copter-prototype-maiden-flight/https://www.navalnews.com/naval-news/2019/11/airbus-vsr700-vtol-uav-enhanced-prototype-performed-maiden-flights/https://www.defenseworld.net/news/25821/Airbus__VSR700_UAS_Makes_First_Flight#.XdOJ2zMzZjUhttps://www.flightglobal.com/news/articles/france-awards-airbus-deal-to-develop-naval-drone-tec-444827/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/21/3924020/3924020_CC60E34BDDD54520AA528F5155C9390A_191121_3924020_Airbus__VSR700_unmanned_aerial_vehicle_conducts__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, VSR700,  VSR700 drone, VSR700 aircraft, Airbus Helicopter, Airbus, Optionally Piloted Vehicle, Airbus Optionally Piloted Vehicle, VSR700 prototype]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924015</guid>
      <title>Brain-infecting virus spread by mosquitoes in Michigan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA farmer from Michigan passed away from complications related to the Eastern Equine Encephalitis virus on Saturday, November 16, according to local news station WNDU.Health officials in Michigan say six people from the state have now succumbed to the deadly virus.The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention states on its website that the virus is spread from avian hosts to mosquitoes. The mosquitoes carry the virus and transmit it to humans.The CDC says that after contracting the virus, a person may become sick with one of two types of illness: systemic or encephalitic.A systemic infection includes flu-like symptoms such as fever, chills or malaise.An encephalitic infection includes symptoms such as fever, headache, vomiting and swelling of the brain.Most people infected do not develop any symptoms. According to CDC statistics, around 5 percent of those infected develop an encephalitic illness. Those older than 50 or younger than 15 are at a greater risk of developing this severe form of the illness.There is currently no human vaccine available against the virus.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. map, man and the Eastern Equine Encephalitis virus2. How the virus is spread3. Explaining what a systemic infection is4. Symptoms of the illness5. No human vaccine is currently available 6. How to prevent an infectionVOICEOVER (in English): "A farmer from Michigan passed away from complications related to the Eastern Equine Encephalitis virus on Saturday, November 16, according to local news station WNDU.""The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention states on its website that the virus is spread from avian hosts to mosquitoes. The mosquitoes carry the virus and transmit it to humans.""The CDC says that after contracting the virus, a person may become sick with one of two types of illness: systemic or encephalitic.""A systemic infection includes flu-like symptoms such as fever, chills or malaise.""An encephalitic infection includes symptoms such as fever, headache, vomiting and swelling of the brain.""There is currently no human vaccine available against the virus.""The CDC advises the public to use insect repellent with active ingredients such as DEET, picaridin or lemon eucalyptus oil.""Officials also advise the public to wear long-sleeved clothing and to close windows to prevent mosquito bites."SOURCES: Fox News, WNDU, Michigan government, Centers for Disease Control and Preventionhttps://www.foxnews.com/health/michigan-farmer-eee-death-6th-statehttps://www.wndu.com/content/news/Eau-Claire-farmer-dies-from-apparent-EEE-complications--565101762.htmlhttps://www.michigan.gov/documents/emergingdiseases/Weekly_Arbovirus_Summary_11-6-2019_670836_7.pdfhttps://www.cdc.gov/easternequineencephalitis/tech/epi.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/21/3924015/3924015_BD116F13FC45448199CF5346B657CC9C_191121_3924015_Brain_infecting_virus_spread_by_mosquitoes_in_Mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mosquitoes, mosquito bite, mosquito infection, mosquito virus,  brain virus, mosquitoes brain virus, EEEV, eastern equine encephalitis virus, eastern equine encephalitis symptoms, eastern equine encephalitis michigan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924887</guid>
      <title>Doctors successfully suspend human in animation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDoctors have put at least one human in suspended animation, the New Scientist reports on Wednesday.They performed it as part of a trial to save gunshot or stabbing victims who may have minutes to live.Maryland University researcher Samuel Tisherman told the New Scientist that traumatic injuries could result in massive blood loss and then cardiac arrest, robbing the brain of oxygen.Irreversible damage would occur to the brain within five minutes and the patient's survival rate is less than five percent, according to the New Scientist.Tisherman said that the emergency preservation and resuscitation technique, or EPR, replaces all of the patient's blood with ice-cold saline solution.The researcher explained that EPR reduces the need for oxygen by cooling the body and brain, which gives surgeons two hours to repair the injuries. According to Tisherman, the trial will compare EPR's results on a group of ten patients to a control group. Both groups will be treated at the university's hospital.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Traumatic injury victim in critical condition 2.  Cardiac arrest leads to brain oxygen deprivation3.  Suspended animation buys doctor time to operate4.  Setup of medical trialVOICEOVER (in English): "Doctors have put at least one human in suspended animation, the New Scientist reports on Wednesday.""They performed it as part of a trial to save gunshot or stabbing victims who may have minutes to live.""Maryland University researcher Samuel Tisherman told the New Scientist that traumatic injuries could result in massive blood loss and then cardiac arrest, robbing the brain of oxygen.""Irreversible damage would occur to the brain within five minutes and the patient's survival rate is less than five percent, according to the New Scientist.""Tisherman said that the emergency preservation and resuscitation technique, or EPR, replaces all of the patient's blood with ice-cold saline solution.""The researcher explained that EPR reduces the need for oxygen by cooling the body and brain, which gives surgeons two hours to repair the injuries." "According to Tisherman, the trial will compare EPR's results on a group of ten patients to a control group. Both groups will be treated at the university's hospital."SOURCES:  New Scientist, Guardianhttps://www.newscientist.com/article/2224004-exclusive-humans-placed-in-suspended-animation-for-the-first-time/https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/nov/20/humans-put-into-suspended-animation-for-first-time***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 11:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/22/3924887/3924887_EF3C946F74DC4139BC75445831147A5C_191122_3924887_Doctors_successfully_suspend_human_in_animation_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Suspended animation, Baltimore, University of Maryland, heart, saline solution, critical medicine, critical care, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924595</guid>
      <title>Ex-British consulate worker says he was tortured after arrest in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA former employee of the UK consulate in Hong Kong claims he was tortured by Chinese authorities, reports CNN.In a Facebook post on Wednesday, ex-UK Hong Kong consulate worker Simon Cheng says he took part in the city's protests but did not break any laws.Cheng approached protesters on Telegram and other social media as part of his job to evaluate travel alerts and protect British citizens, he says in a Facebook post on Wednesday.He was returning from a business trip in August in Shenzhen when police arrested him on the Chinese side of the West Hong Kong Kowloon railway station.According to Cheng, he was then handed over to State Security Bureau officials and detained in Shenzhen.Speaking to CNN, Britain's Foreign Secretary Dominic Raab said he summoned the Chinese Ambassador to express outrage at the brutal and disgraceful treatment of Cheng. China responded on Wednesday with foreign minister Geng Shuang telling reporters that Cheng made a full confession and that the public security bureau "guaranteed all his rights and interests according to law."CNN reports that Cheng fled to an unnamed third country following his detention and is currently seeking asylum.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cheng's involvement in Hong Kong protest2. Arrest in Shenzhen3. Cheng interrogated on 'tiger chair'4. Suspension on cross5. Stress position6. Sleep deprivation7. Cheng's Injuries8. False confessionVOICEOVER (in English): "In a Facebook post on Wednesday, ex-UK Hong Kong consulate worker Simon Cheng says he took part in the city's protests but did not break any laws.""Cheng says he approached protesters on Telegram and other social media as part of his job to evaluate travel alerts and protect British citizens.""He was returning from a business trip in August in Shenzhen when police arrested him on the Chinese side of the West Hong Kong Kowloon railway station.""According to Cheng, he was then handed over to State Security Bureau officials and detained in Shenzhen."  "Cheng says he was buckled to a tiger chair and rendered immobile during his initial interrogation, which lasted for hours.""He says officers took blood and urine samples and confiscated his glasses and cellphone.""Cheng says he was repeatedly tortured. He says, officers would hang him on a "steep X-cross" while he was handcuffed, shackled and blindfolded. This stress position causes extreme pain.""The interrogators forced him to perform exercises such as squatting while he was still blindfolded and restrained by cuffs and shackles.""If he fell from exhaustion, Cheng says, the interrogators would beat him with weapons that felt like sharpened batons.""Cheng says his captors also prevented sleep by making him stand still while under restraints for hours at a time." "If he went under, they would force him to sing the Chinese national anthem.""Cheng says that secret police forbade him from telling prison doctors that the bruises and wounds on his limbs were the result of torture." "He says they stopped applying physical torture after one week, when he became too weak to walk.""Cheng says he ultimately agreed to a filmed confession at the detention center under duress." "He says he was released after falsely confessing to soliciting prostution and betraying the motherland."SOURCES: Simon Cheng (Facebook), CNN, BBChttps://www.facebook.com/notes/cheng-man-kit/for-the-record-an-enemy-of-the-state/2490959950941845/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/20/asia/simon-cheng-china-torture-allegations-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-50457262***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 04:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/22/3924595/3924595_E0CEAF975AD1433C9AC083A418DB7C23_191122_3924595_Ex_British_consulate_worker_says_he_was_tortured_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Simon Cheng, toture, Hong Kong, Shenzhen, China, Ministry of State Security, secret police, human rights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926170</guid>
      <title>A third of African tropical plants risk extinction: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study from the journal Science Advances suggests that roughly 7,000, or 33 percent, of African plant species risk extinction.The researchers focused on two International Union for Conservation of Nature Red List criteria, related to habitat decline and future population reduction, and developed an algorithm to assess more than 20,000 plant species' risk of going extinct.Based on the assessment, four African regions  Ethiopia, west Africa, central Tanzania and the southern Democratic Republic of the Congo  in particular were found to be the most vulnerable, with more than 40 percent of local flora potentially being threatened with extinction.Species at risk include local trees, herbs, lianas and shrubs.The study also pointed to ecoregions concentrated in West Africa that include large numbers of threatened species, specifically the Inner Niger Delta savanna, Sahelian Acacia savanna, Guinean mangroves, western Guinean lowland forest and Guinean montane forests.Researchers said these plant species are threatened by deforestation, climate change and population growth.In addition, scientists found another third of flora species in the region that is likely rare and could potentially risk extinction in the near future.Co-author of the study, Gilles Dauby, from the French National Research Institute for Sustainable Development told the Guardian that these species could likely be threatened if human pressure increases in tropical Africa.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Number of African plant species that risk extinction2. Most vulnerable regions in Africa3. Ecoregions in Africa that house large number of threatened plant species4. Why these species are threatenedVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study from the journal Science Advances suggests that roughly 7,000, or 33 percent, of African plant species risk extinction.""The researchers focused on two International Union for Conservation of Nature Red List criteria, related to habitat decline and future population reduction, and developed an algorithm to assess more than 20,000 plant species' risk of going extinct.""Based on the assessment, four African regions  Ethiopia, west Africa, central Tanzania and the southern Democratic Republic of the Congo  in particular were found to be the most vulnerable, with more than 40 percent of local flora potentially being threatened with extinction.""Species at risk include local trees, herbs, lianas and shrubs.""The study also pointed to ecoregions concentrated in West Africa that include large numbers of threatened species, specifically the Inner Niger Delta savanna, Sahelian Acacia savanna, Guinean mangroves, western Guinean lowland forest and Guinean montane forests.""Researchers said these plant species are threatened by deforestation, climate change and population growth."SOURCES: Science Advances, BBC News, The Guardian, Phy.org https://advances.sciencemag.org/content/5/11/eaax9444https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50477684https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/nov/20/a-third-of-tropical-african-plant-species-at-risk-of-extinction-studyhttps://phys.org/news/2019-11-africa-tropical-flora-threatened-extinction.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/25/3926170/3926170_1B5CC7F0B7EC4B06BE530FB0A892B1B6_191125_3926170_A_third_of_African_tropical_plants_risk_extincti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Africa, African plant species, African flora, tropical African flora, African flora risk extinction, African plant species face extinction, endemic trees  Africa, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926163</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong pro-democracy candidates win big in local elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHong Kong held its local district council elections on Sunday after almost six months of anti-government protests.Voter turnout was more than 71 percent, up from 47 percent in 2015, BBC News reports. The elections are considered to be a test for the current Hong Kong government.The city has a total of 18 district councils, of which the pro-democracy camp won 17, according to the South China Morning Post. District councils mainly advise the government on local issues concerning their district, such as the use of public facilities and public services.Several prominent pro-democracy activists including Jimmy Sham, who was attacked by masked assailants with hammers last month in Kowloon, managed to win district council seats in the local elections.The district councils may play a significant role when electing Hong Kong's chief executive in 2022.This is because the city's leader is elected by a 1,200-member committee, which includes 117 members chosen by district councillors. In this system, whichever campclaims the majority of votes, has the ability to claim all 117 of these seats.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hong Kong local election turnout2. Pro-democracy parties won 17 out of the 18 district councils3. How these elections could influence the votes for the city's chief executive4. How these elections could be tied into gaining seats in the Legislative CouncilVOICEOVER (in English): "Hong Kong held its local district council elections on Sunday after almost six months of anti-government protests.""BBC News reports voter turnout was more than 71 percent, up from 47 percent in 2015.""The elections are considered to be a test for the current Hong Kong government.""The city has a total of 18 district councils, of which the pro-democracy camp won 17, according to the South China Morning Post.""District councils mainly advise the government on local issues concerning their district, such as the use of public facilities and public services.""The district councils may play a significant role when electing Hong Kong's chief executive in 2022.""This is because the city's leader is elected by a 1,200-member committee, which includes 117 members chosen by district councillors. In this system, whichever campclaims the majority of votes, has the ability to claim all 117 of these seats.""This could influence who is chosen to be the city's chief executive as the pro-democracy camp already held roughly 400 committee seats before the district council elections.""As six out of 70 seats are reserved in the city's Legislative Council for district councillors, the pro-democracy camp may also secure seats in the Legislative Council as the majority.""Hong Kong's Legislative Council has the ability to enact, amend, repeal laws or even start an impeachment process against the city's leader."SOURCES: BBC News, South China Morning Post, Hong Kong Free Press, Euronews, Reutershttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-50531408https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3039151/hong-kong-elections-tsunami-disaffection-washes-over-cityhttps://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/11/23/hong-kong-holds-protest-election-will-produce-protest-result/https://www.euronews.com/2019/11/24/hong-kong-elections-four-keys-to-understanding-district-council-pollshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests/hong-kong-democrats-score-landslide-victory-in-local-elections-amid-political-crisis-idUSKBN1XY0MZ?il=0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/25/3926163/3926163_5661EE8B083A4A22B18EFFF1DD359579_191125_3926163_Hong_Kong_pro_democracy_candidates_win_big_in_lo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hong Kong elections, hong kong elections explained, hong kong elections 2019, hong kong district elections, hong kong news, hong kong vote, hong kong voting, hong kong local elections, hong kong local elections results]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3925939</guid>
      <title>China's growing appetite for coal threatens its Paris pledge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report by Global Energy Monitor found that China has increased its coal power capacity by 42.9 gigawatts between January of 2018 and June of 2019. That is enough energy to power 31 million homes, according to the BBC. The report notes that the rest of the world decreased its total coal capacity by 8.1 gigawatts during the same time period.Researchers involved with the study say China would need to reduce its current coal capacity by over 40 percent, from 1,027 gigawatts to 600 gigawatts or less, by 2030 in order to keep its Paris climate agreement pledge to limit the rise in global temperatures to below 2C.The report found that China is constructing 121.3 gigawatts of coal plants and is likely to revive 26.4 gigawatts of other existing coal-related projects that are currently suspended, or a total of 147.7 gigawatts of coal power capacity.This is almost equivalent to the European Union's existing coal power capacity, which stands at 150 gigawatts.China continues to finance a quarter of all coal plant projects around the world, in countries such as South Africa, Pakistan and Bangladesh, the BBC reports.China has invested heavily in clean energy, though the country continues to invest in coal power.Co-author of the study Christine Shearer from Global Energy Monitor, called China's coal power expansion plans "far out of alignment with the Paris Agreement."Shearer said that China needs to make significant reductions to its coal power capacity instead of continued expansion over the coming decade.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China ramps up its coal capacity2. The amount of coal capacity Chinese would need to reduce to keep its Paris climate pledge3. China is expected to further increase its total coal capacity4. Different countries where China is financing coal plant projectsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report by Global Energy Monitor found that China has increased its coal power capacity by 42.9 gigawatts between January of 2018 and June of 2019.""According to the BBC, that is enough energy to power 31 million homes.""The report notes that the rest of the world decreased its total coal capacity by 8.1 gigawatts during the same time period.""Researchers involved with the study say China would need to reduce its current coal capacity by over 40 percent, from 1,027 gigawatts to 600 gigawatts or less, by 2030 in order to keep its Paris climate agreement pledge to limit the rise in global temperatures to below 2C.""The report found that China is constructing 121.3 gigawatts of coal plants and is likely to revive 26.4 gigawatts of other existing coal-related projects that are currently suspended, or a total of 147.7 gigawatts of coal power capacity.""This is almost equivalent to the European Union's existing coal power capacity, which stands at 150 gigawatts.""The BBC reports that China continues to finance a quarter of all coal plant projects around the world, in countries such as South Africa, Pakistan and Bangladesh."SOURCES: BBC News, Global Energy Monitor, The Guardian, Reuters, Global Coal Plant Trackerhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50474824https://endcoal.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/Out-of-Step-English-final.pdfhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/20/china-appetite-for-coal-power-stations-returns-despite-climate-pledge-capacityhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-china-coal/china-coal-fired-power-capacity-still-rising-bucking-global-trend-study-idUSKBN1XU07Yhttps://endcoal.org/tracker/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 06:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/25/3925939/3925939_94E8D82F9DCE4D82AAFA933F07B4B642_191125_3925939_China_s_growing_appetite_for_coal_threatens_its__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, china coal power plant, china coal plant, china coal power, coal power plant pollution, coal plants, climate change, climate warning, climate change china, coal power capacity, coal plant pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926604</guid>
      <title>Excess body weight can weaken efficacy of flu vaccine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found that the flu vaccine is less effective for people with excess weight.A study from the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill found that vaccinated obese adults have twice the risk of flu or flu-like illnesses compared to vaccinated healthy-weight adults.NPR reports that during the 2009 flu outbreak, health experts noticed the infection was worse in individuals who were significantly overweight.The virus grows to higher concentrations and spreads deeper in the lungs.Heavier individuals were also more likely to spread the disease.A University of Maryland study found that more of the virus came out of the exhaled breath of those who were overweight or obese.According to Chapel Hill nutrition professor Melinda Beck, the metabolic shift in people's bodies caused by gaining excess weight affects immune system cells.So although obese people may still make an antibody response, their T-cells aren't functioning, so they can still be infected with the flu despite being vaccinated.Apart from the obese and overweight, elderly people also face the same problem.Because of this, scientists are now working to develop a next-generation flu shot that can address these vulnerabilities, though it has years to go before it's ready.In the meantime, they say people should still continue to get vaccinated, regardless of size or body weight.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flu vaccine less effective in overweight, obese adults2. Flu virus spreads deeper in lungs of overweight, obese individuals3. Obese, overweight individuals more likely to spread virus4. Antibody response present, but T-cells not functioning VOICEOVER (in English): "According to NPR, scientists have found that the flu vaccine is less effective for people with excess weight.""A study from the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill found that vaccinated obese adults have twice the risk of flu or flu-like illnesses compared to vaccinated healthy-weight adults.""NPR reports that during the 2009 flu outbreak, health experts noticed the infection was worse in individuals who were significantly overweight.""The virus grows to higher concentrations and spreads deeper in the lungs.""Heavier individuals were also more likely to spread the disease.""A University of Maryland study found that more of the virus came out of the exhaled breath of those who were overweight or obese. ""According to Chapel Hill nutrition professor Melinda Beck, the metabolic shift in people's bodies caused by gaining excess weight affects immune system cells.""So although obese people may still make an antibody response, their T-cells aren't functioning, so they can still be infected with the flu despite being vaccinated."SOURCES: NPR, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, University of Marylandhttps://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/11/24/782079520/excess-weight-can-weaken-the-flu-shothttps://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/29161078https://www.pnas.org/content/115/5/1081 ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 10:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/26/3926604/3926604_5F5BC3B320754763A2912A8B9993DC71_191126_3926604_Excess_body_weight_can_weaken_efficacy_of_flu_va_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Flu shot, fly vaccine, obese, overweight, flu shot efficacy, flu vaccine efficacy, flu season, flu, influenza, influenza vaccine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927102</guid>
      <title>World's largest radio telescope planned for Australia and South Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDesigns for a next-generation radio telescope called the Square Kilometer Array, have nearly been finalized while construction will commence in Australia and South Africa in early 2021.The telescope itself will be built in two different phases called SKA 1 and SKA 2.SKA 1, which will soon begin construction, includes two instruments, SKA1-Low and SKA1-Mid.SKA1-Low will consist of 130,000 antennas and will be located in western Australia, according to Australia's Telescope National Facility. While SKA1-Mid will have 130 parabolic dish antennas and will be located in South Africa.SKA1-Low will operate in frequencies between 50 and 350 megahertz while SKA1-Mid will operate in frequencies between 350 megahertz and about 15 gigahertz.According to Square Kilometer Array's project website, the telescope will be hundreds of times faster at mapping the sky than other current radio astronomy facilities. The telescope will cover an area of one square kilometer.The website states that it will be strong enough to detect faint radio signals by cosmic sources that are billions of light years away.Square Kilometer Array's website states that the radio telescope is intended to be in operation for over 50 years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Square Kilometer Array radio telescope2. Instruments of the telescope that will be used during phase 13. Difference between the two instruments4. The telescopes scanning the sky and detecting a radio signalVOICEOVER (in English): "Designs for a next-generation radio telescope called the Square Kilometer Array, have nearly been finalized while construction will commence in Australia and South Africa in early 2021.""The telescope itself will be built in two different phases called SKA 1 and SKA 2.""SKA 1, which will soon begin construction, includes two instruments, SKA1-Low and SKA1-Mid.""According to Australia's Telescope National Facility, SKA1-Low will consist of 130,000 antennas and will be located in western Australia.""While SKA1-Mid will have 130 parabolic dish antennas and will be located in South Africa.""SKA1-Low will operate in frequencies between 50 and 350 megahertz while SKA1-Mid will operate in frequencies between 350 megahertz and about 15 gigahertz.""According to Square Kilometer Array's project website, the telescope will be hundreds of times faster at mapping the sky than other current radio astronomy facilities.""The telescope will cover an area of one square kilometer.""The website states that it will be strong enough to detect faint radio signals by cosmic sources that are billions of light years away."SOURCES: Science Magazine, Square Kilometer Array, Australian Government, Australia Telescope National Facility, Community of European Solar Radio Astronomershttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/11/giant-radio-telescope-array-prepares-begin-construction-australia-and-south-africahttps://www.skatelescope.org/https://www.skatelescope.org/the-ska-project/https://www.skatelescope.org/frequently-asked-questions/https://www.industry.gov.au/strategies-for-the-future/astronomy/co-hosting-the-square-kilometre-arrayhttps://www.atnf.csiro.au/projects/ska/index.htmlhttp://www.astro.gla.ac.uk/users/eduard/cesra/?p=2295***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 08:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/27/3927102/3927102_FA1E9AB154B749D9824D3161AD6568C6_191127_3927102_World_s_largest_radio_telescope_planned_for_Aust_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Radio telescope, giant radio telescope, Square Kilometre Array, SKA telescopes, World's largest radio telescope]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927037</guid>
      <title>'Coral IVF' could restore damaged parts of Great Barrier Reef</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists from Australia's Southern Cross University have come up with a technique called "Coral IVF" to restore coral in damaged parts of the Great Barrier Reef.Researchers captured millions of coral larvae during mass spawning events that occur following the full moon in the months of November and December. These larvae were then co-cultured with an algae called zooxanthellae, which was grown in a lab to have higher thermal tolerance.According to a news release from the university, these corals are now living in 'coral nursery' rearer pools designed by the research team.Scientists say the rearer pools allow the baby coral to be 'turbo-charged' due to the algae which increases their chance of survival. Optical sensors were added to track the progress of the baby coral.The team now has six rearer pools housing millions of coral larvae. These corals will be dispersed onto damaged parts of the Great Barrier Reef to help form new coral communities.Peter Harrison, a researcher from the university's Marine Ecology Research Center who was involved with the study, said the technique is similar to a "battery pack" which allows the coral to soak up the algae and potentially gain more energy to grow faster.If the project is successful, "Coral IVF" could be used as a blueprint to help restore damaged or dying coral reefs around the world.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New technique that could restore damaged coral 2. How Coral IVF works3. Coral nursery housing coral larvae4. Coral larvae being dispersed to help form new coral communitiesVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists from Australia's Southern Cross University have come up with a technique called 'Coral IVF' to restore coral in damaged parts of the Great Barrier Reef.""Researchers captured millions of coral larvae during mass spawning events that occur following the full moon in the months of November and December." "These larvae were then co-cultured with an algae called zooxanthellae, which was grown in a lab to have higher thermal tolerance.""According to a news release from the university, these corals are now living in 'coral nursery' rearer pools designed by the research team.""Scientists say the rearer pools allow the baby coral to be 'turbo-charged' due to the algae which increases their chance of survival.""Optical sensors were added to track the progress of the baby coral.""The team now has six rearer pools housing millions of coral larvae. These corals will be dispersed onto damaged parts of the Great Barrier Reef to help form new coral communities."SOURCES: New Atlas, Southern Cross Universityhttps://newatlas.com/environment/coral-ivf-bleaching-great-barrier-reef/https://www.scu.edu.au/engage/news/latest-news/2019/millions-of-coral-babies-turbo-charged-in-floating-nurseries-to-restore-damaged-parts-of-the-great-barrier-reef-.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 07:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/27/3927037/3927037_38E5282BC31649E99EE6B4A484F342D3_191127_3927037__Coral_IVF__could_restore_damaged_parts_of_Great_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Great barrier reef, Great barrier reef new coral, spawning new coral, Great barrier coral, coral IVF, coral IVF great barrier reef, coral larvae, coral nursery rearer pools]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926977</guid>
      <title>Leaked documents reveal conditions at China's Uyghur internment camp</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has built a vast camp system in Xinjiang and interned about a million Uyghurs. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, or ICIJ, says that a new leak has revealed the conditions in the system.The Guardian reports that the documents contain instructions for officials to "never allow escape."The orders demand constant surveillance with no blindspots and building guard towers and layers of fences, the Guardian reports.The BBC reports that every aspect of life in the camps is controlled. The document shows that a detainee must take a fixed position for bed, for workshop, and for lunch queues. The documents include orders to enforce strict discipline for sleeping, waking, closing doors and roll calls, the BBC reports.China claimed the camps give lessons on Chinese language and citizenship, but former detainees described them as brainwashing sessions, the New York Times reports.The ICIJ says the leak showed the extent of China's AI surveillance program. The system tracks VISAs applications, use of encrypted apps and facial recognition to flag thousands for searches and detention.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China's detention system2. Security and surveillance3. Control over detainee 4. Strict discipline5. Indoctrination6. Point system7. AI-powered surveillanceVOICEOVER (in English): "China has built a vast camp system in Xinjiang and interned about a million Uyghurs. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, or ICIJ, says that a new leak has revealed the conditions in the system.""The Guardian reports that the documents contain instructions for officials to 'never allow escape.'""The orders demand constant surveillance with no blindspots and establishing guard towers and layers of fences and walls, according to the Guardian.""The BBC reports that every aspect of life in the camps is controlled. The document shows that a detainee must take a fixed position for bed, for workshop, and for lunch queues.""The documents include orders to enforce strict discipline for sleeping, waking, closing doors and roll calls.""Chinese officials claimed the camps give lessons on Chinese language and citizenship, but former detainees described them as harsh brainwashing sessions, the New York Times reports.""According to the BBC, the camps established a points system based on the detainee's ideological transformation and compliance.""The Guardian reports that those who loses points could be transferred to a higher tier of security camps and see their internment increased from the required term of one year.""The ICIJ says the documents also revealed the extent of China's AI-powered domestic surveillance program.""The predictive system tracks VISAs application records, use of encrypted apps and facial recognition to flag thousands of people for searches and detention."SOURCES: The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, China Cables (Scribd) The Guardian, BBC News, The New York Times https://www.icij.org/investigations/china-cables/exposed-chinas-operating-manuals-for-mass-internment-and-arrest-by-algorithm/https://www.scribd.com/document/436167661/China-Cables-Day-One-main-doc-and-translation#download&from_embedhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/24/china-cables-leak-no-escapes-reality-china-uighur-prison-camphttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-50511063https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/24/world/asia/leak-chinas-internment-camps.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 05:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/27/3926977/3926977_03B1DE8C93664CFDAFF29133DB77807A_191127_3926977_Leaked_documents_reveal_conditions_at_China_s_Uy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, Xinjiang, Uyghur, internment camps, detention camps, indoctrination, brainwashing, human rights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926960</guid>
      <title>Leaked documents reveal conditions at China's Uyghur internment camp</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has built a vast camp system in Xinjiang and interned about a million Uyghurs. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, or ICIJ, says that a new leak has revealed the conditions in the system.The Guardian reports that the documents contain instructions for officials to "never allow escape."The orders demand constant surveillance with no blindspots and building guard towers and layers of fences, the Guardian reports.The BBC reports that every aspect of life in the camps is controlled. The document shows that a detainee must take a fixed position for bed, for workshop, and for lunch queues. The documents include orders to enforce strict discipline for sleeping, waking, closing doors and roll calls, the BBC reports.China claimed the camps give lessons on Chinese language and citizenship, but former detainees described them as brainwashing sessions, the New York Times reports.The BBC reports that the camps created a points system based on the detainee's ideological transformation and compliance. The Guardian reports that punished detainees would be sent to a higher security camps and have their internment terms increased.The ICIJ says the leak showed the extent of China's AI surveillance program. The system tracks VISAs applications, use of encrypted apps and facial recognition to flag thousands for searches and detention.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China's detention system2. Security and surveillance3. Control over detainee 4. Strict discipline5. Indoctrination6. Point system7. AI-powered surveillanceVOICEOVER (in English): "China has built a vast camp system in Xinjiang and interned about a million Uyghurs. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, or ICIJ, says that a new leak has revealed the conditions in the system.""The Guardian reports that the documents contain instructions for officials to 'never allow escape.'""The orders demand constant surveillance with no blindspots and establishing guard towers and layers of fences and walls, according to the Guardian.""The BBC reports that every aspect of life in the camps is controlled. The document shows that a detainee must take a fixed position for bed, for workshop, and for lunch queues.""The documents include orders to enforce strict discipline for sleeping, waking, closing doors and roll calls.""Chinese officials claimed the camps give lessons on Chinese language and citizenship, but former detainees described them as harsh brainwashing sessions, the New York Times reports.""According to the BBC, the camps established a points system based on the detainee's ideological transformation and compliance.""The Guardian reports that those who loses points could be transferred to a higher tier of security camps and see their internment increased from the required term of one year.""The ICIJ says the documents also revealed the extent of China's AI-powered domestic surveillance program.""The predictive system tracks VISAs application records, use of encrypted apps and facial recognition to flag thousands of people for searches and detention."SOURCES: The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, China Cables (Scribd) The Guardian, BBC News, The New York Times https://www.icij.org/investigations/china-cables/exposed-chinas-operating-manuals-for-mass-internment-and-arrest-by-algorithm/https://www.scribd.com/document/436167661/China-Cables-Day-One-main-doc-and-translation#download&from_embedhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/24/china-cables-leak-no-escapes-reality-china-uighur-prison-camphttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-50511063https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/24/world/asia/leak-chinas-internment-camps.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 05:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/27/3926960/3926960_9CCE0218347C4ACA8C877566E8196874_191127_3926960_Leaked_documents_reveal_conditions_at_China_s_Uy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, Xinjiang, Uyghur, internment camps, detention camps, indoctrination, brainwashing, human rights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926917</guid>
      <title>Microplastic particles found in European rivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the Tara Ocean Foundation, an environmental research organization, collected water samples from nine rivers across Europe and found microplastic particles present in every sample.Scientists traveled aboard a research ship called the Tara, across Europe's coastline for six months between May to November and collected 2,700 water samples, according to the foundation's website.These samples were collected from different sites on rivers which included the Thames, Elbe, Rhine and Seine.The microplastic particles found were less than 5 millimeters in size and were mostly microbeads or secondary microplastics, which are formed from larger plastic pieces due to exposure to sunlight.The organization stated that these samples will be analyzed in laboratories in the next 12 to 18 months in order to determine their composition, degradation and their origins.The project's aim is to identify the source of microplastic pollution and its impact on marine life.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Microplastics found in water samples from nine European rivers2. How the samples were collected3. Types of microplastic particles that were found4. Samples being analyzedVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the Tara Ocean Foundation, an environmental research organization, collected water samples from nine rivers across Europe and found microplastic particles present in every sample.""According to the foundation's website, scientists traveled aboard a research ship called the Tara across Europe's coastline for six months between May and November and collected 2,700 water samples.""These samples were collected from different sites on rivers which included the Thames, Elbe, Rhine and Seine.""The microplastic particles found were less than 5 millimeters in size and were mostly microbeads or secondary microplastics, which are formed from larger plastic pieces due to exposure to sunlight.""The organization stated that these samples will be analyzed in laboratories in the next 12 to 18 months to determine their composition, degradation and their origins."SOURCES: Digital Journal, Euronews, Tara Ocean Foundation, CNRS Newshttp://www.digitaljournal.com/news/environment/omnipresence-of-microplastics-in-european-rivers-revealed/article/562338https://www.euronews.com/2019/11/23/microplastics-are-omnipresent-in-european-rivers-scientists-sayhttps://oceans.taraexpeditions.org/en/m/science/news/press-2019-microplastics-mission/https://oceans.taraexpeditions.org/m/science/les-actualites/cp-retour-missionmicroplastiques2019/https://news.cnrs.fr/articles/tracing-plastics-in-rivers***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 04:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/27/3926917/3926917_87B6F583435A42E79CBD6A972B080850_191127_3926917_Microplastic_particles_found_in_European_rivers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, microplastic pollution, microplastic pollution europe, microplastic pollution european rivers, plastic pollution, microplastic particles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927804</guid>
      <title>World's first malaria vaccine introduced in Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe World Health Organization has implemented a large-scale malaria vaccine pilot program for 360,000 children across Africa.The vaccine, called RTS,S, is being tested in Malawi, Kenya and Ghana, and is being administered to children upto the age of 2.However, experts have raised concerns about the vaccine's efficacy, durability and safety. Four doses of the vaccine offer only 30 percent protection from severe malaria, for roughly three years.Children who received vaccinations were found to have a 10 times higher risk of meningitis than those given a control vaccine.A fact sheet by PATH Malaria Vaccine Initiative, an international non-profit organization, says the vaccine is designed to trigger the immune system when malaria parasites enter the bloodstream via mosquito bites.The vaccine blocks the parasite from infecting a person's liver, where it could potentially multiply and reenter the bloodstream to infect red blood cells. This is when symptoms of malaria usually starts to appear.Initial symptoms of malaria include fever, headache and chills. In more serious cases, children may develop severe anaemia or respiratory distress.Children under the age of 5 are the most vulnerable to the disease, according to the World Health Organization. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New malaria vaccine2. Where the malaria vaccine pilot program has been implemented 3. Malaria parasites entering the bloodstream4. How the vaccine works to stop the parasites from multiplying5. Symptoms of malariaVOICEOVER (in English): "The World Health Organization has implemented a large-scale malaria vaccine pilot program for 360,000 children across Africa.""The vaccine, called RTS,S, is being tested in Malawi, Kenya and Ghana, and is being administered to children upto the age of 2.""A fact sheet by PATH Malaria Vaccine Initiative, an international non-profit organization, says the vaccine is designed to trigger the immune system when malaria parasites enter the bloodstream via mosquito bites.""The vaccine blocks the parasite from infecting a person's liver, where it could potentially multiply and reenter the bloodstream to infect red blood cells. This is when symptoms of malaria usually starts to appear.""Initial symptoms of malaria include fever, headache and chills. In more serious cases, children may develop severe anaemia or respiratory distress."SOURCES: Science Magazine, World Health Organization, Malaria vaccine.org, CNN  https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/11/first-malaria-vaccine-rolled-out-africa-despite-limited-efficacy-and-nagging-safetyhttps://www.who.int/news-room/detail/23-04-2019-malaria-vaccine-pilot-launched-in-malawihttps://www.who.int/malaria/media/malaria-vaccine-implementation-qa/en/https://www.who.int/malaria/media/malaria-vaccine-overview/en/https://www.malariavaccine.org/malaria-and-vaccines/rtsshttps://www.malariavaccine.org/sites/www.malariavaccine.org/files/content/page/files/PATH_MVI_RTSS_Fact%20sheet_042019.pdfhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/04/23/health/malaria-africa-worlds-first-vaccine-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 11:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/28/3927804/3927804_9D58B4971BD5429FA3A733CFC3B0A037_191128_3927804_World_s_first_malaria_vaccine_introduced_in_Afri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Malawi, vaccine, malaria africa, malaria vaccine africa, malaria, malaria vaccine, malawi vaccine malaria, malaria vaccine 2019, malaria vaccine child, rts s vaccine, rts s vaccine malawi, malaria cases]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927684</guid>
      <title>Voyager 2 detected high temperatures and gaps in the heliopause sphere: NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUS NASA's Voyager 2 reached the edge of the solar system in early November. The two Voyagers were launched 42 years ago, but Voyager 2 took the longer route to interstellar space.Live Science reports that Voyager 2 detected a fiery plasma wall in the heliopause, where the sun's outward blowing solar winds clash with cosmic rays. This barrier protects the solar system by repulsing and weakening cosmic rays.Citing NASA, Live Science reports that Voyager 1 could not detect the wall because its sensors malfunctioned. However, as Voyager 2 crosses the heliopause, it found holes in the protective shell and temperatures twice as high as past models predicted.According to BBC, the sun's energies charge particles into an ionized plasma state and shoot them out to form solar winds and the heliopause.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Voyager 1 & 2's path to outer space2. Heliopause formation3. Voyager 2 findings4. Explanation for solar windsVOICEOVER (in English): "US NASA's Voyager 2 reached the edge of the solar system in early November. The two Voyagers were launched 42 years ago, but Voyager 2 took the longer route to interstellar space.""Live Science reports that Voyager 2 detected a fiery plasma wall in the heliopause, where the sun's outward blowing solar winds clash with cosmic rays. This barrier protects the solar system by repulsing and weakening cosmic rays.""Citing NASA, Live Science reports that Voyager 1 could not detect the wall because its sensors malfunctioned. However, as Voyager 2 crosses the heliopause, it found holes in the protective shell and temperatures twice as high as past models predicted.""According to BBC, the sun's energies charge particles into an ionized plasma state and shoot them out to form solar winds and the heliopause."SOURCES: NASA, Live Science, BBC Newshttps://svs.gsfc.nasa.gov/10654https://www.livescience.com/voyager-2-detects-heliopause-plasma-shield.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50289353***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/28/3927684/3927684_5A8E5DAAED084BC3BD77CD8BAB9CDB1A_191128_3927684_Voyager_2_detected_high_temperatures_and_gaps_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Voyagers, Voyager 1, Voyager 2, sun, solar system, heliosphere, heliopause, NASA, US, solar wind, solar winds, interstellar wind winds, interstellar, outer space, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927489</guid>
      <title>Helicopter collision takes the lives of 13 French soldiers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA helicopter collision in Mali has taken the lives of 13 French soldiers in France's worst military loss in four decades.On Monday evening, a French Tiger attack helicopter was reinforcing troops on the ground chasing after militants in Mali when the helicopter collided with a Cougar military transport helicopter around 7:40 p.m. local time.The incident occurred near the Mali's border at Burkina Faso and Niger.The two aircraft crashed near each other, killing all 13 French soldiers on board, including an officer and six commandos, according to the BBC. An investigation has been launched to discover the cause of the collision, the heaviest single French military loss since a 1983 attack in Beirut killed 58 paratroopers.In a tweet, French President Emmanuel Macron expressed "deep sadness" and called the soldiers "heroes."French lawmakers observed a minute of silence for the fallen soldiers on Tuesday.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. French Tiger attack helicopter reinforcing ground troops who were chasing after militants2. The helicopter colliding with a Cougar military transport helicopter3. Where the incident occurred4. Crashes and casualtiesVOICEOVER (in English): "On Monday evening, a French Tiger attack helicopter was reinforcing troops on the ground chasing after militants in Mali    when the helicopter collided with a Cougar military transport helicopter around 7:40 p.m. local time.""The incident occurred near the Mali's border at Burkina Faso and Niger.""According to the BBC, the two aircraft crashed near each other, killing all 13 French soldiers on board, including an officer and six commandos.""An investigation has been launched to discover the cause of the collision, the heaviest single French military loss since a 1983 attack in Beirut killed 58 paratroopers."SOURCES: BBC News, Reuters, Associated Press, France 24https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-50557511https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-mali-military/french-mali-troops-died-after-tigre-and-cougar-helicopters-collided-idUSKBN1Y00ZYhttps://apnews.com/9bc294a465f147a2ad77eefbf9f35f4ahttps://www.france24.com/en/20191126-thirteen-french-soldiers-killed-in-mali-helicopter-accident***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 02:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/28/3927489/3927489_0A0F54927B95401190650BBBEBFB4195_191128_3927489_Helicopter_collision_takes_the_lives_of_13_Frenc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, France helicopter collision, France Mali, french troops in mali, french military mali, France mali helicopter collision]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3928509</guid>
      <title>Air bubble barrier helps stop plastic waste from entering the ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDutch-based startup "The Great Bubble Barrier" says that air bubbles could stop plastic waste in rivers from reaching the ocean.The company says its program features a pipe and air compressor that generate bubbles and a trap system that gathers plastics on the canal of Amsterdam's Westerdok.New Atlas reports that a previous trial collected 86 percent of riverbourne plastic trash.The company states that the barrier's diagonal placement uses the water flow to guide the plastic waste to the catchment system on the riverside for collection.The pipe supplements the garbage collection boats that also clean 42 tonnes of plastic trash from the canal each year.While boats could not gather submerged plastic objects, the bubble barrier generates upward flow that brings the plastics to the catchment system on the surface.The company also claims that the bubble barrier pumps oxygen into the river, which prevents algae blooms and bolsters the aquatic ecosystem.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Experimental bubble barrier stops plastic garbage from reaching the sea2. Diagonal placement controls flow of plastic trash 3. The system deals with submerged plastics and prevents algae bloomVOICEOVER (in English): "The Great Bubble Barrier says its program features a pipe and air compressor that generate bubbles and a trap system that gathers plastics on the canal of Amsterdam's Westerdok.""The New Atlas reports that a previous trial collected 86 percent of riverbourne plastic trash.""The company states that the barrier's diagonal placement uses the water flow to guide the plastic waste to the catchment system on the riverside for collection.""The pipe supplements the garbage collection boats that also clean 42 tonnes of plastic trash from the canal each year.""While boats could not gather submerged plastic objects, the bubble barrier generates upward flow that brings the plastics to the catchment system on the surface.""The company also claims that the bubble barrier pumps oxygen into the river, which prevents algae blooms and bolsters the aquatic ecosystem."SOURCES: The Great Bubble Barrier, New Atlas, The Guardianhttps://newatlas.com/environment/amsterdam-bubble-barrier-plastic/https://thegreatbubblebarrier.com/en/amsterdam-en/https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/07/bubble-barrier-launched-to-keep-plastics-out-of-oceans***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 16:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/30/3928509/3928509_77A338E1C432432281206E822251DC3D_191130_3928509_Air_bubble_barrier_helps_stop_plastic_waste_from_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Great Bubble Barrier, bubbles, plastic waste, plastic pollution, plastics, Westerdok, Amsterdam, Netherlands, environment, ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3928445</guid>
      <title>North Korea fires two short-range missiles towards the Sea of Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea launched two unidentified short-range projectiles from the country's South Hamgyong province towards the Sea of Japan on Thursday, November 28, around 4:59 p.m. local time.Both missiles flew around 380 kilometers and reached an altitude of roughly 97 kilometers, according to South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff. The two missiles were fired within 30 seconds of one another.North Korea confirmed that the projectiles were launched from a super-large multiple rocket launcher system. The country's state agency KCNA says the launcher system has a "continuous fire system."This is North Korea's fourth test of the missile launcher system, reports Yonhap News Agency. It was previously tested on August 24, September 10 and October 31, earlier this year.Japan has yet to confirm if the missiles landed in the nation's Exclusive Economic Zone.South Korea's military called on North Korea to immediately "stop such moves," adding that consecutive missiles launches won't help in easing tensions on the Korean Peninsula, Yonhap reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where North Korea launched two unidentified missiles from2. How many kilometers and how high the missiles flew3. Missiles being launched from a super-large multiple rocket launcher system4. This is North Korea's fourth test of the rocket launcher systemVOICEOVER (in English): "North Korea launched two unidentified short-range projectiles from the country's South Hamgyong province towards the Sea of Japan on Thursday, November 28, around 4:59 p.m. local time.""According to South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff, both missiles flew around 380 kilometers and reached an altitude of roughly 97 kilometers.""The two missiles were fired within 30 seconds of one another.""North Korea confirmed that the projectiles were launched from a super-large multiple rocket launcher system.""The country's state agency KCNA says the launcher system has a 'continuous fire system.'""Yonhap News Agency reports this is North Korea's fourth test of the missile launcher system. It was previously tested on August 24, September 10 and October 31, earlier this year."SOURCES: CNN, Reuters, NK News, Korean Herald, Yonhap News Agency https://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/28/asia/north-korea-launch-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles/north-korea-test-fires-rockets-in-thanksgiving-reminder-of-year-end-deadline-for-u-s-idUSKBN1Y20QXhttps://www.reuters.com/article/northkorea-missiles-kim/nkoreas-kim-expressed-great-satisfaction-over-rocket-test-kcna-idUSS6N1QP015https://www.nknews.org/2019/11/north-korea-launches-unidentified-projectile-south-korea-says/http://www.koreaherald.com/view.php?ud=20191128000755https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20191128008553325***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/29/3928445/3928445_6FA0E4E17E0A45738061FF2D4D0D14E2_191129_3928445_North_Korea_fires_two_short_range_missiles_towar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, North korea missile launch, North korea missile test, north korea rockets, north korea missile, kim jong un, north korea weapons, north korea, north korean missile, short range missile, unidentified projectiles, Multiple Launch Rocket System]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3928327</guid>
      <title>Architects propose building towers to clean Delhi air</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Indian architectural firm is proposing to build huge air purifying towers to address air pollution in Delhi.Studio Symbiosis Architects says that its 60-meter-tall Aura towers will form an air cleaning system to protect city residents from pollution, including PM 2.5 particulate matter.According to DesignBoom, the structure's aerodynamic designs include spiraling contours that draw in polluted air and expel clean filtered air. The pressure differentials enables the tower to pull PM 2.5 particles into its internal filtering chamber. The architects claim the smaller iteration of the Aura tower with a height of 18 meters could clean 32 million cubic meters of air per day.The firm says the taller towers will form a protective ring around Delhi's city borders to keep pollution out, while the 18 meter towers will be built by pollution hot spots inside the city.Pollution detecting drones and air cleaner attachments for cars will also form an integrated system with the towers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Aura tower2. Aerodynamic design3. Air intake and purification4. Proposed pollution fighting systemVOICEOVER (in English): "An Indian architectural firm is proposing to build huge air purifying towers that will tackle air pollution in Delhi.""Studio Symbiosis Architects says that its 60-meter-tall Aura towers will form an air cleaning system to protect city residents from pollution, including PM 2.5 particulate matter.""According to DesignBoom, the structure's aerodynamic designs include spiraling contours that draw in polluted air and expel clean filtered air.""The pressure differentials enables the tower to pull PM 2.5 particles into its internal filtering chamber.""The architects claim the smaller iteration of the Aura tower with a height of 18 meters could clean 32 million cubic meters of air per day.""The firm says the taller towers will form a protective ring around Delhi's city borders to keep pollution out, while the 18 meter towers will be built by pollution hot spots inside the city.""Pollution detecting drones and air cleaner attachments for cars will also form an integrated system with the towers."SOURCES: DesignBoomhttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/studio-symbiosis-air-pollution-in-india-aura-tower-11-25-2019/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 11:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/11/29/3928327/3928327_2D9D4A139BF44CD7A350B6CC45F5A730_191129_3928327_Architects_propose_building_towers_to_clean_Delh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
