<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 19:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3644561</guid>
      <title>Convicted criminal breaks out of jail in helicopter escape</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA manhunt is underway in France after a convicted gangster broke out of jail  his second attempt since escaping from a different prison in 2013.AFP reports that on Sunday, three armed men took a flying instructor hostage, ordering him to fly a helicopter to a prison outside Paris where Redoine Faid was serving a 25-year robbery sentence.The helicopter landed in the prison courtyard- the only area not protected by anti-aircraft netting, according to the BBC. Two of the men got out, while the third stayed to guard the pilot.Angle grinders and smoke bombs were used to break Faid out of the visitors' room where he was waiting with his brother, and into the chopper.The helicopter was found abandoned 60 kilometers from the prison. Faid and his accomplices had freed the pilot and boarded a getaway car, which was also later abandoned at a carpark.Authorities have since arrested Faid's brother, and deployed over 3,000 police officers to locate the dangerous fugitive.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of armed men taking flight instructor hostage2. Depiction of helicopter landing in prison courtyard3. Depiction of armed men breaking Redoine Faid out of prison4. Depiction of abandoned helicopter and getaway car VOICEOVER (in English): "On Sunday, three armed men took a flying instructor hostage, ordering him to fly a helicopter to a prison outside Paris where Redoine Faid was serving a 25-year robbery sentence.""The helicopter landed in the prison courtyard, the only area not protected by anti-aircraft netting. Two of the men got out, while the third stayed to guard the pilot.""Angle grinders and smoke bombs were used to break Faid out of the visitors' room where he was waiting with his brother, and into the chopper.""The helicopter was found abandoned 60 kilometers from the prison. Faid and his accomplices had freed the pilot and boarded a getaway car, which was later abandoned at a parking lot."SOURCES: Agence France Presse, BBC, Reutershttps://www.afp.com/en/news/205/notorious-gangster-flees-french-jail-helicopter-doc-16x2dz1https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-44673753https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-gangster-escape/french-gangster-flees-prison-in-spectacular-helicopter-escape-idUSKBN1JR1IR***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 12:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/02/3644561/3644561_66BFBAA85D0B4C1E8EE536C1425102DA_180702_3644561_Convicted_criminal_breaks_out_of_jail_in_helicop_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DB2/F29/DB2F29D526E441149A85FB7B5486621F_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, prison break jail break, helicopter prison break, helicopter, fugitive, gangster, wanted criminal, France most wanted, Redoine Faid, hostage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644497</guid>
      <title>How a Supreme Court Justice is nominated and confirmed by the Senate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJustice Anthony Kennedy is stepping down at the end of July, paving way for the president to nominate a new Supreme Court judge, reports CNBC.When a supreme court justice retires, the president has to nominate a qualified candidate.The nominated candidate will then be questioned by the Senate judiciary committee about key issues, a process that takes an average of 60 days.The Senate judiciary committee sends the candidate to the Senate, where they debate  about his or her qualifications.To end the discussion, 60 votes are required in what is known as a cloture motion. According to CBS News, those voting in the Senate tend to reject or accept candidates based on their political leanings.After ending the debate, the Senate will conduct a simple majority vote, requiring at least 51 votes, with the vice president breaking the tie if necessary.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How US presidents chooses a Supreme Court candidate2. A nominee being questioned by the Senate judiciary committee3. Senate debating whether the candidate is qualified for the job4. Voting process in the SenateVOICEOVER (in English): "When a supreme court justice retires, the president has to nominate a candidate.""The nominated candidate will then be questioned by the Senate judiciary committee about key issues, a process that takes an average of 60 days.""The Senate judiciary committee sends the candidate to the Senate, where they debate back and forth about his or her qualifications. To end the discussion, 60 votes are required in what is known as a cloture motion.""After ending the debate, the Senate will conduct a simple majority vote, requiring at least 51 votes, with the vice president breaking the tie if necessary."SOURCES: The Atlantic, The Washington Post, CBS News, CNBC, Ted-Edhttps://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/06/anthony-kennedy/563939/https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/with-anthony-kennedys-departure-the-supreme-court-will-fall-to-chaos/2018/06/27/a052dfde-5a01-11e7-a9f6-7c3296387341_story.html?utm_term=.2208f4a2bbb3https://www.cbsnews.com/news/justice-anthony-kennedy-supreme-court-retiring-scotus-announcement-today-2018-06-27-live-updates/https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/anthony-kennedy-retiring-from-supreme-court.htmlhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0xnzGSV66x4***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 10:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/02/3644497/3644497_2066E78771B8481DAACB44A8CE6C0A2A_180702_3644497_How_a_Supreme_Court_Justice_is_nominated_and_con_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D84/134/D84134B16BE74FE4812D75872D2E18CE_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, US, Supreme Court justice, Senate, nominating and confirming a Supreme court justice, Senate Committee hearing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644146</guid>
      <title>Astronomers find source of Milky Way's unusual microwave light emissions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers may have finally figured out the decades-old mystery of certain glowing regions in our galaxy: nanodiamonds.According to the Green Bank Observatory, faint microwave lights known as anomalous microwave emissions, or AME, were first spotted in the Milky Way 20 years ago.Infrared-light emitting polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons were initially thought to be responsible, but not all systems with PAH clouds had an AME glow.A new study published in the journal Nature studied 14 newly formed star systems using West Virginia's Green Bank Telescope and the Australia Telescope Compact Array. Researchers noticed AME coming from three newborn star systems, all of which were the only ones surrounded by diamond dust.The light is believed to result from the rapidly spinning nanodiamond particles producing a dipole moment and emitting electromagnetic radiation in the microwave range.Apart from being both unexpected and cool, scientists suggest the findings can shed light on the chemical signatures of early solar systems, with implications on how ours looked right after the Big Bang.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of microwave light emissions across the Milky Way2. Depiction of PAHs initially thought to be responsible 3. Depiction of three newborn star systems surrounded by diamond dust4. Depiction of nanodiamond particles emitting microwave lightVOICEOVER (in English): "Faint microwave lights known as anomalous microwave emissions or AME were first spotted in the Milky Way twenty years ago.""Infrared-light emitting polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons were initially thought to be responsible, but not all systems with PAH clouds had an AME glow.""Using the Green Bank Telescope and the Australia Telescope Compact Array, a new study noticed AME coming from three newborn star systems, all of which were surrounded by diamond dust.""The light is believed to result from the rapidly spinning nanodiamond particles producing a dipole moment and emitting electromagnetic radiation in the microwave range."SOURCES: Green Bank Observatory, The Guardianhttps://greenbankobservatory.org/press/diamond-dust.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jun/11/astronomers-find-source-of-stars-mysterious-microwaves-diamonds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 01:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/02/3644146/3644146_E4BC85DB900A44F7B147C0ADE7BED2AF_180702_3644146_Astronomers_find_source_of_Milky_Way_s_unusual_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/370/EC4/370EC40582A14333B920657B936D3EFB_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, microwaves, nanodiamonds, ame, light emissions, microwave emissions, anomalous microwave emissions, milky way, star systems, newborn stars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644999</guid>
      <title>Ford, Vanderbilt study proposes traffic jam solution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research by Ford and Vanderbilt University may have a new solution to traffic jams.So-called "phantom" traffic jams occur when a driver at the head of a pack of cars slows for an unknown reason. The halting action ripples to all following vehicles causing them to also slow or stop.Ford and Vanderbilt University researchers recently tested Adaptive Cruise Control, ACC, as a means of dealing with phantom traffic jams This system monitors traffic flow and adjusts speed accordingly. Ford say no traffic jam occurred when ACC was switched on.Another method of reducing congestion, according to CNET, is ramp metering. This system uses traffic signals to manage the flow of traffic while vehicles waiting on an on-ramp.Some areas in Ontario, Canada use High Occupancy Toll (HOT) lanes to lessen congestion. Motorists there can pay a premium to access these lanes in high-traffic areas prone to congestion.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of "phantom traffic jams"2. Depiction of adaptive cruise control3. Depiction of road metering4. Depiction of high occupancy toll lanesVOICEOVER (in English): ""Phantom" traffic jams occur when a driver at the head of a pack of cars slows for an unknown reason." "The halting action ripples to all following vehicles causing them to also slow or stop.""Ford and Vanderbilt University researchers recently tested Adaptive Cruise Control as a means of dealing with phantom traffic jams.""This system monitors traffic flow and adjusts speed accordingly. Ford says no traffic jam occurred when ACC was switched on.""Another method of reducing congestion, according to CNET, is ramp metering.""This system uses traffic signals to manage the flow of traffic while vehicles waiting on an on-ramp.""Some areas in Ontario, Canada uses High Occupancy Toll lanes to lessen traffic jams.""Motorists pay a premium to access these lanes in high-traffic areas that are prone to congestion."SOURCES: Ford, CNET, Utah Department of Transportation, Brookings, Ontario Ministry of Transportation, Gizmodohttps://media.ford.com/content/fordmedia/fna/us/en/news/2018/06/29/ford-vanderbilt-phantom-traffic-jams.htmlhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2GYfXxVn2Ochttps://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/traffic-talk-ford-vanderbilt-2018/https://www.brookings.edu/research/traffic-why-its-getting-worse-what-government-can-do/http://www.mto.gov.on.ca/english/highway-bridges/hot-lanes.shtmlhttps://io9.gizmodo.com/could-new-technologies-make-traffic-jams-a-thing-of-the-1602353172***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 05:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/03/3644999/3644999_97FB63688F734714BE388C02E1581559_180703_3644999_Ford__Vanderbilt_study_proposes_traffic_jam_solu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DC7/397/DC73977462944A7C86E3AA927CF5BEAA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, traffic jam solutions, ford, adaptive cruise control, acc traffic jams, phantom traffic jams, phantom traffic jam problem, high occupancy toll lanes, HOT lanes, congestion, traffic management solutions, department of transportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644854</guid>
      <title>AI robot to be sent to International Space Station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn AI robot will be launched in a SpaceX rocket to join astronauts in the International Space Station, according to reports from NASA.The spacecraft will be carrying supplies, food and water to the station, as well as an AI robot. The robot  is named CIMON, for Crew Interactive Mobile Companion, and has a diameter of 32 centimeters. It is also equipped with 14 fans, so it can "float" and maneuver. CIMON will be used to assist astronauts, answering their questions by displaying pictures and videos on its screen. The AI robot is set to be deployed for three months in order to conduct several experiments. One trial will test if CIMON can help astronauts solve a rubik's cube. This is the first time an AI based robot will interact with astronauts in space, reports Orlando Sentinel.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SpaceX craft docking at the International Space Station2. CIMON robot and internal parts3. CIMON assisting astronauts4. CIMON carrying out experimentsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to reports from NASA, an AI robot is set to join astronauts at the International Space Station. A SpaceX rocket will carry supplies, food and water, as well as the new robotic crew member." "The robot is named CIMON  for Crew Interactive Mobile Companion   and has a diameter of 32 centimeters. It also has 14 fans inside so it can "float".""CIMON will be up on the Space Station to assist astronauts, answering their questions by displaying pictures and videos on its screen." "The AI robot is set to be deployed for three months in order to conduct several experiments. One trial will test if CIMON can help astronauts solve a rubik's cube."SOURCES: NASA, The Verge, Orlando Sentinel, ABC News,DLRhttps://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-television-to-air-launch-of-next-space-station-resupply-mission-4https://www.theverge.com/2018/6/28/17513410/spacex-iss-nasa-commercial-resupply-15-falcon-9-launch-dragon-watch-livehttp://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/space/os-bz-spacex-cargo-launch-20180627-story.htmlhttps://abcnews.go.com/Technology/video/meet-robot-headed-international-space-station-56239983https://www.dlr.de/dlr/en/desktopdefault.aspx/tabid-10212/332_read-26307/#/gallery/29912***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/03/3644854/3644854_D88FD10EFED145668B14B3E4E689600C_180703_3644854_AI_robot_to_be_sent_to_International_Space_Stati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1D1/85D/1D185D6213CD48D7B9E17C907BF6535D_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Space, SpaceX rocket, AI robot, astronauts, International space station, NASA, Falcon 9 rocket]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645991</guid>
      <title>Samsung phones sending out photos to contacts due to glitch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA handful of Samsung mobile phones have been sending out camera roll photos via SMS without user permission.As first reported by Gizmodo, Samsung users are complaining of a new bug, which causes phones like the Galaxy S9 and S9+ to send users' stored photos to people on their contacts list without permission.Those who have been affected say evidence of the photo sharing did not appear on the Samsung messages app, but were recorded on phone carrier logs.Many of the complaints have been from T-Mobile subscribers, leading to speculation that the bug was triggered by the carrier's RCS, Rich Communication Services, update which adds features like GIF support, video, location and file sharing to improve texting.While Samsung is still looking into the problem, there are two temporary fixes. Users can revoke Samsung Messages' permissions to access storage, or switch to a different texting app.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Samsung phones sending photos to contacts2. Depiction of photo sharing leaving a record on carrier log, but not in app3. Depiction of RCS updates triggering glitch4. Depiction of temporary fixes for Samsung glitchVOICEOVER (in English): "A number of Samsung phones, including the Galaxy S9 and S9+, have reportedly been sending users' stored photos to people on their contacts list without permission.""Those who have been affected say evidence of the photo sharing did not appear on the Samsung messages app, but were recorded on phone carrier logs.""Many of the complaints have been from T-Mobile subscribers, leading to speculation that the bug was triggered by the carrier's RCS update, which adds features to improve texting.""While Samsung is still looking into the problem, there are two temporary fixes. Users can revoke Samsung Messages' permissions to access storage, or switch to a different texting app."SOURCES: Gizmodo, Seattle Timeshttps://gizmodo.com/a-bug-in-samsungs-default-texting-app-is-sending-random-1827291759?utm_campaign=socialflow_gizmodo_twitter&utm_medium=socialflow&utm_source=gizmodo_twitterhttps://www.seattletimes.com/business/waposamsung-s-texting-app-apparently-sent-pictures-to-people-s-contacts-without-permission/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/04/3645991/3645991_BC775D54F7C845D5AA5AAC4100B8A56B_180704_3645991_Samsung_phones_sending_out_photos_to_contacts_du_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/673/48B/67348B0614054F7B936B575D6C957544_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, samsung, phone glitch, phone problems, samsung bug, samsung glitch, galaxy s9, s9, s9+, t mobile, samsung messages, message app, texting, RCS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645979</guid>
      <title>Plastic eating bacteria discovered by U.S. undergrad</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA U.S. undergraduate student has discovered a new kind of plastic consuming bacteria.Morgan Vague, a senior at Reed College in Oregon has developed a new bacteria that eats polyethylene terephthalate, or P.E.T.This synthetic fiber is a polyester polymer mostly common found in plastic bottles and clothing. P.E.T. takes hundreds of years to break down in the environment and is a major contributor to worldwide waste and pollution.According to the Oregonian, Vague took soil, sand and water samples polluted with petroleum from Galveston Bay in Texas. From these, she narrowed down the microbes that produced the highest amount of plastic dissolving chemicals.Next, she left three with nothing but plastic to feed on and later found them to all have consumed it. Two of the bacteria are known, but the third is a new bacteria discovered by Vague. She is calling it Pseudomonas morganensis, reports the Oregonian. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of plastic eating bacteria and bottle 2. Depiction of PET in oceans3. Depiction of polluted samples and plastic4. Depiction of plastic eating bacteria VOICEOVER (in English): "Morgan Vague, a senior at Reed College in Oregon has developed a new bacteria that eats P.E.T. plastic""This synthetic fiber is a polyester polymer mostly common found in plastic bottles and clothing.""P.E.T. takes hundreds of years to break down in the environment and is a major contributor to worldwide waste and pollution.""According to the Oregonian, Vague took soil, sand and water samples polluted with petroleum from Galveston Bay in Texas.""From these, she narrowed down the microbes that produced the highest amount of plastic dissolving chemicals." "Next, she left three with nothing but plastic to feed on. She later found the three types of microbes had consumed all of the plastic." "Two of the bacteria are known, but the third is a new bacteria discovered by Vague. She is calling it Pseudomonas morganensis."SOURCES: Oregon Live, The Independenthttps://www.oregonlive.com/environment/index.ssf/2018/06/reed_senior_makes_watershed_di.htmlhttps://www.independent.co.uk/environment/plastic-eating-bacteria-pollution-crisis-environment-microbes-student-a8423146.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/04/3645979/3645979_BAE34453035D4EB49AD318F9D3B607B7_180704_3645979_Plastic_eating_bacteria_discovered_by_U_S__under_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/CE1/68C/CE168CE27C394ED7BF46F97E57EDFEB7_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, plastic bacteria, plastic eating bacteria, plastic in the ocean, pollution, plastic and marine life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646742</guid>
      <title>Third-party app developers may be reading Gmail messages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoogle has confirmed that third-party app developers can sometimes read private emails sent by Gmail users. Third-party developers gain access to emails when Google asks users for permission via a pop-up box that asks to "read, send, delete and manage your email," according to CNet.Google indicates the practice is not a violation of policy. The company says third-party developers need access to help Gmail build various services, reports the BBC.According to the Washington Post, Return Path and Edison Software reviewed private emails.   Return Path allegedly read 8000 user emails from two years ago to help Google develop software.Edison Software reviewed hundreds of emails to build a new software feature, according to the BBC.Edison Software says they have "since stopped this practice."Google said users can revoke access from any third-party apps that users have previously given access to by going to its Security Checkup page, reports EnGadget.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Popup box asking for permission to access Gmail messages2. Return Path reading email to develop software for Gmail.3. Edison Software reading emails to create the 'Smart Reply' function on Gmail4. Showing that Gmail has a Security Checkup page where people can check if their emails have been accessed by third-party apps.VOICEOVER (in English): "Google has confirmed that third-party app developers can sometimes read private emails sent by Gmail users. Developers gain access when Google asks users for permission via a pop-up box the app asks to 'read, send, delete and manage your email.'""Return Path allegedly read 8000 user emails from two years ago to develop Google's software.""Edison Software reviewed hundreds of emails to build a new software feature.""EnGadget reports Google said users can revoke access from any third-party apps by going to its Security Checkup page. "SOURCES: BBC, CNet, EnGadgethttps://www.bbc.com/news/technology-44699263https://www.cnet.com/news/third-party-gmail-apps-reportedly-let-employees-read-peoples-emails/https://www.engadget.com/2018/07/03/third-party-app-developers-reading-gmail/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/05/3646742/3646742_C8D892E022284BB3AD52AC30F7EE1827_180705_3646742_Third_party_app_developers_may_be_reading_Gmail__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DD7/4C4/DD74C4EB19824A99A099D6BBAD27574D_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Google, Gmail, messages, private emails,user inbox, app developers, third-party apps, data,software]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646727</guid>
      <title>Solar-powered Switzerland school produces enough surplus energy for 50 homes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Zurich-based architecture firm has designed a school with a rooftop covered in solar panels.The self-sufficient solar-powered school, located in Switzerland, produces enough solar energy to also power 50 homes.The school has around 1,100 solar panels with the buildings connected with a zigzag roof, Inhabitat reports.The building was made by using sustainably sourced tinder and wood. The self-sufficient school covers an area of more than 180,000 square feet. The interior of the building is filled with light because of the number of windows and also because of light generated from solar power.According to DesignBoom, the ground floor would be spacious enough to conduct different learning activities for children.Each classroom would look like a little house because of the folded rooftops, creating a cozy atmosphere, reports Inhabitat.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The school is covered with solar panels, enough to power 50 homes2. Show solar panels appearing on the zigzag rooftop of the school 3. Show the area of the school along with what material it's made out of4. Show the interior of the solar-powered schoolVOICEOVER (in English): "The self-sufficient solar-powered school, located in Switzerland, produces enough energy to also power 50 homes.""Inhabitat reports the school has around 1,100 solar panels with the buildings connected with a zigzag roof .""The building was made by using sustainably sourced tinder and wood. The self-sufficient school covers an area of more than 180,000 square feet.""The interior of the building is filled with light because of the number of windows and also because of light generated from solar power."SOURCES: Inhabitat, DesignBoom,https://inhabitat.com/plus-energy-school-produces-enough-surplus-energy-to-power-50-homes/https://www.designboom.com/architecture/skop-school-port-switzerland-06-15-2018/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/05/3646727/3646727_FB2989E3E02944BE98F8980FCE400245_180705_3646727_Solar_powered_Switzerland_school_produces_enough_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/6D8/397/6D83977B2AAD46AC8994E770E9C51B3E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Switzerland, solar power, solar energy,  going green,  surplus energy, using solar energy to power schools and houses]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646715</guid>
      <title>Man fleeing Pompeii eruption killed via asphyxiation, not giant stone: archaeologists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew evidence has been unearthed in the case of the history's unluckiest man.Archaeologists searching the site of the man believed to have been crushed by a stone block during the Mt Vesuvius eruption in 79 A.D. have found the rest of his remains.They found the other remains buried deeper below the man's lower body in a tunnel created several hundred years ago. They recovered his thorax, upper limbs and skull.Analysis of the remains revealed they belonged to a 30 year-old man with a limp, reports CNN. Archaeologists now believe the man's death was brought about by pyroclastic asphyxiation resulting from the eruption.Researchers say more analysis needs to be performed on the bones in order to get a better picture of the man's final moments.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of dig site and new bones2. Depiction of bones inside man3. Depiction of man in ancient Rome area4. Depiction of pyroclastic flow and asphyxiationVOICEOVER (in English): "Archaeologists searching the site of a man believed to have been crushed by a stone block during the Mt Vesuvius eruption in 79 A.D. have found the rest of his remains.""They found the other remains buried deeper below the man's lower body in a tunnel created several hundred years ago.""They recovered his thorax, upper limbs and skull"."Analysis of the remains revealed they belonged to a 30 year-old man with a limp.""Archaeologists now believe the man's death was brought about by pyroclastic asphyxiation resulting from the eruption."SOURCES: Parco Archeologico di Pompei, CNNhttp://www.pompeiisites.org/Sezione.jsp?titolo=Head%20of%20the%20fugitive%20discovered&idSezione=7742https://edition.cnn.com/2018/06/30/europe/pompeii-victim-new-findings/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/05/3646715/3646715_EE21F3C81499465482A2A65E2C25C6B7_180705_3646715_Man_fleeing_Pompeii_eruption_killed_via_asphyxia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D1F/9AF/D1F9AF542E504FD18F1674511013B89E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, pompeii, skeleton, mount vesuvius, excavation, volcanic eruption, stone block, man crushed by rock, ancient rome, pyroclastic flow, volcanic blast]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646697</guid>
      <title>Super absorbent gauze could save troops' lives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Army is developing a super absorbent wound dressing that could potentially save the lives of soldiers on the battlefield. According to the Army, around 80 to 90 percent of potentially survivable deaths by American troops in battle occur as the result of uncontrolled bleeding.   Researchers published their results in the journal ACS Publications. According to Digital Trends, the new polystyrene and rubber wound dressing can absorb up to 800 percent of the material's weight in liquid. The new material is 5.7 times more absorbent than the current state-of-the-art wound dressing. The plasticity of the dressing makes it stronger and more flexible, while acrylic acid gives it the super absorbent properties which allow it to pull water out of the blood, so that it can clot faster. As the material swells, the bandage forms a tough hydrogel shell three times stronger than gauze. The project currently is still in the research phase with animal tests set to be the next step in the testing process. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of soldiers wounded in battlefield2. New material is polystyrene and rubber3. Depiction of medic applying new wound dressing4. Depiction of hydrogel shell around woundVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Army is developing a super absorbent wound dressing that could potentially save soldiers' lives." "According to Digital Trends, the new polystyrene and rubber wound dressing can absorb up to 800 percent of the material's weight in liquid." "The plasticity of the dressing makes it stronger and more flexible, while acrylic acid gives it the super absorbent properties which allow it to pull water out of the blood, so that it can clot faster." "As the material swells, the bandage forms a tough hydrogel shell three times stronger than gauze around the wound." SOURCES: Digital Trendshttps://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/wound-dressing-swell-soldiers-combat/amp/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 08:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/05/3646697/3646697_51FC2FBC14B74581A27446D8E4D6BADB_180705_3646697_Super_absorbent_gauze_could_save_troops__lives_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/591/48A/59148A316E864E06B46B66BEC17ACE8F_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, wound dressing, super absorbent wound dressing, uncontrolled bleeding, gauze]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647922</guid>
      <title>How Russian nerve agent Novichok used in UK poisonings works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo more people have become victims of the Russian nerve agent that affected a former Russian spy and his daughter, reports the BBC.Charlie Rowley and Dawn Sturgess were found unconscious in Salisbury in southwest England where they were poisoned by the same nerve agent, Novichok, as the Russian ex-spy Sergei Skripal and his daughter Yulia Skripal.Rowley and Sturgess were in Salisbury were taken to the hospital when Sturgess collapsed and was found "foaming at the mouth" and Rowley fell ill and was found with eyes "wide open" and he was "sweating … and making weird noises," reports the BBC. According to the BBC, Novichok nerve agent is five to eight times more toxic than the VX nerve agent.Novichok nerve agents may exist as liquids, in solid form or as an ultra-fine powder.Novichok works by inhibiting an enzyme called acetylcholinesterase, which is involved in muscle movement, according to the National Institutes of Health.Motor neurons release a neurotransmitter called acetylcholine, which signals muscles to contract.Acetylcholinesterase removes the neurotransmitter, relaxing the muscle. Novichok prevents acetylcholinesterase from relaxing the muscle, resulting in muscles contracting involuntarily and no longer functioning normally.The effects are wide-ranging, but the most critical are the effects on lung and heart function. These include respiratory paralysis and cardiac arrest, according to a Reuters report.If one is exposed to the nerve agent, they should immediately remove their clothes, rinse their eyes, and wash the exposed skin with water and soap, reports the BBC.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  The nerve agent in various forms2.  How neurotransmitters work in our body normally to regulate muscle contraction3.  What happens to these neurotransmitters when affected by the Novichok nerve agent4.  What happens inside the body as a result of Novichok poisoningVOICEOVER (in English): "Novichok nerve agents may exist as liquids, in solid form or as an ultra-fine powder.""Novichok works by inhibiting an enzyme called acetylcholinesterase, which is involved in muscle movement.""Motor neurons release a neurotransmitter called acetylcholine, which tells muscles to contract.""Acetylcholinesterase removes the neurotransmitter, relaxing the muscle.""Novichok prevents acetylcholinesterase from relaxing the muscle, resulting in muscles contracting involuntarily and no longer functioning normally.""The effects are wide-ranging, but the most critical are the effects on lung and heart function. These include respiratory paralysis and cardiac arrest."SOURCES: The BBC, The Verge,The New York Times, Reuters,https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-43377698https://www.theverge.com/2018/7/4/17535024/novichok-nerve-agent-strikes-two-new-victims-in-the-ukhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/04/world/europe/salisbury-poison-skripal-amesbury.html?action=Click&amp;contentCollection=BreakingNews&amp;contentID=67253633&amp;pgtype=Homepagehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-poison-facts-factbox/factbox-what-do-we-know-and-do-not-know-about-the-novichok-poisonings-idUSKBN1JV1J7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/06/3647922/3647922_903789FE464F4DE7905CB8CAEB325C2D_180706_3647922_How_Russian_nerve_agent_Novichok_used_in_UK_pois_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FAB/B2F/FABB2F0E2FEE4677854E6E14EA734704_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Nerve agent, Novichok nerve agent, symptoms of nerve agent, how novichok nerve agent works, Russian Nerve agent]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647907</guid>
      <title>How will rescuers get trapped Thai soccer team out of cave?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwelve boys and their soccer coach were finally found nine days after going missing inside a northern Thailand cave, but the problem now is how to get them out.With most of the passageways inside Chiang Rai's complex Tham Luang cave system still underwater, there are four options to safely extract the trapped boys, reports the BBC.Rescuers are pumping water out of the cave to create walkable conditions, and have drained the first 1.5 kilometers. But the operation could be set back by heavy rains predicted in the coming days.Rising waters may force the team to dive to safety, donning full scuba masks and suits and being guided by experienced divers through the 5-hour journey with the help of guide ropes, according to the Guardian.But though this method is the fastest, it's also the most dangerous. The dive through narrow passageways under zero-visibility conditions is risky even for seasoned divers.One rescue diver has already died after delivering supplies to the trapped team.A third option being considered is drilling into the cave from above and pulling the boys out, but this is the least feasible since it requires a thorough survey of the cave system to know where to drill.If all else fails, officials say the boys and their coach have enough food and water to last them through the four-month wait for flood waters to recede, so they can walk out.For now, rescuers are keeping an eye on the team and monitoring their condition. A fiber optic cable is also being fitted so the boys can talk to their worried parents.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of water being pumped out of flooded cave2. Depiction of trapped boys diving out to safety3. Depiction of drilling into mountain to get trapped boys out4. Depiction of boys waiting for flood waters to recedeVOICEOVER (in English): "Rescuers are pumping water out of the cave to create walkable conditions, and have drained the first 1.5 kilometers. But the operation could be set back by heavy rains predicted in the coming days.""Rising waters may force the team to dive to safety. They would don full scuba masks and suits, and be helped by experienced divers and guide ropes during the 5-hour journey.""A third option being considered is drilling into the cave from above and pulling the boys out, but this is the least feasible since it requires a thorough survey of the cave system to know where to drill.""If all else fails, officials say the boys and their coach have enough food and water to last them through the four-month wait for flood waters to recede, at which point they could simply walk out."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardianhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-44691457https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/05/rescuers-draining-thai-cave-in-hope-football-team-can-walk-out-before-rains***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/06/3647907/3647907_DAA170AFE4DD482EB94DD12375806C13_180706_3647907_How_will_rescuers_get_trapped_Thai_soccer_team_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/041/655/041655FF76F24A9698244B947DD2C4DA_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, thai cave rescue, cave rescue, thailand cave, thai soccer team, boys trapped in cave, drilling, diving, cave diving, flooded cave, rescue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647436</guid>
      <title>How soccer players dive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSoccer players dive to gain an unfair advantage by falling to the ground and possibly faking an injury  all to give the impression that a foul has been committed.A 2009 study identified four distinct actions that may indicate a player is taking a dive. These are: Taking fully controlled strides before falling; clutching a part of the body where the player was not hit, such as when a player is kicked in the right leg, but clutches the left leg; taking extra rolls after falling and hitting the ground; and performing an exaggerated and unnatural gesture of raising the arms above the shoulders and extending the chest while falling, which researchers dubbed "the archer's bow."The 2009 study was published in the Springer Journal of Nonverbal Behavior by Paul Morris, an expert on the embodiment of emotions and intentions in the Department of Psychology at the University of Portsmouth. A separate study, led by Robbie Wilson of the University of Queensland, found that dives most often occur when a player is near the offensive goal or when a match is tied. Wilson's study found players dove more often when referees rewarded such behavior.Case in point: During this year's World Cup in Russia, Brazil's Neymar has found himself the subject of relentless mockery for his frequent flops. But with Brazil in the round of eight, what incentive does he have to stop?RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show the first indication of a dive, taking full strides before falling2. Show player clutching a part of the where the player was not hit3. Show player taking extra rolls after falling to the ground4. Show player gets tackled and VOICEOVER (in English): "A 2009 study identified four distinct actions that may indicate a player is taking a dive. These are: Taking fully controlled strides before falling""clutching a part of the body where the player was not hit, such as when a player is kicked in the right leg, but clutches the left leg""taking extra rolls after falling and hitting the ground""and performing an exaggerated and unnatural gesture of raising the arms above the shoulders and extending the chest while falling, which researchers dubbed "the archer's bow."SOURCES: SCIENCE DAILYhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2009/09/090915202242.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 07:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/06/3647436/3647436_684FADB9A3ED4EFDACFD6C9D851D5577_180706_3647436_How_soccer_players_dive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/978/600/978600BC0BEF4CC5A2C4BFBB9BCCBDED_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, …]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649656</guid>
      <title>Four boys rescued from Thai cave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOperations to extract the remaining eight boys and their coach from the flooded Thai cave system have resumed, after the first four were safely taken out.CNN reports that 18 cave-diving experts retrieved the trapped boys on Sunday, guiding them through the cave system, which had been installed with guide ropes and air tanks every 25 meters.Wearing full scuba masks, wetsuits, and helmets, each boy is escorted by two divers. He is tethered to the diver in front, who is also in charge of his air supply.According to the Chiang Rai governor, the first boy emerged from the cave at 5:40 p.m., with the second one following 10 minutes later. Two more boys came out at 7:40 p.m. and 7:50 p.m.All four were transported by helicopter to a nearby hospital, where they are currently being monitored.Oxygen tanks had to be refilled before rescuers resumed the next phase, which is currently being threatened by heavy rainfall that's expected to continue in the coming days.Divers are currently on a race against water and time to get the boys out. Monsoon season is only just beginning, which means flooding will likely worsen and hamper efforts to pump water out of the cave.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of rescue divers inside cave2. Depiction of divers escorting boy through flooded cave3. Depiction of four boys emerging from cave4. Depiction of heavy rains forecast in coming daysVOICEOVER (in English): "Eighteen cave diving experts retrieved the trapped boys on Sunday, guiding them through the cave system, which had been installed with guide ropes and air tanks every 25 meters.""Wearing full scuba masks, wetsuits, and helmets, each boy is escorted by two divers. He is tethered to the diver in front, who is also in charge of his air supply.""According to the Chiang Rai governor, the first boy emerged from the cave at 5:40 p.m., with the second one following 10 minutes later. Two more boys came out at 7:40 and 7:50 p.m.""Oxygen tanks had to be refilled before rescuers resumed the next phase, which is currently being threatened by heavy rainfall that's expected to continue in the coming days."SOURCES: CNN, BBC, The Nationhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/08/asia/thai-cave-rescue-mission-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-44760896http://www.nationmultimedia.com/detail/national/30349608***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/09/3649656/3649656_9938ACE9F4D240DB95B4AA7E7768FEB0_180709_3649656_Four_boys_rescued_from_Thai_cave_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D2D/5A9/D2D5A98C73EB4993AB2B35E742CCFDF0_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, thai cave rescue, thai cave, trapped boys, cave diving, thai soccer team, wild boars, chiang rai cave rescue, tham luang cave, rescue mission, rain, monsoon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649647</guid>
      <title>How toxic algae is impacting Florida's coastline.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFlorida's coastline is being threatened by toxic algal bloom, and it seems to be getting worse every year, the Tampa Bay Times reports.An algal bloom is a "rapid increase of the population of algae" in a relatively short period of time and can take place on freshwater or marine water systems, reports CNBA.Algal bloom is caused by the overabundance of nutrients nitrogen and phosphorus. This nutrients typically come from rainfall and waste water outflows.The nutrients combined with the temperature of the sea, sunlight and water movement can work to trigger an algal bloom.According to the EPA, the toxic blooms hurt marine life by blocking out sunlight as well as creating toxins that hurt small fish and shellfish after they consume it.Not only do the algae hurt the environment, they also end up creating dead zones in the water where "aquatic life can no longer survive" because of the lack of oxygen, forcing marine life to either leave the area or die. Environmentalists are urging the state government to do more to "address its polluted water", reports Tampa Bay Times.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  How algal bloom is caused.2. What factors play a part in causing the algal bloom.3. How toxic algal bloom affects marine life.4. How the toxic bloom affects the area around it and force marine life to either migrate or die.VOICEOVER (in English): "Algal bloom is caused by the overabundance of nutrients nitrogen and phosphorus. This nutrients typically come from rainfall and waste water outflows.""The nutrients combined with the temperature of the sea, sunlight and water movement can work to trigger an algal bloom.""According to the EPA, the toxic blooms hurt marine life by blocking out sunlight as well as creating toxins that hurt small fish and shellfish after they consume it.""Not only do the algae hurt the environment, they also end up creating dead zones in the water where 'aquatic life can no longer survive' because of the lack of oxygen, forcing marine life to either leave the area or die." SOURCES: EPA, CBS News, Tampa Bay Times, Center for Earth and Environmental Science(CEES),https://www.epa.gov/nutrientpollution/effects-environmenthttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/florida-lake-okeechobee-toxic-algae-problem-2018-07-06/http://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2018/06/30/its-kind-of-horrific-toxic-algae-bloom-threatens-florida-coasts-again/https://cees.iupui.edu/research/algal-toxicology/bloomfactors***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/09/3649647/3649647_7A6EB769DC1F46B0B1EA6B1B3F79DE60_180709_3649647_How_toxic_algae_is_impacting_Florida_s_coastline_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/376/037/37603716ED534D3F86AF429BCC0A3F7A_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, US, Marine life, ecosystem, algae, toxic algae, algal blooms, algae bloom]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649643</guid>
      <title>Spiders can fly through the air using electricity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpiders have been known to release long strands of silk to carry them up to 2.5 miles up in the air and over a thousand miles out to sea  a process known as ballooning, according to a new study published in the journal Current Biology.The common belief is that the strands catch on to the wind and help generate lift. But since it doesn't explain how spiders balloon even on days with light wind, another theory emerged: electrostatic repulsion.When spiders release their silk, it picks up a negative charge, which repels the earth's similarly negatively charged surface and creates enough force to propel them into the air.The University of Bristol study tested the theory by putting the arachnids on vertical cardboard strips in a plastic box, and then generated an artificial electric field.Sensory hairs on the spiders' feet detected the charge and prompted them to start ballooning. They were able to take-off despite no wind, but dropped when the electric field was turned off.While the study proved that spiders can fly using electricity alone, scientists believe air currents may still play a role in it. Previous studies have recorded the crawlers raising their front legs into the wind, possibly to determine how strong it is.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of spiders ballooning2. Depiction of common wind theory3. Depiction of lab experiment involving electrostatic repulsion4. Depiction of spiders ballooning using  only electricityVOICEOVER (in English): "Spiders have been known to release long strands of silk to carry them up to 2.5 miles up in the air and over a thousand miles out to sea  a process known as ballooning.""The common belief is that the strands catch on to the wind and help generate lift. But since it doesn't explain how spiders balloon even on days with light wind, another theory emerged: electrostatic repulsion.""A University of Bristol study tested the theory by putting the arachnids on vertical cardboard strips in a plastic box, and then generated an artificial electric field.""Sensory hairs on the spiders' feet detected the charge and prompted them to start ballooning. They were able to take-off despite no wind, but dropped when the electric field was turned off."SOURCES: Current Biology, The Atlantichttps://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(18)30693-6?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0960982218306936%3Fshowall%3Dtruehttps://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2018/07/the-electric-flight-of-spiders/564437/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/09/3649643/3649643_88EC894E11FE4DE2A4B0634EC47EA1DF_180709_3649643_Spiders_can_fly_through_the_air_using_electricit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/8A0/F47/8A0F475E05F5480E8181866B59046AA8_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, spider, spiders, flying spider, ballooning spider, ballooning, electrostatic force, wind, electricity, animal science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649417</guid>
      <title>Baidu debuts new self-driving buses.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's Baidu has announced they have begun production of driverless buses in partnership with Chinese manufacturer King Long, reports Xinhua.Baidu released video footage of the bus, called Apolong, which shows it to be much smaller than a regular sized bus.The buses will first be put to use in cities such as Beijing, Shenzhen and even Tokyo, reports the South China Morning Post.According to Xinhua, the bus will initially be used in tourist spots, airports and other enclosed areas.Local reports say Apolong is capable of Level 4 operations, which means it is able to drive without any drivers in specific areas and has 14 seats inside it with no steering wheel.The autonomous vehicle will be powered by Baidu's own open autonomous driving platform.Baidu says they will be working with Mobileye, a subsidiary of Intel, to incorporate the Responsible, Sensitive Safety (RSS) driving model to its buses which would "mimic human judgment" while it's driving. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Driverless bus in the production line.2. Comparing a driverless bus to a regular-sized bus.3. Inside of the driverless bus.4. How the safety model RSS will be incorporated into the self-driving bus.VOICEOVER (in English): "Xinhua reports China's Baidu has announced they have begun production of driverless buses.""Baidu released video footage of the bus, called Apolong, which shows it to be much smaller than a regular sized bus.""Local reports say Apolong is capable of Level 4 operations, which means it is able to drive without any drivers in specific areas and has 14 seats inside it with no steering wheel.""Baidu says they will be working with a subsidiary of Intel to incorporate the Responsible, Sensitive Safety driving model to its buses, which would 'mimic human judgment' while it's driving."SOURCES: XinhuaNet, Bloomberg, South China Morning Post, The Verge, Engadget, TechCrunch,http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-07/04/c_137301071.htmhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-04/baidu-unveils-ai-chip-as-it-revs-up-self-driving-bus-productionhttps://www.scmp.com/tech/article/2153694/baidu-says-first-100-self-driving-buses-have-rolled-production-lineshttps://www.theverge.com/2018/7/4/17534874/baidu-autonomous-buses-japan-ai-self-driving-apollo-apolonghttps://www.engadget.com/2018/07/04/baidu-self-driving-buses-japan/https://techcrunch.com/2018/07/03/baidu-just-made-its-100th-autonomous-bus-ahead-of-commercial-launch-in-china/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 08:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/09/3649417/3649417_688A07822DAA4F0896BF47ECD4C3B245_180709_3649417_Baidu_debuts_new_self_driving_buses__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/CC3/D59/CC3D59E32E4D488BBB1A6DF5D4DDE618_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, China, Self-driving buses, buses, Baidu, driverless buses, Apolong, RSS driving model]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650478</guid>
      <title>Modified polio virus used to treat brain cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new experimental treatment is using a modified version of a once-dreaded virus to fight against a deadly form of brain cancer.Glioblastoma is a type of cancer that occurs in the brain or spinal cord that is typically treated using surgery, radiation therapy, or chemotherapy. It is an aggressive disease, with only a 12 to 18 month prognosis for those with grade 4 tumors.According to a study published in the New England Journal of Medicine, Duke University researchers removed genetic code from the polio virus and replaced it with DNA from the rhinovirus, which causes the common cold.The modified virus is then injected directly into the tumors of glioblastoma patients through a catheter.Instead of replicating itself, it attaches to receptors on the surface of the cancer cells, infecting them and prompting the body's immune system to attack.Of the 61 glioblastoma patients treated using the re-engineered virus, 21% are                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         still alive three years later, compared to only 4% for those who underwent conventional treatment.The experimental treatment, like many immunotherapies, had varied, sometimes dramatic effects on the subjects.Scientists are still figuring out how to get the virus to produce the exact same results in different people, but are confident that it can be done.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of polio virus being modified2. Depiction of modified polio virus injected directly into brain tumor3. Depiction of virus effects on glioblastoma4. Depiction of results in patientsVOICEOVER (in English): "Duke University researchers removed genetic code from the polio virus and replaced it with DNA from the rhinovirus, which causes the common cold.""The modified virus is injected directly into tumors of glioblastoma patients through a catheter.""Instead of replicating itself, it attaches to receptors on the surface of the cancer cells, infecting them and prompting the body's immune system to attack.""Of the 61 glioblastoma patients treated using the re-engineered virus, 21% are                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         still alive three years later, compared to only 4% for those who underwent conventional treatment."SOURCES: New England Journal of Medicine, Reutershttps://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1716435https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cancer-vaccine-brain/modified-polio-vaccine-extends-lives-in-u-s-brain-cancer-study-idUSKBN1JM18J***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 14:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/10/3650478/3650478_4E95EF63AE39442599D4F3A62E883DC3_180710_3650478_Modified_polio_virus_used_to_treat_brain_cancer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/3F6/B4A/3F6B4A4ECDCB4351B0A7E70DCB2AD4D1_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, brain tumor, cancer, cancer cure, cure for cancer, glioblastoma, brain cancer, glioma, polio virus, polio, cancer treatment, experimental treatment, duke university]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650397</guid>
      <title>China found using banned chemical CFCs.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA home insulation chemical used extensively throughout China may be damaging the earth's ozone layer, reports the BBC.The chemical, CFC-11, was completely banned eight years ago because it resulted in a "massive rise in emissions of a gas" to the earth's protective layer.According to the BBC, around 70% of sales in China used the illegal gas to insulate their houses because it is "better quality and much cheaper" than other alternatives.CFC-11 is made from chemicals such as carbon, chlorine and fluorine.CFC-11, or trichlorofluoromethane, was mainly used as a refrigerant and is a colorless liquid which is quick to escape containers even if it is packed tightly.When CFCs are exposed to UV rays in the atmosphere, the molecule breaks down into individual atoms which includes chlorine.The oxygen atoms in the ozone then react with the chlorine atom and 'rips apart' the ozone molecule, which damages the ozone layer.Because of the sheer amount of CFC-11 being used, this could have the potential to "reverse the healing that is starting to take place in the ozone layer."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Atoms used to create CFC-11.2. How CFC-11 molecule exists and is released into the atmosphere.3. UV rays causes the chlorine to separate from the rest of the molecule.4. How holes appear in the ozone layer.VOICEOVER (in English): "CFC-11 is made from chemicals such as carbon, chlorine and fluorine. ""CFC-11, or trichlorofluoromethane, was mainly used as a refrigerant and is a colorless liquid which is quick to escape containers even if it is packed tightly.""When CFCs are exposed to UV rays in the atmosphere, the molecule breaks down into individual atoms which includes chlorine.""The oxygen atoms in the ozone then react with the chlorine atom and 'rips apart' the ozone molecule, which damages the ozone layer."SOURCES: BBC, EIA,New York Times, National Geographic, https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-44138984https://eia-global.org/reports/20180709-blowing-it-illegal-production-and-use-of-banned-cfc-11-in-chinas-foam-blowing-industryhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/24/world/asia/china-ozone-cfc.htmlhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aU6pxSNDPhs***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 12:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/10/3650397/3650397_4AAEB216F77C466DBEA34500EAA58B93_180710_3650397_China_found_using_banned_chemical_CFCs__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/65A/005/65A00506B2934F72A806F9A3E2756A50_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, China, CFC-11, banned chemicals, CFC emissions,  gas emissions,  Earth's ozone layer, ozone layer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650250</guid>
      <title>Thai tourist boat accident kills 42</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDozens are dead and several others missing after a tourist boat capsized off southern Thailand in one of the country's worst sea disasters.Reuters reports that the double decker cruise ship Phoenix had been off the coast of Phuket on Thursday, carrying 89 tourists mostly from mainland China, and 12 Thai crew and tour guides.The ship encountered bad weather at sea, and reportedly capsized after being hit by a 16-foot wave.More than 40 passengers and crew managed to jump from the sinking boat and have since been rescued.Divers sent to check the sunken vessel found that many had been trapped in the lower deck. As of Monday, 42 are confirmed dead, and five are still missing, according to the provincial governor of Phuket.The Phoenix and several other boats were out at sea despite severe weather warnings, prompting authorities to investigate.Its captain has since been charged for negligence, along with the captain of another boat, Serenita, which also overturned around the same time but did not result in any casualties.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of tour boat location and number of passengers2. Depiction of tour boat being hit by 16-foot wave3. Depiction of capsized tour boat, survivors4. Depiction of sunken vessel, number of dead and missingVOICEOVER (in English): "The double decker cruise ship Phoenix had been off the coast of Phuket on Thursday, carrying 89 tourists mostly from mainland China, and 12 Thai crew and tour guides.""The ship encountered bad weather at sea, and reportedly capsized after being hit by a 16-foot wave.""More than 40 passengers and crew managed to jump from the sinking boat and have since been rescued.""Divers sent to check the sunken vessel found that many had been trapped in the lower deck. As of Monday, 42 are confirmed dead, and five are still missing."SOURCES: Reuters, BBC, Xinhuahttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-accident-boat/thai-minister-blames-tour-operators-for-boat-disaster-11-still-missing-idUSKBN1JZ0FShttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-44728478http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-07/09/c_137311888.htmhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-07/08/c_137310539.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 09:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/10/3650250/3650250_0AEF0610B6A84C239D2F8E7F3CD3EB15_180710_3650250_Thai_tourist_boat_accident_kills_42_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F5D/F81/F5DF8197621B44AFA14E9ADD2AA2E596_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, thailand boat disaster, thailand boat accident, thai boat rescue, tour boat disaster, tour boat sinking, tour boat accident, phoenix, phuket, chinese tourists, thai tourism, storm warning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651124</guid>
      <title>How are lip fillers removed?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSocialite Kylie Jenner recently announced that she'd had her lip fillers removed, prompting many to wonder how this can be done.According to cosmetic surgeons interviewed by the Irish Examiner, People, and several other publications, lip fillers are made of hyaluronic acid, a substance found naturally in the body, typically in the skin, hair follicles, eyes, gums, and joints.The fillers are temporary, and need maintenance every six to eight months. Otherwise, the hyaluronic acid will dissolve and wear off, which is the simplest way to undo them.Another way to get rid of them is by injecting hyaluronidase, an enzyme that speeds up the filler's breakdown and helps it dissolve in about 48 hours.The procedure is completely safe if done by a professional. There may be side effects from the needle, but not so much from the enzyme and filler, which are both harmless substances. In most cases, the lip goes back to how it was pre-filler.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of main component of lip fillers 2. Depiction of lip fillers naturally dissolving without maintenance3. Depiction of hyaluronidase enzyme dissolving filler fasterVOICEOVER (in English): "Lip fillers are made of hyaluronic acid, a substance found naturally in the body, typically in the skin, hair follicles, eyes, gums, and joints.""The fillers are temporary, and need maintenance every six to eight months. Otherwise, the hyaluronic acid will dissolve and wear off, which is the simplest way to undo them.""Another way to remove them is by injecting hyaluronidase, an enzyme that speeds up the filler's breakdown and helps it dissolve in about 48 hours."SOURCES: Irish Examiner, Clinic Doctor Frodo Gaymans, Peoplehttps://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/lifestyle/healthandlife/inspired-by-kylie-jenners-new-look-this-is-how-lip-fillers-are-removed-854022.htmlhttps://www.dokterfrodo.nl/en/hyaluronic-acidhttps://people.com/health/kylie-jenner-removing-lip-fillers-plastic-surgeon-explainer/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 10:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/11/3651124/3651124_B92B17C8A88248CC960F8F3DF92EDE6F_180711_3651124_How_are_lip_fillers_removed__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/6F0/36E/6F036ECA92B345C091693D45FF97B00E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, lip fillers, kylie jenner, kardashians, fillers, lip procedure, full lips, duck lips, temporary filler, plastic surgery, cosmetic procedure, hyaluronic acid, hyaluronidase]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651071</guid>
      <title>Facebook's facial recognition tools raise privacy concerns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSocial media giant Facebook is pushing facial recognition as a way to safeguard online identities, but is instead raising concerns over privacy in several sectors.According to the New York Times, Facebook's facial recognition technology works by analyzing users' photos and generating a string of numbers called a 'template' that's unique to each user. When photos and videos are posted to the social network, the unnamed faces are scanned and matched to names and templates stored in a database.A Facebook spokeswoman claims that if the system cannot find a match, it doesn't identify the unknown face, adding that the facial data is deleted immediately.While it's possible to turn facial recognition off, critics still find the software problematic, since it scans every image- even of people who have opted out of the feature.Facebook has also applied for several patents that use the technology. One aims to tailor ads by analyzing users' facial expressions via their phone camera. Another checks shoppers' online profile and uses it to determine a 'trust level'.This Big Brother-style approach to facial data is worrisome, especially since Facebook doesn't exactly have the best track record for honesty, or for keeping user data safe.Fortunately, a lot of groups recognize this and are moving to protect biometric data. The company is facing a class-action suit filed by Illinois consumers for violating a state biometric privacy law, and could stand to lose money and what's left of their reputation if it moves forward.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Facebook generating unique user facial template2. Depiction of Facebook matching faces to names and facial template in database3. Depiction of Facebook deleting facial scans for unmatched photos4. Depiction of Facebook's facial recognition patentsVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook's facial recognition technology works by analyzing users' photos and generating a string of numbers called a 'template' that's unique to each user.""When photos and videos are posted to the social network, the unnamed faces are scanned and matched to names and templates stored in a database.""A Facebook spokeswoman claims that if the system cannot find a match, it doesn't identify the unknown face, adding that the facial data is deleted immediately.""Facebook has also applied for several patents that use the technology. One aims to tailor ads by analyzing users' facial expressions via their phone camera. Another checks shoppers' online profile and uses it to determine a 'trust level'."SOURCES: New York Times, CB Insightshttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/09/technology/facebook-facial-recognition-privacy.htmlhttps://www.cbinsights.com/research/facebook-emotion-patents-analysis/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/11/3651071/3651071_FCD347DD933A4E0B8FFDE37CFE494B45_180711_3651071_Facebook_s_facial_recognition_tools_raise_privac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DD4/885/DD4885E49A8643F0BAB88749E7AB97A5_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  facebook, facial recognition, facial recognition tech, facial scan, big brother, photo tagging, facebook settings, privacy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651059</guid>
      <title>Boys rescued from Thai cave may face "cave disease"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAll the boys and their coach have been rescued from the cave in Thailand, but they may have to face another challenge: cave disease.Cave disease, also called histoplasmosis, is a fungus infection that is "aided by nutrients it gets from bat and bird droppings," reports ABC News.The disease is reportedly transmitted via air, with the fungus becoming airborne through its spores that are so tiny they are "undetectable to the human eye."However, the disease itself is not contagious from person to person.According to the CDC, any movement that disturbs the ground like digging or even walking can spread the disease.Histoplasmosis may affect those with a weaker immune system, causing the disease to "spread from the lungs to … the brain."Those who don't get sick may appear to have a flu, or have body aches and chest pain.One way to prevent "cave disease" is to avoid walking into any caves where bird and bat droppings are suspected to be there.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How histoplasmosis occurs.2. How histoplasmosis is transmitted.3. How histoplasmosis may be spread.4. Symptoms of histoplasmosis. VOICEOVER (in English): "ABC News reports cave disease, also called histoplasmosis, is a fungus infection which is 'aided by nutrients it gets from bat and bird droppings.'""The disease is reportedly transmitted via air, with the fungus becoming airborne through its spores that are so tiny they are 'undetectable to the human eye.'""According to the CDC, any movement that disturbs the ground like digging or even walking can spread the disease.""However, the disease itself is not contagious from person to person.""Histoplasmosis may affect those with a weaker immune system, causing the disease to 'spread from the lungs to...the brain.""Those who don't get sick may appear to have a flu, or have body aches and chest pain."SOURCES: ABC News, LA Times, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, https://abcnews.go.com/Health/boys-trapped-thailand-cave-face-unusual-disease/story?id=56454631http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-thai-cave-boys-health-20180709-story.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/fungal/diseases/histoplasmosis/causes.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 09:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/11/3651059/3651059_383AA54E39034588B8F1913670151B0D_180711_3651059_Boys_rescued_from_Thai_cave_may_face__cave_disea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/CBE/6CD/CBE6CD394AA942219F583A072E7F5737_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, thai cave, boys trapped in thai cave, thailand cave rescue, unusual disease, cave disease, histoplasmosis, health risks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651995</guid>
      <title>A rare sexually transmitted disease may turn into a "superbug"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMycoplasma Genitalium, or MG, is a rare sexually transmitted infection that may become a "superbug" if it is not taken seriously, reports the BBC.MG is a bacterium which can live in the urinary and genital tracts of the body, causing a burning sensation during urination or pain during sex, reports Newsweek.MG causes inflammation of the urethra in men, and inflammation of the reproductive organs, such as the womb and the fallopian tubes, for women, the BBC reports.In the worse case scenario, the infection may cause infertility for women.The infection is often misdiagnosed as chlamydia and treated as such, which is why the infection is currently "developing resistance" to some of the antibiotics used to treat it.The British Association of Sexual Health and HIV issued guidelines saying the disease may be treated with the antibiotic doxycycline for seven days, followed by azithromycin.Dr. Peter Greenhouse, a member of the association, is urging the public to take precautions and use condoms to prevent the spread of Mycoplasma Genitalium, reports the BBC.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The MG bacterium in the urinary and genital tracts2. Where the MG bacterium causes inflammation for the male and female body3. Showing the MG bacterium as being misdiagnosed as chlamydia4. Showing how the disease may be treatedVOICEOVER (in English): "Newsweek reports MG is a bacterium which can live in the urinary and genital tracts of the body, causing a burning sensation during urination or pain during sex.""The BBC reports MG causes inflammation of the urethra in men, and inflammation of the reproductive organs, such as the womb and the fallopian tubes, for women.""The infection is often misdiagnosed as chlamydia and treated as such, which is why the infection is currently 'developing resistance' to some of the antibiotics used to treat it.""The British Association of Sexual Health and HIV issued guidelines saying the disease may be treated with the antibiotic doxycycline for seven days, followed by azithromycin."SOURCES: The BBC, British Association of Sexual Health and HIV(BASHH)Guidelines, Newsweek, RT, https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-44777938https://www.bashhguidelines.org/media/1182/bashh-mgen-guideline-2018_draft-for-consultation.pdfhttp://www.newsweek.com/mycoplasma-genitalium-sexually-transmitted-infection-superbug-1017524https://www.rt.com/uk/432650-sti-superbug-sexual-health/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 12:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/12/3651995/3651995_6E63A88F39534375965E2A09180081CC_180712_3651995_A_rare_sexually_transmitted_disease_may_turn_int_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1C0/338/1C03388D5F1D469F9B6D1C14103B554E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, UK, MG, rare sex disease, sex infection, STD, mycoplasma genitalium, superbug]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651922</guid>
      <title>How plastic straw ban negatively affects people with disabilities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe recent crackdown down on plastic straws may be good for the environment, but it's not doing the disabled any favors.CNN reports that single-use plastics like straws have been facing a growing backlash because of the harm it causes the environment. As a result, many cities and establishments have banned or are planning to ban their use entirely  a decision applauded by many.But the ban will also negatively affect people living with physical disabilities, for whom plastic straws are a necessity.According to NPR, current alternatives are not as efficient as plastic. Paper straws, for example, dissolve in hot drinks. Metal ones can get too hot or cold, and like bamboo and glass, are hard and inflexible  which poses a safety risk.Going without straws is equally problematic, especially for those struggling with mobility, and may cause choking or leak liquid into the lungs.Seattle's new plastic straw ban does exempt people with medical conditions who need the disposable straws, but most places aren't aware of this.It's also been suggested that instead of an outright ban, companies should come up greener alternatives that will work for everyone, including the disabled.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of straws contributing to plastic pollution2. Depiction of plastic straws being banned3. Depiction of people with disabilities relying on plastic straws4. Depiction of why alternative straws not as efficient as plastic5. Depiction of potential hazards of disabled drinking without strawsVOICEOVER (in English): "Single-use plastics like straws have been facing a growing backlash because of the harm it causes the environment.""As a result, many cities and establishments have banned or are planning to ban their use entirely  a decision applauded by many.""But the ban will also negatively affect people living with physical disabilities, for whom plastic straws are a necessity.""Current alternatives are not as efficient as plastic. Paper straws, for example, dissolve in hot drinks. Metal ones can get too hot or cold, and like bamboo and glass, are hard and inflexible  which poses a safety risk.""Going without straws is equally problematic, especially for those struggling with mobility, and may cause choking or leak liquid into the lungs."SOURCES: CNN, NPRhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/11/health/plastic-straw-bans-disabled-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/07/11/627773979/why-people-with-disabilities-want-bans-on-plastic-straws-to-be-more-flexible***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 10:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/12/3651922/3651922_6578C8E3B12D453BBD0C45D1469F1F4B_180712_3651922_How_plastic_straw_ban_negatively_affects_people__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BC1/A20/BC1A20FE09294A28B42A168AF1E16D15_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, plastic straw ban, disabled, disability, plastic straw, straw ban, plastic ban, people with disabilities, plastic pollution, single use plastics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651736</guid>
      <title>Timeline of how Thailand soccer team and coach were rescued</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA dozen boys and their soccer coach went missing on June 23 after entering the Tham Luang Nang Nom cave system in Thailand's northern Chiang Rai province, prompting a rescue mission that lasted almost an entire month.The boys and their coach were not located until July 2 after having been missing for nine days. The rescue operation ended on July 10 after all 12 boys and their coach has been freed.The following animation shows a rough timeline of how the group was found and rescued from the flooded cave.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Soccer team enters the cave2. Authorities find handprints and footprints at a T-junction inside the cave3. Thai Royal Navy SEAL divers launch rescue operation4. Heavy rains continue, causing flood waters to rise5. Pump is brought in to extract water6. Command center erected at entrance of cave7. Soccer team and coach found8. Extraction of soccer team and coachVOICEOVER (in English): "A dozen boys aged 11 to 16 and their 25-year-old soccer coach went missing on June 23 after entering the Tham Luang Nang Non cave system in northern Thailand.""Authorities discovered footprints and handprints at a T-junction within the cave on June 24. They also found backpacks the group had left behind.""On June 25, Thai Royal Navy SEAL divers launched a rescue operation, bringing with them oxygen tanks and supplies.""However, heavy rains caused flood waters in the cave system to rise, forcing rescuers back.""Operations were put on hold on June 28, as a pump was brought in to begin extracting water.""On July 1, a command center was set up at the entrance of the cave, with oxygen tanks and supplies placed every 25 meters to aid the divers in their rescue efforts.""The team of soccer players and their coach were found on July 2 in an enclave that was some 400 meters behind Pattaya Beach and 800 to 1,000 meters underground.""July 8, rescuers began extracting boys from the cave, with the first four boys emerging within 11 hours. Four more boys were rescued on July 9, and the remaining four boys along with their coach were freed on July 10."SOURCES: Fortune, Business Insiderhttp://fortune.com/2018/07/10/thai-cave-rescue-operation-timeline/http://uk.businessinsider.com/thai-cave-rescue-timeline-how-it-unfolded-2018-7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/12/3651736/3651736_2B7C4F1BC03447B3A9A25786B00B600F_180712_3651736_Timeline_of_how_Thailand_soccer_team_and_coach_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/B56/2B8/B562B891914643CC90E0AF62286A0C8E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Thailand cave rescue, Thailand soccer team, Thai Navy Royal SEAL, soccer team lost, soccer team found, Chiang Rai, Tham Luang cave]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652788</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover the world's oldest biological color</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a recent study from Australian National University, pink pigment was found in the marine black shales deep beneath the Sahara desert in Africa.The researchers reportedly crushed the rocks into powder then extracted and analysed the molecules of ancient organisms inside those rocks.The bright pink pigment discovered was actually the "molecular fossils" of chlorophyll produced by ancient photosynthetic organisms living in an ancient ocean, which no longer exists.The fossils itself range from "blood red to deep purple" in concentrated form, and turn bright pink when it's diluted.A researcher involved in the study commented saying after analyzing the ancient pigment, confirm tiny cyanobacteria used to live in the ocean a billion years ago.Ancient oceans filled with cyanobacteria started to disappear around 650 million years ago, which is when algae started to spread rapidly which helped the ecosystems to evolve.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show where the pink pigment was found.2. Showing the pink pigment with the chlorophyll we know of today.3. Showing the cyanobacteria which used to be common in the past.4. Showing the algae started spreading rapidly in the ocean.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a recent study from Australian National University, pink pigment was found in the marine black shales deep beneath the Sahara desert in Africa.""The bright pink pigment discovered was actually the 'molecular fossils' of chlorophyll produced by ancient photosynthetic organisms living in an ancient ocean, which no longer exists.""A researcher involved in the study commented saying after analyzing the ancient pigment, confirm tiny cyanobacteria used to live in the ocean a billion years ago.""Ancient oceans filled with cyanobacteria started to disappear around 650 million years ago, which is when algae started to spread rapidly which helped the ecosystems to evolve."SOURCES:Fox News, Australian National University (ANU), CNN,  The Guardianhttp://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/07/11/scientists-reveal-have-found-worlds-oldest-color.htmlhttp://www.anu.edu.au/news/all-news/anu-scientists-discover-the-world%E2%80%99s-oldest-colourshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/10/health/oldest-color-pink-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jul/09/scientists-discover-worlds-oldest-colour-bright-pink-sahara***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 11:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/13/3652788/3652788_43EE415080724CD78B12545CA6342CF1_180713_3652788_Scientists_discover_the_world_s_oldest_biologica_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FC8/211/FC821171FED84B0E802087FD1455FA25_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Scientists, color,earth, bright pink, oldest color, Sahara desert, ancient rocks,cyanobacteria, pink pigment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652499</guid>
      <title>China to use birdlike drones to surveil people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has started using birdlike drones to monitor everyday civilians, reports The South China Morning Post.The Chinese government has reportedly sent the "dove" drones to at least five different provinces across China, especially to Xinjiang, which is home to a large Muslim population.These robotic doves look so authentic when they fly high in the sky, that even real doves start flying with them. The robotic drone mimics the flapping motion of a dove and would be able to 'evade human detection, The South Morning Post reports.The robot doves may even be camouflaged with feathers to further "distort radar signals."The interior of the robotic dove contains mechanisms such as a GPS antenna, a Data link antenna, a battery, an HD camera, flapping mechanism, and a flight control system.The project, code-named "Dove", is being led by a team of researchers who conducted various experiments such as flying the dove drones over a flock of sheep, who paid no attention to the drones above.One of the researchers of the project told the South China Morning Post technology has the potential to be used not only for military purposes but also for "disaster relief and emergency response."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show the robotic drone flying in the sky and being joined by actual birds.2. Show how realistic the robotic dove looks and may even bypass radars if it is in camouflage. 3. Show the interior of the robotic dove.4. Showing the robotic dove watching over a flock of sheep without them ever noticing.VOICEOVER (in English): "These robotic doves look so authentic when they fly high in the sky, that even real doves start flying with them."The South China Morning Post reports the robotic drone mimics the flapping motion of a dove and would be able to 'evade human detection.""The robot doves may even be camouflaged with feathers to further 'distort radar signals'""The interior of the robotic dove contains mechanisms such as a GPS antenna, a Data link antenna, a battery, an HD camera, flapping mechanism, and a flight control system.""The project, code-named 'Dove', is being led by a team of researchers who conducted various experiments such as flying the dove drones over a flock of sheep, who paid no attention to the drones above."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, Newsweek, Defense Aviation Post, http://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2152027/china-takes-surveillance-new-heights-flock-robotic-doves-do-theyhttp://www.newsweek.com/china-military-drone-birds-surveillance-drones-993034https://defenceaviationpost.com/gone-to-the-birds-china-has-lifelike-dove-surveillance-drones/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 06:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/13/3652499/3652499_82191797508F4FA3B51E763DD0CB2EBD_180713_3652499_China_to_use_birdlike_drones_to_surveil_people_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D71/A0D/D71A0D20B8F64F2D916257E081A63246_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China, Surveillance, china surveillance, bird drone, robotic drone,robotic birds,  robotic dove, spy birds, drone surveillance, birdlike drones, china surveillance system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652363</guid>
      <title>Car vibrations may be making you sleepier</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that feeling drowsy behind the wheel may not always be due to tiredness or lack of sleep- turns out it's your car.The Transport Accident Commission of Victoria estimates that about 20% of fatal car crashes in Australia are caused by driver fatigue.A growing body of evidence suggests that gentle vibrations made by car seats during a drive can lull the brain and body and contribute to feelings of sleepiness.To test the theory, a study from Melbourne's RMIT University hooked volunteers to a virtual driving simulator and tested them once with low frequency 4 to 7 hertz vibrations, and once without.Volunteers showed signs of drowsiness within 15 minutes of the vibrations, as indicated by their heart variability. It became significant at 30 minutes, with participants becoming sleepier until the end of the 60-minute test.Researchers believe one explanation could be that the brain becomes synchronized with the vibrations and enters the early stages of sleep.It's also been suggested that some frequencies may keep people awake instead of lulling them to sleep. But to harness these "good vibrations", more work is needed to examine a wider range of frequencies.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of driver fatigue 2. Depiction of car vibrations causing drowsiness3. Depiction of driving simulation with and without vibrations4. Depiction of simulation test resultsVOICEOVER (in English): "The Transport Accident Commission of Victoria estimates that about 20% of fatal car crashes in Australia are caused by driver fatigue.""A growing body of evidence suggests that gentle vibrations made by car seats during a drive can lull the brain and body and contribute to feelings of sleepiness.""To test the theory, an RMIT University study hooked volunteers to a virtual driving simulator and tested them once with low frequency 4 to 7 hertz vibrations, and once without.""Volunteers showed signs of drowsiness within 15 minutes of the vibrations, as indicated by their heart variability. It became significant at 30 minutes, with participants becoming sleepier until the end of the 60-minute test."SOURCES: RMIT University, Ergonomics, Victoria Transport Accident Commission https://www.rmit.edu.au/news/all-news/2018/jul/vibrations-cars-drivers-sleepyhttps://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/00140139.2018.1482373http://www.tac.vic.gov.au/road-safety/statistics/summaries/fatigue-statistics***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/13/3652363/3652363_39BA10737CAE427AA6DBBA72A057A07A_180713_3652363_Car_vibrations_may_be_making_you_sleepier_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/91D/B82/91DB822A239E40F6AF3187D30ADCF5B2_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, snooze mobile, sleepy driver, car drowsiness, car sleepiness, car vibrations, drowsy driving, why driving makes you sleepy, vibrations, car accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3654633</guid>
      <title>Seat standards may be coming to U.S. airlines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAirline seat sizes may be getting regulated, after years of shrinking legroom, passenger complaints, and safety concerns.Non-profit group Flyer Rights claims plane seats have been narrowing since the early 2000s. Seat width has gone from 18.5 to 17 inches, while the distance between seat rows have gone down to between 28 and 31 inches from an average of 35, as airlines sacrifice space to increase the number of seats, Bloomberg reports.Some are concerned that cramped cabins may impact passenger evacuation during an emergency, which should take only 90 seconds.To address this, a provision in the recently passed FAA Reauthorization Bill requires the agency to set minimum seat-size standards, and to do so within the year. This is expected to greatly improve passenger wellness, and maybe help reduce air rage incidents, since people aren't feeling as cramped up or claustrophobic.But experts say airlines intent on cutting costs could do so by reducing padding or taking out standard features like tray tables. Alternatively, they could also raise prices.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of shrinking airplane seats, increase in number of seats on board2. Depiction of 90-second standard for deplaning during emergencies3. Depiction of FAA setting minimum seat size4. Depiction of consequences of minimum seat sizeVOICEOVER (in English): "Non-profit group Flyer Rights claims the width and pitch of plane seats have been narrowing since the early 2000s, with airlines sacrificing space to increase the number of seats.""Some are concerned that cramped cabins may impact passenger evacuation during an emergency, which should take only 90 seconds.""To address this, a provision in the recently passed FAA Reauthorization Bill requires the agency to set minimum seat-size standards, and to do so within the year.""But experts say airlines intent on cutting costs could do so by reducing padding or taking out standard features like tray tables. Alternatively, they could also raise prices."SOURCES: USA Today, Bloomberghttps://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/advice/2018/07/15/airline-seat-standards-government-regulations-coming/777040002/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-03/airline-seat-sizes-don-t-need-regulation-for-safety-faa-says***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 09:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/16/3654633/3654633_12940A4C3A584BF7BF7EE286814E17F7_180716_3654633_Seat_standards_may_be_coming_to_U_S__airlines_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/955/31A/95531AE6E14C4C66B25C2F8FE5C574BB_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, airline seat standards, seat standards plane seats, shrinking plane seats, seat size, plane seat size, minimum seat size, FAA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3654512</guid>
      <title>Flight attendants linked to higher rates of cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study of around 5,300 U.S. flight attendants has found the profession holds higher cancer rates.The Harvard study found that female flight attendants have higher cases of breast cancer, as well as melanoma and non-melanoma skin cancers. According to a Harvard news release, cabin crew are frequently exposed to carcinogens. This includes large doses of ionizing radiation. According to information from the FAA, this is believed to come from supernovae and the sun. Ionizing radiation has subatomic particles that can cause atom's in the body to break apart within the nucleus. This can lead to increased risk of fatal cancer among flight attendants and can affect their children if they are irradiated while pregnant.Citing the study Live Science reports, at these cancer rates were found despite those surveyed having lower levels of obesity and smoking.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of flight attendant in cabin2. Depiction of different kinds of cancers female flight attendants are at increased risk from3. Depiction of ionizing radiation from supernova and sun4. Depiction of ionizing radiation in the cabinVOICEOVER (in English): "A study of around 5,300 U.S. flight attendants has found the profession holds higher cancer rates compared to the general population."  "The Harvard study found that female flight attendants have higher cases of breast cancer, as well as melanoma and non-melanoma skin cancers.""According to a Harvard news release, cabin crew are frequently exposed to carcinogens.""This includes large doses of ionizing radiation. The FAA says this is believed to come from supernovae and the sun." "Ionizing radiation has subatomic particles that can cause atoms in the body to break apart within the nucleus.""This can lead to increased risk of fatal cancer among flight attendants and can affect their children if they are irradiated while pregnant."SOURCES: Harvard, Environmental Health, FAA, Live Sciencehttps://www.hsph.harvard.edu/news/press-releases/flight-attendants-cancer-risk/https://ehjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12940-018-0396-8https://www.faa.gov/data_research/research/med_humanfacs/oamtechreports/2000s/media/0316.pdfhttps://www.livescience.com/62913-cancer-risk-flight-attendants.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 07:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/16/3654512/3654512_A57C56FA940D40E18085A4F870343799_180716_3654512_Flight_attendants_linked_to_higher_rates_of_canc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1DC/9A7/1DC9A7CCA11B422583DE85791EE43987_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, flight attendant, cancer, cosmic ionizing radiation, medical, planes and health, cosmic radiation, air crew, flight attendant, flight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3654463</guid>
      <title>Federal government reopens 1955 Emmett Till murder case</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Justice Department has reopened the 63-year-old murder case of a black teen, whose violent death helped build momentum for the civil rights movement.CNN reports that in 1955, while visiting family in Money, Mississippi, Emmett Till was falsely accused of making advances on a white woman named Carolyn Donham.Four days later, Donham's husband Roy Bryant and his half brother J.W. Milam kidnapped the 14-year-old. He was beaten viciously and then shot in the head.The boy's mutilated body was found in the Tallahatchie River, weighed down by a 75-pound cotton gin fan that had been strapped to his neck with barbed wire.Despite being identified by eyewitnesses and admitting to the kidnapping, Bryant and Milam were acquitted by an all-white jury. A year later, the pair confessed to the murder during a magazine interview, but weren't retried.Renewed interest in the case was supposedly sparked by the discovery of new information, though what is remains unspecified.Some believe it may have to do with the release of a book on the murder, in which Donham admits to lying about Till grabbing and making vulgar remarks to her.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Emmett Till accused of making advances at a white woman2. Depiction of Emmett Till being kidnapped, beaten, and shot3. Depiction of Emmett Till's body in the river4. Depiction of killers being acquitted by juryVOICEOVER (in English): "In 1955, while visiting family in Money, Mississippi, Emmett Till was falsely accused of making advances on a white woman named Carolyn Donham.""Four days later, Donham's husband Roy Bryant and his half brother J.W. Milam kidnapped the 14-year-old. He was beaten viciously and then shot in the head.""The boy's mutilated body was found in the Tallahatchie River, weighed down by a 75-pound cotton gin fan that had been strapped to his neck with barbed wire.""Despite being identified by eyewitnesses and admitting to the kidnapping, Bryant and Milam were acquitted by an all-white jury. They later confessed to the murder in an interview, but weren't retried."SOURCES: New York Times, CNN, CBShttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/12/us/emmett-till-death-investigation.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/12/us/emmett-till-murder-case-reopened-doj/index.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/emmett-till-lynching-government-reopens-investigation-today-2018-07-12/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 06:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/16/3654463/3654463_442156ACF591454A83AA2450F2BEC04E_180716_3654463_Federal_government_reopens_1955_Emmett_Till_murd_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D3D/121/D3D1215E3315414EAC5129DE71AC25CC_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  emmett till, emmett till murder, civil rights movement, murder case, black violence, racial violence, carolyn donham, roy bryant, jw milam, old murder cases]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3655613</guid>
      <title>Study shows moisturizers with SPF not as effective as sunscreen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study conducted by the British Association of Dermatologists shows that using a moisturizer with sun protection factor isn't as effective as applying sunscreen. The participants were asked to apply moisturizer with SPF where they missed around 16 percent of their face, of which 21% of their eyelids were missed, according to the study.Participants were then asked to apply sunscreen on their face, with a UV-sensitive camera taking pictures of their faces before and after application.They reportedly missed 10% of their whole face, while an average of 14% of their eyelid area was missed.As UVA rays and UVB rays penetrate the skin, it is important to use SPF protection of at least 15.If the skin is not protected from the sun, skin damage such as freckles and dark spots may occur.According to the National Health Service, additional protection such as a hat, a t-shirt, and sunglasses is also recommended.Researchers also reminded the public to apply sunscreen thoroughly to avoid diseases such as skin cancer in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing how the face looks like with moisturizer with SPF.2. Showing how the face looks like with SPF.3. Showing how the UV rays penetrate the skin.4. Showing the effects of not protecting the skin from the sun.VOICEOVER (in English): "The participants were asked to apply moisturizer with SPF where they missed around 16 percent of their face, which 21% of their eyelids were missed, according to the study.""Participants were then asked to apply sunscreen on their face, with a UV-sensitive camera taking pictures of their faces before and after application.""As UVA rays and UVB rays penetrate the skin, it is important to use SPF protection of at least 15.""If the skin is not protected from the sun, skin damage such as freckles and dark spots may occur."SOURCES: Elle, British Association of Dermatologists,  Irish Examiner, Global News https://www.elle.com.au/beauty/is-spf-in-moisturiser-effective-1-18022http://www.bad.org.uk/media/newshttps://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/lifestyle/healthandlife/skin-savers-staying-safe-in-the-sun-853253.htmlhttps://globalnews.ca/news/4313968/moisturizers-with-spf-not-effective/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 13:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/17/3655613/3655613_3AB8527AF5AC484AA535AFEE28EED66B_180717_3655613_Study_shows_moisturizers_with_SPF_not_as_effecti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C69/42B/C6942B6F1BC84C7DA530593059CEC17C_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, study, SPF, sunscreen, moisturizer, moisturizer with spf, spf 15, sun]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656060</guid>
      <title>Scientists estimate there are a quadrillion tons of diamond below Earth's surface</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study from MIT suggests the interior of Earth is "filled with a quadrillion tons of diamonds."Scientists estimate the diamonds are more than 100 miles below the surface, beneath the continental tectonic plates.The study estimates 1-2 percent of the cratonic roots may be filled with diamonds.A statement from MIT News says scientists came to this conclusion while they were trying to "construct an image of what the earth's interior might look like."Researchers created virtual rock models to test what material would allow sound waves to travel that quickly through the cratonic roots. The result was diamonds. Scientists came up with an estimate of around a quadrillion tons of diamonds by taking into account the total volume of cratonic roots scattered inside Earth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  Showing the diamonds in Earth's interior2. Showing that the diamonds are approximately 100 miles beneath Earth's surface.3.  How much of the cratonic roots is actually filled with diamonds.4. Showing how the scientists conducted the experiment with virtual rocks and sound waves.VOICEOVER (in English): "A new study from MIT suggests the interior of Earth is 'filled with a quadrillion tons of diamonds.'""Scientists estimate the diamonds are more than 100 miles below the surface, beneath the continental tectonic plates.""The study estimates 1-2 percent of the cratonic roots may be filled with diamonds.""Researchers created virtual rock models to test what material would allow sound waves to travel that quickly through the cratonic roots. The result was diamonds. "SOURCES: Live Science, Newsweek, Science Day, MIT Newshttps://www.livescience.com/63074-earth-interior-full-of-diamonds.htmlhttps://www.newsweek.com/diamond-found-earth-1026382https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/07/180716114538.htmhttp://news.mit.edu/2018/sound-waves-reveal-diamond-cache-deep-earths-interior-0716***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 06:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/18/3656060/3656060_F43CFAB5471E43D885CAFA4A49955B6A_180718_3656060_Scientists_estimate_there_are_a_quadrillion_tons_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D77/1BF/D771BF25D81F42389FB77254054E6FF7_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Earth, diamond, diamonds in earth, scientists, study, cratonic roots, Earth's interior, rocks, sound waves]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656759</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover ancient iceman's final meal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found out what an ancient iceman ate before he died.Otzi the Iceman was a hunter who died in the Alps 5,300 years ago, and his mummified body was discovered near the Italy-Austria border in 1991, National Geographic reports.Researchers had been unable to locate the hunter's stomach until a CT scan revealed the organ was tucked under his rib cage.An analysis published in the journal Current Biology revealed that half the stomach contents consisted of the fat and meat of an alpine goat. They also found red deer meat, whole wheat seeds, and traces of toxic bracken fern.The toxic fern may have been ingested accidentally, or possibly as medicine for whipworm parasites, which was previously found in his intestines, the Guardian reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Otzi the iceman's mummified remains2. Depiction of CT scan finding Otzi the iceman's misplaced stomach3. Depiction of iceman's stomach contents4. Depiction of how iceman may have ingested toxic fern VOICEOVER (in English): "Otzi the Iceman had been a hunter who died in the Alps 5,300 years ago, whose mummified body was discovered near the Italy-Austria border in 1991.""Researchers had been unable to locate the hunter's stomach until a CT scan revealed the misplaced organ tucked under the rib cage.""An analysis revealed that half the stomach contents consisted of the fat and meat of an alpine goat. They also found red deer meat, whole wheat seeds, and traces of toxic bracken fern.""The toxic fern may have been ingested accidentally, or possibly as medicine for whipworm parasites, which had previously found in his intestines."SOURCES: Current Biology, The Guardian, National Geographichttps://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(18)30703-6https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jul/12/otzis-last-supper-mummified-hunters-final-meal-revealedhttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/07/news-otzi-iceman-food-DNA-diet-meat-fat/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 03:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/19/3656759/3656759_F6E2111ED71A444B99795CF473F32EF7_180719_3656759_Scientists_discover_ancient_iceman_s_final_meal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/4C2/53C/4C253CE770D24A5CBB9A30939348223E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, otzi the iceman, iceman, ancient iceman, last meal, stomach contents, ancient diet, goat meat, alpine ibex, deer, toxic fern, toxic bracken, stomach parasites, whipworm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656749</guid>
      <title>2,500-year-old Egyptian mummification workshop found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDuring a dig in Saqqara, Egypt, a team of Egyptian and German archeologists discovered a mummification workshop dating back more than 2,500 years, according to a press statement released by Egypt's Ministry of State of Antiquities.The statement added that an embalming workshop contained labeled bowls and measuring cups, which held oils and substances that were used in the mummification process.Two basins were also found, which archaeologists believe may have been used to dry the mummies and prepare the bandages used to wrap them. A 30-meter burial shaft was also discovered near the mummification workshop in the Saqqara necropolis in Egypt.Five mummies with their sarcophagi were found. Archaeologists found a mummy with a gilded silver mask with eyes containing calcite, obsidian and a black gemstone inside one of the sarcophagi.Shabti figurines, which were placed with the dead to accompany them into the afterlife, and alabaster vessels were also found at the excavation site.More excavations in the area are expected to take place this year.The findings will soon be displayed in a museum, with Egypt hoping the discoveries will attract more tourists to the country.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ancient embalming workshop was found with labelled bowls and cups for mummification.2. A burial shaft was also found nearby.3. Five mummies were discovered. Archaeologists opened one and found a gilded silver mask.4. Other artifacts such as the Shabti figurines and alabaster vessels were also uncovered at site.VOICEOVER (in English): "Egypt's Ministry of State of Antiquities says a mummification workshop has been discovered. The embalming workshop contains labeled bowls and measuring cups, which held oils and substances used in the mummification process.""A 30-meter burial shaft was also discovered near the workshop.""Also found were five mummies with their sarcophagi.  A mummy with a gilded silver mask with eyes containing calcite, obsidian and a black gemstone was found inside onf of the sarcophagi.""Shabti figurines, which were placed with the dead to accompany them into the afterlife, and alabaster vessels were also found. "SOURCES: The Guardian, Ancient-origins, NBC News, New York Post, Fox News, https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/14/a-goldmine-mummies-secrets-uncovered-in-egypthttps://www.ancient-origins.net/news-history-archaeology/ancient-egyptian-mummy-workshop-giza-pyramids-021974https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/new-discovery-mummies-burial-shaft-egypt-sheds-light-embalming-process-n891446https://nypost.com/2018/07/15/archaeologists-in-egypt-discover-mummification-workshop/http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/07/15/archaeologists-in-egypt-discover-ancient-mummification-worskshop.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/19/3656749/3656749_0534837772E642D4AF192B6108F9A0FF_180719_3656749_2_500_year_old_Egyptian_mummification_workshop_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1DA/E45/1DAE45B811E54A9DB52A7B4E7EEB6C42_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Egypt, mummies, burial site, sarcophagus, mummy burial, excavation, mummy workshop]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656745</guid>
      <title>Russia to build laser cannon to vaporize space debris</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Russian space agency is planning to get rid of space debris by shooting it with a laser cannon, reports RT.Scientists have noted the increasing amount of space debris floating outside of Earth's atmosphere, most of which is "the size of a marble" while around ⅓ of the debris is the "size of a softball."The cannon will be based on the 3-meter optical telescope, which is already being made. It will be designed to monitor space satellites and keep an eye out for potentially dangerous space debris.The optical telescope will eventually be transformed into a powerful laser cannon, if things go according to plan.The laser cannon will be supplied power from a type of solid-base generator, and will supposedly use a process called "laser ablation" to remove debris surrounding Earth's atmosphere.The energy of the laser would heat and pierce and object until it evaporates.Different countries such as China, Australia, and Japan have tried their hand at getting rid of the space debris..without any success so far, RT reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the Earth and the debris surrounding it2. Showing the optical telescope monitoring space3. Showing the telescope turning into a laser cannon and shooting a laser beam into the sky.4. Showing how the laser beam will pierce and get rid of the space debrisVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have noted the increasing amount of space debris floating outside of Earth's atmosphere, most of which is 'the size of a marble' while around ⅓ of the debris is the size of a softball.""The cannon will be based on the 3-meter optical telescope, which is already being made. It will be designed to monitor space satellites and keep an eye out for potentially dangerous space debris.""The optical telescope will eventually be transformed into a powerful laser cannon, if things go according to plan." "The laser cannon will supposedly use a process called 'laser ablation' to remove debris surrounding Earth's atmosphere. The energy of the laser would heat and pierce into the debris until it evaporates."SOURCES: BGR.com, RT, Metro, Sputniknewshttp://bgr.com/2018/06/13/space-junk-laser-russia-roscosmos/https://www.rt.com/news/429291-laser-clear-space-junk/https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/11/russia-building-space-gun-laser-death-ray-terrifying-sounds-7621352/https://sputniknews.com/science/201806101065288031-laser-cannon-space-debris/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 02:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/19/3656745/3656745_B6C1CA9C1EB04848AECC4C61B67FACC5_180719_3656745_Russia_to_build_laser_cannon_to_vaporize_space_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D8D/7A9/D8D7A9E4951F4028976C9140175CB1B8_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Space, Russia, Space Debris, Space Laser cannon, Blasting space debris with a laser,Space debris around Earth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657974</guid>
      <title>Trump to redesign Air Force One to be 'red, white and blue'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn an interview with CBS News, U.S. President Donald Trump confirmed that he will redesign the presidential plane Air Force One into a more patriotic color scheme.***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 11:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/20/3657974/3657974_5755B315D1414707BFFAF04753951954_180720_3657974_Trump_to_redesign_Air_Force_One_to_be__red__whit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/68E/ED4/68EED469A02743B79F724F2FC0FA1193_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, air force one trump, air force one trump plane,air force one new paint job, air force one redesign, us air force one, us air force one plane, air force one us president aircraft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657749</guid>
      <title>Esports set to debut at 2018 Asian Games</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEsports is finally being included in the Asian Games for the first time since it started.Reuters reports esports, or electronic competitive gaming, was recognized as a sport by the International Olympic Committee in November.Esports has over 250 million players around the world, and a growing market worth a billion dollars a year.The 2018 Asian Games in Jakarta, held from August 18 to September 2, will only feature esports as a demonstration event, but it's set to debut as a medal event at the 2022 games in Hangzhou, China.Six game titles have been confirmed for the 2018 roster: League of Legends, Hearthstone, Pro Evolution Soccer, Starcraft II, Clash Royale, and Arena of Valor.Twenty-seven countries and regions had signed up for the Qualifier Competitions from June 6 to 20. Matches were held online and offline in in Hong Kong, Ho Chi Minh, and Changzhou.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of esports recognized as a sport activity2. Depiction of esports statistics3. Depiction of esports in the 2018 and 2022 Asian Games4. Depiction of game titles in 2018 rosterVOICEOVER (in English): "Esports, or electronic competitive gaming, was recognized as a sport by the International Olympic Committee in November.""According to Reuters, esports has over 250 million players around the world, and a growing market worth a billion dollars a year.""The 2018 Asian Games in Jakarta games will only feature esports as a demonstration event, but it's set to debut as a medal event at the 2022 games in Hangzhou, China.""Six game titles have been confirmed for the 2018 roster: League of Legends, Hearthstone, Pro Evolution Soccer, Starcraft II, Clash Royale, and Arena of Valor."SOURCES: Reuters, Asian Electronic Sports Federation, Esports Observerhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-esports-asia/stakeholders-call-for-esports-regulations-ahead-of-asian-games-debut-idUSKBN1HX2FUhttps://www.aesf.com/news.html?w=news8https://esportsobserver.com/asian-games-2018-esports/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 07:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/20/3657749/3657749_B557208773734A3C92EDEC9F2E97009D_180720_3657749_Esports_set_to_debut_at_2018_Asian_Games_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/418/354/4183543F72BF482F8E4C5474C551E25C_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, esports, asian games, 2018 asian games, gaming, competitive gaming, sports, league of legends, hearthstone, arena of valor, pes 2018, starcraft, clash royale]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657730</guid>
      <title>Marine biologist finds six pregnant male sharks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA researcher has discovered six hermaphrodite sharks pregnant off the coast in eastern India, reports Science News.Marine biologist Alissa Barnes noticed there were more male bigeye houndsharks than females, yet the males had a "visible stomach bulge."Barnes dissected the fish and found the 'male sharks' had external claspers  like most male houndsharks   but they also had ovaries like their female counterparts.In her published report, Barnes called this phenomenon "intersexuality."Six of the seven dissected sharks turned out to be pregnant, with Barnes finding at least two baby sharks in one.Another shark biologist told Science News that hermaphroditism  an organism containing both male and female reproductive systems  is rare in sharks.Barnes claims this abnormality may have been caused by "pollutants in the water" or "hormonal changes," reports Science News.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing six bigeye houndsharks in the waters.2. Showing that more male bigeye houndsharks were present compared to their female counterparts.3. Showing the external claspers of the male sharks and the ovaries found in the male sharks.4. Showing that six of the seven male sharks turned out to be pregnant, with at least one found having two shark babies.VOICEOVER (in English): "Science News reports a researcher has discovered six hermaphrodite sharks pregnant off the coast in eastern India.""Marine biologist Alissa Barnes noticed there were more male bigeye houndsharks than females … yet the males had a 'visible stomach bulge'.""Barnes dissected the fish and found the 'male sharks' had external claspers  like most male houndsharks   but they also had ovaries like their female counterparts.""Six of the seven dissected sharks turned out to be pregnant, with Barnes finding at least two baby sharks in one."SOURCES: The Charlotte Observer, Science News, 5th International Marine Conservation Congresshttps://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article214916655.htmlhttps://www.sciencenews.org/article/surprise-shark-looks-male-outside-its-made-babieshttp://programme.exordo.com/imcc5/delegates/presentation/477/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 07:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/20/3657730/3657730_0AD81103306F45E5A44030F74EB12E41_180720_3657730_Marine_biologist_finds_six_pregnant_male_sharks_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/CB6/A5F/CB6A5F26AF8A4A049FFFD8A838014886_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, marine life, sharks, male sharks, bigeye houndshark, hermaphroditism, pollutants, water, ocean, sea, pregnant male sharks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657556</guid>
      <title>Study finds alcohol more young people dying of liver disease</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in the British Medical Journal states that more young people are dying from liver disease than in the past.Data from the CDC shows the number of 24-34 year olds who died due to alcohol-related liver disease has nearly tripled between 1999-2016  from 259 in 1999 to 767 in 2016.Dr. Elliot Tapper, who co-wrote the study, believes that it may have something to do with the global financial crisis … as a "loss of opportunity" and "psychological burden" may have led some to "abusive drinking."According to the study, ethnic groups such as whites, Native Americans and Hispanic Americans saw an increase of liver-related deaths while Asian Americans saw a decrease. Binge drinking is defined by the CDC as drinking five or more "standard drinks" in a few hours for men and four for women.The CDC warns that drinking too much alcohol can cause liver cancer and may also cause liver cirrhosis.However, Dr. Tapper did have some encouraging news: liver disease is often reversible. The sooner the patients stop drinking, the better their chances of recovering.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing data from the CDC.2. Showing why young adults may take to alcohol.3. Illustration of the CDC's definition of binge drinking.4. Illustration of what too much alcohol can do to the liver.VOICEOVER (in English): "Data from the CDC shows the number of 24-34 year olds who died due to alcohol-related liver disease has nearly tripled between 1999-2016  from 259 in 1999 to 767 in 2016.""Dr. Elliot Tapper, who co-wrote the study, believes that it may have something to do with the global financial crisis … as a 'loss of opportunity' and 'psychological burden' may have led some to 'abusive drinking'.""Binge drinking is defined by the CDC as drinking five or more 'standard drinks' in a few hours for men and four for women.""The CDC warns that drinking too much alcohol can cause liver cancer and may also cause liver cirrhosis."SOURCES: NPR, British Medical Journal, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, NBC News, The Washington Post, The New York Times, https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2018/07/18/630275042/a-spike-in-liver-disease-deaths-among-young-adults-fueled-by-alcoholhttps://www.bmj.com/content/362/bmj.k2817https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db314.htmhttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/deaths-liver-disease-are-surging-drinking-blame-n892521https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2018/07/18/alcohol-related-liver-deaths-have-increased-sharply/?utm_term=.ae35e4d9a23dhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/18/health/cirrhosis-liver-cancer.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/20/3657556/3657556_98DB90F410FA4ED4A86855F7F59E6111_180720_3657556_Study_finds_alcohol_more_young_people_dying_of_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/D86/63D/D8663D78C2A741C1AE507DC9BDF66070_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Study, USA, Alcohol, young adults, liver cancer, liver disease, liver cirrhosis, alcoholism]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657549</guid>
      <title>How mosquitoes transfer viruses and diseases to humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe diseases that mosquitoes transmit kill hundreds of thousands of people each year, Scientific American reports.Female mosquitoes only bite humans when they require blood to feed their eggs. To suck blood, female mosquitoes use six needle-like parts, which scientists refer to as stylets. Two of these are called maxillae[a]; they are equipped with saw-like teeth that are able ot cut through human skin without a person noticing.Another set of needles, the mandibles[b], hold tissue apart to allow the Labrum[c] to dig through human skin in search for blood. Once it locates a source, it sucks it out.The hypopharynx[d] injects saliva into blood vessels, delivering chemicals that keep the blood flowing. Mosquito saliva causes blood vessels dilate, blocks a person's immune response and lubricates the proboscis. This results in a person suffering from itchy welts. During this process, dangerous viruses, such as Zika and West Nile virus, can be transferred into the human body.Texas, Colorado, Utah, Ohio, Indiana are all experiencing outbreaks of the West Nile virus, with the number of mosquitoes carrying the virus seem to be growing as well.About 1 in 150 people who are infected with West Nile virus develop severe illness that affects the central nervous system. About 1 out of 10 people who develop this illness die.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the six needle-like parts and show maxillae cut through human skin2. Depiction of the mandibles and the labrum3. Depiction of the hypopharynx4. Depiction of blood vessels dilate; itchy welts done by the bite and transfers of virusesVOICEOVER (in English): "Mosquitoes have six needle-like parts, two of them are called maxillae[e], they are equipped with saw-like teeth to cut through your skin without you noticing it.""Another set of needles, the mandibles[f], hold human tissues apart so one needle called the Labrum[g] can dig around under human skin searching for blood, ultimately sucking it out.""The sixth needle – called the hypopharynx[h] – drools saliva into blood vessels, and delivers chemicals that keep the blood flowing." "Mosquito saliva makes our blood vessels dilate, blocks our immune response and lubricates the proboscis. It gives us itchy welts, also transfers dangerous viruses such as Zika and West Nile virus."SOURCES: https://www.cdc.gov/westnile/symptoms/index.htmlhttps://www.khou.com/article/news/local/explainer-how-do-mosquitoes-transfer-viruses-diseases/285-574894317https://www.kqed.org/science/728086/how-mosquitoes-use-six-needles-to-suck-your-bloodhttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-other-reason-mosquitoes-want-to-suck-your-blood/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/20/3657549/3657549_C18987BD0269403E9EA1CAE18CC6EC4B_180720_3657549_How_mosquitoes_transfer_viruses_and_diseases_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/6B8/7B4/6B87B494FED844518BEF55BD4895D86F_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, mosquitoes viruses, viruses transmitted by mosquitoes, how do mosquitoes spread viruses, mosquitoes diseases, diseases spread by mosquitoes, how mosquitoes transmit diseases, west nile virus, zika]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657539</guid>
      <title>NASA, Lockheed Martin developing silent supersonic jet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLockheed Martin and NASA have partnered to develop a quiet supersonic plane named the X-59. According to information from the space agency's website, the proposed single-pilot craft has a wingspan of 29.5 feet, is 94 feet long and weighs 32,300 pounds at total fuel capacity. NASA says the X-59 will be powered by a General Electric F414 engine. This is the same engine used by F/A-18 E/F fighter jets. The craft's hull is designed to abate the noise from shockwaves traditionally associated with mach speed travel. During that, shockwaves come together and create loud sonic booms. The space agency says the X-59 is designed to separate these shockwaves, resulting in a much less noise reaching the ground.The aircraft's first test flight is scheduled for 2021, according to a Lockheed Martin news release.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of aircraft specifications2. Depiction of aircraft engine3. Depiction of sound barrier shockwaves from traditional aircraft4. Depiction of sound barrier shockwaves from X-59VOICEOVER (in English): "Lockheed Martin and NASA have partnered to develop a quiet supersonic plane named the X-59." "The proposed single-pilot craft has a wingspan of 29.5 feet, is 94 feet long and weighs 32,300 pounds at total fuel capacity.""NASA says the X-59 will be powered by a General Electric F414 engine. This is the same engine used by F/A-18 E/F fighter jets.""The craft's hull is designed to abate the noise from shockwaves traditionally associated with mach speed travel. "During that, shockwaves come together and create loud sonic booms.""The space agency says the X-59 is designed to separate these shockwaves, resulting in a much less noise reaching the ground."SOURCES: NASA, Lockheed Martinhttps://www.nasa.gov/centers/armstrong/feature/NASA_advances_schlieren_imagery_for_supersonic_aircraft.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/aero/nasa-experimental-supersonic-aircraft-x-59-quessthttps://news.lockheedmartin.com/2018-04-03-NASA-Selects-Lockheed-Martin-Skunk-Works-R-to-Build-X-Plane***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/20/3657539/3657539_0385467D8A3B4314971240A4AB49D538_180720_3657539_NASA__Lockheed_Martin_developing_silent_superson_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/3E5/E85/3E5E855114294AD49784B22A563E842C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, x-59, supersonic jet, supersonic speed, mach speed, nasa airplane, nasa jet, lockheed martin, x-59 quesst, quiet supersonic sound technology, noise reduction technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659842</guid>
      <title>Israel's Defense Ministry unveils new smart battle tank</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIsrael plans to equip its battle tank with artificial intelligence.The Merkava Mark 4 Barak will reportedly be the first tank to have a smart mission computer to manage tasks.Israel's Merkava Mark 4 Barak would have an advanced AI system which would help to locate targets and strike accurately, reports New Atlas.Virtual reality will also be added onto the tank, with combat soldier using a helmet called Iron View, developed by Elbit Systems, to "see the outside environment from inside the combat vehicle."Virtual reality simulations are aimed at allowing the soldiers to partake in military exercises in real time.A press release claims updated sensors equipped on the outside the tank would "allow the combat soldiers to operate the tank in a simple and advanced way."The press release also states these improvement will help the tank "carry out missions that are up to 30% longer than current ones."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the Merkava Mark 4 Barak with its smart computer.2. Showing Merkava Mark 4 Barak's smart AI system with the ability to accurately locate targets. 3. Showing Iron View, the helmet which uses virtual reality to see the outside environment within the smart tank.4. Showing sensors equipped on the outside of the tank.VOICEOVER (in English): "The Merkava Mark 4 Barak will reportedly be the first tank to have a smart mission computer to manage tasks.""According to reports from New Atlas, Israel's Merkava Mark 4 Barak would have an advanced AI system which would help to locate targets and strike accurately.""Virtual reality will also be added onto the tank, with combat soldier using a helmet called Iron View to 'see the outside environment from inside the combat vehicle.'""Reports from a press release claim updated sensors equipped on the outside the tank would 'allow the combat soldiers to operate the tank in a simple and advanced way..'"SOURCES: New Atlas, Army Recognition.com, Defense Blog, The Jerusalem Posthttps://newatlas.com/merkava-mk-4-barak-smart-tank/55556/https://www.armyrecognition.com/july_2018_global_defense_security_army_news_industry/new_israeli-made_merkava_mk4_barak_tank_used_in_guerrilla_warfare.htmlhttps://defence-blog.com/army/israel-reveals-details-next-generation-merkava-main-battle-tank.htmlhttps://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/IDF-General-Latest-Merkava-tank-APC-to-ensure-superiority-on-the-battlefield-492064***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/23/3659842/3659842_3C03BAC27B904E1294707A243A042DAF_180723_3659842_Israel_s_Defense_Ministry_unveils_new_smart_batt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/16C/75C/16C75C78E5F04541AB899F673DBDDAAF_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, smart battle tank, AI, smart mission computer, sensors, military exercises, virtual reality, VR]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659536</guid>
      <title>Study shows teen ADHD symptoms may be linked to digital media usage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Journal of the American Medical Association has published a study which suggests the more teens use digital media, the more likely for symptoms of ADHD to develop.The study found nearly 81% of students reported using at least one type of digital media multiples times daily.At the beginning of the study, the students involved had to complete a survey in which they answered how often they consumed 14 different media activities such as social media, texting, watching videos online, and more, reports CNN.The students took a total of five surveys in the fall 2014, spring of 2015, fall of 2015, spring of 2016, and fall of 2016."Reports also say it is possible that phone notifications distract the students' attention, making it harder to develop concentration skills."According to the surveys, the teens who reported "infrequently using digital media" had a 4.6% chance of reporting ADHD symptoms in the surveys that followed.For teens who reported using seven digital media platforms, the percentage almost doubled to 9.5%.And for the students who said they use all 14 digital platforms on a daily basis, the percentage climbed to 10.5.Adam Leventhal, the lead author of the study, said to CNN there weren't any clinicians involved in the study to "provide a diagnosis" as the study was based on self-reports on digital media use compared to ADHD symptoms. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Percentage of at least one type of digital media usage by students.2. The students involved in the study had to complete a survey about 14 different media activities.3. Smartphone notifications.4. Percentage of teens reporting ADHD symptoms in correlation with how many different digital platforms they tended to consume.VOICEOVER (in English): "The study found nearly 81% of students reported using at least one type of digital media multiples times daily.""CNN reports at the beginning of the study, the students involved had to complete a survey in which they answered how often they consumed 14 different media activities such as social media, texting, watching videos online, and more. ""Reports also say it is possible that phone notifications distract the students' attention, making it harder to develop concentration skills.""According to the surveys, the teens who reported 'infrequently using digital media' had a 4.6% chance of reporting ADHD symptoms in the surveys that followed.""For teens who reported using seven digital media platforms, the percentage almost doubled to 9.5%.""And for the students who said they use all 14 digital platforms on a daily basis, the percentage climbed to 10.5."SOURCES: Journal of the American Medical Association, CNN, ABC27, The Verge, NBC News, LA Times.https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2687861https://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/17/health/adhd-symptoms-digital-media-study/index.html?no-st=1531894303https://www.abc27.com/health/health-center/new-study-finds-the-more-teens-use-digital-devices-the-greater-the-risk-of-adhd/1308572322https://www.theverge.com/2018/7/17/17581486/adhd-digital-media-technology-teenshttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/adhd-may-have-modest-link-teen-tech-use-n892121http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-digital-media-adhd-20180717-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 07:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/23/3659536/3659536_C7812692B16F4F89B6B39569AC077B0D_180723_3659536_Study_shows_teen_ADHD_symptoms_may_be_linked_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/2D0/CA4/2D0CA4DBA5B74FFC990C6D2A1A0C1E31_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Study, teens, ADHD, ADHD symptoms, stimulation, digital media technology, social media, smartphones, social networking, texting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659339</guid>
      <title>New York could earn millions by legalizing recreational marijuana</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report claims the benefits of legalizing marijuana in New York outweighs the risks.Medical marijuana is allowed but tightly regulated in New York. It can only be taken by patients with certain conditions in pill, oil, or vape form  smoking and direct ingestion are not permitted.The state limits the number of medical marijuana dispensaries and requires vertical integration, which means businesses must grow, harvest, and manufacture what they sell.Many are pushing for full legalization, but Governor Andrew Cuomo isn't fully on board, famously calling marijuana a "gateway drug". However, a new report from the state Department of Health supports legalizing recreational use in New York, finding that it could bring millions in tax revenue.The report predicts that the move could also decrease opioid use and reduce criminal arrests which disproportionately affect minorities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of medical marijuana regulations in New York2. Depiction of vertical integration in New York dispensaries3. Depiction of potential revenue if recreational marijuana is legalized in New York4. Depiction of other benefits of legalizing recreational marijuanaVOICEOVER (in English): "Marijuana for medical use is allowed but tightly regulated in New York. It can only be taken by patients with certain conditions in pill, oil, or vape form  no smoking or direct ingestion.""The state limits the number of medical marijuana dispensaries and requires vertical integration, which means businesses grow, harvest, and manufacture what they sell.""A new Health Department report supports legalizing recreational marijuana in New York, finding that it could bring millions in tax revenue.""The report predicts that the move could also decrease opioid use and reduce criminal arrests which disproportionately affect minorities."SOURCES: Syracuse University, Department of Health, New York Times, WNYChttps://onlinebusiness.syr.edu/blog/new-york-marijuana-legalization/https://www.health.ny.gov/regulations/regulated_marijuana/docs/marijuana_legalization_impact_assessment.pdfhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/13/nyregion/marijuana-new-york-cuomo-legalization.htmlhttps://www.wnyc.org/story/heres-why-new-yorks-medical-marijuana-rules-are-about-change/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 02:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/23/3659339/3659339_AFB8DACDA2034B3387556B30469D3F74_180723_3659339_New_York_could_earn_millions_by_legalizing_recre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/8CD/EA5/8CDEA543E1C0440197F539E8C02563C4_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, marijuana, medical marijuana, legal marijuana, recreational marijuana, legalizing marijuana, drug, weed, pot, department of health, new york]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660557</guid>
      <title>China recalls rabies vaccine and heart drugs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo Chinese pharmaceutical companies have recalled their rabies vaccine and heart medication respectively after they were found to be tainted.Changchun Changsheng Biotechnology was found to be illegally producing "freeze-dried human rabies vaccines," reports Xinhua.The company reportedly fabricated production records and product inspection records.Zhejiang Huahai Pharmaceutical voluntarily suspended production of a heart drug after it was found to contain N-nitrosodimethylamine, or NDMA, reports Precision Vaccinations.The European Medicines Agency found the chemical  "tainted with an impurity linked to cancer," reports Reuters.NDMA was found in an ingredient called valsartan, which the company used to create drugs aimed at treating high blood pressure and heart failure.According to Xinhua, authorities have launched an investigation and plan to conduct more unannounced inspections in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the rabies vaccine on the production line.2. Showing the heart drugs being produced on the production line and the molecule which caused it to stop production.3. The NDMA molecule flashing red to show it was found linked to cancer.4. Showing the valsartan drug which is used to treat high blood pressure and heart failure.VOICEOVER (in English): "Xinhua reports Changchun Changsheng Biotechnology was found to be illegally producing 'freeze-dried human rabies vaccines.'""Precision Vaccinations reports, Zhejiang Huahai Pharmaceutical voluntarily suspended production of a heart drug after it was found to contain N-nitrosodimethylamine, or NDMA.""Reuters reports the European Medicines Agency found the chemical  'tainted with an impurity linked to cancer.'""NDMA was found in an ingredient called valsartan, which the company used to create drugs aimed at treating high blood pressure and heart failure."SOURCES: Xinhua, CNBC, SCMP, Reuters,http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-07/23/c_137341693.htmhttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/23/fresh-scandal-erupts-over-vaccine-safety-in-china.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/business/china-business/article/2156417/investors-lose-faith-pharma-stocks-chinas-vaccine-scandalhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-pharmaceuticals-europe-china/china-heart-drug-sold-globally-may-have-had-impurity-since-2012-idUSKBN1K72D5https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-vaccines/fresh-scandal-erupts-over-vaccine-safety-in-china-idUSKBN1KC0CWhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/policies-politics/article/2156525/three-cancers-attacking-health-chinas-vaccine-system***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/24/3660557/3660557_D2B0C0C35DAB4EB393FB017D2C0143C8_180724_3660557_China_recalls_rabies_vaccine_and_heart_drugs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A90/6D1/A906D1F7EC794514B9257F16F35EF3E6_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, pharmaceutical company, heart drug, rabies vaccine, illegal production, valsartan, NDMA, cancer, vaccine recall, drug recall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660468</guid>
      <title>Longest lunar eclipse of this century to take place this month</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe longest lunar eclipse of this century is expected to take place on July 27 for about 1 hour and 43 minutes, reports Space.com.NASA reports Earth's shadow is made from three different parts, the outer part known as the penumbra, the central part known as the umbra and the antumbra, which is beyond the penumbra and umbra. The moon will reportedly turn a "ruddy brown color" when it enters the umbra.The entire event, from start to finish, will take about four hours.According to Express, this month's moon will be at apogee, at its farthest possible distance from Earth.However, when the moon is at its nearest to Earth, it is called a perigee.According to space.com, the blood moon will be visible in most places, except in north America.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing Earth's different shadows.2. Showing the moon turning red when it enters a specific shadow.3. Explaining what an apogee is and where the moon will be.4. Explaining what an perigee is.VOICEOVER (in English): "The Earth's shadow is made from three different parts, the outer part known as the penumbra, the central part known as the umbra and the antumbra, which is beyond the penumbra and umbra.""The moon will turn a 'ruddy brown color,' when it enters the umbra.""According to Express, this month's moon will be at apogee, at its farthest possible distance from Earth.""However, when the moon is at its nearest to Earth, it is called a perigee."SOURCES:AL.com, Space.com., Express, Khaleej Times, NASAhttps://www.al.com/news/index.ssf/2018/07/blood_moon_2018_best_times_pla.htmlhttps://www.space.com/41007-blood-moon-2018-longest-lunar-eclipse-guide.htmlhttps://www.express.co.uk/news/science/982695/Eclipse-2018-Blood-Moon-visible-how-long-total-lunar-eclipse-visiblehttps://www.khaleejtimes.com/international/20180714/centurys-longest-lunar-eclipse-will-occur-this-monthhttps://www.nasa.gov/audience/forstudents/5-8/features/nasa-knows/what-is-an-eclipse-58***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/24/3660468/3660468_D3736217E7914F64AA47A37B3F240C1D_180724_3660468_Longest_lunar_eclipse_of_this_century_to_take_pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/713/053/713053778ABA4B3D80ECD75CAB72D500_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, moon, lunar eclipse, earth, blood moon, perigee, apogee, penumbra, umbra, antumbra]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660073</guid>
      <title>Venezuelans turn to 'dog carts'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVenezuelans struggling with the country's nonexistent transportation system are resorting to dangerous and often illegal means of getting around.Reuters reports that two years ago, passenger buses in Venezuela numbered at least 280,000, but have disappeared gradually due to expensive or unavailable parts.Public transportation has become scarce, with 95% of buses, cars, and taxis no longer on the road. Instead, residents are relying on over 150,000 unlicensed vehicles, nicknamed "kennels" or "dog carts", to get to their destination.This alternative means of transport often takes takes the form of delivery trucks or vans that standing passengers can cram themselves into.The "kennels" are so named for their cramped and unsafe conditions, which this year alone has caused 39 deaths and 275 injuries, according to opposition lawmaker Nora Bracho.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Venezuela passenger buses disappearing2. Depiction of scarce public transportation3. Depiction of passengers riding a 'kennel'4. Depiction of dangers of 'kennels'VOICEOVER (in English): "Two years ago, passenger buses in Venezuela numbered at least 280,000, but have disappeared gradually due to expensive or unavailable parts.""Public transportation has become scarce, with 95% of buses, cars, and taxis no longer on the road. Instead, residents are relying on over 150,000 unlicensed 'kennels'.""This alternative means of transport often takes takes the form of delivery trucks or vans that standing passengers can cram themselves into.""The 'kennels' are so named for their cramped and unsafe conditions, which this year alone has caused 39 deaths and 275 injuries."SOURCES: Reuters, Miami Heraldhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-transportation/weary-venezuelans-rely-on-dog-cart-transports-as-buses-succumb-to-crisis-idUSKBN1K72BJhttps://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article214709185.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 02:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/24/3660073/3660073_3B428E15F631465F87BEB722F286AE3E_180724_3660073_Venezuelans_turn_to__dog_carts__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/B5F/511/B5F511906F444002B3FCA56C60E716BF_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, kennel, dog cart, venezuela, transportation, public transportation, public transport, illegal transport, cargo, delivery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661321</guid>
      <title>TSA and AA developing new 3D luggage scanners for US airports</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe TSA is working with American Airlines to bring about a new scanning machine that may change the experience of security lines for many travelers, reports CBS News.Travellers in the U.S. have become accustomed to long TSA lines where shoes and belts are removed, and smartphones are placed within X-ray machines, among other things.X-ray machines may soon be replaced with a CT, or computed tomography bag-scanning machine, which would create 3D images of the contents within a piece of luggage, reports Fortune.This way, passengers would not be required to take anything out of their carry-on baggage, as the machine would be able to "see through" it.The machine would allow officers to directly zoom in and rotate the 3D image, which reportedly would be "much better at detection."Pekoske also said that in around five years, they expect passengers to not have to remove any items from their carry-on bags.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the old X-ray machine where people had to take out many things from their carry-on suitcase to put in a tray.2. Showing the CT carry-on scanner and the 3D image it would create.3. The machine 'seeing through' the luggage.4. Officers would be to zoom in and rotate the luggage to check what's inside.VOICEOVER (in English): "Travellers in the U.S. have become accustomed to long TSA lines where shoes and belts are removed, and smartphones are placed within X-ray machines, among other things.""Fortune reports X-ray machines may soon be replaced with a CT, or computed tomography bag-scanning machine, which would create 3D images of the contents within a piece of luggage.""This way, passengers would not be required to take anything out of their carry-on baggage, as the machine would be able to 'see through' it.""The machine would allow officers to directly zoom in and rotate the 3D image, which reportedly would be 'much better at detection.'"SOURCES: Fortune, CBS News, Chicago Tribune, USA Today, American Airlines Newsroomhttp://www.fortune.com/2018/07/24/tsa-american-airlines-airport-security-screenings-3d-scanner-images-analogic/https://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-3-d-scanners-could-ease-hassle-of-air-travelers/http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-3d-luggage-scanner-20170619-story.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/todayinthesky/2018/07/19/tsa-american-airlines-test-3-d-screening-carry-bags-new-york-jfk/800520002/http://news.aa.com/news/news-details/2018/American-Airlines-TSA-Testing-New-State-of-the-Art-Screening-Technology-in-New-York/default.aspx***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 13:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/25/3661321/3661321_6BC72D9D39DC45F9A6A18FA0E41A1875_180725_3661321_TSA_and_AA_developing_new_3D_luggage_scanners_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/859/255/859255FD84CD414CAB010F8D3E38D3CB_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, TSA, American airlines, airport security screening, X-ray machine, CT bag scanning machine, suitcase, travelling, 3D carry-on luggage scanner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660805</guid>
      <title>Realnetworks offer free facial recognition tech to US K-12 schools</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRealnetworks has announced that it will offer facial recognition technology to schools for free, with the aim at making schools in U.S. safe, Geekwire reported.According to Realnetworks, SAFR is a highly accurate facial recognition software powered by artificial intelligence; it works with IP cameras to match faces in real-time.Schools will need a database with photos of people authorized to be on campus. When an unauthorized person or someone who poses potential threat appears on campus, SAFR notifies a member of the staff.Realnetworks says the facial data and images SAFR collects are encrypted as a privacy protection and the school gets to keep them.SAFR is also designed to function in rural schools with limited internet connectivity.However, facial recognition tech in general  and for kids in school in particular  is a growing area of concern for privacy supporters and parents alike, Geekwire reported.The tech is currently being tested at a school in Seattle where students can unlock a gate by smiling at a surveillance camera.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Introduce SAFR.2. SAFR identifies unauthorized personnel with via the photos it has stored.3. The photos SAFR stored are encrypted and school gets to keep them.4. SAFR can also work in rural schools.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to provider Realnetworks, SAFR is a highly accurate facial recognition software powered by artificial intelligence, it works with IP cameras to match faces in real-time.""Schools will need a database with photos of people authorized to be on campus. When an unauthorized person or someone who poses potential threat appears on campus, SAFR notifies a member of the staff.""Realnetworks said the facial data and images SAFR collects are encrypted as a privacy protection and the school gets to keep them.""SAFR is also designed to function in rural schools with limited internet connectivity."SOURCES: https://www.geekwire.com/2018/realnetworks-debuts-facial-recognition-software-k-12-schools-raising-ethical-questions/https://safr.ai/k12/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 02:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/25/3660805/3660805_AB8D6B52E1704ED48D43EDB60046158B_180725_3660805_Realnetworks_offer_free_facial_recognition_tech__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FD0/BC3/FD0BC35DD74442458E7E460272899241_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, facial recognition technology, facial recognition technology school, facial recognition school, facial recognition software in schools, facial recognition privacy, facial recognition privacy issues, facial recognition privacy laws, facial recognition privacy policy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662135</guid>
      <title>How Narcan saved Demi Lovato from an overdose</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPop star Demi Lovato is in a Los Angeles hospital after reports indicate she overdosed on an undisclosed drug.The 25-year-old had been with friends at her Hollywood Hills home when she suffered an apparent drug overdose around noon on Tuesday.A source told US Weekly that one of her friends reportedly had Narcan on hand and administered it before paramedics arrived to take the unconscious Lovato to the hospital.Overdoses are caused by excessive opioids, which flood the brain and lock onto opiate receptors, causing insufficient breathing, pinpoint pupils, and unconsciousness.Narcan is used to reverse the effects of an overdose and can be administered in two ways: using a nasal spray or via a syringe injected into the thigh, butt, or arm muscles.According to the U.S. Surgeon General's Office, the emergency medication works by knocking the opioids out of the receptors in the brain, blocking and temporarily reversing the effects for 30 to 90 minutes.Narcan has a high efficacy rate, but doesn't always work when administered too late or when too many drugs are present in the body.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Demi Lovato suffering an overdose2. Depiction of Narcan being administered3. Depiction of a synthetic opioid overdose4. Depiction of Narcan as nasal spray5. Depiction of Narcan as injectable drug6. How Narcan reverses an opioid overdose7. Depiction of circumstances in which Narcan is ineffectiveVOICEOVER (in English): "Demi Lovato had been with friends at her Hollywood Hills home when she suffered an apparent drug overdose around noon on Tuesday.""One of her friends reportedly had Narcan on hand and administered it before paramedics arrived to take the unconscious Lovato to the hospital.""Overdoses are caused by excessive opioids, which flood the brain and lock onto opiate receptors, causing insufficient breathing, pinpoint pupils, and unconsciousness.""Narcan is used to reverse the effects of an overdose and can be administered in two ways: using a nasal spray or via a syringe injected into the thigh, butt, or arm muscles.""The emergency medication works by knocking the opioids out of the receptors in the brain, blocking and temporarily reversing the effects for 30 to 90 minutes.""Narcan has a high efficacy rate, but doesn't always work when administered too late or when too many drugs are present in the body."SOURCES: U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, US Weeklyhttps://www.surgeongeneral.gov/priorities/opioid-overdose-prevention/naloxone-advisory.htmlhttps://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/demi-lovatos-friends-saved-her-life-with-emergency-narcan/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/26/3662135/3662135_290FBEAA72304BB3B373295BEFB42273_180726_3662135_How_Narcan_saved_Demi_Lovato_from_an_overdose_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DBB/E7E/DBBE7E06336441429EF6765673C1481E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, demi lovato, narcan, naloxone, opioid, addiction, drug addiction, overdose, accidental overdose, medication, emergency medication]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661815</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show North Korea dismantling key missile test site</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea has begun dismantling key facilities of the Sohae Satellite Launching Station, reports 38 North.According to satellite images of the launching site, the rail-mounted processing building  where different launch vehicles were formerly prepared   was partially dismantled and now has been completely removed.Satellite images taken from July 20 to July 22 show the dismantling of the nuclear site.The nearby rocket engine test stand where there were liquid fuel engines for the ballistic missiles and launch vehicles have also been removed.However, in the images taken, the new fuel/oxidizer bunkers, the main processing building and gantry tower seem to be left untouched.Trump commented on North Korea's dismantling of key facilities of the satellite launch station and said "we appreciate that," reports CNN.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Before and after images of the nuclear missile testing site.2. Showing the rail-mounted processing building being dismantled.3. Showing that the rocket engine test stand has also been removed.4. Some of the elements of the nuclear testing site such as the fuel/oxidizer bunkers, the main processing building and gantry tower are still there.VOICEOVER (in English): "38 North reports North Korea has begun dismantling key facilities of the Sohae Satellite Launching Station.""According to satellite images of the launching site , the rail-mounted processing building  where different launch vehicles were formerly prepared   was partially dismantled and now has been completely removed.""The nearby rocket engine test stand where liquid fuel engines for the ballistic missiles and launch vehicles have also been removed.""However, in the images taken, the new fuel/oxidizer bunkers, the main processing building and gantry tower seem to be left untouched."SOURCES: Business Insider, 38 North, CNN, KBS World Radio,https://www.businessinsider.com/north-korea-dismantles-sohae-missile-site-satellite-launch-vehicle-win-for-trump-2018-7https://www.38north.org/2018/07/sohae072318/https://edition.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/07/24/north-korea-dismantling-test-site-starr-dnt-lead-vpx.cnnhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/23/politics/north-korea-satellite-images-38-north-sohae/index.htmlhttp://world.kbs.co.kr/service/news_view.htm?lang=e&Seq_Code=138055***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 08:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/26/3661815/3661815_A9D8F2EB9465479E97DA8408F244CDC4_180726_3661815_Satellite_images_show_North_Korea_dismantling_ke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/374/979/3749798D8EEB4AEC921ED323AEF7B5CC_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,North Korea, missile testing site, dismantling key missing testing site, Sohae Satellite launching station, nuclear missile testing site]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661576</guid>
      <title>Vertical farm company to grow local produce for North Texas stores</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new farming company is planning to offer vertically grown, local produce on a large scale.Eden Green aims to grow produce in vertical lines in a greenhouse to supply to different large-chain grocery stores, reports Forbes.Conventional soil-based farms have an average of two harvests a year, while Eden Green expects to have around 10 to 15 harvests a year.Their first produce line, Crisply, will include vegetables such as lettuce, stevia plants, and other greens.Each plant would be enclosed in a soil-free microclimate bubble free of chemicals, pesticides and herbicides.The company has come up with technology to enable the plants to feed on a steady flow of nutrient-filled water and natural sunlight, instead of LED lights. Eden Green Technology said that the produce are picked and packaged on the same day by the same facility, unlike traditional retailers where the process takes up to nine days.The vertically grown produce can be found at Walmarts across Texas starting this month.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Produce on vines in greenhouse2. Vertical farm harvest compared to traditional farm harvest3. Types of produce grown in greenhouse4. How plant get nutrients from the vertical growing systemVOICEOVER (in English): "Forbes reports Eden Green aims to grow produce in vertical lines in a greenhouse to supply to different large-chain grocery stores.""Conventional soil-based farms have an average of two harvests a year, while Eden Green expects to have around 10 to 15 harvests a year.""Their first produce line, Crisply, will include vegetables such as lettuce, stevia plants, and other greens.""The company has come up with technology to enable the plants to feed on a steady flow of nutrient-filled water and natural sunlight, instead of LED lights. "SOURCES: Forbes, Fox News, FoodBev Media https://www.forbes.com/sites/amyblankson/2018/06/28/cracking-the-food-code-eden-green-technology-aims-to-eliminate-food-deserts/#726afe0c5006https://www.fox4news.com/news/343184175-videohttps://www.foodbev.com/news/eden-green-technology-debuts-new-vertically-farmed-produce/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 03:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/26/3661576/3661576_89131EA9EB904D48B68A9C48A321AEEE_180726_3661576_Vertical_farm_company_to_grow_local_produce_for__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/34E/BDB/34EBDB0B4A9A4D969FDEB9252CBFEBBB_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, vertical farming, vertically stacked layers, vertical farming company, vertical farming firm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662726</guid>
      <title>Here's what the luxurious Airlander 10 could look like</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAerospace company Hybrid Air Vehicles (HAV) has unveiled what the interior of the world's largest aircraft will look like.The Airlander 10 is powered by four 325-horsepower turbocharged diesel engines and uses aerodynamic lift, like a fixed-wing aircraft to take off. Helium keeps the Airlander aloft.The airship can carry payloads of up to 10,000 kilograms and stay in the air for five days at a time with a crew. It also doesn't require a runway.The 302-foot-long airship is about 60 feet longer than the world's largest passenger plane, the Airbus A380.Travelling up to 91 miles per hour, the airship will be able to carry up to 19 passengers to take part in a three-day journey.Designed by aviation and automobile design firm Design Q, the airship features en-suite bedrooms, a bar, and a lounge area. And there's also floor-to-ceiling windows so passengers can enjoy the views from 16,000 feet.Stephen McGlennan, CEO of HAV, said in a press release that Airlander challenges people to rethink the skies. He also mentioned that air travel has become about getting from A to B as quickly as possible, what they are offering is a way of making the journey a joy.In the past, the airship had suffered some setbacks, from a nosedive in August 2016 to a safety feature was triggered that caused the airship deflated in 2017.Airlander 10 has completed six successful test flights so far. It needs to complete 200 incident-free hours to be able to carry passengers for commercial flights.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show Airlander 10 is powered by four turbocharged diesel engines.2. Show Airlander 10 can carry up to 10,000 kg.3. Show Airlander 10 is 60 feet longer than Airbus A380.4. Show Airlander 10 can travel up to 91 mph and carries up to 19 passengers.5. Show Airlander 10 has bedrooms, a bar, and a lounge area.6. Show Airlander 10 interior has floor-to-ceiling windows. VOICEOVER (in English): "Designed by aviation and automobile design firm Design Q, the 302-foot-long Airlander 10 is about 60 feet longer than the world's largest passenger plane, the Airbus A380.""The airship can carry payloads of up to 10,000 kilograms and stay in the air for five days at a time with a crew. It also doesn't require a runway.""Travelling up to 146.45 kilometers, the luxurious airship will be able to carry up to 19 passengers to take part in a three-day journey.""For the interior, the airship features en-suite bedrooms, a bar, and a lounge area.""And there's also floor-to-ceiling windows so passengers can enjoy the views from 16,000 feet."SOURCES: https://www.cntraveler.com/story/the-worlds-largest-aircraft-will-have-luxurious-bedrooms-and-glass-floorshttps://www.hybridairvehicles.com/aircraft/airlander-10http://www.designq.co.uk/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 07:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/27/3662726/3662726_150DE92AAA0A4A049F6D2E9B3FB2F143_180727_3662726_Here_s_what_the_luxurious_Airlander_10_could_loo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1DF/8B5/1DF8B56560D246C2988A892267ED0A25_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, airlander interior, airlander 10 interior, airlander 10 airship interior, hybrid air vehicles, design Q, world's largest aircraft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662390</guid>
      <title>Wearing a tie could be detrimental to your health</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists in Germany recently conducted a study which shows that wearing a tie could actually be bad for you health.According to Business Insider, the study was conducted by taking MRI scans of 15 men who wore ties and 15 men who didn't.The researchers found that tie-wearers received 7.5% less cerebral blood flow than those who didn't wear ties.According to a separate study conducted by the British Journal of Ophthalmology, wearing a tie could also increase the risk of eye problems such as glaucoma and cataracts, as it restricts the blood flow in the arteries and veins of the neck.Researchers at Yonsei University found that people who wear ties usually find their range of motion 'significantly decreased' when they wear a tight necktie.Even the risk of musculoskeletal trauma can be increased just by wearing a tie as tension would accumulate in muscles such as the upper trapezius.However, researchers involved did warn those who have high blood pressure and other health issues may suffer from headaches and nausea if a necktie is worn for too long.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the MRI scan procedure conducted by the scientists.2. Showing the cerebral blood flow percentage decrease the more a person wears a tie.3. Showing the risks of eye problems such as glaucoma and cataracts, and blood flow being restricted.4. Increase of muscle tension in areas such as the upper trapezius.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Business Insider, the study was conducted by taking MRI scans of 15 men who wore ties and 15 men who didn't.""The researchers found that tie-wearers received 7.5% less cerebral blood flow than those who didn't wear ties.""According to a separate study conducted by the British Journal of Ophthalmology, wearing a tie could also increase the risk of eye problems such as glaucoma and cataracts, as it restricts the blood flow in the arteries and veins of the neck.""Even the risk of musculoskeletal trauma can be increased just by wearing a tie as tension would accumulate in muscles such as the upper trapezius."SOURCES: Business Insider, US National Library of Medicine National Institutes of Health, The British Journal of Ophthalmology, Neuroradiology, News Scientisthttps://www.businessinsider.com/wearing-a-tie-could-seriously-damage-your-body-heres-how-2018-7https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs00234-018-2048-7https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/21709362https://www.newscientist.com/article/2173623-wearing-a-tie-may-be-restricting-blood-flow-to-your-brain/https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1771792/https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/21709362***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 03:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/27/3662390/3662390_0E4F189BC0254CD697E98CFC976ECCE9_180727_3662390_Wearing_a_tie_could_be_detrimental_to_your_healt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/ACA/F1E/ACAF1E4C576A4E71A2C9EC1774E6AAFA_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, nausea, arteries, veins, cerebral brain flow, eye problems, glaucoma, cataracts, scientists, necktie, restricted blood flow, muscles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3663500</guid>
      <title>Alphabet-owned Loon plans to bring internet balloons to Kenya</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoogle's sister company Loon, has announced it will soon deploy balloons to bring internet access to remote parts of Kenya.The "internet" balloons are the size of a tennis court and are made of polyethylene. It is also filled with helium and uses a solar panel for power, reports the BBC.The balloons will fly in the stratosphere, around 20 kilometers above sea level.Loon has designed the balloons to stay in the air for months.The company has programmed the balloons to move by wind channels. Its software will predict speed and direction, then maneuver itself to go where it needs to go, reports Wired.The "internet" balloons also have antennas that receive wireless internet signals from a local telecom partner Telkom Kenya, and relays the signal to other balloons in the region.According to a Reuters report, the balloons will provide 4G coverage to areas where internet connection is limited.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing how big the internet balloon is as well as what is inside it. 2. Showing how high the balloon will fly in the stratosphere.3. Showing that the balloon will be powered by software to maneuver using the wind channels.4. Showing how the internet balloon will receive the wireless internet signals from the telecom towers and relay the signal to other balloons. VOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports Loon's 'internet' balloons are the size of a tennis court and are made of polyethylene. It is also filled with helium and uses a solar panel for power.""The balloons will fly in the stratosphere, around 20 kilometers above sea level." "Wired reports the company has programmed the balloons to move by wind channels. Its software would predict the speed and directions then maneuver itself to go where it needs to go.""The 'internet' balloons also have antennas which receives wireless internet signals from a local telecom partner and relays the signal it receives to the other balloons in the region."SOURCES: The BBC, Reuters, EnGadget, Wired,https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-44886803https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-alphabet/alphabet-to-deploy-balloon-internet-in-kenya-with-telkom-in-2019-idUSKBN1K90SVhttps://www.engadget.com/2018/07/19/alphabet-loon-internet-balloon-kenya/https://www.wired.com/story/loon-internet-balloons-kenya-google-alphabet-x/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 09:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/28/3663500/3663500_1CAF48E1B23446E28D596E3B33E62AA7_180728_3663500_Alphabet_owned_Loon_plans_to_bring_internet_ball_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/226/C9E/226C9E7B03FE4495A21896F5462F1DD7_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Alphabet, Loon, balloons, balloons with internet, Kenya, technology, wireless internet connection, internet connection, wind channels]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3664599</guid>
      <title>Worms frozen in permafrost have been brought back to life after 42,000 years by Russian scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study conducted by Russian scientists in collaboration with Princeton University found 300 prehistoric worms in Yakutia, one of the coldest regions of Russia.Two of the worms were "shown to contain viable nematodes", also known as roundworms, reports the Siberian Times.One worm is estimated to be around 32,000 years old while the other is around 42,000 years old.One of the worms was found in an ancient squirrel burrow's permafrost, while the other was found by the Alazeya River.After being defrosted in a laboratory at The Institute of Physico-Chemical and Biological Problems in Moscow, the worms started to move, eat, and show other signs of life.According to the Siberian Times, both the worms are female and are part of the "oldest living animals on the planet."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing where frozen worms were found in Russia.2. Showing that two of the worms contained nematodes. 3. Showing the areas where the two worms were found.4. Showing the defrosting of the worms and them showing signs of life.VOICEOVER (in English): "A study conducted by Russian scientists in collaboration with Princeton University found 300 prehistoric worms in Yakutia, one of the coldest regions of Russia.""The Siberian Times reports, two of the worms were 'shown to contain viable nematodes' also known as roundworms.""One of the worms was found in an ancient squirrel burrow's permafrost, while the other was found by a river.""After being defrosted in a laboratory in Moscow, the worms started to move, eat, and show other signs of life."SOURCES: Ancient Origins.met, RT, The Siberian Times, Viable Nematodes from Late Pleistocene Permafrost of the Kolyma River Lowland Studyhttps://www.ancient-origins.net/news-general/cryobiosis-0010442https://www.rt.com/news/434375-frozen-worms-alive-siberia-permafrost/https://siberiantimes.com/science/casestudy/news/worms-frozen-in-permafrost-for-up-to-42000-years-come-back-to-life/https://link.springer.com/article/10.1134%2FS0012496618030079***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/30/3664599/3664599_2380E8F52AD7489CBFA37E4512FE69B8_180730_3664599_Worms_frozen_in_permafrost_have_been_brought_bac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/ADD/FEB/ADDFEBB67DE64CF691254D0FEBA87D44_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Russia, permafrost worms, worms brought back to life, nematodes, permafrost, roundworms, Siberia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665612</guid>
      <title>Apple's iCloud to store user data in state-run servers in China.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANApple has announced state-owned China Telecom will now store iCloud user data in China.Apple had originally made a deal with Guizhou-Cloud Big Data, to move data from U.S. based servers to Chinese servers, reports TechCrunch.China Telecom then made a deal with Guizhou-Cloud Big Data to provide storage for iCloud in China.The encryption keys to iCloud data used to be stored in the U.S. but now will more than likely be stored in China.In a statement, Apple says it was forced to comply with new Chinese laws.Apple also told Reuters, even though they "advocated against iCloud being subject to these laws," they were ultimately unsuccessful.There are privacy concerns as this gives the Chinese government easier access to personal information, reports the BBC.However, Apple claims users in China can choose to opt out by choosing a country other than China for their iCloud account.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Apple's US based servers making a deal to move data to Guizhou-Cloud Big Data.2.  Depiction of the data moving from Guizhou-Cloud Big Data to China-Telecom.3.  Depiction of the encryption keys guarding personal data moving from the US to China.4.  Depiction of iCloud settings to choose another country.VOICEOVER (in English): "TechCrunch reports, Apple had originally made a deal with Guizhou-Cloud Big Data, to move data from U.S. based servers to Chinese servers.""China Telecom then made a deal with Guizhou-Cloud Big Data to provide storage for iCloud in China.""The encryption keys to iCloud data used to be stored in the U.S. but now will more than likely be stored in China.""However, Apple claims users in China can choose to opt out by choosing a country other than China for their iCloud account."SOURCES: Tech Crunch, The BBC, C Net, The Verge, Global Times, WeChat post from China Telecomhttps://techcrunch.com/2018/07/17/apples-icloud-user-data-in-china-is-now-handled-by-a-state-owned-mobile-operator/https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-44870508https://www.cnet.com/news/chinas-state-owned-telecom-company-is-now-storing-icloud-data/https://www.theverge.com/2018/7/18/17587304/apple-icloud-china-user-data-state-run-telecom-privacy-securityhttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1111251.shtmlhttps://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/c2-hQ7WFWkGRNcfD0YlYVw***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/31/3665612/3665612_166768CEB86F40DE925B93AFB5B03063_180731_3665612_Apple_s_iCloud_to_store_user_data_in_state_run_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/0CA/8D4/0CA8D4A277424F1997BED26FA5421C11_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, China, Apple, iCloud, China Telecom, privacy, user data, user storage, iCloud data, security concerns, encryption]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665122</guid>
      <title>Time capsule from 1968 to be opened this year in September</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA time capsule from the year 1968 will be opened in September this year, 50 years after it was placed inside the Helium Time monument in Texas.The Helium Time monument is a six story, stainless steel structure which was made to commemorate the 100th anniversary of the discovery of helium.The monument holds four time capsule columns that are slanted and hold books, artifacts, and documents to "tell the future generation about … life … in 1968," reports the Atlas Obscura.Helium is pumped into each column to "protect fragile documents" and other items from deteriorating.Each of the time capsules are scheduled to be opened at different time periods. The first one was opened after 25 years in 1993, and the rest will be opened after 50, 100, and 1000 years after their placements. The monument was reportedly created to remind future generations "the importance for efficiently utilizing natural resources."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the structure of the Helium Time monument. 2. Showing the time capsules and the objects it holds inside.3. Showing how helium helps to preserve the objects inside.4. Showing how the time capsules are meant to be open at different times.VOICEOVER (in English): "The Helium Time monument is a six story, stainless steel structure which was made to commemorate the 100th anniversary of discovering helium.""The Atlas Obscura reports the monument holds four time-capsule columns which are slanted and have books, artifacts, and documents to 'tell the future generation about..life..in 1968.""Helium is pumped into each column and is used to "protect fragile documents" and other items from deteriorating.""Each of the time capsule would be opened at different time periods. The first one was opened after 25 years in 1993, and the rest will be opened after 50, 100, and 1000 years after being placed. "SOURCES: Atlas Obscura, North Texas Ramblings, https://www.atlasobscura.com/places/helium-time-columns-monumenthttp://northtexasramblings.com/helium-monument-in-amarillo/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 02:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/31/3665122/3665122_4A6FC5D4FE5949898CCA5B58EA3A0CF2_180731_3665122_Time_capsule_from_1968_to_be_opened_this_year_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/8D0/904/8D090437CE5E4757AE3574E17537C52B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, US, Time capsule, monument, 1968, time-capsule columns, helium-filled columns, natural resources, books, artifacts, documents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665118</guid>
      <title>Old railway to be converted into a green corridor in Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn old railway in central Taiwan will soon be designed into a public green space, reports Taiwan News.Part of the old railway will be transformed into a mile-long partially elevated greenway, where people can stroll around.The new green corridor will also include a bicycle lane.Mecanoo, the architecture firm designing the project, explained there will also be a tree-lined river along the newly transformed green corridor.Mecanoo said their goal is to "preserve the area's strong historic character" while giving new life to the old railway.The firm plans to integrate gardens, playgrounds, parks etc into the green corridor, reports Inhabitant.Local media reports the green corridor will be a space for leisure and recreational activities.Reports from local media say the project is expected to start later this year and be completed by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show the old railway and the partially elevated greenway2. Show railroad tracks being transformed into bikeway3. Show the tree-lined river 4. Showing the green corridorVOICEOVER (in English): "Part of the old railway will be transformed into a mile-long partially elevated greenway.""The new green corridor will also include a bicycle lane.""Mecanoo, the architecture firm designing the project, explained there will also be a tree-lined river along the newly transformed green corridor.""Local media reports the green corridor will be a space for leisure and recreational activities."SOURCES: Inhabitant, CNA, Taiwan News,China Times,https://inhabitat.com/a-disused-railway-will-be-reborn-as-a-sustainable-green-corridor-in-taiwan/http://www.cna.com.tw/news/aloc/201806190107-1.aspxhttps://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3451214http://www.chinatimes.com/realtimenews/20180619001835-260415***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 02:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/07/31/3665118/3665118_0E6F9EEBFD7143AE9AFEE5E2AB43899B_180731_3665118_Old_railway_to_be_converted_into_a_green_corrido_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/197/1B5/1971B52395C14D599691C2F4F5A69140_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Taiwan, old railway, Green space, public green space, going green, green design, green corridor, old railway to turn into green corridor, greenway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666260</guid>
      <title>Facebook shuts down political influence campaign targeting 2018 midterms</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook has uncovered a complex disinformation campaign that may have been aimed at influencing the upcoming U.S. midterm elections.According to a report from Facebook, 32 false pages and accounts on Facebook and Instagram between March 2017 and May 2018 have been removed after they violated a ban on coordinated inauthentic behavior.The operatives put out a total of 9,500 posts Facebook, luring 290,000 people, who reportedly followed at least one of the pages.From April 2017 to June this year, the accounts ran 150 ads worth $11,000, paid for in American and Canadian dollars. They also created 30 events which attracted the interest of 4,700 accounts.One bogus page that promoted a counterprotest even coordinated with administrators from legitimate pages to co-host the event. Those admins have since been notified.Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg says investigation into the operation is still ongoing, reports the Washington Post.And while they haven't expressly identified the Russians as the culprits, tools and techniques used in this case were similar to those used by the Internet Research Agency, a Kremlin-linked group believed to have interfered with the 2016 presidential elections.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of false pages and accounts on Facebook, Instagram2. Depiction of number of posts and followers3. Depiction of online ads and events created by the operation4. Depiction of inauthentic administrator connecting with admins from legit pages to co-host eventVOICEOVER (in English): "Thirty-two false pages and profiles on Facebook and Instagram between March 2017 and May 2018 have been removed after they violated a ban on coordinated inauthentic behavior.""The operatives put out a total of 9,500 posts Facebook, luring 290,000 people, who reportedly followed at least one of the pages.""From April 2017 to June this year, the accounts ran 150 ads worth $11,000, paid for in American and Canadian dollars. They also created 30 events which attracted the interest of 4,700 accounts.""One bogus page that promoted a counterprotest even coordinated with administrators from legitimate pages to co-host the event. Those admins have since been notified."SOURCES: Facebook, Washington Post, New York Timeshttps://newsroom.fb.com/news/2018/07/removing-bad-actors-on-facebook/https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2018/07/31/facebook-says-it-has-uncovered-coordinated-disinformation-operation-ahead-midterm-elections/?utm_term=.e92701c7c2e6https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/31/us/politics/facebook-political-campaign-midterms.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 10:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/01/3666260/3666260_EA46D315D8CD49DABFBA90FB367468E6_180801_3666260_Facebook_shuts_down_political_influence_campaign_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/499/ED9/499ED96F44F740CBA715F1194D29208D_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Facebook, fake accounts, Instagram, 2018 midterms, midterm elections, disinformation campaign, disinformation operation, Russian interference, internet research agency, politics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665883</guid>
      <title>Study shows dehydration can impact cognitive thinking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in the Medicine & Science in Sports & Exercise shows that even becoming mildly dehydrated has the ability to affect one's ability to think clearly.Dehydration can impair the brain's ability to complete tasks such as proofreading, mental math, and even map recognition, Reuters reports.Mindy Millard-Stafford, co-author of the study, told NPR that it wouldn't take long to become mildly dehydrated in the summer, especially if you exercise outside.The study found that participants lost up to 1 to 6 percent of fluids equal to their body mass through exercise alone.Millard-Stafford commented to Reuters, saying human brain cells need water just like the cells in muscle.However, NPR reports, coffee or other caffeinated beverages also have a hydrating effect.Dr. Ronald Roth, a professor at the University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine, said if a person experiences fatigue, confusion, and muscle weakness among other symptoms, is a reminder to consume more fluids.Dr. Roth also said it is important to know when you are overdoing it and taking in too much water as that may lead to hyponatremia, which is an excess of water in the body compared to the ratio of sodium, Reuters reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the brain becoming impaired to complete simple tasks such as proofreading, mental math, and map recognition. 2. Showing a beaker of fluid to represent the fluid in our body, and how it decreases.3. Showing that the brain cells need water just like the cells in our muscles.4. Showing other beverages that could replace water to hydrate the body.VOICEOVER (in English): "Reuters reports dehydration can impair the brain's ability to complete tasks such as proofreading, mental math, and even map recognition.""The study found that participants lost up to 1-6 percent of fluids equal to their body mass through exercise alone.""Millard-Stafford commented to Reuters, saying human brain cells need water just like the cells in muscle." "However, NPR reports, coffee or other caffeinated beverages also have a hydrating effect."SOURCES: NPR, Medicine & Science in Sports & Exercise report, Newser, Reutershttps://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2018/07/30/632480321/off-your-mental-game-you-could-be-mildly-dehydratedhttps://journals.lww.com/acsm-msse/Abstract/publishahead/Dehydration_Impairs_Cognitive_Performance___A.96880.aspxhttp://www.newser.com/story/262666/dehydrated-your-brainpower-could-be-impacted.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-dehydration-cognition/dehydration-may-muddle-your-thinking-idUSKBN1JV30M***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 02:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/01/3665883/3665883_0602CAC793E44A5E813BBB0453B34C1E_180801_3665883_Study_shows_dehydration_can_impact_cognitive_thi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BF7/D4B/BF7D4B00C5F54A2BA33A678E137177E9_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Study, cognitive thinking, dehydration, mildly dehydrated, water intake, dehydration symptoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665875</guid>
      <title>Different ways your cryptocurrency could be lost</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWith the rise of cryptocurrency, there is also the risk of losing your digital currency because of its decentralized model.Fraud is on the rise for cryptocurrency as anonymous accounts are usually used and there is no way of noticing suspicious transactions, reports Entrepreneur Asia Pacific.Password recovery can also be a problem because of the complex structure put in to supposedly prevent fraud, denying people access to their own account.Hacking is another issue for cryptocurrency. There are a large amount of crypto wallets out there which once hacked, won't ever be able to recover the digital money because of a weak security system.Virtual currency scams is another reason why some end up losing their cryptocurrency, with some on social media offering to send you a 100 Ether coins, or any other digital currency, if you send them just one, reports Bloomberg.As the number of cryptocurrencies available online keep on growing, sooner or later it may have to regulated because of the amounts of problems caused by deregulation of crypto.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing cryptocurrencies transactions.2. Showing how losing your password account could result in loss of digital money. 3. Showing crypto wallets being hacked because of a weak security system. 4. Showing how virtual currency scams online could lead to the loss of cryptocurrency.VOICEOVER (in English): "Entrepreneur Asia Pacific reports fraud is on the rise for cryptocurrency as anonymous accounts are usually used and there is no way of noticing suspicious transactions.""Password recovery can also be a problem because of the complex structure put in to supposedly prevent fraud, denying people access to their own account.""Hacking is another issue for cryptocurrency. There are a large amount of crypto wallets out there which once hacked, won't ever be able to recover the digital money because of a weak security system.""Bloomberg reports virtual currency scams is another reason why some end up losing their cryptocurrency, with some on social media offering to send you a 100 Ether coins, or any other digital currency, if you send them just one. "SOURCES:Entrepreneur, Bloomberg, Cryptocurrency Hub, Bitcoinist, Equities, https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/316802https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-29/cryptocurrency-all-the-ways-you-can-lose-your-bitcoinhttps://cryptocurrencyhub.io/5-stupid-ways-to-lose-your-bitcoin-millions-7b169093436ehttps://bitcoinist.com/5-ways-lose-bitcoins-prevent/https://www.equities.com/news/7-risks-of-cryptocurrency-investing-and-how-to-handle-them***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 02:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/01/3665875/3665875_A3AAA010821A450997F65BCC4A2923B3_180801_3665875_Different_ways_your_cryptocurrency_could_be_lost_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/7AF/414/7AF414691B3A42E09571C64C24EFFB7B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, cryptocurrency, hacking, virtual money, bitcoin, virtual scams, deregulation, crypto,digital currency, cryptocurrency explained, cryptocurrency investing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
