<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 11:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3993803</guid>
      <title>North and South Korean troops fire at each other across the DMZ: South Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth and South Korean troops exchanged small arms fire in the demilitarized zone on May 3. Citing a statement from the South Korean joint chiefs of staff, the Korea Herald reports North Korea fired first but inflicted no casualties on South Korean forces.According to the Yonhap News Agency, North Korean troops fired multiple shots at a South Korean outpost early in the morning, while the garrison returned two shots.The South Korean military states North Korea apparently fired "unintentionally."The state-funded news agency cites the military as saying the morning's fog would have obscured firing targets. Additionally, the ground occupied by North Korean troops offered no tactical advantage over the outpost.The 155-mile or 250-km-long DMZ is heavily defended by mines, fences and guard posts, and rates as the world's most militarized border.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korean troops reportedly initiated the exchange by opening fire at border outpost2. South Korean soldiers returned two shots and took no casualties3. North Korea reportedly opened fire unintentionally 4. The demilitarized zone is considered the world's most heavily armed borderVOICEOVER (in English): "North and South Korean troops exchanged small arms fire in the demilitarized zone on May 3." "Citing a statement from the South Korean joint chiefs of staff, the Korea Herald reports North Korea fired first but inflicted no casualties on South Korean forces.""According to the Yonhap News Agency, North Korean troops fired multiple shots at a South Korean outpost early in the morning, while the garrison returned two shots.""The South Korean military states North Korea apparently fired, quote, 'unintentionally.'""The state-funded news agency cites the military as saying the morning's fog would have obscured firing targets." "Additionally, the ground occupied by North Korean troops offered no tactical advantage over the outpost.""The 155-mile or 250-km-long DMZ is heavily defended by mines, fences and guard posts, and rates as the world's most militarized border."SOURCES: The Korea Herald, Yonhap News Agency, The New York Times http://www.koreaherald.com/view.php?ud=20200503000176https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20200503002451325https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20200503003551315https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2020/05/03/asia-pacific/south-korea-gunshots-north-korea-guard-post/#.Xq9ksEYzY2whttps://www.nytimes.com/2020/05/02/world/asia/South-Korea-North-Gunfire-DMZ.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 08:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/04/3993803/3993803_322597A214214B6983320BE0918763F8_200504_3993803_North_and_South_Korean_troops_fire_at_each_other_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, North Korea, South Korea, exchanged gunfire, DMZ, 38th parallel, border skirmish, international relations, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3993782</guid>
      <title>World's largest iceberg may soon break up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIt looks like the beginning of the end for the world's largest iceberg, the BBC reports. New satellite images show Iceberg A-68 lost a 175 square km chunk of ice, which will likely be called Iceberg A-68c, between satellite passes on April 21 and April 22, according to images from the Copernicus Sentinel-1 mission.Iceberg A-68 broke off from the Larsen Ice Shelf in July of 2017 and remained largely intact for three years as it drifted past the Antarctic Peninsula in the Weddell Sea. Today it is around 5,000 square km, almost four times the size of Greater London. Currents in the Southern Ocean are now pushing the iceberg past the South Orkney Islands into increasingly warmer waters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of Iceberg A-68 when Iceberg A-68c breaks off2. Size comparison of Iceberg A-68 to Greater London, Cyprus and Hawaii3. Iceberg A-68 calved from Antarctica's Larsen C Ice Shelf in July of 20174. Iceberg A-68 being pushed north by currents in the Southern OceanVOICEOVER (in English): "It looks like the beginning of the end for the world's largest iceberg." "New satellite images show Iceberg A-68 lost a 175 square km chunk of ice, which will likely be called Iceberg A-68c, between satellite passes on April 21 and April 22.""When it first calved from Antarctica's Larsen C Ice Shelf, Iceberg A-68 was nearly 6,000 square km in size, according to images from the Copernicus Sentinel-1 mission.""Today it is around 5,000 square km. That's almost four times the size of Greater London, or roughly half the size of the islands of Hawaii or Cyprus." "The giant chunk of ice is 160 km long, but only a couple of hundred meters thick, making it remarkably thin for an iceberg of its size.""Iceberg A-68 broke off from the Larsen Ice Shelf in July of 2017, losing a small piece called Iceberg A-68b shortly after it calved. Iceberg A-68 then remained largely intact for three years as it drifted past the Antarctic Peninsula in the Weddell Sea.""Currents in the Southern Ocean are now pushing the iceberg past the South Orkney Islands. As it drifts into warmer waters, it is expected to fragment into smaller ice blocks, many of which could last for years among the ice surrounding Antarctica." SOURCES: BBC, Weather Network, Copernicus Programme, NASAhttps://ca.news.yahoo.com/satellite-images-reveal-iceberg-68s-202000789.htmlhttps://adrianluckman.wordpress.com/2019/07/11/happy-second-birthday-iceberg-a68/https://earthobservatory.nasa.gov/images/146603/a-68a-holding-it-together***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 08:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/04/3993782/3993782_33110D153D6A45F89DD8155DCD32E7D3_200504_3993782_World_s_largest_iceberg_may_soon_break_up_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Iceberg A-68, Iceberg A68, Iceberg A-68a, Iceberg A-68c, A68 iceberg, A68, iceberg collapse, icebergs breaking off, iceberg]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994011</guid>
      <title>Microplastics disrupt hermit crabs' ability to select shells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in the journal Biology Letters has found that exposure to microplastics can disrupt a hermit crab's ability to choose a shell. Researchers from Queen's University Belfast and Liverpool John Moores University placed 29 female hermit crabs into a tank containing microplastics. A control group of 35 crabs was placed into a tank with no microplastics. After five days the crabs were moved into lower-quality shells and presented with the option to choose a higher-quality shell. Only nine of the crabs that had been exposed to microplastics moved into the new shells, compared to 21 from the control group.This suggests exposure to microplastics impairs the crabs' cognition, and that microplastics in general can have important effects on an animal's behavior.Gareth Arnott, co-author of the new research from Queen's University Belfast, told the Guardian he was surprised by the results. "We hypothesize that either some aspect of the polyethylene is getting into them to affect their decision making, or else it is an indirect effect that the presence of the plastic in the tank might be influencing their feeding behavior, for example," he said.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hermit crab changing shells2. One group of hermit crabs exposed to microplastics, control group not exposed3. Hermit crabs exposed to microplastics less likely to explore and move into optimal shell4. Hermit crab feeding on ocean floor contaminated by microplastics VOICEOVER (in English): "Hermit crabs do not grow their own shells but instead use shells from other marine creatures, typically those of sea snails, to protect themselves. As they grow they swap shells for ones that are a better fit.""Researchers from Queen's University Belfast and Liverpool John Moores University placed 29 female hermit crabs into a tank containing seawater, seaweed and 4mm-diameter polyethylene beads. A control group of 35 crabs was placed into a tank with only seawater and seaweed.""After five days the crabs were moved into lower-quality shells and presented with the option to choose a higher-quality shell. Only 10 of the crabs that had been exposed to microplastics explored the more ideal shell, compared to 25 crabs from the control group. Only nine of the crabs that had been exposed to microplastics moved into the new shells, compared to 21 from the control group.""This suggests exposure to microplastics impairs the crabs' cognition, and that microplastics in general can have important effects on an animal's behavior."SOURCES: The Guardian, Biology Lettershttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/apr/29/microplastics-disrupt-hermit-crabs-ability-to-choose-shell-study-suggestshttps://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsbl.2020.0030***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/05/3994011/3994011_49EDC8430EBF4D49A89E431850445697_200505_3994011_Microplastics_disrupt_hermit_crabs__ability_to_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, hermit crabs, ocean pollution, plastic in the ocean, plastic in the ocean, microplastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic affecting marine life, plastic affecting our environment, plastic cognition, plastic animal behavior, plastic, environment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3993988</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus pandemic could last up to two years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA report by the University of Minnesota's Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy published last Thursday predicts that the coronavirus pandemic could last from 18 to 24 months.Experts who participated in the study believe the pandemic will not stop until around 60 to 70 percent of the population becomes immune to the virus.The coronavirus's longer incubation period and high R0, or reproduction number, make it a highly contagious virus. According to a study published in Emerging Infectious Diseases, COVID-19's R0 is a median of 5.7, meaning an infected individual can spread the virus to five to six people.The study suggests all authorities should prepare for the worst-case scenario or scenario 2, which according to their study is one where the first wave of the spread is followed by a larger wave in the fall or winter of this year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Spread of coronavirus2. Two-thirds of population infected and then immunized to the coronavirus3. R0 number of coronavirus 4. People using facemasks to prevent spread of virusVOICEOVER (in English): "A report by the University of Minnesota's Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy published last Thursday predicts that the coronavirus pandemic could last from 18 to 24 months.""Experts who participated in the study believe the pandemic will not stop until around 60 to 70 percent of the population becomes immune to the virus.""The coronavirus's longer incubation period and high R0, or reproduction number, make it a highly contagious virus. According to a study published in Emerging Infectious Diseases, COVID-19's R0 is a median of 5.7, meaning an infected individual can spread the virus to five to six people.""The study suggests all authorities should prepare for the worst-case scenario or scenario 2, which according to their study is one where the first wave of the spread is followed by a larger wave in the fall or winter of this year."SOURCES: Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy, Emerging Infectious Diseaseshttps://www.cidrap.umn.edu/sites/default/files/public/downloads/cidrap-covid19-viewpoint-part1_0.pdfhttps://wwwnc.cdc.gov/eid/article/26/7/20-0282_article***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/05/3993988/3993988_5FD04BC3B82C436A88E9C7C93507304A_200505_3993988_Coronavirus_pandemic_could_last_up_to_two_years_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus animation, covid-19 animation, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus spread, coronavirus pandemic, COVID-19, COVID-19 virus, COVID-19 pandemic, novel coronavirus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994743</guid>
      <title>Explainer: Why is the coronavirus so deadly?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVOICEOVER:"COVID-19 is an airborne disease that spreads in tiny droplets that contain the new coronavirus, known as SARS-CoV-2. When people inhale contaminated droplets, the virus enters into the nose and the throat.""COVID-19 infection usually begins in the nose and throat, because the mucous membranes of these sites contain epithelial cells that are rich in ACE2 cell surface receptors. The virus needs to exploit ACE2 to get into human cells.""The coronavirus's outer coating is covered in spike proteins that give the virus its crown-like appearance. The spike protein possesses receptor binding domains, or RBDs, that the virus uses to pry open receptors before penetrating the cellular membrane.""The ACE2 receptor normally regulates blood pressure. But the coronavirus's downward RBD can bind with this receptor and allow the virus to enter, and then hijack, the host cell.""Once the virus enters the human cell, its coating dissolves and frees viral RNA to hijack the host cell's apparatuses. The cell's endoplasmic reticulum produces viral RNA and proteins, while its Golgi body packages them into whole new viruses.""As the virus multiplies, the infected person may develop early symptoms, such as a sore throat and dry cough, while spreading plentiful amounts of the virus to others. Other symptoms for the first week of infection include fever; a loss of smell and taste; and muscle aches.""The lungs contain air sacs called alveoli that keep us alive by exchanging carbon dioxide for oxygen. If the virus moves down the lungs, it attacks the alveoli, which are lined with vulnerable, ACE2 receptor-rich cells.""To fight off infections, white blood cells release cytokines to summon more immune cells. Pneumonic COVID-19 may trigger cytokine storm syndrome, a phenomenon where the body scrambles too many immune cells.""As the virus attacks the lungs, the cytokine storm floods the lungs with white blood cells that destroy both healthy and infected cells. This fills the air sacs with liquids, mucous and the detritus of dead cells.""Pneumonic COVID-19 disrupts the exchange of oxygen and damages the lungs extensively, which leads to dangerously low oxygen levels that may become fatal.""When the virus gets into the heart, it strikes blood vessel cells that are rich in ACE2 receptors. Clinical studies suggest the viral onslaught causes blood clots that obstruct the artilleries and trigger heart attacks.""Intestinal cells that are responsible for absorbing nutrition called enterocytes also express the RNA for ACE2 and a related enzyme that the virus also exploits, which makes the intestines vulnerable.""A clinical study from the Chinese city of Wuhan found more than a third of COVID-19 patients suffered neurological complications." "According to the neurological study, as many as 35 percent of patients had neurological complications including impaired cognition, stroke and muscle damage. Blood clots that travelled to the brain could be the cause of the strokes."SOURCES: National Library of Medicine, Lancet, JAMA Neurology, Nature, MIT, American Academy of Otolaryngology, Europe PMChttps://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/15141377https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(20)30628-0/fulltexthttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/2764549https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-020-0868-6https://news.mit.edu/2020/researchers-cells-targeted-covid-19-0422https://www.entnet.org/content/aao-hns-anosmia-hyposmia-and-dysgeusia-symptoms-coronavirus-diseasehttps://europepmc.org/article/med/32026671***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 09:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/06/3994743/3994743_96CBD83303AC457A89CA60CC3DD6C4B2_200506_3994743_Explainer__Why_is_the_coronavirus_so_deadly__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, pneumonia, cytokine storm, cytokine storm syndrome, immune system overreaction, heart failure, neurological complications, explainer, health, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994630</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered microbe can stop mosquitoes from carrying malaria: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers in Kenya discovered a microbe that can completely prevent mosquitoes from carrying malaria.According to the study published in Nature Communications, the microbe could be used to check the spread of malaria around the world.The research teams from the UK and Kenya found that the malaria-stopping fungal microbe called Microsporidia MB was present in 5 percent of the mosquitoes they sampled.The fungus grows in the genitalia and digestive system of mosquitoes, and the data suggests it is 100 percent effective in stopping malaria from infecting mosquitoes.Speaking to the BBC, the authors say they do not as yet know how the fungus stops malaria.The paper's lead author Jeremy Heren says at least 40 percent of mosquitoes in a region need to be infected with the fungus to curb malaria transmission.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mosquito researchers found a malaria-blocking microbe 2. Fungal microbe Microsporidia MB is present in 5 percent of mosquitoes in the region3. The microbe grows in mosquito genitalia and guts4. Microbe must infect 40 percent of mosquitoes in a region to act as check on malariaVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers in Kenya discovered a microbe that can completely prevent mosquitoes from carrying malaria.""According to the study published in Nature Communications, the microbe could be used to check the spread of malaria around the world.""The research teams from the UK and Kenya found that the malaria-stopping fungal microbe called Microsporidia MB was present in 5 percent of the mosquitoes they sampled.""The fungus grows in the genitalia and digestive system of mosquitoes, and the data suggests it is 100 percent effective in stopping malaria from infecting mosquitoes." "Speaking to the BBC, the authors say they do not as yet know how the fungus stops malaria.""The paper's lead author Jeremy Heren says at least 40 percent of mosquitoes in a region need to be infected with the fungus to curb malaria transmission."SOURCES: Nature Communications, BBChttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-020-16121-yhttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-52530828***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/06/3994630/3994630_F32F5883D43442C1A49D35A39337F9D8_200506_3994630_Newly_discovered_microbe_can_stop_mosquitoes_fro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Microsporidia MB, fungus, microbe, fungal microbe, fungal parasite, mosquitoes, mosquito, malaria, malaria-blocking, Kenya, Africa, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994568</guid>
      <title>Invasive 'Murder Hornets' could threaten bee populations in the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLast December, the Washington State Department of Agriculture confirmed two reports of Asian giant hornets in Blaine, Washington. Reuters reports that two more unconfirmed sightings were reported in Custer, Washington. These killer hornets are now coming out of winter hibernation.Native to Southeast Asia, China and Taiwan, Asian giant hornets can measure between 1.5 to 2 inches, or 3.8 to 25 centimeters, in length. Vespa mandarinia, also known as Murder Hornets, have stingers that deliver venom to their victims and mandibles capable of decapitating bees.According to the WSU Insider, the Asian giant hornet queen wakes from hibernation in April, finds nourishment and then looks for a place to establish a colony that will later go out to bring back food.The bee population in the United States is most threatened by these hornets from late summer to early fall. While they hunt for food for their next queens, the hornets will decapitate honey bees and eat the bee's larvae and pupae.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of giant Asian hornet sightings2. Size of giant Asian hornet3. Giant Asian hornet awakening from hibernation4. Giant Asian hornets attacking a honeybee beehiveVOICEOVER (in English):"Last December, the Washington State Department of Agriculture confirmed two reports of Asian giant hornets in Blaine, Washington. Reuters reports that two more unconfirmed sightings were reported in Custer, Washington.""These killer hornets are now coming out of winter hibernation.""Native to Southeast Asia, China and Taiwan, Asian giant hornets can measure between 1.5 to 2 inches, or 3.8 to 25 centimeters, in length. Vespa mandarinia, also known as Murder Hornets, have stingers that deliver venom to their victims and mandibles capable of decapitating bees.""According to the WSU Insider, the Asian giant hornet queen wakes from hibernation in April, finds nourishment and then looks for a place to establish a colony that will later go out to bring back food.""The bee population in the United States is most threatened by these hornets from late summer to early fall. While they hunt for food for their next queens, the hornets will decapitate honey bees and eat the bee's larvae and pupae."SOURCES: Washington State University, Washington State Department of Agriculturehttps://news.wsu.edu/2020/04/06/wsu-scientists-enlist-citizens-hunt-giant-bee-killing-hornet/https://wastatedeptag.blogspot.com/2019/12/pest-alert-asian-giant-hornet.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 03:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/06/3994568/3994568_A5133F0214974DF3AF10DD5B78215F98_200506_3994568_Invasive__Murder_Hornets__could_threaten_bee_pop_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, giant asian hornet, giant hornet, murder hornet, murder hornets, asian hornet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3995127</guid>
      <title>Researchers discover evidence of ancient rivers on Mars: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists believe water may have run in rivers on ancient Mars 3.7 billion years ago, according to a paper published in Nature Communications.Researchers speculate that the system these rivers formed existed for more than 100,000 years in Mars's geological history. Using data gathered by NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter, scientists surveyed the Hellas Basin and discovered signs on a 200-meter-tall cliff that suggests the region used to support a river system.Writing in a news release, the team says the extremely high-resolution image from the orbiter's camera allowed them to read the cliff face and see sedimentary rocks that one would find on riverbanks.According to the researchers, these ancient rivers probably changed their gullies and left behind sandbanks like certain rivers on Earth, such as the Rhine in Germany and rivers in Northern Italy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. River system may have existed on Mars2. Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter3. Cliff in Hellas Basin show evidence of sedimentation4. Martian rivers left behind remains of gullies and sandbanksVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists believe water may have run in rivers on ancient Mars 3.7 billion years ago, according to a paper published in Nature Communications.""Researchers speculate that the system these rivers formed existed for more than 100,000 years in Mars's geological history." "Using data gathered by NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter, scientists surveyed the Hellas Basin and discovered signs on a 200-meter-tall cliff that suggests the region used to support a river system.""Writing in a news release, the team says the extremely high-resolution image from the orbiter's camera allowed them to read the cliff face and see sedimentary rocks that one would find on riverbanks.""According to the researchers, these ancient rivers probably changed their gullies and left behind sandbanks like certain rivers on Earth, such as the Rhine in Germany and rivers in Northern Italy."SOURCES: Nature Communications, Utrecht University https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-020-15622-0https://www.uu.nl/en/news/reading-the-rocks-to-find-ancient-water-on-mars***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 09:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/07/3995127/3995127_48FF7639EF9646379C467CA8FE3D53DB_200507_3995127_Researchers_discover_evidence_of_ancient_rivers__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mars, water, rivers, river network, river system, Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter, Hellas, Utrecht University, NASA, technology, science, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3995521</guid>
      <title>Scientists may have spotted the black hole nearest to Earth: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists may have spotted a black hole so close to Earth that its two companion stars are visible to the naked eye, according to a paper in Astronomy and Physics.Writing in a news release, researchers at the European Southern Observatory say the black hole is 1,000 light-years distant in the system HR 6819 system, which is part of the constellation Telescopium.According to the paper, the black hole is 1,000 light-years distant in the system HR 6819 system, which is part of the constellation Telescopium.Scientists say a black hole is usually identified by the accretion disk it forms as it devours a nearby star and the energy that it releases into space.However, the black hole of HR 6819 exists peacefully with its stellar companions, and astronomers used the orbits of the two stars to infer that an object with four times the solar mass is in the system, which can only be a black hole.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location and distance from Earth of the newly discovered black hole2. Black holes are usually identified as they absorb nearby stars3. The new black hole is not visible because it does not devour stellar companions VOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists at the European Southern Observatory report they may have spotted a black hole so close to Earth that its two companion stars are visible to the naked eye.""According to the paper in Astronomy and Physics, the black hole is 1,000 light-years distant in the system HR 6819 system, which is part of the constellation Telescopium.""Writing in a news release, the scientists say a black hole is usually identified by the accretion disk it forms as it devours a nearby star and the energy that it releases into space.""However, the black hole of HR 6819 exists peacefully with its stellar companions, and astronomers used the orbits of the two stars to infer that an object with four times the solar mass is in the system, which can only be a black hole."SOURCES: Astronomy and Physics, European Southern Observatoryhttps://www.eso.org/public/archives/releases/sciencepapers/eso2007/eso2007a.pdfhttps://www.eso.org/public/news/eso2007/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 09:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/08/3995521/3995521_EF53F11DC8B34DC78C239C0C3313E79C_200508_3995521_Scientists_may_have_spotted_the_black_hole_neare_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, black hole, black hole nearest to Earth, black hole closest to earth, invisible black hole, HR 6819, Telescopium, constellation Telescopium, European Southern Observatory, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3995511</guid>
      <title>The shooting of Ahmoud Arbery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to The Baltimore Sun, on February 23, Ahmaud Arbery, 25, was running inside the Satilla Shores neighborhood in Brunswick, Georgia when Gregory McMichael, 64, who was standing in his front yard, noticed him.Gregory believed Arbery looked like a man responsible for several break-ins in the neighborhood so he notified his son, 34-year-old Travis McMichael. They both got into a white pickup truck to go after Arbery. They were carrying a .357 Magnum and a shotgun, respectively.The father and son then proceeded to chase Arbery, stopping their vehicle in front of the road at which point Arbery ran around the pickup truck.Video footage believed to be shot by William Bryan, a third individual participating in the pursuit, shows Travis McMichaels holding a shotgun while having a physical altercation with Arbery. Three shots can be heard. Arbery succumbed from his wounds.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Arbery is jogging and noticed by Gregory McMichael2. Gregory McMichael and Travis McMichael get on pick up truck and start following Arbery3. The McMichaels block Arbery with their car, Arbery runs around their car4. Arbery and Travis McMichael have an altercation, shots are fired and Arbery is killedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Baltimore Sun, on February 23, Ahmaud Arbery, 25, was running inside the Satilla Shores neighborhood in Brunswick, Georgia when Gregory McMichael, 64, who was standing in his front yard, noticed him.""Gregory believed Arbery looked like a man responsible for several break-ins in the neighborhood so he notified his son, 34-year-old Travis McMichael. They both got into a white pickup truck to go after Arbery. They were carrying a .357 Magnum and a shotgun, respectively. ""The father and son then proceeded to chase Arbery, stopping their vehicle in front of the road at which point Arbery ran around the pickup truck.""Video footage believed to be shot by William Bryan, a third individual participating in the pursuit, shows Travis McMichaels holding a shotgun while having a physical altercation with Arbery. Three shots can be heard. Arbery succumbed from his wounds."SOURCES: Georgia Bureau of Investigation, The Baltimore Sun https://gbi.georgia.gov/press-releases/2020-05-06/ahmaud-arbery-death-investigationhttps://www.baltimoresun.com/news/nation-world/ct-nw-nyt-what-we-know-shooting-death-ahmaud-arbery-georgia-20200506-qhl2l7ax4bdprb7f4pgyk6bcom-story.htmlhttps://georgiarecorder.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Barnhill-letter-Brunswick-shooting.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 09:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/08/3995511/3995511_9AB572ECD70D4EF196FF4E0BB0FE6A85_200508_3995511_The_shooting_of_Ahmoud_Arbery_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ahmoud arbery, ahmoud arbery shooting, amour arbery killed, Travis McMichaels, Gregory McMichaels, Georgia Bureau of Investigation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3995445</guid>
      <title>Thieves Steal 97 Cars During Lockdown in New Zealand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA group of thieves broke into a Jucy Rentals parking lot, stealing 97 vehicles in total. According to the BBC, a group of thieves cut through a fence of a Jucy Rentals parking lot in Auckland, New Zealand. They lifted the gate and began taking cars, stealing 97 vehicles in total. Jucy Rentals chief executive Tim Alpe told the New Zealand Herald he believed the heist occurred on April 25. The New Zealand Herald reports the thieves stole unbranded Holden Captivas, Mazda 3s, and Suzuki Swifts along with some green and purple branded campervans.Lockdown regulations have kept New Zealand's streets mostly empty. However, police were still patrolling when they began chasing a car that they believed looked suspicious.The BBC reports that 85 of the 97 stolen cars have been found and returned to Jucy, and 29 individuals believed to be linked with the heist have been arrested.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Thieves break into parking lot2. Models of cars stolen3. Police follow a stolen vehicle4. Cars returned to Jucy RentalsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, a group of thieves cut through a fence of a Jucy Rentals parking lot in Auckland, New Zealand. They lifted the gate and began taking cars, stealing 97 vehicles in total. ""Jucy Rentals chief executive Tim Alpe told the New Zealand Herald he believed the heist occurred on April 25. The New Zealand Herald reports the thieves stole unbranded Holden Captivas, Mazda 3s, and Suzuki Swifts along with some green and purple branded campervans.""Lockdown regulations have kept New Zealand's streets mostly empty. However, police were still patrolling when they began chasing a car that they believed looked suspicious.""The BBC reports that 85 of the 97 stolen cars have been found and returned to Jucy, and 29 individuals believed to be linked with the heist have been arrested."SOURCES: BBC, New Zealand Heraldhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-52555036https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&objectid=12329501https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&objectid=12327831&ref=art_readmore***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 07:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/08/3995445/3995445_0D13D5FC0A744DE48EB2E0B71BB6AD27_200508_3995445_Thieves_Steal_97_Cars_During_Lockdown_in_New_Zea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, New Zealand heist, nz heist, coronavirus in new zealand, jucy stolen vehicles, jucy, new zealand, jucy heist, jucy rental heist,  coronavirus, covis-19, sars-cov-2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3996445</guid>
      <title>Geophysicists may have found an explanation for the Earth's wondering Northern Magnetic Pole: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists now say they may understand why the North Magnetic Pole is moving, according to a new study.The North Magnetic Pole has been shifting its position from Canada to Siberia, and since the 2000s, the movement has been picking up speed. Writing in Nature Geoscience, the scientists say there are jets of molten material in the outer core of the Earth, and alterations to the flow are moving the North Magnetic Pole.According to the paper, researchers utilized the European Space Agency's Swarm satellites to collect the magnetic data needed for the study.Citing the authors, BBC reports the molten jet is located much further south than the researchers originally thought in their presentation to the American Geophysical Union two years ago.The study's lead author is cited as saying that the flow made the Canadian magnetic node weaker in relation to the Siberian node, which causes Russia to win the subterranean tug of war for the Magnetic North Pole.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Magnetic Pole has been moving from Canada to Russia2. Polar drift is caused by molten jets in the Earth's outer core 3. The jet is further to the south than study authors previously thought4. The flow strengthens the magnetic node in Siberia and weakens one in CanadaVOICEOVER (in English): "The Earth's North Magnetic Pole has been shifting its position from Canada to Siberia, and since the 2000s, the movement has been picking up speed. According to a new study, scientists now say they may understand why the pole is moving.""Writing in Nature Geoscience, the scientists say there are jets of molten material in the outer core of the Earth, and alterations to the flow are moving the North Magnetic Pole.""Citing the authors, BBC reports the molten jet is located much further south than the researchers originally thought in their presentation to the American Geophysical Union two years ago.""The study's lead author is cited as saying that the flow made the Canadian magnetic node weaker in relation to the Siberian node, which causes Russia to win the subterranean tug of war for the Magnetic North Pole."SOURCES: Nature Geoscience, Nature, BBChttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41561-020-0570-9.epdf?sharing_token=IAPs3EIo1un-0wQ5OB9HWtRgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0NKkhOOgKzOVqiZYU4nlxXxWIa8QRdBhLYpnuGEXoit2DO8byiCfBiQWz-qT3pRJY8157ETFTeLnqr9ytIXmBuEwakcNVtz6tRLYfunU6Ls5tX81DFYktlO7NHAoM1k-dkek1RbwXOTuyDoim1qPnwIHJaw2wchYbHsBJ3RaOmOtNaJ2PGR5p0XRBFVBDxNYrJFP5h4rdgwD6p2v_qwHSzj&tracking_referrer=www.bbc.comhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41561-020-0570-9https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-52550973***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 08:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/11/3996445/3996445_26F3C554BF3B4255A896F0F37A986E49_200511_3996445_Geophysicists_may_have_found_an_explanation_for__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, magnetic north, north magnetic pole, magnetic pole, earth core, outer core, World Magnetic Model, iron jet, siberia, canada, University of Leeds, britain, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3996394</guid>
      <title>Work to begin on world's longest immersed tunnel linking Denmark and Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDenmark has approved the start of construction for what will become the longest tunnel of its kind, connecting it with Germany across a strait in the Baltic.Work on the Danish side of the world's longest immersed tunnel is scheduled to begin on January 1, 2021, Denmark's Ministry of Transport said in a statement on April 24.The Femern Belt link will connect the Danish island of Lolland and Puttgarden, a village and ferry harbor on the island of Fehmarn in Northern Germany.The project is estimated to cost 52.6 billion Danish kroner, or US$7.6 billion, and will include an 18-kilometer electrified double-track railway and four motorway lanes.When completed it will shorten the journey across the Femern Belt to 10 minutes by car or seven minutes by train, compared to today's 45-minute ferry crossing. It is expected to open for traffic in mid-2029, New Europe reports, citing a press conference by Denmark's Minister of Transport Benny Engelbrecht.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Construction of factory harbor2. Location of Femern Belt link on a map3. Tunnel made from precast sections3. Excavation of tunnel trench4. Tunnel sections tugged from work harbor5. Immersion of tunnel elements into trench6. Cross section views of completed tunnelVOICEOVER (in English): "Work on the Danish side of the world's longest immersed tunnel is scheduled to begin on January 1, 2021, Denmark's Ministry of Transport said in a statement on April 24.""The Femern Belt link will connect the Danish island of Lolland and Puttgarden, a village and ferry harbor on the island of Fehmarn in Northern Germany.""First, a 60-meter wide, 16-meter deep, trench will be excavated from the floor of the Baltic Sea." "Unlike other underwater tunnels, like the Channel Tunnel or Japan's Seikan Tunnel, which are bored tunnels, the Femern Belt link will be made from precast tunnel sections immersed in a trench 35 meters beneath the surface of the Baltic Sea.""Each tunnel section will be more than 40 meters wide and up to 15 meters deep and weigh 73,000 tonnes." "They will be cast in a factory on the Danish side and towed by tug boats to the immersion site. Immersion pontoons will be used to lower the tunnel sections down into the trench.""The project is estimated to cost 52.6 billion Danish kroner, or US$7.6 billion, and will include an 18-kilometer electrified double-track railway and four motorway lanes.""It will shorten the journey across the Femern Belt to 10 minutes by car or seven minutes by train, compared to today's 45-minute ferry crossing." "It is expected to open for traffic in mid-2029."SOURCES: Femern A/S, The Engineer, New Europe, The New York Times  https://femern.com/enhttps://www.theengineer.co.uk/total-immersion-the-worlds-longest-immersed-tunnel/https://www.neweurope.eu/article/denmark-greenlights-start-of-work-for-underwater-tunnel-to-germany/https://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2020/04/24/world/europe/24reuters-denmark-germany-infrastructure.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 06:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/11/3996394/3996394_4CE175D3DFE248FE9269AC0E503C0713_200511_3996394_Work_to_begin_on_world_s_longest_immersed_tunnel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, world's longest immersion tunnel, Lolland, Puttgarden, Fehrman, Femern Belt link, Femer Bælt, Femernbelt, Femern Bælt, world's longest tunnels, engineering, construction, infrastructure, Denmark, Germany. Fehmarn Belt Fixed Link, Baltic Sea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3997288</guid>
      <title>New research finds evidence that Uranus was knocked askew by collision with ancient ice planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Solar System's seventh planet Uranus is a ringed gas giant with a horizontal rotational axis, or tilt, that is unique in the solar system.According to a pre-print study, scientists may have uncovered new evidence that explains the gas giant's idiosyncratic rotation.Writing in a press release, the research team says Uranus's tilt is highly usual, as most other planets in the system  such as Earth and Jupiter  rotate with an axis close to perpendicular to their the orbit.According to the research team, during the early Solar System, an ice planet as large as three times the mass of Earth may have impacted Uranus and knocked the gas giant off its axis.Although the ice planet would have vaporized on impact, the team says their model shows that the hypothetical impact would lead to the formation of Uranus's ring system and moons, which they dubbed the smoking gun for the collision.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Uranus's axial tilt is flat with its orbit2. Most planets in the system rotate on a near perpendicular axis 3. Impact with ice planet may have knocked Uranus off its original tilt4. Model shows the impact would form Uranus's system of rings and moonsVOICEOVER (in English): "The Solar System's seventh planet Uranus is a ringed gas giant with a horizontal rotational axis, or tilt, that is unique in the solar system.""According to a pre-print study, scientists may have uncovered new evidence that explains the gas giant's idiosyncratic rotation.""Writing in a press release, the research team says Uranus's tilt is highly usual, as most other planets in the system  such as Earth and Jupiter  rotate with an axis close to perpendicular to their the orbit.""According to the research team says that during the early Solar System, an ice planet as large as three times the mass of Earth may have impacted Uranus and knocked the gas giant off its axis.""Although the ice planet would have vaporized on impact, the team says their model shows that the hypothetical impact would lead to the formation of Uranus's ring system and moons, which they dubbed the smoking gun for the collision."SOURCES: Arxiv.org, Tokyo Institute of Technologyhttps://arxiv.org/abs/2003.13582https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-04/tiot-mou040120.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 09:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/13/3997288/3997288_BF282424DE1844F28CBE6196AFC71C37_200513_3997288_New_research_finds_evidence_that_Uranus_was_knoc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Uranus, rotational axis, axial tilt, ice planet, collision, impact, early Solar System, Tokyo Institute of Technology, science, space, astronomy, Japan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3997142</guid>
      <title>U.S. Space Force prepares to launch drone space plane on science mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Space Force will launch the X-37B on an Atlas V rocket from Florida's Cape Canaveral Air Force Station on May 16, according to the service's news release.According to United Launch Alliance, the Atlas V is a two-stage rocket that can be augmented with up to five additional solid-fuel rockets, for a maximum thrust of 10,400 kN.The robot shuttle is stowed in a capsule that the rocket will carry into space.According to Space.com, the Space Force's parent service the Air Force has two X-37Bs. The spacecraft has a wingspan of 15 feet, or 4.6 meters, and a length of 29 feet, or 8.8 meters.Its payload bay is about the size of the bed of a small pickup truck.The Space Force says the spacecraft will deploy the FalconSat-8, which is a small satellite developed by the Air Force.The module will for the first time host experiments, including a study on the effects of radiation on various materials and food seeds.Additionally, the X-37B will carry out an experiment to convert solar power into microwave energy, which could then be transmitted to Earth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Atlas V rocket will be utilized for the launch 2. X-37B dimensions and payload 3. Satellite deployment and materials, seeds experiments4. Solar energy to microwave conversion experimentVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Space Force will launch the X-37B on an Atlas V rocket from Florida's Cape Canaveral Air Force Station on May 16, according to the service's news release.""The robot shuttle is stowed in a capsule that the rocket will carry into space.""According to Space.com, the Space Force's parent service the Air Force has two X-37Bs. The spacecraft has a wingspan of 15 feet, or 4.6 meters, and a length of 29 feet, or 8.8 meters.""Its payload bay is about the size of the bed of a small pickup truck.""The Space Force says the spacecraft will deploy the FalconSat-8, which is a small satellite developed by the Air Force.""The module will for the first time host experiments, including a study on the effects of radiation on various materials and food seeds.""Additionally, the X-37B will carry out an experiment to convert solar power into microwave energy, which could then be transmitted to Earth."SOURCES: Space Force, Space.comhttps://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article/2177702/next-x-37b-orbital-test-vehicle-scheduled-to-launchhttps://www.space.com/x-37b-space-plane-secret-mission-otv-6-launch-date.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 05:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/13/3997142/3997142_E3264B335D4E4B848DE39B5A29636DC6_200513_3997142_U_S__Space_Force_prepares_to_launch_drone_space__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, X-37B, Atlas V, robot, drone, uncrewed, shuttle, solar power, solar energy, science mission, microwave, United Launch Alliance, Space Force, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3997495</guid>
      <title>Remains of female warriors found in Mongolia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArcheologists from California State University, Los Angeles, told Live Science that they found the remains of two women warriors while excavating a cemetery at the Airagiin Gozgor archaeological site in Orkhon, Mongolia.Specialists examined remains found in 29 burial sites. These include human remains from 16 men, 10 women, and three unidentified individuals. Researchers were looking for evidence of the effects of horseback riding, archery, and trauma on the body.Christine Lee from California State University, Los Angeles, lead researcher on the yet-to-be-published study, said the remains of the two warriors showed signs that both practiced horseback riding and archery, just like the remains of the men and male adolescents.The two women are believed to have been 20 and 50 years old and lived during the Xianbei period, which lasted from 147 to 552 AD. This period was marked by political turmoil. Lee and fellow researcher Yahaira Gonzalez said it is likely they practiced archery and horseback riding because they may have been needed to fight alongside the men.The research has yet to be published in a peer-reviewed journal. It was meant to be presented at the American Association of Physical Anthropologists annual conference in mid-April. However, the conference was canceled to the coronavirus pandemic. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of excavation site in Mongolia2. Types of remains found in archaeological site3. Two warrior women found in site4. Two warrior women riding on horseback and shooting arrowsVOICEOVER (in English): "Archeologists from California State University, Los Angeles, told Live Science that they found the remains of two women warriors while excavating a cemetery at the Airagiin Gozgor archaeological site in Orkhon, Mongolia.""Specialists examined remains found in 29 burial sites. These include human remains from 16 men, 10 women, and three unidentified individuals. Researchers were looking for evidence of the effects of horseback riding, archery, and trauma on the body.""Christine Lee from California State University, Los Angeles, lead researcher on the yet-to-be-published study, said the remains of the two warriors showed signs that both practiced horseback riding and archery, just like the remains of the men and male adolescents.""The two women are believed to have been 20 and 50 years old and lived during the Xianbei period, which lasted from 147 to 552 AD. This period was marked by political turmoil. Lee and fellow researcher Yahaira Gonzalez said it is likely they practiced archery and horseback riding because they may have been needed to fight alongside the men."SOURCES:LiveSciencehttps://www.livescience.com/mongolia-warrior-women-mulan.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 01:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/14/3997495/3997495_C10B9D3BA9E4415381250C32926E4A71_200514_3997495_Remains_of_female_warriors_found_in_Mongolia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mongolia, mongolia archeological site, mongolia archeology, Yahaira Gonzalez, Christine Lee California State University Los Angeles, mulan, huamulan, hua mulan, ballad of mulan, mongolian warriors, female mongolian warriors, woman mongolian warriors]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3998008</guid>
      <title>Polar vortex brings springtime snow to the U.S. East Coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe polar vortex dumped snow and cold Arctic air on parts of the northeast United States and Canada over Mother's Day weekend, the Associated Press reports.According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, the polar vortex is a band of low pressure Arctic air normally centered around the North Pole. It is located in the middle and upper tropospheres and extends into the stratosphere.The polar vortex is usually held in place by a current called the jet stream. Disturbances in the jet stream can push frigid, wintry air to parts of Canada and the U.S., while high-pressure systems of warmer air bulge northwards elsewhere.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Polar vortex seen from above the North Pole2. Polar vortex extends from stratosphere to middle of the troposphere3. Polar vortex bulges due to disturbances in the jetstream4. Polar vortex brings unseasonably cold temperatures and rare winter snowVOICEOVER (in English): "The polar vortex unleashed frigid temperatures and rare snow on parts of the northeast United States and Canada over Mother's Day weekend.""The polar vortex is a band of low pressure Arctic air normally centered around the North Pole. It is located in the middle and upper tropospheres and extends into the stratosphere.""The polar vortex is held in place by a current called the jet stream. Disturbances in the jet stream can push frigid, wintry air to parts of Canada and the U.S., while high-pressure systems of warmer air bulge northwards elsewhere.""On Mother's Day weekend the wobbly polar vortex dumped freezing temperatures on parts of the Midwest and eastern U.S., with springtime snow falling in parts of New York and New Jersey."SOURCES: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, Associated Press, Live Science, CTV News, Fox Newshttps://www.noaa.gov/multimedia/infographic/science-behind-polar-vortex-you-might-want-to-put-on-sweater https://www.ny1.com/nyc/all-boroughs/ap-top-news/2020/05/09/polar-vortex-brings-rare-may-snow-low-temps-to-us-easthttps://www.livescience.com/extreme-may-weather-polar-vortex.htmlhttps://barrie.ctvnews.ca/polar-vortex-shatters-record-temperatures-across-the-region-1.4935839https://www.foxnews.com/us/polar-vortex-may-snow-maine-power-outage-low-temperature-records-broken-east***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 08:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/15/3998008/3998008_26E30C75DA904079A4F6F3DE7C6BF3A3_200515_3998008_Polar_vortex_brings_springtime_snow_to_the_U_S___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, polar vortex, cold weather, jet stream, weather, U.S., United States, cold, extremely cold weather]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3997992</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus linked to novel inflammatory syndrome affecting children</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNearly 100 children from the United Kingdom developed severe inflammation possibly in connection to the coronavirus, according to the BBC. Medical workers sounded the alarm in April after eight children from London fell ill, including a 14-year-old who died.The BBC reports that most of the eight children did not have respiratory issues, but they did share high fever, red eyes, rash, general pain and swelling, citing doctors at Evelina London Children's Hospital.Despite the absence of breathing or lung problems, seven of the original eight children were put on ventilators to ease heart and circulatory troubles.Liz Whittaker at Imperial College London told the BBC doctors believe the mystery inflammatory disease is likely a "post-infectious phenomenon" related to antibody buildup following a COVID-19 infection. Children make up between 1 and 2 percent of coronavirus infections.The Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health is cited as saying the syndrome "is exceptionally rare" and that parents in the UK need not confine their children as lockdown measures are eased.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Coronavirus linked to new inflammatory syndrome among children in the UK2. Symptoms include high fever, rash, general pain and swelling3. Several children are put on ventilators due to heart and circulatory issues4. Syndrome likely caused by antibody buildup following COVID-19 infection5. Children make up a small percentage of coronavirus patientsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, nearly 100 children from the UK developed severe inflammation possibly in connection to the coronavirus." "Medical workers sounded the alarm in April after eight children from London fell ill, including a 14-year-old who died.""The BBC reports that most of the eight children did not have respiratory issues, but they did share high fever, red eyes, rash, general pain and swelling, citing doctors at Evelina London Children's Hospital.""Despite the absence of breathing or lung problems, seven of the original eight children were put on ventilators to ease heart and circulatory troubles.""Liz Whittaker at Imperial College London told the BBC doctors believe the mystery inflammatory disease is likely a 'post-infectious phenomenon' related to antibody buildup following a COVID-19 infection." "Children make up between 1 and 2 percent of coronavirus infections." "The Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health is cited as saying the syndrome 'is exceptionally rare' and that parents in the UK need not confine their children as lockdown measures are eased."SOURCES: BBC, Pediatric Intensive Care Society United Kingdoms (Twitter), the Lancethttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-52648557https://twitter.com/PICSociety/status/1254508725227982848https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(20)31103-X/fulltext***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 07:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/15/3997992/3997992_BF8B38112493463FB7E1268230F0154D_200515_3997992_Coronavirus_linked_to_novel_inflammatory_syndrom_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mystery inflammation syndrome, severe inflammation, children, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus, Kawasaki disease shock syndrome, Kawasaki, London, Britain, U.K.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3997894</guid>
      <title>Atomic testing during the Cold War affected rainfall patterns in Scotland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a study published in Physical Review Letters, the electric charge from radioactivity caused by atomic testing during the Cold War caused a rise in precipitation on the Shetland Islands in Scotland.During the Cold War, radioactive pollution from American and Soviet Union atomic testing sites in the 1960s spread across the atmosphere.Specialists from the Reading, Bath and Bristol universities participating in the study used information from bomb tests and records from the United Kingdom's national weather service to determine the long-term effects of bomb radioactivity.According to data gathered from a research station in Scotland, experts found that on days when radioactivity was increased, clouds were heavier and rain increased by 24 percent.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Atomic bomb testing2. Radioactive particles from atomic bomb testing3. Scientists compare the data from the explosion 4. Increase in radioactivity causes an increase in rainVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Physical Review Letters, The Guardianhttps://journals.aps.org/prl/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevLett.124.198701https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/may/13/atomic-tests-cold-war-increased-rainfall-on-shetland***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 03:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/15/3997894/3997894_A59DDFDB4AEC4D499DEC6A9260A1A48F_200515_3997894_Atomic_testing_during_the_Cold_War_affected_rain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cold war, nuclear testing, physical review letters, nuclear bomb, nuclear bomb testing, radioactivity, cold war atomic tests, atomic tests, rainfall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3998291</guid>
      <title>China to conduct major military exercise in South China Sea: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's People's Liberation Army Navy plans to conduct a large-scale amphibious assault drill off Hainan Island in August, according to the Japan Times.Citing unnamed Chinese sources, the Japan Times reports the drill will involve landing ships, hovercraft and helicopters, while the carrier Shandong has been deployed in Hainan since December last year. The exercise is designed to simulate a navy and marines attack on the Taiwan-held Pratas, a strategically important islet that sits astride China's military egress from Hainan to the Pacific Ocean.According to Reuters, Taiwan in April announced plans to buy arms from France to upgrade its fleet of six French-made La Fayette-class frigates.The U.S. Naval Institute reports a U.S. Navy Arleigh Burke-class destroyer made a transit through the Taiwan Strait to warn Beijing's leadership against taking aggressive action in the region.The Japan Times reports U.S. electronic warfare aircraft may have passed the strait 14 times in April alone.According to Taiwan's state-run Central News Agency, a Chinese Y-8 aircraft flew into Taiwan's air defense identification zone before being headed off by fighter jets on April 8.This is the seventh time Chinese military planes flew near Taiwan's airspace this year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China's planned amphibious assault exercise 2. Drill aimed to simulate invading Taiwan's Pratas Island3. US warship recently passed through Taiwan Strait to deter China4. Taiwan fighter jets turned away a Chinese Y-8 plane from its ADIZVOICEOVER (in English): "China's People's Liberation Army Navy plans to conduct a large-scale amphibious assault drill off Hainan Island in August.""Citing unnamed Chinese sources, the Japan Times reports the drill will involve landing ships, hovercraft and helicopters, while the carrier Shandong has been deployed in Hainan since December last year." "According to the Japan Times, the exercise is designed to simulate a navy and marines attack on the Taiwan-held Pratas, a strategically important islet that sits astride China's military egress from Hainan to the Pacific Ocean.""The U.S. Naval Institute reports a U.S. Navy Arleigh Burke-class destroyer made a transit through the Taiwan Strait to warn Beijing's leadership against taking aggressive action in the region." "The Japan Times reports U.S. electronic warfare aircraft may have passed the strait 14 times in April alone.""According to Taiwan's state-run Central News Agency, a Chinese Y-8 aircraft flew into Taiwan's air defense identification zone before being headed off by fighter jets on April 8." "This is the seventh time Chinese military planes flew near Taiwan's airspace this year."SOURCES: The Japan Times, Reuters, U.S. Naval Institute, NHK, Central News Agency (Taiwan) https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2020/05/14/asia-pacific/china-military-drill-taiwan/#.Xr3ndEYzY2whttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-france-taiwan/china-warns-france-not-to-sell-weapons-to-taiwan-idUSKBN22P1EThttps://news.usni.org/2020/05/14/uss-mccampbell-transits-taiwan-strait-ahead-of-taiwanese-presidential-inaugurationhttps://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20200514_24/https://www.cna.com.tw/news/firstnews/202005085007.aspx***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 03:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/16/3998291/3998291_D897CC8FC2BB439B9A0A0536EC1CA2B7_200516_3998291_China_to_conduct_major_military_exercise_in_Sout_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Chinese military drill, Chinese military exercise, South China Sea, Hainan, Pratas, Pratas Island, Shandong, PLA, PLAN, U.S. Navy, destroyer, Taiwan Strait, Taiwan, China, U.S., defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3998913</guid>
      <title>Astronomers find rare super-Earth in Earth-like orbit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers from the University of Canterbury in New Zealand have discovered a new "super-Earth" orbiting a star located near the Milky Way's "galactic bulge," a dense region of stars in the center of our galaxy, according to a press release published by the university on May 11.This rare super-Earth is 25,000 light-years away. It is one of only a handful among the 4,000 exoplanets to have been detected that is similar to Earth in both size and orbit.According to their research, which was published on May 7 in The Astronomical Journal, the world is four times the mass of Earth.It orbits a dim dwarf star that is only 10 percent the mass of our Sun. This star is so small that the researchers could not determine if it is a low-mass star or a kind of failed star called a brown dwarf.The newly discovered orbits at a distance between Venus and Earth from its parent star. But because its star's mass is so small, a year on this world lasts 617 days.To find the planet, the researchers used a method called gravitational microlensing. "The combined gravity of the planet and its host star caused the light from a more distant background star to be magnified in a particular way. We used telescopes distributed around the world to measure the light-bending effect," University of Canterbury astronomer Antonio Herrera Martin, said in the news release."These experiments detect around 3,000 microlensing events each year, the majority of which are due to lensing by single stars," the paper's co-author Michael Albrow was quoted as saying in the news release. "Dr Herrera Martin first noticed that there was an unusual shape to the light output from this event, and undertook months of computational analysis that resulted in the conclusion that this event was due to a star with a low-mass planet."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Newly discovered "super-Earth" located near the Milky Way's "galactic bulge" 2. Newly discovered planet is four times the mass of Earth3. Planet orbits a dim dwarf star that is 10 percent the mass of the Sun 4. Planet orbits its star at a location between Venus and Earth from its parent starVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers from the University of Canterbury in New Zealand have discovered a new 'super-Earth' orbiting a star located near the Milky Way's 'galactic bulge,' a dense region of stars in the center of our galaxy.""This rare super-Earth is 25,000 light-years away. It is one of only a handful among the 4,000 exoplanets to have been detected that is similar to Earth in both size and orbit." "According to their research, which was published on May 7 in The Astronomical Journal, the world is four times the mass of Earth.""It orbits a dim dwarf star that is only 10 percent the mass of our Sun. This star is so small that the researchers could not determine if it is a low-mass star or a kind of failed star called a brown dwarf.""The newly discovered orbits at a distance between Venus and Earth from its parent star. But because its star's mass is so small, a year on this world lasts 617 days."SOURCES: University of Canterbury, The Astronomical Journal (via arXiv), NASA https://www.canterbury.ac.nz/news/2020/uc-planet-hunters-discover-new-one-in-a-million-super-earth-.htmlhttps://arxiv.org/pdf/2003.02983.pdfhttps://exoplanets.nasa.gov/exoplanet-catalog/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 09:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/18/3998913/3998913_DC355D50A2774E25ABE6EEB5809E794E_200518_3998913_Astronomers_find_rare_super_Earth_in_Earth_like__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3998757</guid>
      <title>Hokkaido gypsy moth detected for the first time in the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA recent proclamation issued by the governor of the State of Washington, Jay Inslee, warns about the detection of Hokkaido gypsy moths in areas in Snohomish County, Washington. This is the first detection of the species in the U.S., the Washington State Department of Agriculture said in a press release. The Hokkaido gypsy moth is native to Russia, according to the National Invasive Species Information Center from the U.S. Department of Agriculture.Asian gypsy moths measure three and a half inches (about 9 centimeters) long and female moths can lay from 500 to 1,000 eggs, according to the U.S. Customs and Border Protection.In a press release, the Washington Department of Agriculture said European gypsy moth caterpillars eat more than 500 types of trees, plants and shrubs.However, Karla Salp, a spokeswoman for the department, told UPI that Asian gypsy moths pose a greater threat than European gypsy moths because they can consume more species of plants.If the species establishes itself in Washington it would become a threat to forest ecosystems and could lead to quarantine restrictions and increased homeowner pesticide use, according to Washington's agriculture department.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location where Hokkaido gypsy moths were found2. Size of moths3. Caterpillars consuming folliage4. Caterpillars affecting local plantsVOICEOVER (in English): "A recent proclamation issued by the governor of the State of Washington, Jay Inslee, warns about the detection of Hokkaido gypsy moths in areas in Snohomish County, Washington. This is the first detection of the species in the U.S., the Washington State Department of Agriculture said in a press release. ""The Asian gypsy moth is native to Russia, according to the National Invasive Species Information Center from the U.S. Department of Agriculture.""Asian gypsy moths measure three and a half inches (about 9 centimeters) long and female moths can lay from 500 to 1,000 eggs, according to the U.S. Customs and Border Protection.""In a press release, the Washington Department of Agriculture said European gypsy moth caterpillars eat more than 500 types of trees, plants and shrubs.""However, Karla Salp, a spokeswoman for the department, told UPI that Asian gypsy moths pose a greater threat than European gypsy moths because they can consume more species of plants.""If the species establishes itself in Washington it would become a threat to forest ecosystems and could lead to quarantine restrictions and increased homeowner pesticide use, according to Washington's agriculture department."SOURCES: United Press International, Washington State Department of Agriculture, State of Washington Office of the Governor https://www.upi.com/Top_News/US/2020/05/11/Giant-Asian-gypsy-moth-threatens-trees-in-Washington/6351588876757/?ur3=1https://agr.wa.gov/about-wsda/news-and-media-relations/news-releases?article=30548https://www.governor.wa.gov/sites/default/files/proclamations/20-54%20Gypsy%20Moth%20%28tmp%29.pdf?utm_medium=email&utm_source=govdelivery***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 01:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/18/3998757/3998757_14214F86C16B432E9AE78B037580FFFA_200518_3998757_Hokkaido_gypsy_moth_detected_for_the_first_time__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Washington State Department of Agriculture, giant asian gypsy moth, giant moth, gypsy moth, moth, moth pest, pest, agriculture, horticulture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999239</guid>
      <title>Fake baby formula tied to rickets, swollen heads in Chinese toddlers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese authorities in Hunan are currently investigating a baby product shop following reports of five children being diagnosed with rickets after consuming fake milk powder sold by the store.Several parents of children allergic to regular milk formula in Yongxing County, Hunan Province went to a baby product shop looking for an amino acid-based milk alternative for their babies only to be sold a protein mix, the South China Morning Post reports, citing local media.One of the parents surnamed Zhu said that staff at the shop told her the product called Bei An Min was an alternative to baby formula, despite its packaging labeling it as a protein drink. Zhu's daughter drank the powdered protein drink for more than two years.According to a report by thepaper.cn, five toddlers were reported to have lost weight, and developed eczema and a swollen head after drinking the protein beverage.The paper.cn also reported that some children would slap their heads and all of them were diagnosed with rickets, a condition caused by vitamin D, calcium or phosphate deficiency.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Parents purchase fake baby formula at shop2. Mother feeds baby formula to her child3. Child becomes thinner, we see it developed eczema and its forehead is swollen4. Child hits his head with its handsVOICEOVER (in English): "Several parents of children allergic to regular milk formula in Yongxing County, Hunan Province went to a baby product shop looking for an amino acid-based milk alternative for their babies only to be sold a protein mix, the South China Morning Post reports, citing local media.""One of the parents surnamed Zhu said that staff at the shop told her the product called Bei An Min was an alternative to baby formula, despite its packaging labeling it as a protein drink. Zhu's daughter drank the powdered protein drink for more than two years.""According to a report by thepaper.cn, five toddlers were reported to have lost weight, and developed eczema and a swollen head after drinking the protein beverage.""The paper.cn also reported that some children would slap their heads and all of them were diagnosed with rickets, a condition caused by vitamin D, calcium or phosphate deficiency."SOURCES: The South China Morning Post, Thepaper.cn, BBChttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3084271/china-investigates-claims-babies-sickened-fake-milk-formulahttps://www.thepaper.cn/newsDetail_forward_7377257https://www.thepaper.cn/newsDetail_forward_7420593***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 07:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/19/3999239/3999239_6760487544E8478E934120FF45BF1C88_200519_3999239_Fake_baby_formula_tied_to_rickets__swollen_heads_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, milk powder, fake milk powder, milk powder scandal, bei an min powder, bei an min, rickets, eczema]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999176</guid>
      <title>Melting glacier may trigger a destructive tsunami in Alaska's Prince William Sound: scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA melting Alaskan glacier may set off a landslide and trigger a tsunami in Prince William Sound, according to a public letter by climate scientists and geologists at institutions including the University of Alaska, the Ohio State University and the University of British Columbia. This event could happen as soon as next year and no later than 20 years from now, they say. The researchers say the Barry Glacier's retreat inland could send its scarp tumbling down the Barry Arm. A complete failure of the scarp will cause a destructive tsunami to crash down Barry Arm and Harriman Fiord, while partially endangering Port Wells.If the scarp fails completely, it would raise waves as high as 1,000 feet, which would threaten fishing boats and the hundreds of fishermen and tourists who frequent the region. Even locations far from the Barry Glacier may experience 30-foot tall waves.According to the letter, climate change is melting Barry Glacier, and the retreating ice has left a swath of the cliff unsupported by its mass. The loose scarp then entered into a slow-motion landslide that is now showing signs of speeding up.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Barry Glacier's melting could trigger a landslide-caused tsunami 2. Tsunami may affect Barry Arm, Harriman Fiord and Port Wells3. Waves could reach a height of 1,000 feet and endanger fishermen and tourists4. Glacier's retreat leaves cliff unsupported by ice, which leads to the landslideVOICEOVER (in English): "A melting Alaskan glacier may set off a landslide and trigger a tsunami in Prince William Sound, according to a public letter by climate scientists and geologists at institutions including the University of Alaska, the Ohio State University and the University of British Columbia.""This event could happen as soon as next year and no later than 20 years from now, they say.""The researchers say the Barry Glacier's retreat inland could send its scarp tumbling down the Barry Arm. A complete failure of the scarp will cause a destructive tsunami to crash down Barry Arm and Harriman Fiord, while partially endangering Port Wells.""If the scarp fails completely, it would raise waves as high as 1,000 feet, which would threaten fishing boats and the hundreds of fishermen and tourists who frequent the region.""Even locations far from the Barry Glacier may experience 30-foot tall waves.""According to the letter, climate change is melting Barry Glacier, and the retreating ice has left a swath of the cliff unsupported by its mass." "The loose scarp then entered into a slow-motion landslide that is now showing signs of speeding up."SOURCES: DocumentCloud, Anchorage Daily News, Woods Home Research Centerhttps://www.documentcloud.org/documents/6890609-5-14-20-Barry-Arm-Landslide-Working-Group-Letter.htmlhttps://www.adn.com/alaska-news/science/2020/05/14/scientists-warn-about-risk-of-massive-tsunami-in-prince-william-sound-potentially-within-the-next-year/#_https://whrc.org/scientists-warming-temps-thawing-glacier-creates-tsunami-risk-in-alaskas-barry-arm/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 04:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/19/3999176/3999176_73AC76C9B6DA4B638F899B8A9F7FCE91_200519_3999176_Melting_glacier_may_trigger_a_destructive_tsunam_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Barry Glacier, landslide, tsunami, climate change, climate warming, global warming, Prince William Sound, Alaska, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999770</guid>
      <title>India, Bangladesh brace as super cyclone is poised for landfall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIndia and Bangladesh are evacuating millions before the path of Tropical Cyclone Amphan, which is expected to make imminent landfall on the evening of May 20. Amphan is the second-ever super cyclone on record to hit the Bay of Bengal. The powerful storm was sustaining an airspeed of 172 km per hour at the time of report.Citing India's weather department, the BBC reports the storm will bring a 3 to 5-meter surge, and the authorities have called on fishing boats to stay ashore.The U.S. Pacific Center says up to 33.6 million people in India and 5.3 million people in Bangladesh are exposed to the storm, with capital exposures of up to $273.9 billion.The cyclone will likely fall on the India-Bangladesh border and the projected path will bring the storm near the Indian city of Kolkata.More than 14 million people reside in this densely populated urban center.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tropical Cyclone Amphan is expected to strike India and Bangladesh 2. The storm's sustained airspeed and surge dangers3. Population exposure in India and Bangladesh4. Kolkata with 14 million people is threatened by the cycloneVOICEOVER (in English): "India and Bangladesh are evacuating millions before the path of Tropical Cyclone Amphan, which is expected to make imminent landfall on the evening of May 20." "Amphan is the second-ever super cyclone on record to hit the Bay of Bengal. The powerful storm was sustaining an airspeed of 172 km per hour at the time of report.""Citing India's weather department, the BBC reports the storm will bring a 3 to 5-meter surge, and the authorities have called on fishing boats to stay ashore.""The U.S. Pacific Center says up to 33.6 million people in India and 5.3 million people in Bangladesh are exposed to the storm, with capital exposures of up to $273.9 billion.""The cyclone will likely fall on the India-Bangladesh border and the projected path will bring the storm near the Indian city of Kolkata.""More than 14 million people reside in this densely populated urban center."SOURCES: BBC, CNN, U.S. Pacific Disaster Centerhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-52718826https://edition.cnn.com/2020/05/19/asia/super-cyclone-amphan-india-banglash-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.pdc.org/wp-content/uploads/PDC_TC_Amphan_Wind_Impacts_ADV11_18MAY20_2100UTC.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 10:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/20/3999770/3999770_2F296566FC3540328A2DA96E2B008CD1_200520_3999770_India__Bangladesh_brace_as_super_cyclone_is_pois_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, amphan, tropical cyclone, super cyclone, storm, Kolkata, India, Bangladesh, natural disaster]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999683</guid>
      <title>Newly spotted red giant could be one of the oldest stars in the universe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers have discovered a red giant 3,500 light-years from Earth that could be one of the oldest stars in the cosmos, according to a paper published in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society.Writing in a news release, researchers say the very first stars created by the Big Bang are believed to be extinct, but the red giant they spotted in the galactic halo is likely a descendent of those much older stars.The red giant contains the least amount of iron ever detected, or 1.5 million times lower than that found in the Sun. Since metallic elements are created by ancient stars, an anemic star is likely to be much older than metallic stars.The first stars were believed to be made of pure hydrogen and helium. When these stars die, they explode into supernovas and create metal elements. This explains why the red dwarf, a direct progeny of the first stars, contains so little iron.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ancient star is located 3,500 light-years from Earth2. The red giant belongs to the second-ever generation of stars3. The star's age is suggested by its iron content, the least ever observed in a star 4. The iron found in the red giant are residues from a first generation starVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers have discovered a red giant 3,500 light-years from Earth that could be one of the oldest stars in the cosmos, according to a paper published in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society.""Writing in a news release, researchers say the very first stars created by the Big Bang are believed to be extinct, but the red giant they spotted in the galactic halo is likely a descendent of those much older stars.""The red giant contains the least amount of iron ever detected, or 1.5 million times lower than that found in the Sun. Since metallic elements are created by ancient stars, an anemic star is likely to be much older than metallic stars.""The first stars were believed to be made of pure hydrogen and helium. When these stars die, they explode into supernovas and create metal elements. This explains why the red dwarf, a direct progeny of the first stars, contains so little iron."SOURCES: Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, ARC Centre of Excellence in All-Sky Physicshttps://academic.oup.com/mnrasl/article-abstract/488/1/L109/5533336?redirectedFrom=fulltexthttps://phys.org/news/2019-08-anaemic-star-ancient-ancestor.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/20/3999683/3999683_5E283F3FC08142218A9E587340103229_200520_3999683_Newly_spotted_red_giant_could_be_one_of_the_olde_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, red dwarf, lowest ever detected iron content, metallic stars, metallic elements, big bang, ancient stars, first stars, space, astronomy, Australia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999681</guid>
      <title>Asteroid as large as the Golden Gate Bridge approaching Earth on May 21</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThis year's second-largest "potentially hazardous" near-Earth object is approaching Earth at speeds of over 11,000 kilometers per second and will zoom past our planet on May 21, according to NASA's Center for Near-Earth Object Studies.Asteroid 136796, also known as 1997 BQ, is estimated by NASA to be between 640 meters and 1.4 kilometers wide, or roughly the size of the Golden Gate Bridge.1997 BQ orbits our Sun every 844 days. According to NASA's Asteroid Watch, on May 21 it will pass Earth at a distance of 6.2 million kilometers, slightly closer than this year's largest potentially hazardous near-Earth object, 1998 OR2, which flew past Earth on April 29 at a distance of 6.3 million kilometers.NASA classifies a near-Earth object  either a comet or an asteroid  as a potentially hazardous object if its orbit brings it within 7.5 million kilometers of Earth's orbit and it is greater than 140 meters in size.According to NASA's Center for Near-Earth Object Studies, as of April 21, some 22,582 near-Earth objects had been discovered. Of these, 9,085 were 140 meters or larger in size, and 902 were estimated to be larger than one kilometer.By comparison, the Chicxulub asteroid that wiped out the dinosaurs is estimated to have been 11 to 81 kilometres in diameter.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of 136796 (1997 BQ) near Earth2. Estimated size of 1997 BQ3. Orbit of 1997 BQ4. Closest distance of 1997 BQ to Earth and comparison to Asteroid 1998 OR2VOICEOVER (in English): "This year's second-largest 'potentially hazardous' near-Earth object is incoming at speeds of over 11,000 kilometers per second and will zoom past our planet on May 21.""Asteroid 136796, also known as 1997 BQ, is estimated by NASA to be between 640 meters and 1.4 kilometers wide. That's roughly the size of the Golden Gate Bridge.""1997 BQ orbits our Sun every 844 days. It crosses Earth's orbit twice on its journey around the Sun on its closest approach and travels beyond Mars and near the Asteroid Belt at its farthest point.""According to NASA's Asteroid Watch, on May 21 it will pass Earth at a distance of 6.2 million kilometers. That's more than 16 times the average distance between Earth and the Moon, but slightly closer than this year's largest potentially hazardous near-Earth object, 1998 OR2, flew past Earth on April 29."SOURCES: NASA Center for Near-Earth Object Studies, NASA Jet Propulsion Laboratory, NASA Asteroid Watchhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/ca/https://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?sstr=136795&orb=1https://www.spacereference.org/asteroid/136795-1997-bqhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/edu/pdfs/ssbeads_answerkey.pdfhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/asteroidwatch/https://twitter.com/AsteroidWatchhttps://www.nasa.gov/planetarydefense/did-you-knowhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/stats/totals.htmlhttps://www2.jpl.nasa.gov/sl9/back2.htmlhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/stats/size.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/five-years-after-the-chelyabinsk-meteor-nasa-leads-efforts-in-planetary-defense***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 07:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/20/3999681/3999681_0AA9553DBF0F4C4DBDC032EA12339D4D_200520_3999681_Asteroid_as_large_as_the_Golden_Gate_Bridge_appr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, asteroid, asteroid 2020, asteroid May 21 2020, asteroid coming toward earth, 136796, 1997 BQ, NASA, space, potentially hazardous near-Earth object, asteroid 21 May 2020, asteroid May 2020]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999540</guid>
      <title>Explainer: Annular solar eclipse to sweep across Africa and Asia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Moon will cast its shadow over parts of the Eastern Hemisphere from Africa and Eastern Europe to the Pacific in a solar eclipse on June 21, on the same day as the Northern Hemisphere's summer solstice.According to NASA, the annular phase of this solar eclipse  when only the Sun's outer edges are visible around the Moon in a fiery ring  will cross the Democratic Republic of the Congo, South Sudan, Ethiopia, Eritrea, Yemen, Saudi Arabia, Oman, Pakistan, India, China and Taiwan.People thousands of kilometers north and south of this area will be able to see varying stages of a partial eclipse.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. View from Earth of a solar eclipse2. Moon casting a shadow on Earth during an eclipse3. There are 13 new moons per year4. Moon's orbit is tilted five degrees to earth's orbit5. A solar eclipse occurs only twice a year6. Stages of a solar eclipse7. Where partial eclipse will be visible and path of annular eclipse over the Eastern HemisphereVOICEOVER (in English): "The Moon will cast its shadow over parts of the Eastern Hemisphere from Africa and Eastern Europe to the Pacific in a solar eclipse on June 21, on the same day as the Northern Hemisphere's summer solstice.""A solar eclipse takes place only during a new moon, when the Moon passes directly between the Earth and the Sun. As the Moon passes between the Earth and the Sun, it casts a full shadow on some parts of the planet and a partial shadow on a wider region of the Earth.""New moons occur frequently  13 times a year to be exact. Yet, we don't see 13 solar eclipses each year, because the Moon's orbit is tilted five degrees to the Earth's orbit around the Sun." "This means the Moon is only perfectly aligned between the Earth and the Sun twice a year.""According to NASA, the annular phase of this solar eclipse  when only the Sun's outer edges are visible around the Moon  will cross the Democratic Republic of the Congo, South Sudan, Ethiopia, Eritrea, Yemen, Saudi Arabia, Oman, Pakistan, India, China and Taiwan.""Viewers thousands of kilometers north and south of this area will be able to see varying stages of a partial eclipse." "The annular eclipse will first appear at the border between the Republic of the Congo and the Democratic Republic of the Congo.""The point of greatest eclipse, when the axis of the Moon's shadow cone passes closest to the center of the Earth, will occur over India near the borders with Nepal and China."SOURCES: NASAhttps://eclipse.gsfc.nasa.gov/SEgoogle/SEgoogle2001/SE2020Jun21Agoogle.htmlhttps://eclipse.gsfc.nasa.gov/SEgoogle/SEgoogle2001/SE2020Dec14Tgoogle.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 03:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/20/3999540/3999540_6B1313CF8EAC4BB49DEF926A0BA1F5C2_200520_3999540_Explainer__Annular_solar_eclipse_to_sweep_across_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, solar eclipse 2020, solar eclipse, solar eclipse, annular solar eclipse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999533</guid>
      <title>Asteroid as large as the Golden Gate Bridge approaching Earth on May 21</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThis year's second-largest "potentially hazardous" near-Earth object is approaching Earth at speeds of over 11,000 kilometers per second and will zoom past our planet on May 21, according to NASA's Center for Near-Earth Object Studies.Asteroid 136796, also known as 1997 BQ, is estimated by NASA to be between 640 meters and 1.4 kilometers wide, or roughly the size of the Golden Gate Bridge.1997 BQ orbits our Sun every 844 days. According to NASA's Asteroid Watch, on May 21 it will pass Earth at a distance of 6.2 million kilometers, slightly closer than this year's largest potentially hazardous near-Earth object, 1998 OR2, which flew past Earth on April 29 at a distance of 6.3 million kilometers.NASA classifies a near-Earth object  either a comet or an asteroid  as a potentially hazardous object if its orbit brings it within 7.5 million kilometers of Earth's orbit and it is greater than 140 meters in size.According to NASA's Center for Near-Earth Object Studies, as of April 21, some 22,582 near-Earth objects had been discovered. Of these, 9,085 were 140 meters or larger in size, and 902 were estimated to be larger than one kilometer.By comparison, the Chicxulub asteroid that wiped out the dinosaurs is estimated to have been 11 to 81 kilometres in diameter.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of 136796 (1997 BQ) near Earth2. Estimated size of 1997 BQ3. Orbit of 1997 BQ4. Closest distance of 1997 BQ to Earth and comparison to Asteroid 1998 OR2VOICEOVER (in English): "This year's second-largest 'potentially hazardous' near-Earth object is incoming at speeds of over 11,000 kilometers per second and will zoom past our planet on May 21.""Asteroid 136796, also known as 1997 BQ, is estimated by NASA to be between 640 meters and 1.4 kilometers wide. That's roughly the size of the Golden Gate Bridge.""1997 BQ orbits our Sun every 844 days. It crosses Earth's orbit twice on its journey around the Sun on its closest approach and travels beyond Mars and near the Asteroid Belt at its farthest point.""According to NASA's Asteroid Watch, on May 21 it will pass Earth at a distance of 6.2 million kilometers. That's more than 16 times the average distance between Earth and the Moon, but slightly closer than this year's largest potentially hazardous near-Earth object, 1998 OR2, flew past Earth on April 29."SOURCES: NASA Center for Near-Earth Object Studies, NASA Jet Propulsion Laboratory, NASA Asteroid Watchhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/ca/https://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?sstr=136795&orb=1https://www.spacereference.org/asteroid/136795-1997-bqhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/edu/pdfs/ssbeads_answerkey.pdfhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/asteroidwatch/https://twitter.com/AsteroidWatchhttps://www.nasa.gov/planetarydefense/did-you-knowhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/stats/totals.htmlhttps://www2.jpl.nasa.gov/sl9/back2.htmlhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/stats/size.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/five-years-after-the-chelyabinsk-meteor-nasa-leads-efforts-in-planetary-defense***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 03:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/20/3999533/3999533_D5995FFBA02C4E91B6755FE732C6C071_200520_3999533_Asteroid_as_large_as_the_Golden_Gate_Bridge_appr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, asteroid, asteroid 2020, asteroid May 21 2020, asteroid coming toward earth, 136796, 1997 BQ, NASA, space, potentially hazardous near-Earth object, asteroid 21 May 2020, asteroid May 2020]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4000233</guid>
      <title>Explainer: Deadly virus threatens pets and wild rabbits in North America</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRabbits are under threat as a deadly hemorrhagic virus spreads across the southwestern United States.According to a report from the USGS National Wildlife Health Center published on May 7, rabbit hemorrhagic disease virus serotype 2 or RHDV2, a viral disease deadly to rabbits, is spreading across the southwestern United States.Rabbit hemorrhagic disease virus can infect domestic rabbits and wild rabbits such as hares, jackrabbits and cottontails. According to the United States Department of Agriculture, the virus can cause sudden death and nose bleeds caused by internal bleeding. Other symptoms include fever, loss of appetite, swelling and signs of nervousness or irregular breathing.RHDV2 can survive on a dead animal's carcass for at least three months. It can also spread if an animal or individual comes into contact with an infected animal's droppings or blood.RHDV2 can also spread through food, water or any other material that has been exposed to the virus. Humans can also spread the virus by carrying it on clothes and shoes. RHDV2 does not affect human health.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rabbits dying due to the virus2. Types of lagomorphs affected by the virus3. Virus survives on animal carcasses, feces and blood4. Humans spread virus through clothingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report from the USGS National Wildlife Health Center published on May 7, rabbit hemorrhagic disease virus serotype 2 or RHDV2, a viral disease deadly to rabbits, is spreading across the southwestern United States.""Rabbit hemorrhagic disease virus can infect domestic rabbits and wild rabbits such as hares, jackrabbits and cottontails.""According to the United States Department of Agriculture, the virus can cause sudden death and nose bleeds caused by internal bleeding.""Other symptoms include fever, loss of appetite, swelling and signs of nervousness or irregular breathing.""RHDV2 can survive on a dead animal's carcass for at least three months. It can also spread if an animal or individual comes into contact with an infected animal's droppings or blood.""RHDV2 can also spread through food, water or any other material that has been exposed to the virus. Humans can also spread the virus by carrying it on clothes and shoes. RHDV2 does not affect human health."SOURCES: USGS National Wildlife Health Center, ScienceMag, United States Department of Agriculture, USA Todayhttps://prd-wret.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/assets/palladium/production/atoms/files/WHB%202020-5%20RHDV2%20update.pdfhttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/05/deadly-virus-killing-wild-rabbits-north-america#https://www.aphis.usda.gov/publications/animal_health/fs-rhdv2.pdfhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/05/19/deadly-virus-killing-wild-rabbits-united-sates/5219265002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 11:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/21/4000233/4000233_38CE5F7B0A65421A85E0FEA0E59EE542_200521_4000233_Explainer__Deadly_virus_threatens_pets_and_wild__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Rabbit Hemorrhagic Disease Virus Type 2, Virus,  Rabbit Hemorrhagic Disease Virus, rabbit, rabbits, lagomorph, RHDV2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4000225</guid>
      <title>Scientists capture photo of formation of new planets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA group of astronomers has successfully captured an image of the birth of two planets orbiting the star PDS 70, according to a report published in The Astronomical Journal.The team of researchers used an infrared pyramid wavefront sensor for adaptive optics located at the W. M. Keck Observatory in Hawaii to process images of two protoplanets forming from the circumstellar disk of PDS 70.Using the infrared sensor, the team implemented a new adaptive optics correction technique to interpret image signals taken from PDS 70 multi-planetary system.This new infrared sensor measures light distortions caused by the Earth's atmosphere.  Sylvain Cetre, a software engineer at Keck Observatory, told Phys.org that the sensor, "dramatically improved our ability to study exoplanets, especially those around low-mass stars where planet formation is actively occurring."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Visualization of PDS 70 multi-planetary system2. Location of W. M. Keck Observatory3. Visualization of PDS 70 next to the Keck II telescope4. Scientists working with the Near-Infrared Camera on the Keck II telescopeVOICEOVER (in English): "A group of astronomers has successfully captured an image of the birth of two planets orbiting the star PDS 70, according to a report published in The Astronomical Journal.""The team of researchers used an infrared pyramid wavefront sensor for adaptive optics located at the W. M. Keck Observatory in Hawaii to process images of two protoplanets forming from the circumstellar disk of PDS 70.""Using the infrared sensor, the team implemented a new adaptive optics correction technique to interpret image signals taken from PDS 70 multi-planetary system.""This new infrared sensor measures light distortions caused by the Earth's atmosphere.  Sylvain Cetre, a software engineer at Keck Observatory, told Phys.org that the sensor, 'dramatically improved our ability to study exoplanets, especially those around low-mass stars where planet formation is actively occurring.'"SOURCES:The Astronomical Journal, Phys.org, https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/1538-3881/ab8aefhttps://phys.org/news/2020-05-astronomers-giant-newborn-planets-pds.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 11:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/21/4000225/4000225_63ADECE6F309427B85A2348343F50771_200521_4000225_Scientists_capture_photo_of_formation_of_new_pla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pds 70, pds 70 system, Keck Observatory, multi-planetary system, circumstellar disk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4000678</guid>
      <title>Unusual neutrino signals caught in the Antarctic, explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of scientists discovered unusual signals caused by high-energy neutrinos using a radio detector called the Antarctic Impulsive Transient Antenna, or ANITA, according to a study published in The Astrophysical Journal submitted on January 6.ANITA floats above the Antarctic, suspended above the continent's ice sheets by a helium balloon. ANITA is designed to detect high-energy neutrinos that hit the Antarctic floor and generate radio light.According to the study, ANITA detected signals that seemed to be caused by extremely high-energy neutrinos behaving in an abnormal way.Usually high-energy neutrinos come to Earth from space. However, these detections showed the neutrinos were hitting the antenna at abnormal angles which suggests they had traveled through the planet. This may mean that the detections could either be physics beyond the Standard Model or a systematic error.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Antarctic Impulsive Transient Antenna floating above Antarctica 2. ANITA receiving signals from neutrinos3. Neutrinos moving abnormally4. Neutrinos enter Earth from space, then begin moving randomlyVOICEOVER (in English): "Using a radio detector called the Antarctic Impulsive Transient Antenna, or ANITA, a team of scientists discovered unusual signals caused by high-energy neutrinos, according to a study published in The Astrophysical Journal submitted on January 6.""ANITA floats above the Antarctic, suspended above the continent's ice sheets by a helium balloon. ANITA is designed to detect high-energy neutrinos that hit the Antarctic floor and generate radio light.""According to the study, ANITA detected signals that seemed to be caused by extremely high-energy neutrinos behaving in an abnormal way.""Usually high-energy neutrinos come to Earth from space. However, these detections showed the neutrinos were hitting the antenna at abnormal angles which suggests they had traveled through the planet. This may mean that the detections could either be physics beyond the Standard Model or a systematic error."SOURCES: Universe Today, LiveScience, The Astrophysical Journal, Ice Cube South Pole Neutrino Observatory, ScienceAlerthttps://www.universetoday.com/146095/high-energy-neutrinos-are-coming-from-supermassive-black-holes/https://www.livescience.com/64827-neutrinos.htmlhttps://arxiv.org/pdf/2001.01737.pdfhttps://icecube.wisc.edu/news/view/709https://www.sciencealert.com/of-course-nasa-did-not-detect-a-parallel-universe-in-antarctica***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 12:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/22/4000678/4000678_DE8C1AF4A91D43E8910630A57D6C2E83_200522_4000678_Unusual_neutrino_signals_caught_in_the_Antarctic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Parallel universe, anita, ANtarctic Impulsive Transient Antenna]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4000667</guid>
      <title>NASA renames its next-gen telescope after woman chief astronomer credited with launching the Hubble telescope</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has renamed its next-generation Wide Field Infrared Survey Telescope after Nancy Roman, the agency's first chief astronomer known as the Mother of Hubble. NASA plans to launch the Roman Space Telescope in the mid-2020s.The Roman Space Telescope has a silvered primary mirror array that is 2.4-meters wide, about the same size as the Hubble's.The Roman will include the 300-megapixel Wide Field Instrument, which has a field of view 100 times greater than the Hubble's infrared instrument. One image from the Roman will hold as much detail as 100 Hubble images.In addition, the new telescope will carry the Coronagraph Instrument, a high-contrast imaging and spectroscopy device.The Roman will survey the Milky Way with the aim of finding around 2,600 exoplanets. Its primary mission will last five years, with another five in a potential extended mission.NASA also plans to use the Roman Space Telescope to find clues about dark energy, which could yield the key to understanding the expansion of the cosmos.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Nancy Roman Telescope2. Primary mirror system and Wide Field Instrument3. The Roman Telescope's field of view is 100 times greater than the Hubble4. The scope will scan the Milky Way for exoplanets5. The scope will investigate dark energy and the expansion of the universeVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has renamed its next-generation Wide Field Infrared Survey Telescope after Nancy Roman, the agency's first chief astronomer known as the Mother of Hubble. NASA plans to launch the Roman Space Telescope in the mid-2020s.""The Roman Space Telescope has a silvered primary mirror array that is 2.4-meters wide, about the same size as the Hubble's." "The Roman will include the 300-megapixel Wide Field Instrument, which has a field of view 100 times greater than the Hubble's infrared instrument." "One image from the Roman will hold as much detail as 100 Hubble images.""In addition, the new telescope will carry the Coronagraph Instrument, a high-contrast imaging and spectroscopy device." "The Roman will survey the Milky Way with the aim of finding around 2,600 exoplanets. Its primary mission will last five years, with another five in a potential extended mission.""NASA also plans to use the Roman Space Telescope to find clues about dark energy, which could yield the key to understanding the expansion of the cosmos."SOURCES: NASA, Nancy Grace Roman Space Telescope, YouTube (NASA)https://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-telescope-named-for-mother-of-hubble-nancy-grace-romanhttps://roman.gsfc.nasa.gov/about.htmlhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YulCMpGs2LU***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 11:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/22/4000667/4000667_15A6360730144C3ABDF65CA2C3C1A36C_200522_4000667_NASA_renames_its_next_gen_telescope_after_woman__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Nancy Grace Roman, Nancy Grace Roman Space Telescope, Roman Space Telescope, Hubble Space Telescope, Hubble, exoplanets, successor to the Hubble,  dark matter, dark energy, space, space exploration, NASA, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4000505</guid>
      <title>Scientists create mice chimeras with an unprecedented amount of human cells: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have engineered mice that have up to 4 percent of their body made of human cells, or the highest amount achieved in human-mice chimeras, according to a study in Science Advances.To create the chimeras, scientists took human stem cells and chemically suppressed a protein called mTOR for three hours. This forces the cells to revert back to the "naive" state, which enables them to grow inside mice embryos.As the embryos matured, researchers found the tissues that would become the heart, liver and bone marrow to contain human cells, which were also found in the blood. Science News reports the technology may help scientists to use chimeras as a source for human organs.Scientists did not detect any trace of human material in the cells that would develop into mice sperm or egg. This eliminates ethical concerns of chimeras capable of reproduction.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chimeric mice made out of 4 percent human cells2. Inhibiting mTOR proteins allows human stem cells to grow in mice embryos3. Embryonic heart, liver and bone marrow tissue found to contain human cells4. Human-mice chimera embryonic gametes contain no human cellsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have engineered mice that have up to 4 percent of their body made of human cells, or the highest amount achieved in human-mice chimeras, according to a study in Science Advances.""To create the chimeras, scientists took human stem cells and chemically suppressed a protein called mTOR for three hours. This forces the cells to revert back to the 'naive' state, which enables them to grow inside mice embryos.""As the embryos matured, researchers found the tissues that would become the heart, liver and bone marrow to contain human cells, which were also found in the blood. Science News reports the technology may help scientists to use chimeras as a source for human organs.""Scientists did not detect any trace of human material in the cells that would develop into mice sperm or egg. This eliminates ethical concerns of chimeras capable of reproduction."SOURCES: Science Advances, Science Newshttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/20/eaaz0298https://www.sciencenews.org/article/mouse-human-chimera-hybrid-embryos***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 07:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/22/4000505/4000505_7972D9829ACB4114835372F10432A6A9_200522_4000505_Scientists_create_mice_chimeras_with_an_unpreced_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, chimeras, chimera, human-mice chimeras, human-mice chimera, human cells, stem cells, embryo, embryo, mTOR, human organs, biology, science, medicine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4001888</guid>
      <title>Cosmic rays may be the source of biological 'handedness'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANInteraction between cosmic rays and early life-forms may be responsible for the fundamental property of chirality, or "handedness," in biological molecules, according to a paper in The Astrophysical Journal Letters.Cosmic rays are constantly bombarding Earth. When they hit the atmosphere, they degrade into cascades of elementary particles.Many organic molecules such as DNA and RNA can be constructed in "left-handed" and "right-handed" versions. In the paper, the researchers propose that the prebiotic soup on ancient Earth produced both left and right-handed versions of these nucleic acids.The paper argues that charged particles from cosmic rays affected right and left-handed molecules differently, conferring an evolutionary advantage on one chirality. This led to life dominated by a single biological handedness.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cosmic rays bombarding Earth2. Cosmic rays degrade into elementary particles in the Earth's atmosphere3. Ancient Earth produced both left and right-handed proto-lifeforms4. Charged particles from cosmic rays affected "right-handed" and "left-handed" molecules differently, offering an evolutionary advantage to one chiralityVOICEOVER (in English): "In new research published in The Astrophysical Journal Letters, scientists from New York University and Stanford University speculate that the interaction between cosmic rays and early life-forms may be responsible for the fundamental property of chirality in biological molecules.""Showers of highly energetic, charged particles from the Sun called cosmic rays are constantly bombarding the Earth. When they hit the Earth's atmosphere, they degrade into cascades of elementary particles.""Many organic molecules such as DNA and RNA can be constructed in 'left-handed' and 'right-handed' versions that are mirror images of each other. In the paper, the researchers propose that the prebiotic soup on ancient Earth produced both left and right-handed versions of these nucleic acids.""The paper argues that when charged particles from cosmic ray cascades reached the Earth's surface, they affected right-handed and left-handed molecules differently, giving an evolutionary advantage to one chirality. Over time this led to life dominated by a single biological handedness."SOURCES: The Astrophysical Journal Lettershttps://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.02525.pdfhttps://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/2041-8213/ab8dc6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 08:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/26/4001888/4001888_E26F9A603C20477898861BCC948EA9CC_200526_4001888_Cosmic_rays_may_be_the_source_of_biological__han_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cosmic rays, chirality, left-handed helix, right-handed helix, left-handed molecule, right-handed molecule, biology, biological handedness, DNA, RNA, nucleic acid, evolution, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4001880</guid>
      <title>Cosmic rays may be the source of biological 'handedness'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANInteraction between cosmic rays and early life-forms may be responsible for the fundamental property of chirality, or "handedness," in biological molecules, according to a paper in The Astrophysical Journal Letters.Cosmic rays are constantly bombarding Earth. When they hit the atmosphere, they degrade into cascades of elementary particles.Many organic molecules such as DNA and RNA can be constructed in "left-handed" and "right-handed" versions. In the paper, the researchers propose that the prebiotic soup on ancient Earth produced both left and right-handed versions of these nucleic acids.The paper argues that charged particles from cosmic rays affected right and left-handed molecules differently, conferring an evolutionary advantage on one chirality. This led to life dominated by a single biological handedness.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cosmic rays bombarding Earth2. Cosmic rays degrade into elementary particles in the Earth's atmosphere3. Ancient Earth produced both left and right-handed proto-lifeforms4. Charged particles from cosmic rays affected "right-handed" and "left-handed" molecules differently, offering an evolutionary advantage to one chiralityVOICEOVER (in English): "In new research published in The Astrophysical Journal Letters, scientists from New York University and Stanford University speculate that the interaction between cosmic rays and early life-forms may be responsible for the fundamental property of chirality in biological molecules.""Showers of highly energetic, charged particles from the Sun called cosmic rays are constantly bombarding the Earth. When they hit the Earth's atmosphere, they degrade into cascades of elementary particles.""Many organic molecules such as DNA and RNA can be constructed in 'left-handed' and 'right-handed' versions that are mirror images of each other. In the paper, the researchers propose that the prebiotic soup on ancient Earth produced both left and right-handed versions of these nucleic acids.""The paper argues that when charged particles from cosmic ray cascades reached the Earth's surface, they affected right-handed and left-handed molecules differently, giving an evolutionary advantage to one chirality. Over time this led to life dominated by a single biological handedness."SOURCES: The Astrophysical Journal Lettershttps://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.02525.pdfhttps://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/2041-8213/ab8dc6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/26/4001880/4001880_20E4095F0C9142ECAFAB617E891E8AA4_200526_4001880_Cosmic_rays_may_be_the_source_of_biological__han_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4001758</guid>
      <title>New research sheds light on why it feels harder to wake up in cold winter mornings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch done on fruit flies shows that a special batch of neurons sensitive to outer temperatures "suppresses" other neurons in charge of morning "activeness."A new study published in the journal Current Biology shows scientists have identified a thermometer-like circuit of neurons that inhibits neurons in a fly's brain that activate alertness, particularly in the mornings.Neurobiologists from Northwestern University found receptors in the fly's antennas that respond to temperatures below around 25 degrees Celsius, or 77 degrees Fahrenheit."The main recipients of these neurons are another batch of brain neurons. These neurons are part of a larger circuit of brain cells that are in charge of regulating wakefulness and sleep rhythms.When the circuit of neurons is activated due to a decrease in external temperatures, certain neurons that are normally activated by morning light are shut down.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fly on window, night turns into day2. Temperature at which temperature-sensitive neurons start inhibiting other neurons3. Fly neurons4. Fly neurons activated by sunlight and suppressed at nighttimeVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study published in the journal Current Biology shows scientists have identified a thermometer-like circuit of neurons that inhibits neurons in a fly's brain that activate alertness, particularly in the mornings.""Neurobiologists from Northwestern University found receptors in the fly's antennas that respond to temperatures below around 25 degrees Celsius, or 77 degrees Fahrenheit.""The main recipients of these neurons are another batch of brain neurons. These neurons are part of a larger circuit of brain cells that are in charge of regulating wakefulness and sleep rhythms.""When the circuit of neurons is activated due to a decrease in external temperatures, certain neurons that are normally activated by morning light are shut down."SOURCES: Current Biology, Science Daily https://www.cell.com/current-biology/pdf/S0960-9822(20)30552-2.pdf?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0960982220305522%3Fshowall%3Dtruehttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/05/200522154559.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 03:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/26/4001758/4001758_9DF1DDB257934C978B8C5EB140A15856_200526_4001758_New_research_sheds_light_on_why_it_feels_harder__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Drosophila melanogaster, Drosophila, Northwestern University, sleep-wake cycle, fruit flies, fly, flies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4002459</guid>
      <title>U.S. field tests high-energy laser weapon: Pacific Fleet Command</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Navy shot down an aerial drone with a solid state laser weapon during a test off Pearl Harbor on May 16, according to the Pacific Fleet.The exercise marked the first shot fired by the Laser Weapon System Demonstrator at sea.The amphibious dock Portland was selected as a test platform for the experimental weapon.Naval documents published by The Drive suggest the laser should include power and cooling units, other subsystems, and integration with the Aegis Combat System. According to the U.S. Navy Institute, the LWSD represents advancements in laser director and spectral beam combining technology, which combines multiple beams of different wavelengths into a more powerful laser.Additionally, the Navy is developing other lasers that will be suitable for the fleet's destroyers that lack the energy output for solid state-type weapons.These lasers would include hard-kill systems as well as less-than-lethal dazzlers that would dissuade approaching boats and disable surveillance platforms.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Solid state laser shots down aerial drone2. U.S.S. Portland carried out the test with the prototype weapon3. LWSD MK 2 features improved laser director and spectral beam combination4. Surface combats will use lasers against hostile drones and boatsVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Navy shot down an aerial drone with a solid state laser weapon during a test off Pearl Harbor on May 16, according to the Pacific Fleet.""The exercise marked the first shot fired by the Laser Weapon System Demonstrator at sea.""The amphibious dock Portland was selected as a test platform for the experimental weapon.""Naval documents published by The Drive suggest the laser should include power and cooling units, other subsystems, and integration with the Aegis Combat System." "According to the U.S. Navy Institute, the LWSD represents advancements in laser director and spectral beam combining technology, which combines multiple beams of different wavelengths into a more powerful laser.""Additionally, the Navy is developing other lasers that will be suitable for the fleet's destroyers that lack the energy output for solid state-type weapons.""These lasers would include hard-kill systems as well as less-than-lethal dazzlers that would dissuade approaching boats and disable surveillance platforms."SOURCES: U.S. Pacific Fleet, U.S. Navy Institute, The Drivehttps://www.cpf.navy.mil/news.aspx/130628https://news.usni.org/2020/05/22/video-uss-portland-fires-laser-weapon-downs-drone-in-first-at-sea-testhttps://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/30500/that-big-mystery-object-northrop-is-barging-from-redondo-beach-is-a-high-power-laser***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 11:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/27/4002459/4002459_034B846C1AFF466CB269A79139CBE249_200527_4002459_U_S__field_tests_high_energy_laser_weapon__Pacif_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, laser weapon, directed energy weapon, high energy laser, solid state laser, Laser Weapon System Demonstrator, LWSD, SSL-TM,  Solid State Laser Technology Maturation, Northrop Grumman, U.S.S. Portland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4002405</guid>
      <title>Asteroid that led to dinosaur extinction impacted Earth at 'deadliest possible angle': study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have determined the angle of impact for the asteroid that contributed to the dinosaurs' extinction 66 million years ago, according to a study in Nature Communications.Writing on behalf of the researchers, Imperial College London says in a news release that the asteroid had struck "at the deadliest possible" angle for life on Earth.Using geological data from the Chicxulub crater in Mexico in a computer model, scientists calculated the space rock's angle of attack at 60 degrees.The asteroid with its steep impact angle reached sulfur, carbonates and water deep in the Earth.The vapors and debris were flung into the atmosphere and triggered a nuclear winter that wiped out the dinosaurs.The researchers found asymmetries between the centers of the mountains inside the crater, the crater's physical center point, and the center of uplifted mantle 30 km beneath the surface.Scientists then worked backward to model the asteroid's impact.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid that resulted in dinosaur extinction impacted Earth at a steep angle2. Scientists calculate the impact angle at 60 degrees3. The steep impact threw debris and vapor that caused a nuclear winter4. Modeling utilized asymmetries in the impact crater's geologyVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have determined the angle of impact for the asteroid that contributed to the dinosaurs' extinction 66 million years ago, according to a study in Nature Communications.""Writing on behalf of the researchers, Imperial College London says in a news release that the asteroid had struck 'at the deadliest possible' angle for life on Earth.""Using geological data from the Chicxulub crater in Mexico in a computer model, scientists calculated the space rock's angle of attack at 60 degrees.""The asteroid with its steep impact angle reached sulfur, carbonates and water deep in the Earth.""The vapors and debris were flung into the atmosphere and triggered a nuclear winter that wiped out the dinosaurs.""The researchers found asymmetries between the centers of the mountains inside the crater, the crater's physical center point, and the center of uplifted mantle 30 km beneath the surface." SOURCES: Nature Communications, Imperial College London, New Atlas https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-020-15269-xhttp://www.imperial.ac.uk/news/197694/dinosaur-dooming-asteroid-struck-earth-deadliest-possible/https://newatlas.com/science/dinosaur-killing-asteroid-deadliest-possible-angle/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 10:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/27/4002405/4002405_57FFDC6B789B4675B2FD8C76B6A6326C_200527_4002405_Asteroid_that_led_to_dinosaur_extinction_impacte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dinosaurs, extinction, asteroid, asteroid, deadliest possible angle, impact angle, Imperial College London, Chicxulub crater, Mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4002209</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How the Sagittarius galaxy has affected the formation of the Milky Way</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in the journal Nature Astronomy using data from Gaia, a space observatory from the European Space Agency, shows the effects of the Sagittarius Dwarf Spheroidal Galaxy on the formation of the Milky Way Galaxy.Due to gravitational forces, the Sagittarius dwarf galaxy crashes time and time again through the Milky Way's disc. One of these collisions occurred roughly at the same time as the formation of our Sun, around 4.7 billion years ago. It is possible this impact contributed to the Sun's creation.The team of researchers examined luminosities, distances and colors of stars within 6,500 light-years around the Sun and then compared the information with already available stellar evolution models to understand the effects of the crashes.Data from Gaia showed three periods of increased star formation. There were peaks 5.7 billion years ago, 1.9 billion years ago and 1 billion years ago. These periods coincide with times where the Sagittarius dwarf galaxy is believed to have crashed through the disc of the Milky Way.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gaia Space Observatory2. Formation of our solar system's Sun3. Saggitarius collides with the Milky Way4. Saggitarius collides with the Milky WayVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study published in the journal Nature Astronomy using data from Gaia, a space observatory from the European Space Agency, shows the effects of the Sagittarius Dwarf Spheroidal Galaxy on the formation of the Milky Way Galaxy.""Due to gravitational forces, the Sagittarius dwarf galaxy crashes time and time again through the Milky Way's disc.""One of these collisions occurred roughly at the same time as the formation of our Sun, around 4.7 billion years ago. It is possible this impact contributed to the Sun's creation.""The team of researchers examined luminosities, distances and colors of stars within 6,500 light-years around the Sun and then compared the information with already available stellar evolution models to understand the effects of the crashes.""Data from Gaia showed three periods of increased star formation. There were peaks 5.7 billion years ago, 1.9 billion years ago and 1 billion years ago." "These periods coincide with times where the Sagittarius dwarf galaxy is believed to have crashed through the disc of the Milky Way."SOURCES: European Space Agency, Nature Astronomyhttps://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Space_Science/Gaia/Galactic_crash_may_have_triggered_Solar_System_formationhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-020-1097-0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 04:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/27/4002209/4002209_3C1701BEF2D7426B9D93CE56219BC5DB_200527_4002209_Explainer__How_the_Sagittarius_galaxy_has_affect_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Milky Way Galaxy, Milky Way Galaxy's warp, warp, galactic collision, gaia, sagittarius, Sagittarius Dwarf Spheroidal Galaxy, dwarf galaxy, European Space Agency, esa, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4002837</guid>
      <title>Ozone depletion may have sparked prehistoric extinction event: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOzone depletion may have triggered a mass die-off of ancient fish and plants by ultraviolet ray exposure 358 million years ago, according to a new study in Science Advances.Science Magazine reports the research team took a "perfect" six-meter-long mudstone drilled core. Preserved in the sample were spores from land plants that had flourished in the Devonian period, when Greenland was part of the Old Redstone Continent.According to the study, the fossilized spores showed a transition from healthy, normal spores to malformed and blackened spores. The deformities observed strongly suggest the parent plants suffered DNA damage from high levels of ultraviolet-B rays.The spores dated to the Late Devonian die-off, the second mass extinction in the period that saw the disappearance of many species, including giant armored sharks. The descendants of the surviving bony fish and sharks would populate today's oceans. Importantly, the second-wave extinction wiped out the first four-limbed fish that had ventured onto land. This means another group of five-toed tetrapods became the precursor of land animals. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ozone depletion and UV ray exposure caused second Devonian extinction2. Study utilizes fossilized spores in mudstone sample 3. Spore fossils show signs of radiation damage and deformity4. Die-off led to the extinction of many armored fish species5. First group of limbed, land-venturing fish becomes extinctVOICEOVER (in English): "Ozone depletion may have triggered a mass die-off of ancient fish and plants by ultraviolet ray exposure 358 million years ago, according to a new study in Science Advances.""Science Magazine reports the research team took a quote 'perfect' six-meter-long mudstone drilled core.""Preserved in the sample were spores from land plants that had flourished in the Devonian period, when Greenland was part of the Old Redstone Continent.""According to the study, the fossilized spores showed a transition from healthy, normal spores to malformed and blackened spores.""The deformities observed strongly suggest the parent plants suffered DNA damage from high levels of ultraviolet-B rays.""The spores dated to the Late Devonian die-off, the second mass extinction in the period that saw the disappearance of many species, including giant armored sharks." "The descendants of the surviving bony fish and sharks would populate today's oceans." "Importantly, the second-wave extinction wiped out the first four-limbed fish that had ventured onto land." "This means another group of five-toed tetrapods became the precursor of land animals." SOURCES: Science Advances, Science Magazine, New Atlashttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/22/eaba0768https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/05/no-asteroids-or-volcanoes-needed-ancient-mass-extinction-tied-ozone-loss-warminghttps://newatlas.com/science/ozone-depletion-mass-extinction-radiation/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 10:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/28/4002837/4002837_21673CA6F523401CB7D82727EBC6AC0E_200528_4002837_Ozone_depletion_may_have_sparked_prehistoric_ext_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Devonian period, mass extinction, die off, ozone depletion, spores, uv, ultraviolet, DNA damage, UV-B, ultraviolet-b, age of fishes, armored fish, armored shark, tetrapod, tetrapods, Greenland, University of Southhampton, U.K.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4002771</guid>
      <title>Rates of climate change in deep oceans could be severely affected, even in the best case scenario: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEarth's oceans could be experiencing rates of climate change seven times higher than levels today by the second half of the century, even if greenhouse gas emissions drop significantly, according to a report published in Nature Climate Change.A team of international scientists analyzed present and future models of climate velocity. This is the speed at which marine animals would have to move in order to live in waters with certain temperatures as different ocean layers become warmer.Scientists then used climate models to estimate climate velocity rates today in three different scenarios: One scenario is where greenhouse gas emissions start falling from now; another is in which emissions would begin to fall in the middle of this century; and the final scenario is one where emissions would continue to rise up to 2100.However, even in the scenario where emissions would start declining now, climate velocity in the ocean's layer that covers from 200 meters deep up to 1 kilometer down  what is known as the mesopelagic layer  would change from about 6 kilometers per decade to 50 kilometers by mid-century. Conversely, in the same period, the climate velocity rate would halve on the ocean's surface level.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Warming oceans affected by climate change2. Upper layer of ocean becoming warmer3. Types of scenarios of warming analyzed4. Ocean layer becomes warmer and causes fish to migrateVOICEOVER (in English): "Earth's oceans could be experiencing rates of climate change seven times higher than levels today by the second half of the century, even if greenhouse gas emissions drop significantly, according to a report published in Nature Climate Change.""The team of international scientists analyzed present and future models of climate velocity. This is the speed at which marine animals would have to move in order to live in waters with certain temperatures as different ocean layers become warmer.""Scientists then used climate models to estimate climate velocity rates today in three different scenarios: One scenario is where greenhouse gas emissions start falling from now; another is in which emissions would begin to fall in the middle of this century; and the final scenario is one where emissions would continue to rise up to 2100.""However, even in the scenario where emissions would start declining now, climate velocity in the ocean's layer that covers from 200 meters deep up to 1 kilometer down  what is known as the mesopelagic layer  would change from about 6 kilometers per decade to 50 kilometers by mid-century. Conversely, in the same period, climate velocity rate would halve on the ocean's surface level."SOURCES: Nature Climate Change, Hokkaido University, The Guardianhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41558-020-0773-5https://www.global.hokudai.ac.jp/blog/there-is-no-escaping-from-climate-change-even-in-the-deep-sea/https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/may/26/climate-change-in-deep-oceans-could-be-seven-times-faster-by-middle-of-century-report-says***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 08:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/28/4002771/4002771_78B331097CEB4C43ACA3BC9496C6469D_200528_4002771_Rates_of_climate_change_in_deep_oceans_could_be__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Climate change, climate change in deep oceans, global warming, climate shift, warming oceans, Hokkaido university, University of Queensland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4003085</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong national security law changes, explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese authorities on May 28 bypassed Hong Kong's legislature to approve a national security law that threatens the foundations of the city's freedoms and autonomy. This new law, which will be implemented upon promulgation by Hong Kong's government, forbids acts of sedition, secession and subversion of China's central government.This new Beijing-backed security plan raises concerns, particularly for pro-democracy activists, Chinese dissidents and journalists who could fall victim to greater extralegal persecution.The new law could allow authorities to push back or silence pro-democracy lawmakers in the region. Reuters reports that on May 28, two pro-democracy lawmakers in Hong Kong were removed from the Legislative Council.Their removal reportedly happened during a meeting where lawmakers were discussing the first amendment to the new law which would make it a criminal offense to insult the Chinese national anthem.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Standing Committee of China's National People's Congress2. Authorities arrest protester and censor journalist3. Legislative Council of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region4. Authorities arrest student for not singing the Chinese national anthemVOICEOVER (in English): "Chinese authorities on May 28 bypassed Hong Kong's legislature to approve a national security law that threatens the foundations of the city's freedoms and autonomy. This new law, which will be implemented upon promulgation by Hong Kong's government, forbids acts of sedition, secession and subversion of China's central government.""This new Beijing-backed security plan raises concerns, particularly for pro-democracy activists, Chinese dissidents and journalists who could fall victim to greater extralegal persecution.""The new law could allow authorities to push back or silence pro-democracy lawmakers in the region. In fact, Reuters reports that on May 28, two pro-democracy lawmakers in Hong Kong were removed from the Legislative Council.""Their removal reportedly happened during a meeting where lawmakers were discussing the first amendment to the new law which would make it a criminal offense to insult the Chinese national anthem."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, CNNhttps://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3086076/beijings-new-national-security-law-will-not-harm-hong-kongshttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/05/22/asia/hong-kong-china-national-security-law-intl-hnk/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 03:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/29/4003085/4003085_149C472317724666A0936C5EFFDE3240_200529_4003085_Hong_Kong_national_security_law_changes__explain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hong Kong demonstrations, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, security law, hong kong security law, beijing security law, china security law,  National People's Congress, Article 23, Article 23 of the Basic Law, china national anthem, china, hong kong, mainland china, NPC Standing Committee]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
