<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3956918</guid>
      <title>California-based startup to hurl rockets into space with mechanical centrifuge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA U.S. aerospace company is building a huge centrifuge to launch spacecraft into orbit.Wired.com reports that the SpinLaunch's centrifuge, or the kinetic launch system, has an internal vacuum chamber with a diameter of 100 meters.The SpinLaunch rocket is about the size of an SUV and the vehicle's design will allow it to carry a satellite payload of about 200 pounds.The centrifuge's electric motor will spin the tethered rocket for an hour to build up speed.Once the rocket is ratcheted up to a speed of over 5,000 miles per hour, the release mechanism will cut the vehicle loose and let it fly through the 35 degree launch tunnel.When the vehicle reaches the edge of the stratosphere, the rocket's internal propulsion will fire and push the spacecraft through the final stretch to space.Citing SpinLaunch, Wired reports that the centrifuge could launch up to five small satellites a day and reduce launch costs by a factor of almost 20.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The centrifuge launch system and dimensions of the internal vacuum chamber2. Size of the rocket and its payload3. The centrifuge spin the rocket for one hour to reach a speed of 5,000 miles per hour4. Advantages of mechanical centrifuge in rate of launch and cost reduction VOICEOVER (in English): "A U.S. aerospace company is building a huge centrifuge to launch spacecraft into orbit.""Wired.com reports that the SpinLaunch's centrifuge, or the kinetic launch system, has an internal vacuum chamber with a diameter of 100 meters.""The SpinLaunch rocket is about the size of an SUV and the vehicle's design will allow it to carry a satellite payload of about 200 pounds.""The centrifuge's electric motor will spin the tethered rocket for an hour to build up speed.""Once the rocket is ratcheted up to a speed of over 5,000 miles per hour, the release mechanism will cut the vehicle loose and let it fly through the 35 degree launch tunnel.""When the vehicle reaches the edge of the stratosphere, the rocket's internal propulsion will fire and push the spacecraft through the final stretch to space.""Citing SpinLaunch, Wired reports that the centrifuge could launch up to five small satellites a day and reduce launch costs by a factor of almost 20."SOURCES: WIRED https://www.wired.com/story/inside-spinlaunch-the-space-industrys-best-kept-secret/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 13:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/31/3956918/3956918_5333F5EF0426418BBA9E2930F45A4AA9_200131_3956918_California_based_startup_to_hurl_rockets_into_sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Centrifuge, space launch, throwing rockets into space, slinging rockets into space, giant centrifuge, launch rockets, kinetic launch system, spinlaunch, U.S., space, aerospace]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956859</guid>
      <title>New coronavirus capable of exponential growth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese Researchers find that the novel coronavirus epidemic doubled in size every 7.4 days during the initial outbreak from December last year to early January.The statistical study published in the New England Journal of Medicine suggests human to human transmission occurred early in the outbreak's beginning.Examining the first 425 confirmed cases of coronavirus infection, the scientists estimate that the mean incubation period was 5.2 days.Before January 1, 2020, 55 percent of the symptomatic cases were linked to the Wuhan wet market, but just 8.6 percent of the subsequent cases were connected to the market.The authors say that it is clear that human-to-human transmission is occurring and that the epidemic has been spreading in recent weeks.MedPage Today reports that virus' reproductive number of 2.2 means a carrier will infect two people on average, which is more than Ebola.Citing Infectious Diseases Society of America, the outlet reports that the reproductive number is situational and quarantining a patient could reduce the number to zero.New England Journal of Medicine, MedPage Today, Healiohttps://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2001316?query=featured_homehttps://www.medpagetoday.com/infectiousdisease/publichealth/84620https://www.healio.com/infectious-disease/emerging-diseases/news/online/%7B686f7316-c3e1-454d-971e-b131b74c388a%7D/evidence-shows-human-transmission-of-coronavirus-since-mid-decemberRUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The viral outbreak is capable of exponential growth2. The estimated incubation period3. Human to human transmission occurred early on and the disease is spreading4. The virus is potentially capable of outpacing Ebola in transmission speed VOICEOVER (in English): "Chinese Researchers find that the novel coronavirus epidemic doubled in size every 7.4 days during the initial outbreak from December last year to early this month.""The statistical study published in the New England Journal of Medicine suggests human to human transmission occurred early in the outbreak's beginning.""Examining the first 425 confirmed cases of coronavirus infection, the scientists estimate that the mean incubation period was 5.2 days.""Before January 1, 2020, 55 percent of the symptomatic cases were linked to the Wuhan wet market, but just 8.6 percent of the subsequent cases were connected to the market.""The authors say that it is clear that human-to-human transmission is occurring and that the epidemic has been spreading in recent weeks.""MedPage Today reports that virus' reproductive number of 2.2 means a carrier will infect two people on average, which is more than Ebola.""Citing Infectious Diseases Society of America, the outlet reports that the reproductive number is situational and quarantining a patient could reduce the number to zero."SOURCES: New England Journal of Medicine, MedPage Today, Healiohttps://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2001316?query=featured_homehttps://www.medpagetoday.com/infectiousdisease/publichealth/84620https://www.healio.com/infectious-disease/emerging-diseases/news/online/%7B686f7316-c3e1-454d-971e-b131b74c388a%7D/evidence-shows-human-transmission-of-coronavirus-since-mid-december***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 11:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/31/3956859/3956859_EA6F17B1DD9241E7A39F638B09AEE958_200131_3956859_New_coronavirus_capable_of_exponential_growth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, wuhan virus, china pneumonia, faster than the Ebola, faster than ebola, reproduction number, 2019-ncov, 2019 ncov, novel coronavirus, new coronavirus,  TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956709</guid>
      <title>Iranian missile strike injures 50 troops: Pentagon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Pentagon now says that 50 U.S. troops stationed in Iraq have been diagnosed with traumatic brain injury after an Iranian missile strike earlier this month.The agency previously said that 34 troops had been injured in the Iranian attacks.In an earlier statement, the Department of Defense explained that Iran launched more than a dozen ballistic missiles that targeted U.S. military and coalition forces in Iraq on January 7.The attack was an act of retaliation against the U.S. after the killing of Qassem Soleimani, an Iranian Revolution Guard general.Thirty-one of the soldiers were treated in Iraq and have since returned to duty, Reuters reports, citing a statement. Eighteen troops have been sent to Germany for further treatment while one was sent to Kuwait and has since returned to duty.According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, symptoms of traumatic brain injury include headaches, dizziness, nausea, and sensitivity to noise or light.The Trump administration has been criticized for taking so long to reveal the extent of casualties caused by the Iranian missile attack, reports BBC News. U.S. President Donald Trump initially said that no U.S. soldier had been injured right after the attack, before raising the number of casualties to 34 and now 50. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Amount of troops diagnosed with traumatic brain injury after Iran's missile strike 2. How many missiles Iran launched towards U.S. forces stationed in Iraq3. Where the soldiers were treated4. Symptoms of traumatic brain injury VOICEOVER (in English): "The Pentagon now says that 50 U.S. troops stationed in Iraq have been diagnosed with traumatic brain injury after an Iranian missile strike earlier this month.""The agency previously said that 34 troops had been injured in the Iranian attacks.""In an earlier statement, the Department of Defense explained that Iran launched more than a dozen ballistic missiles that targeted U.S. military and coalition forces in Iraq on January 7.""Citing a statement from the Pentagon, Reuters reports that 31 of the soldiers were treated in Iraq and have since returned to duty." "Eighteen troops have been sent to Germany for further treatment while one was sent to Kuwait and has since returned to duty.""According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, symptoms of traumatic brain injury include headaches, dizziness, nausea, and sensitivity to noise or light."SOURCES: BBC News, NPR, Department of Defense, Reuters, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Times of Israelhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51301825https://www.npr.org/2020/01/29/800770355/pentagon-now-says-50-troops-not-34-suffered-brain-injuries-in-iran-strikehttps://www.defense.gov/Newsroom/Releases/Release/Article/2052103/dod-statement-on-iranian-ballistic-missile-attacks-in-iraq/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iraq-security-usa-casualties/u-s-says-50-troops-now-diagnosed-with-traumatic-brain-injury-after-iran-strike-idUSKBN1ZS057https://www.cdc.gov/traumaticbraininjury/symptoms.htmlhttps://www.timesofisrael.com/pentagon-now-says-50-troops-suffered-brain-injuries-in-iran-missile-strike/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 07:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/31/3956709/3956709_B57CA03FE7524FB98239C2FADE71A540_200131_3956709_Iranian_missile_strike_injures_50_troops__Pentag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, iran vs usa, iranian attack on us airbase, iranian attack on us airbase in Iraq, US troops injured in Iraninan attack, Ain al-Asad air base, iranian attack 2020, US troops traumatic brain injury]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956703</guid>
      <title>Wuhan coronavirus spreads to every region in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has confirmed its first case of novel coronavirus in Tibet. This means the Wuhan virus has now spread to every single region across China, bringing up the total number of confirmed cases to nearly 9,800 as of Friday, according to the New York Times.According to CNN, the number of coronavirus cases has already surpassed the number of SARS cases, which was 5,327, inside China back in 2003. The virus has taken the lives of 213 people in China.On Thursday, the World Health Organization declared the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak a global health emergency.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Every Chinese region is now infected with the coronavirus2. Other countries the virus has spread to3. Countries that are moving their citizens out of Wuhan4. Countries are advising citizens to avoid all non-essential travel to China5. Symptoms of the virus6. How the virus spreads7. Precautions taken against the virusVOICEOVER (in English): "China has confirmed its first case of novel coronavirus in Tibet." "This means the Wuhan virus has now spread to every single region across China, bringing up the total number of confirmed cases to nearly 9,800 as of Friday, according to the New York Times.""BBC News reports the novel coronavirus has spread to at least 19 other nations including Japan, South Korea, Vietnam, Cambodia, Malaysia, Singapore, the U.S. and Canada.""Since the outbreak, countries including Japan and the U.S. have rushed to evacuate their citizens out of the Chinese city of Wuhan, where the virus is believed to have originated.""According to CNN, other countries including Australia, Germany, Italy and Spain said that they are working with local authorities in China and are expected to repatriate their citizens out of Wuhan later this week.""BBC News reports that a large number of countries are advising their citizens to avoid all non-essential travel to China.""Symptoms of the coronavirus include severe coughing, fever and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.""The coronavirus is believed to have originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there are now documented cases of the virus being transmitted between humans.""The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention advised the public to wear facemasks and cover the mouth when coughing or sneezing to prevent the spread of the coronavirus.""The CDC also advised the public to avoid using unwashed hands to touch their eyes, nose and mouth, and to avoid sharing items that could easily be infected."SOURCES: BBC News, CNN, China Daily, Caixin, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, New York Times, Business Insider   https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51305526https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51299735https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/29/world/wuhan-coronavirus-evacuations-intl/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/asia/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-01-30-20-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/28/asia/wuhan-coronavirus-update-jan-29-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/30/asia/wuhan-coronavirus-update-china-spread-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202001/30/WS5e32318ca310128217273a9a.htmlhttps://www.caixinglobal.com/2020-01-30/wuhan-virus-latest-china-reports-second-pneumonia-linked-death-101505300.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/about/prevention-treatment.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/30/world/asia/coronavirus-china.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/china-virus-everything-we-know-deadly-2019-ncov-wuhan-spread-2020-1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 07:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/31/3956703/3956703_1AB850523F584D6BB21B317042A4DF4A_200131_3956703_Wuhan_coronavirus_spreads_to_every_region_in_Chi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, china virus outbreak 2020, china virus outbreak, chinese virus, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957961</guid>
      <title>Stars bolster Einstein's theory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn a new study published in Science, astronomers write that a dwarf star in the Musca constellation has so much mass that it measurably distorts space and time.According to OzGrav, the dwarf star's stellar companion, an exotic pulsar, courses around the bigger star in a speedy five-hour orbit.Space.com reports that the white dwarf is the size of the Earth, but according to OzGrav, the star's mass and density is hundreds of thousands of times greater than our planet.According to Space.com, the pulsar is the corpse of a star that had gone supernova and the dead star crushes protons and electrons to emit neutrons.The white dwarf's powerful gravity and rapid spin cause frame-dragging, or distortions in space-time.Frame-dragging imparts a wobbling effect on the pulsar and makes the neutron star twirl on its axis about 30 times an hour.The drift in the pulsar's orbit is then picked up by Australia's telescopes, including Parkes, which allowed astrophysicists to corroborate Einstein 's theory of general relativity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The binary star system of white dwarf and pulsar in Musca constellation2.  Characteristics of the white dwarf and pulsar3.  White dwarf's gravity causes frame-fragging4.  Pulsar's spin detected by Australia's telescopesVOICEOVER (in English): "In a new study published in Science, astronomer writes that a dwarf star in the Musca constellation has so much mass that it measurably distorts space and time.""According to OzGrav, the dwarf star's stellar companion--an exotic pulsar--courses around the bigger star in a speedy five hour orbit.""Space.com reports that the white dwarf is the size of the Earth, but according to OzGrav, the star's mass and density is hundreds of thousands of times greater than our planet.""According to Space.com, the pulsar is the corpse of a star that had gone supernova and the dead star crushes protons and electrons to emit neutrons.""The white dwarf's powerful gravity and rapid spin cause 'frame-dragging,' or distortions in space-time.""Frame-dragging imparts a wobbling effect on the pulsar and makes the neutron star twirl on its axis about 30 times an hour.""The drift in the pulsar's orbit is then picked up by Australia's telescopes, including Parkes, which allowed astrophysicists to corroborate Einstein 's theory of general relativity."SOURCES: Science, Youtube (OzGrav), Space.com, New Atlashttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/367/6477/577https://www.youtube.com/watch?time_continue=59&v=GOb3MCAg9zM&feature=emb_logohttps://www.space.com/einstein-general-relativity-frame-dragging.htmlhttps://newatlas.com/space/stars-twisting-dragging-spacetime/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 11:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/03/3957961/3957961_9801B11A9CF94696B5F5BBE6C0FDD6E6_200203_3957961_Stars_bolster_Einstein_s_theory_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, White dwarf, giant stars, giant star, twisting space and time, distorting space and time, space-time continuum, space time, pulsar, space-time distortion, frame-dragging, frame dragging, gravity, binary stars, albert einstein,  general theory of relativity, general relativity, relativity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957952</guid>
      <title>China confirms H5N1 bird flu outbreak in Hunan province</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has confirmed the latest outbreak of the highly pathogenic H5N1 bird flu in Hunan province.On Sunday, China's Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Affairs reported the discovery of an H5N1 cluster on a farm in the province's city of Shaoyang[a].The incident occurred on a farm with about 7,900 chicken, where 4,500 of the birds have died. Local authorities have responded by culling the infected birds.According to the WHO, H5N1 is an influenza virus that is highly contagious among birds and can cause severe respiratory disease in avians.The virus does not infect people easily and human to human transmission is rare.However, the WHO reports that people associated with close contact with dead or live birds could contract the H5N1 and that the infection is fatal to humans 60 percent of the time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Outbreak of H5N1 reported in China's Hunan2. The incident killed 4,500 chickens out of 7,900 on the farm3. H5N1 virus is highly infectious to chickens but does not usually transmit to humans4. People who handle birds may contract the disease with a 60 percent mortality rateVOICEOVER (in English): "China has confirmed the latest outbreak of the highly pathogenic H5N1 bird flu in Hunan province.""On Sunday, China's Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Affairs reported the discovery of an H5N1 cluster on a farm in the province's city of Shaoyang[b].""The incident occurred on a farm with about 7,900 chicken, where 4,500 of the birds have died. Local authorities have responded by culling the infected birds.""According to the WHO, H5N1 is an influenza virus that is highly contagious among birds and can cause severe respiratory disease in avians.""The virus does not infect people easily and human to human transmission is rare.""However, the WHO reports that people associated with close contact with dead or live birds could contract the H5N1 and that the infection is fatal to humans 60 percent of the time."SOURCES: Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Affairs (China), World Health Organiation, Reuters, South Morning China Post, Business Insiderhttp://www.moa.gov.cn/gk/yjgl_1/yqfb/202002/t20200201_6336498.htmhttps://www.who.int/influenza/human_animal_interface/avian_influenza/h5n1_research/faqs/en/https://www.reuters.com/article/health-birdflu-china/china-reports-h5n1-bird-flu-outbreak-in-hunan-province-idUSL4N2A10GChttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3048566/china-reports-outbreak-deadly-bird-flu-among-chickens-hunanhttps://www.businessinsider.com/bird-flu-china-coronavirus-pathogenic-strain-of-h5n1-highly-2020-2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/03/3957952/3957952_49C55FA8820C488FA0A451987D67E1EA_200203_3957952_China_confirms_H5N1_bird_flu_outbreak_in_Hunan_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Bird flu, avian flu, H5N1, influenza, flu, Chinese bird flu, China bird flu outbreak,  China bird flu outbreak 2020,  Chinese bird flu outbreak 2020, highly pathogenic, chicken, health, chicken farm, shaoyang, huna]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957877</guid>
      <title>Hackers target United Nations networks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLeaked documents from the United Nations reveal that the body's networks had been compromised by hackers last year.Thirty-three servers were compromised at the United Nations Geneva headquarters while at least four were infected at the agency's Vienna office. The United Nations Human Rights Geneva office also had three of its servers compromised.Hackers exploited a flaw in Microsoft's SharePoint software to infiltrate the United Nations' networks, the Associated Press reports, citing the report. Hackers were able to exfiltrate roughly 400 gigabytes of data.According to the New Humanitarian, which had access to the documents, hackers may have been able to access internal documents, emails and databases from the United Nations.The publication says staff records, health insurance and commercial contract information were also compromised. Staff members were asked to change their passwords but were not informed of the breach.A UN official told the Associated Press that it was possible the cyber attack was state-sponsored as it appeared "sophisticated."Technicians isolated the agency's data center from the internet and rebuilt its infrastructure and replaced keys and credentials to ensure network systems were protected, the Associated Press reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The United Nations' networks were compromised2. How the hackers infiltrated the networks3. What the hackers may have accessed4. Person data of staff members may have also been compromisedVOICEOVER (in English): "Leaked documents from the United Nations reveal that the body's networks had been compromised by hackers last year.""Thirty-three servers were compromised at the United Nations Geneva headquarters while at least four were infected at the agency's Vienna office." "The United Nations Human Rights Geneva office also had three of its servers compromised.""Citing the report, the Associated Press reports that hackers exploited a flaw in Microsoft's SharePoint software to infiltrate the United Nations' networks.""Hackers were able to exfiltrate roughly 400 gigabytes of data.""According to the New Humanitarian, which had access to the documents, hackers may have been able to access internal documents, emails and databases from the United Nations.""The publication says staff records, health insurance and commercial contract information were also compromised.""Staff members were asked to change their passwords but were not informed of the breach."SOURCES: Associated Press, The New Humanitarian, CNet, Timehttps://apnews.com/0d958e15d7f5081dd612f07482f48b73https://www.thenewhumanitarian.org/investigation/2020/01/29/united-nations-cyber-attackhttps://www.cnet.com/news/united-nations-reportedly-suffered-a-hack-which-it-tried-to-keep-secret/https://time.com/5773654/united-nations-server-hacked/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/03/3957877/3957877_2918A69553C64EC2922E77945A323D5C_200203_3957877_Hackers_target_United_Nations_networks_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, United Nations, United Nations hacked, United Nations networks hacked, hacking operation, United Nations breach, United Nations security breach, UN hacked]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957796</guid>
      <title>Longest ever smuggling tunnel found at U.S.-Mexico border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAuthorities have found what they are calling the "longest" smuggling tunnel ever discovered on the U.S.-Mexico border.In a statement on January 29, the U.S. Customs and Border Protection agency announced that it had uncovered the cross-border tunnel along the U.S. border with Mexico.The underground tunnel has a total length of 4,309 feet, making it the longest smuggling on the southwestern border found to date.Officials said that the tunnel was concealed by a small industrial building in Tijuana, Mexico, and stretched over three-quarters of a mile to San Diego, California.Images shared by the U.S. border officials show that the tunnel is narrow, only two feet wide and roughly five and a half feet high. Officials said they discovered hundreds of sandbags at the end of the tunnel blocking what is suspected to be an old exit to the city of San Diego.U.S. authorities also uncovered an incomplete offshoot from the main cross-border tunnel leading into the U.S.The tunnel housed an extensive transport system including an elevator at the entrance and a rail system. The cross-border tunnel was also found to contain an air ventilation system, a drainage system and high voltage electrical cables.U.S. officials have yet to make any arrests regarding the discovery of the tunnel.Previously, authorities had found a 2,966-foot-long tunnel in San Diego in 2014.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cross-border tunnel between Mexico and the U.S.2. How the tunnel was concealed3. Dimensions of the tunnel and how it was blocked4. Facilities inside the tunnelVOICEOVER (in English): "In a statement on January 29, the U.S. Customs and Border Protection agency announced that it had uncovered the cross-border tunnel along the U.S. border with Mexico.""The underground tunnel has a total length of 4,309 feet, making it the longest smuggling on the southwestern border found to date." "Officials said that the tunnel was concealed by a small industrial building in Tijuana, Mexico, and stretched over three-quarters of a mile to San Diego, California.""Images shared by the U.S. border officials show that the tunnel is narrow, only two feet wide and roughly five and a half feet high.""Officials said they discovered hundreds of sandbags at the end of the tunnel blocking what is suspected to be an old exit to the city of San Diego.""The tunnel housed an extensive transport system including an elevator at the entrance and a rail system.""The cross-border tunnel was also found to contain an air ventilation system, a drainage system and high voltage electrical cables."SOURCES: BBC News, New York Times, U.S. Customs and Border Protection, Washington Posthttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51304861https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/30/world/americas/tunnel-us-mexico-border.html?auth=linked-googlehttps://www.cbp.gov/newsroom/local-media-release/longest-cross-border-tunnel-discovered-san-diegohttps://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2020/01/30/border-smuggling-tunnel-mexico-cbp/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/03/3957796/3957796_C719644DA7094FF2A06D04F61ADC7EB5_200203_3957796_Longest_ever_smuggling_tunnel_found_at_U_S__Mexi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US mexico border, US mexico tunnel, US mexico border wall, smuggling tunnel, mexican smuggling tunnel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958423</guid>
      <title>The impact of plants on global warming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from Boston University have found that increased vegetation growth, or greening, has effectively slowed global warming. Greening usually involves intensive land use for farming, planting trees at a large scale or natural reforestation of lands that have been abandoned. The study found that roughly half of Earth's vegetated land has been greened due to this technique.For the study, scientists analyzed satellite images from the 1980s to the 2010s. They noticed an increase of greening in China and India over the decades due to afforestation efforts.As green leaves convert sunlight to sugar, carbon dioxide in the atmosphere is replaced with water vapor which cools Earth's surface. In the study, researchers explained that global greening may have slowed the rate of global warming by roughly 0.2 to 0.23 degrees Celsius.Study authors Shilong Piao and Xuhui Wang, explained in a Boston University news release that this provides "credible evidence" that human activities are dramatically impacting Earth's climate.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How global warming has slowed2. What greening is3. How plants change help to change carbon dioxide into water vapor4. Global warming may be have been slowed by roughly 0.2 to 0.23 CelsiusVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from Boston University have found that increased vegetation growth, or greening, has effectively slowed global warming.""Greening usually involves intensive land use for farming, planting trees at a large scale or natural reforestation of lands that have been abandoned.""The study found that roughly half of Earth's vegetated land has been greened due to this technique.""As green leaves convert sunlight to sugar, carbon dioxide in the atmosphere is replaced with water vapor which cools Earth's surface.""In the study, researchers explained that global greening may have slowed the rate of global warming by roughly 0.2 to 0.23 degrees Celsius."SOURCES: Boston University, Nature Reviews Earth & Environmenthttps://www.bu.edu/articles/2020/plants-are-slowing-global-warming/https://www.nature.com/articles/s43017-019-0001-x***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/04/3958423/3958423_D66DC5F3B562442CA1D51CC7FE582B2A_200204_3958423_The_impact_of_plants_on_global_warming_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Global warming, climate change, plants slowing global warming, global warming plants, effect of plants on global warming, impact of plants on global warming, plants and global warming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958217</guid>
      <title>Greece plans to install sea barrier to prevent influx of migrants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGreece wants to put up a sea barrier to deter refugees and asylum-seekers from reaching its islands.According to the BBC, migrants fleeing persecution and violence in countries like Afghanistan and Syria often try to reach Europe by traveling through Turkey to Greece.Migrant camps on several Greek islands are now overcrowded, but plans to create new ones have only angered residents, who took to the streets to protest them.With arrivals proving hard to manage, Greece is planning to install a floating barrier near the island of Lesbos on the Aegean Sea.According to the Guardian, the 2.7-kilometer long netted barrier will rise from pylons 50 meters above water, and will be equipped with flashing lights.Greece's defense ministry said the budget for the project is 500,000 euros, which includes around four years of maintenance costs.The BBC reports that such barriers rising above sea level will make it difficult for small boats to pass, and may present a problem for propeller-driven vessels.Greek authorities believe a sea barrier will be able to curb flows in a similar manner to the barbed-wire fence built in Evros, along the northern land border with Turkey, in 2012.Amnesty International, meanwhile, criticized Greece's plan, warning that it would only add to the dangers refugees are already facing in their quest for safety.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Refugee route to to Greece via Turkey2. Floating sea barrier near Lesbos3. Boats unable to pass barrier4. Evros barbed-wire fence along northern land borderVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, migrants fleeing persecution and violence in countries like Afghanistan and Syria often try to reach Europe by travelling through Turkey to Greece.""With arrivals proving hard to manage, Greece is planning to install a floating barrier near the island of Lesbos on the Aegean Sea.""According to the Guardian, the 2.7-kilometer long netted barrier will rise from pylons 50 meters above water, and will be equipped with flashing lights.""The BBC reports that such barriers rising above sea level will make it difficult for small boats to pass, and may present a problem for propeller-driven vessels.""Greek authorities believe a sea barrier will be able to curb flows in a similar manner to the barbed-wire fence built in Evros, along the northern land border with Turkey, in 2012."SOURCES: The Guardian, BBC, New York Timeshttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jan/30/greece-plans-to-build-sea-barrier-off-lesbos-to-deter-migrantshttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51308506https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/01/world/europe/greece-migrants-floating-barrier.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/04/3958217/3958217_6D94D879043543A19534EE66DB9E7304_200204_3958217_Greece_plans_to_install_sea_barrier_to_prevent_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Greek sea barrier, sea barrier, sea fence, Lesbos sea fence, floating sea barrier, floating barrier, EU refugees, Greek refugees, asylum seekers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959020</guid>
      <title>U.S. creates first ever coupled quantum dots</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCoupled quantum dots  which act like artificial atoms that share an electron  could potentially form a robust qubit to revolutionize computing.According to a study in Physical Review B, scientists have created the first ever pair of this substance.The U.S. National Institute of Standards and Technology says that classical computers are made of binary bits that store information as fix values of either one or zero.Qubits can take on multiple values simultaneously, which enables quantum computers that utilize qubits to perform larger and more complex tasks.To create the coupled quantum dots, NIST researchers hovered a scanning tunneling microscope above a sheet of graphene with an underlying layer of boron nitride.The STM's electrical charge penetrates the graphene and releases electrons from the boron nitride, which the graphene then captured. Afterward, the team applied a magnetic field on the microscope's tip and forced the electrons to take up residence in two concentric rings.This process leads to the creation of the coupled system, but the research team states that they are unable to explain their success with the current state of quantum theory. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Scientists create first-ever coupled quantum dots2. Coupled quantum dots potentially a key to breakthrough in quantum computing3. Scanning tunneling microscope utilized to create the coupled dots4. Magnified STM tip completes the processVOICEOVER (in English): "Coupled quantum dots  which act like artificial atoms that share an electron  could potentially form a robust qubit to revolutionize computing.""According to a study in Physical Review B, scientists have created the first ever pair of this substance.""The U.S. National Institute of Standards and Technology says that classical computers are made of binary bits that store information as fix values of either one or zero.""Qubits can take on multiple values simultaneously, which enables quantum computers that utilize qubits to perform larger and more complex tasks.""To create the coupled quantum dots, NIST researchers hovered a scanning tunneling microscope above a sheet of graphene with an underlying layer of boron nitride.""The STM's electrical charge penetrates the graphene and releases electrons from the boron nitride, which the graphene then captured.""Afterward, the team applied a magnetic field on the microscope's tip and forced the electrons to take up residence in two concentric rings.""This process leads to the creation of the coupled system, but the research team states that they are unable to explain their success with the current state of quantum theory."SOURCES:  Physical Review B, National Institute of Standards and Technologyhttps://journals.aps.org/prb/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevB.101.035428https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2020/01/what-pair-coupled-quantum-dots-may-offer-new-way-store-quantum-information***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 12:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/05/3959020/3959020_A72E48C7A5904AC4A92D6B644FF77745_200205_3959020_U_S__creates_first_ever_coupled_quantum_dots_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, coupled quantum dots, quantum dots, quantum bits, qubits, qubit, quantum computers, quantum computing, computer science, quantum physics, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958994</guid>
      <title>Experiencing discrimination could increase pain sensitivity in racial minorities: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in Nature Human Behavior suggests that discrimination can change how different ethnic groups perceive and respond to pain. The University of Miami says scientists gave pain stimuli to the participants' arm, then gauged their pain via MRI.Researchers learned that when the same pain is applied by a heating device, African Americans reported more pain than Hispanic or non-Hispanic white American participants.Scientists found that two areas of the brain  the ventral striatum and ventromedial prefrontal cortex  responded to pain more strongly in African Americans.Those brain areas have been linked to chronic pain."Since stressful experiences are correlated to chronic pain later in life, the researchers believe that stress from racial discrimination may cause increased pain sensitivity.Yet data suggests that doctors tend to believe African Americans to be more pain tolerant, which might make them less inclined to alleviate black pain.The research team writes in a statement: 'Understanding why these pain biases exist, therefore, is a key step toward ... eliminating racial and ethnic disparities in pain and its treatment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Research methodology2. African Americans more sensitive to pain than Hispanic and white Americans3. Specific regions of the brain linked to heightened pain sensitivity and chronic4. Stress, including experience of discrimination, could cause pain sensitivityVOICEOVER (in English): "A study published in Nature Human Behavior suggests that discrimination can change how different ethnic groups perceive and respond to pain. "The University of Miami says scientists gave pain stimuli to the participants' arm, then gauged their pain via MRI.""Researchers learned that when the same pain is applied by a heating device, African Americans reported more pain than Hispanic or non-Hispanic white American participants.""Scientists found that two areas of the brain  the ventral striatum and ventromedial prefrontal cortex  responded to pain more strongly in African Americans.""Those brain areas have been linked to chronic pain.""Since stressful experiences are correlated to chronic pain later in life, the researchers believe that stress from racial discrimination may cause increased pain sensitivity.""Yet data suggests that doctors tend to believe African Americans to be more pain tolerant, which might make them less inclined to alleviate black pain."SOURCES: Nature Human Behavior, University of Miamihttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41562-020-0819-8https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-02/uom-bsi020120.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 11:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/05/3958994/3958994_DA51E5CD24BC4253899F025597B6686C_200205_3958994_Experiencing_discrimination_could_increase_pain__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, ethic pain disparity, pain, racial discrimination, discrimination, minorities, African Americans, ethnic minorities, stress, chronic pain, brain, neurology, neurobiology, neuroscience]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958893</guid>
      <title>Study links red meat consumption to heart disease and early death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in the journal JAMA Internal Medicine has found that eating two servings of red meat or processed meat every week is linked to a 3 to 7 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease and premature death.The study included more than 29,000 participants who were asked about their dietary habits.One of the study's authors said that it's worth trying to cut down on red meat and processed meat such as pepperoni, bologna and deli meats.Scientists also found those who consumed two servings of poultry a week had a 4 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease. Though researchers noted that this might be related to the cooking method of the chicken which may have been fried or due to consumption of chicken skin rather than chicken meat itself.The study did not find any association between eating fish and cardiovascular disease or early death.The researchers recommended consuming fish, seafood and plant-based protein sources such as nuts, legumes, beans and peas as healthier alternatives.The study's findings are in stark contrast to a meta-analysis published just a few months ago which claimed that there was no need for people to reduce their intake of red meat or processed meat for good health.Nutritionists at NutriRECS said at the time that their analysis did not find "any certainty that eating red meat or processed meat causes cancer, diabetes or heart disease," CNN reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Red meat and processed meat is linked to a higher risk of heart disease and premature death2. Those who consumed chicken were also found to have a higher risk of heart disease3. The study didn't find any link between fish and heart disease or early death4. What researchers recommend us to eatVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study published in the journal J.A.M.A. Internal Medicine has found that eating two servings of red meat or processed meat every week is linked to a 3 to 7 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease and premature death.""The study included more than 29,000 participants who were asked about their dietary habits.""Scientists also found those who consumed two servings of poultry a week had a 4 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease.""Though researchers noted that this might be related to the cooking method of the chicken which may have been fried or due to consumption of chicken skin rather than chicken meat itself.""The study did not find any association between eating fish and cardiovascular disease or early death.""The researchers recommended consuming fish, seafood and plant-based protein sources such as nuts, legumes, beans and peas as healthier alternatives."SOURCES: Northwestern University, JAMA Internal Medicine, CNN  https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/02/200203114328.htmhttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/article-abstract/2759737https://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/03/health/red-meat-processed-meat-chicken-fish-health-risks-wellness/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/09/30/health/red-meat-low-quality-evidence-controversy-wellness/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/05/3958893/3958893_1E91EB20C9514745BA1E77AA92BB63DB_200205_3958893_Study_links_red_meat_consumption_to_heart_diseas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Red meat, processed meat, processed meat health, processed food, red meat study, processed meat study, red meat heart disease]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959525</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's effective response to novel coronavirus attributed to three major steps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan has drawn from lessons learned during the SARS epidemic to mount an effective and immediate response to the 2019 novel coronavirus outbreak, using three major steps. According to a report by Mirror Media, Taiwan's first response to the novel coronavirus came on December 31, when China reported 27 cases of a mysterious Wuhan pneumonia to the WHO.Direct flights from Wuhan became subject to onboard health screening, and passengers had to declare their health status.It wasn't until January 21 that the island nation reported its first confirmed case. A 55-year-old businesswoman who returned to Taiwan from Wuhan was brought directly to the hospital upon arrival.Taiwan's second step was made on January 15, when the country's Centers for Disease Control listed the Wuhan pneumonia as a Category 5 communicable disease.According to Focus Taiwan, this made it mandatory to report suspected cases within 24 hours. Quarantining those who exhibited symptoms also became compulsory.When a man in Kaohsiung neglected to report viral symptoms after returning from Wuhan, the government fined him NT$300,000, or about US$10,000.On January 16, Taiwan's CDC raised the travel alert for Wuhan, after a Taiwanese expert team sent to the city to observe the epidemic suspected the possibility of human-to-human transmission.As of February 6, Taiwan has 13 confirmed cases of the virus. According to a CDC press release, patients are being treated in isolation wards and are in a stable condition.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Taiwan conducting health screening on Wuhan flights2. First coronavirus case in Taiwan3. Early listing of virus as Category 5 communicable disease4. Suspected human to human transmission detected by Taiwan experts early onVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report by Mirror Media, Taiwan's first response to the novel coronavirus came on December 31, when China reported 27 cases of a mysterious Wuhan pneumonia to the WHO.""Direct flights from Wuhan became subject to onboard health screening, and passengers had to declare their health status.""It wasn't until January 21 that the island nation reported its first confirmed case. A 55-year-old businesswoman who returned to Taiwan from Wuhan was brought directly to the hospital upon arrival.""Taiwan's second step was made on January 15, when the country's Centers for Disease Control listed the Wuhan pneumonia as a Category 5 communicable disease.""According to Focus Taiwan, this made it mandatory to report suspected cases within 24 hours. Quarantining those who exhibited symptoms also became compulsory.""On January 16, Taiwan's CDC raised the travel alert for Wuhan, after a Taiwanese expert team sent to the city to observe the epidemic suspected the possibility of human-to-human transmission."SOURCES: Mirror Media, Taiwan News, Focus Taiwan, Taiwan Centers for Disease Controlhttps://www.mirrormedia.mg/story/20200204inv002https://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3871532https://focustaiwan.tw/society/202001150023https://focustaiwan.tw/society/202001250011https://www.cdc.gov.tw/En/Bulletin/Detail/wn02wbpI_2YrRLcxS_pZnA?typeid=158***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/06/3959525/3959525_F55B7050E2C54EAAA949F7CB848DA3FD_200206_3959525_Taiwan_s_effective_response_to_novel_coronavirus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Taiwan epidemic prevention, Taiwan outbreak, Taiwan outbreak response, epidemic prevention, epidemic, outbreak, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959512</guid>
      <title>Plane overshoots runway in Istanbul, leaving at least three dead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe crashed airplane, a Pegasus Airlines Boeing 737-800 on Flight 2193 from Izmir to Istanbul, arrived at the  Sabiha Gokcen[b] airport at 6:19 p.m. on Wednesday.The plane was carrying 177 passengers and six crew.According to International Flight Network, weather conditions were poor with heavy rains and a powerful tailwind that may have caused the plane to touch down too late.The Boeing overshot the runway and had trouble slowing down on the rain slicked surface.Flight data indicates that the Boeing's last recorded speed was dangerously fast at 117 km per hour.Speaking at a news conference, Istanbul Governor Ali Yerlikaya said the plane was dragged 50 meters before falling down a 30-meter slope, the New York Times reports.The jet broke into three pieces and social media footage apparently shows passengers fleeing the wreckage after the crash.The New York Times reports that three people were killed and 157 were hospitalized.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pegasus Airlines Boeing 737-800 on Flight 2193 and its route2. Poor weather conditions, rain and tailwind may have contributed to the crash3. Jet overshoots runway and falls into a ditch4. The Boeing breaks apart; 3 are reported dead and 157 hospitalizedVOICEOVER (in English): "The crashed airplane, a Pegasus Airlines Boeing 737-800 on Flight 2193 from Izmir to Istanbul, arrived at the  Sabiha Gokcen[c] airport at 6:19 p.m. on Wednesday.""The plane was carrying 177 passengers and six crew.""According to International Flight Network, weather conditions were poor with heavy rains and a powerful tailwind that may have caused the plane to touch down too late.""The Boeing overshot the runway and had trouble slowing down on the rain slicked surface." "Flight data indicates that the Boeing's last recorded speed was dangerously fast at 117 km per hour.""Speaking at a news conference, Istanbul Governor Ali Yerlikaya said the plane was dragged 50 meters before falling down a 30 meter-slope, the New York Times reports.""The jet broke into three pieces and social media footage apparently shows passengers fleeing the wreckage after the crash." "The New York Times reports that three people were killed and 157 were hospitalized."SOURCES: International Flight Network, Flight Radar 24, New York Times, Sky News, Aviation Follower (Youtube), BBC Newshttps://www.ifn.news/posts/pegasus-flight-pc2193-breaks-into-pieces-following-runway-overrun/https://www.flightradar24.com/blog/pegasus-airlines-flight-2193-overruns-runway-in-istanbul/https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/05/world/middleeast/istanbul-airplane-crash.htmlhttps://news.sky.com/story/plane-splits-in-two-after-skidding-off-istanbul-runway-11926970https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F2ptkRckm_0https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51384667***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/06/3959512/3959512_A9970880EE0B450F9D28BF0DFEA280E8_200206_3959512_Plane_overshoots_runway_in_Istanbul__leaving_at__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Plane crash, air crash, airplane crash, Boeing 737, Boeing 737-800, Boeing, Pegasus Airlines, Pegasus, Flight 2193, overshooting runway, PC2193, Instanbul, Turkey]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959506</guid>
      <title>Pluto's frozen heart gives rise to planetary nitrogen winds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a study in the Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets, Pluto's frozen heart of nitrogen ice may be the main driver of the dwarf planet's winds. Pluto's heart shaped Tombaugh Regio is a vast structure made of nitrogen ice and its left lobe Sputnik Planitia contains 1,000 km of ice sheet within its 5 km basin.During the day, a thin layer of the frozen nitrogen evaporates in relative heat; at night, the gas condenses and returns to icy form.The sequence pumps nitrogen wind through Pluto's atmosphere like rhythmic heartbeats.As nitrogen in Tombaugh Regio vaporizes in the north and freeze into ice in the south, the process triggers a westerly wind.Citing the study's authors, Phys.org says this behavior is unique in the entire solar system with perhaps the exception of Neptune's moon Triton.The study's other discovery is that Sputnik Planitia's high cliffs trap winds within the basin before releasing the strengthened currents to the west.The atmospheric movement is similar to certain wind patterns on Earth, such as the Kuroshio in Eastern Asia. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pluto's heart shaped Tombaugh Regio is a structure of frozen nitrogen2. Nitrogen vaporization and condensation causes atmospheric movement 3. Tombaugh Regio's vaporizing north and condensing south creates westerly winds4.  Sputnik Planitia has wind patterns similar to Earth's Kuroshio VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study in the Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets, Pluto's frozen heart of nitrogen ice may be the main driver of the dwarf planet's winds.""Pluto's heart shaped Tombaugh Regio is a vast structure made of nitrogen ice and its left lobe Sputnik Planitia contains 1,000 km of ice sheet within its 5 km basin.""During the day, a thin layer of the frozen nitrogen evaporates in relative heat; at night, the gas condenses and returns to icy form.""The sequence pumps nitrogen wind through Pluto's atmosphere like rhythmic heartbeats.""As nitrogen in Tombaugh Regio vaporizes in the north and freeze into ice in the south, the process triggers a westerly wind.""Citing the study's authors, Phys.org says this behavior is unique in the entire solar system with perhaps the exception of Neptune's moon Triton.""The study's other discovery is that Sputnik Planitia's high cliffs trap winds within the basin before releasing the strengthened currents to the west.""The atmospheric movement is similar to certain wind patterns on Earth, such as the Kuroshio in Eastern Asia."SOURCES: Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets, Phys.orghttps://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1029/2019JE006120https://phys.org/news/2020-02-pluto-icy-heart.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/06/3959506/3959506_F34DB8A4558F4FDFB93315A015A90A3A_200206_3959506_Pluto_s_frozen_heart_gives_rise_to_planetary_nit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Pluto, nitrogen, Tombaugh Regio, Sputnik Planitia, atmospheric circulation, dwarf planet, retro-rotation, American Geophysical Union, AGU, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959336</guid>
      <title>Fireflies threatened by artificial light: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA joint study by Tuft University and the International Union for the Conservation of Nature has found that fireflies are being threatened by habitat loss, light pollution and pesticide use.Researchers surveyed 49 firefly experts from around the world in order to get a better understanding of prominent threats faced by roughly 2,000 different firefly species.Habitat loss was believed to be the largest threat to fireflies worldwide as their habitats are shrinking due to loss of land. Artificial light pollution is the second largest threat to fireflies globally as it interferes with their natural light which is used for communication and mating purposes. The use of pesticides was regarded to be the third largest threat as it is harmful to insects that fireflies consume for survival.Study author Sara M. Lewis, told the Washington Post that this was the first time a comprehensive list of threats, based on expert opinions, has been written about fireflies from around the world.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Why fireflies may risk extinction2. Habitat loss is the largest threat to fireflies3. Artificial light pollution interferes with the nature light of the fireflies4. Pesticides are another threat as it is harmful to the insects that are consumed by fireflies VOICEOVER (in English): "A joint study by Tuft University and the International Union for the Conservation of Nature has found that fireflies are being threatened by habitat loss, light pollution and pesticide use.""Researchers surveyed 49 firefly experts from around the world in order to get a better understanding of prominent threats faced by roughly 2,000 different firefly species.""Habitat loss was believed to be the largest threat to fireflies worldwide as their habitats are shrinking due to loss of land.""Artificial light pollution is the second largest threat to fireflies globally as it interferes with their natural light which is used for communication and mating purposes.""The use of pesticides was regarded to be the third largest threat as it is harmful to insects that fireflies consume for survival."SOURCES: Tuft University, Bioscience, American Institute of Biological Sciences, The Washington Posthttps://now.tufts.edu/news-releases/lights-out-fireflies-face-extinction-threats-habitat-loss-light-pollution-pesticideshttps://academic.oup.com/bioscience/advance-article/doi/10.1093/biosci/biz157/5715071https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-02/aiob-ffg013020.phphttps://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2020/02/03/worlds-fireflies-threatened-by-habitat-loss-light-pollution-experts-warn/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 07:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/06/3959336/3959336_93C449E2C6D948D5B6669F37749F871A_200206_3959336_Fireflies_threatened_by_artificial_light__Study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Fireflies, fireflies bioluminescence, bioluminescence, fireflies light show, fireflies light, fireflies light vs artificial light, fireflies light pollution, how fireflies are threatened]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959187</guid>
      <title>Air Canada Boeing 767 lands safely following engine failure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOn Monday, Air Canda's Toronto-bound Flight 837 had to request an emergency landing almost immediately after taking off from the Barajas International Airport in Madrid.The Associated Press reports that the Boeing 767 had a ruptured tire and that one engine had failed.Citing a Spanish civil aviation official, AP reports that the landing gear did not fold up properly and a piece of it may have been ingested by the engine, causing damage.According to the Spanish edition of The Local, the Spanish air force scrambled an F-18 to escort the Boeing and help assess the damage.AP reports that the commercial jet circled over Madrid for nearly four hours to burn off fuel until it was light enough to attempt a landing.Shortly after 7:10 p.m., the Boeing 767 made a safe landing back in Barajas with no injuries to the 128 passengers and eight crew on board.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boeing 767's landing gear, the engine suffered failures during takeoff2. The engine reportedly ingested debris from the landing gear3. The airplane circled over Madrid for four hours to burn off excess fuel4. The jet made a safe landing with no injuriesVOICEOVER (in English): "On Monday, Air Canda's Toronto-bound Flight 837 had to request an emergency landing almost immediately after taking off from the Barajas International Airport in Madrid.""The Associated Press reports that the Boeing 767 had a ruptured tire and that one engine had failed.""Citing a Spanish civil aviation official, AP reports that the landing gear did not fold up properly and a piece of it may have been ingested by the engine, causing damage.""According to the Spanish edition of The Local, the Spanish air force scrambled an F-18 to escort the Boeing and help assess the damage.""AP reports that the commercial jet circled over Madrid for nearly four hours to burn off fuel until it was light enough to attempt a landing.""Shortly after 7:10 p.m., the Boeing 767 made a safe landing back in Barajas with no injuries to the 128 passengers and eight crew on board."SOURCES: Associated Press, Sky News, The Localhttps://apnews.com/bfd48d002544aac1663a88b32f55f0c7https://news.sky.com/story/air-canada-flight-returning-to-madrid-after-landing-gear-fell-into-engine-11925661https://www.thelocal.es/20200203/madrid-airport-prepares-for-emergency-landing-of-air-canada-flight***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 02:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/06/3959187/3959187_1E47D8AE4C7A425DB69CCF98C5BF005D_200206_3959187_Air_Canada_Boeing_767_lands_safely_following_eng_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, fAir Canada, AC837, Flight 837, Boeing 767, Boeing 767-300, landing gear, engine failure, emergency landing, safe landing, Barajas, Madrid, Spain, Toronto, Canada]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960044</guid>
      <title>Cruise ship passengers exposed to viruses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThousands of travelers are stranded on cruise ships after coronavirus cases were discovered on board.CNN reports that the World Dream cruise ship is quarantined at the port of Hong Kong, while the Diamond Princess is kept at bay in Yokohama by Japan.According to Live Science, the confined spaces of a cruise ship provide almost the ideal environment for viruses that rely on person-to-person contact to thrive.Coughing and sneezing, contaminated water and shared food onboard are all potential paths of infection.For instance, a trace amount of feces in the food or water can infect any passenger that dined in the buffet.Some pathogens can linger on surfaces that an infected person touched and transmit to the next victim.Not only that crews have limited time to sterilize the ship between cruises, but certain viruses including the norovirus can survive  bleaching even by a 10 percent solution.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. World Dream, Diamond Princess cruise ships quarantined by Hong Kong and Japan2. Cruise ships' confined spaces are conductive to viral disease transmission3. Norovirus often spread through ship buffets4. Sanitation efforts are often inadequate for killing resistant virusesVOICEOVER (in English): "Thousands of travelers are stranded on cruise ships after coronavirus cases were discovered on board.""CNN reports that the World Dream cruise ship is quarantined at the port of Hong Kong, while the Diamond Princess is kept at bay in Yokohama by Japan.""According to Live Science, the confined spaces of a cruise ship provide almost the ideal environment for viruses that rely on person-to-person contact to thrive.""Coughing and sneezing, contaminated water and shared food onboard are all potential paths of infection.""For instance, a trace amount of feces in the food or water can infect any passenger that dined in the buffet.""Some pathogens can linger on surfaces that an infected person touched and transmit to the next victim.""Not only that crews have limited time to sterilize the ship between cruises, but certain viruses including the norovirus can survive  bleaching even by a 10 percent solution."SOURCES: CNN, Live Sciencehttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/05/asia/wuhan-coronavirus-update-death-toll-spike-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/05/asia/coronavirus-cruise-quarantines-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.livescience.com/32852-are-cruise-ships-a-health-risk.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/07/3960044/3960044_539950F4197E476EA1BC8C13881DA2B6_200207_3960044_Cruise_ship_passengers_exposed_to_viruses_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media,Cruise ships, cruise liners, diamond princess, world dream, hygiene, public health, China news, Yokohma, Japan, Hong Kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960020</guid>
      <title>New coronavirus spreads despite Beijing's efforts at containment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOn Thursday, China's number of confirmed novel coronavirus infections grew to 28,000 cases or a 15 percent increase over the previous day.According to CNN, reported deaths have spiked, which increased the death toll to 600 fatalities.The contagion continues to spread rapidly despite population control and quarantine protocols Beijing imposed in central China.BBC reports that the new coronavirus has infected about 28,300 people worldwide, compared to SARS's 8,100 cases and MERS's 2,500 cases.Citing an epidemiologist, BBC reports that the Wuhan pneumonia appears to have lower mortality rates than the two other viruses.Al Jazeera reports that China has built hospitals at a frantic pace in Wuhan, including the Huoshenshan Hospital built over 10 days with 1,000 beds, which opened Monday.CNN reports that a second new hospital named Leishenshan opened on Thursday.The CNN reports that common symptoms include headache, malaise, coughing and muscle pains.Complications include fever over 39 degrees Celsius, troubled breathing and pneumonia, and sepsis that could result in death.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China's new coronavirus deaths and confirmed cases rising despite countermeasures2. New Coronavirus infections outstripped SARS, MERS3. Beijing responds by massive hospital construction projects4. Update on known common symptoms and potential complications VOICEOVER (in English): "On Thursday, China's number of confirmed novel coronavirus infections grew to 28,000 cases or a 15 percent increase over the previous day." "According to CNN, reported deaths have spiked, which increased the death toll to 600 fatalities.""The contagion continues to spread rapidly despite population control and quarantine protocols Beijing imposed in central China.""BBC reports that the new coronavirus has infected about 28,300 people worldwide, compared to SARS's 8,100 cases and MERS's 2,500 cases.""Citing an epidemiologist, BBC reports that the Wuhan pneumonia appears to have lower mortality rates than the two other viruses.""Al Jazeera reports that China has built hospitals at a frantic pace in Wuhan, including the Huoshenshan Hospital built over 10 days with 1,000 beds, which opened Monday.""CNN reports that a second new hospital named Leishenshan opened on Thursday.""The CNN reports that common symptoms include headache, malaise, coughing and muscle pains.""Complications include fever over 39 degrees Celsius, troubled breathing and pneumonia, and sepsis that could result in death."SOURCES: CNN, BBC, Al Jazeerahttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/05/asia/wuhan-coronavirus-update-death-toll-spike-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/specials/asia/wuhan-coronavirus-intl-hnkhttps://edition.cnn.com/asia/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-02-06-20-intl-hnk/h_e8b6fe2a9f295eb25b7ee10558232ed4 https://www.bbc.com/news/world-51235105https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2020/02/china-races-build-hospitals-coronavirus-outbreak-grows-200205033913557.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/07/3960020/3960020_7DCA22016D0742F198D7EDEED6D0AE5F_200207_3960020_New_coronavirus_spreads_despite_Beijing_s_effort_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, hospitals, hospital construction, huoshenshan hospital, leishenshan hospital, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959888</guid>
      <title>How the Wuhan virus is impacting airlines and car manufacturers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs the Wuhan virus continues to spread at an alarming rate, it is starting to impact cruise ships, airlines and other international companies.Two cruise ships traveling in Asia have been forced to quarantine thousands of passengers. According to Bloomberg, Japanese health workers said 61 passengers on one of the ships were found to test positive for the novel coronavirus.Air travel has been disrupted, with more than 73 airlines around the world either suspending or restricting flights to China, as reported by Business Insider.The coronavirus has already spread to 28 countries and regions outside of China. More than 31,000 people in China have been affected with the virus so far. The virus has caused 636 deaths in China, with two additional deaths from the virus in the Philippines and in Hong Kong.Symptoms of the coronavirus include severe coughing, fever and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cruise ships under quarantine2. Airlines are suspending or restricting flights to China3. Car manufacturing firms have been forced to shut down factories4. Aircraft manufacturers have also been forced to halt assembly lines and close plane making facilitiesVOICEOVER (in English): "Reuters reports that two cruise ships traveling in Asia have been forced to quarantine thousands of passengers. One of the ships is anchored off of Japan while the other is in Hong Kong.""According to Bloomberg, Japanese health workers said 61 passengers on one of the ships were found to test positive for the novel coronavirus.""Business Insider reports that air travel has been disrupted, with more than 73 airlines around the world either suspending or restricting flights to China.""This includes airlines such as Japan Airlines, Air Canada, Air France, Cathay Pacific and American Airlines.""Global car manufacturing firms have been forced to shut down factories for an extended amount of time in China following the outbreak of the coronavirus.""Car companies that have closed down their Chinese factories include Hyundai, Tesla, Ford and Nissan among others.""Bloomberg reports that Airbus SE is halting one of its assembly lines in China, while Boeing and French company Safran SA are both closing plane making facilities in China in order to minimize workers' exposure to the virus."SOURCES: Reuters, BBC News, Bloomberg, Associated Press, CNBC, CNN, Business Insider  https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health/china-virus-hits-cruise-ships-carmakers-airlines-and-airbus-idUSKBN1ZZ06Lhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health-airlines-factbox/factbox-airlines-suspend-china-flights-because-of-coronavirus-outbreak-idUSKBN1ZX1PIhttps://www.bbc.com/news/business-51383284https://www.bbc.com/news/business-51386575https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-05/china-virus-shuts-airbus-plant-hitting-narrow-body-jet-outputhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-06/doctor-who-issued-warning-dies-deaths-top-632-virus-updatehttps://apnews.com/905489d29a3d4f8788f17a40003548a0https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/06/coronavirus-latest-updates-china-hubei.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/05/asia/wuhan-coronavirus-update-death-toll-spike-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/airlines-canceling-changing-flights-to-china-amid-coronavirus-fears-2020-1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/07/3959888/3959888_B2DC94AE7E26478F91C8E7AD3C3D819C_200207_3959888_How_the_Wuhan_virus_is_impacting_airlines_and_ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China virus, china virus economic impact, wuhan virus, coronavirus, coronavirus outbreak, coronavirus economic effect, coronavirus china economic impact, coronavirus china economy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961235</guid>
      <title>British Airways set new speed record for transatlantic flights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA British Airways Boeing 747-400 set the record for the fastest ever subsonic flight across the Atlantic on Sunday. Flightradar24.com reports that BA112 flew consistently at Mach 0.86.  CNN reports that the overnight flight from New York coincided with Storm Ciara, which boosted the Boening's speed and allowed it to arrive at London in 4 hours and 56 minutes.FlightRadar 24 reports that the jet stream gave eastbound flights including BA112 a significant increase in airspeed and reduced their fuel consumption.Citing the online outlet, CNN reports the plane reached a top speed of nearly 825 miles per hour.CNN reports that the jet landed nearly two hours ahead of schedule at Heathrow airport at 4:43 am.The plane was faster by one minute than a Virgin Airways A350 that also took advantage of the jet stream.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. British Airways Boeing 747-400 set new speed record for subsonic transatlantic flight2. The New York to London flight took 4 hours and 56 seconds3. Storm Ciara increased the plane's speed and reduced fuel consumption4. BA112 beat two other Virgin Airways VOICEOVER (in English): "A British Airways Boeing 747-400 set the record for the fastest ever subsonic flight across the Atlantic on Sunday." "Flightradar24.com reports that BA112 flew consistently at Mach 0.86."  "CNN reports that the overnight flight from New York coincided with Storm Ciara, which boosted the Boening's speed and allowed it to arrive at London in 4 hours and 56 minutes.""FlightRadar24 reports that the jet stream gave eastbound flights including BA112 a significant increase in airspeed and reduced their fuel consumption.""Citing the online outlet, CNN reports the plane reached a top speed of nearly 825 miles per hour.""CNN reports that the jet landed nearly two hours ahead of schedule at Heathrow airport at 4:43 am.""The plane was faster by one minute than a Virgin Airways A350 that also took advantage of the jet stream."SOURCES: Flightradar24.com, CNN https://www.flightradar24.com/blog/british-airways-sets-new-transatlantic-speed-record/https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/british-airways-fast-flight-scli-intl-gbr/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/10/3961235/3961235_310D780F88E748B88BB8D444C1F0B15C_200210_3961235_British_Airways_set_new_speed_record_for_transat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media,British Airways, Boening, Boeing 747-400, transatlantic, speed record, subsonic, New York, London, BA 112, Flight 112, ciara, storm ciara]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961201</guid>
      <title>Twenty-nine dead in mass shooting in Thailand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Thai soldier went on a shooting rampage over the weekend, killing 29 people in the country's deadliest ever mass shooting.Sergeant Major 1st Class Jakrapanth Thomma[d][e][f] made his way to his commanding officer's house in Nakhon Ratchasima, Thailand on Saturday, February 8 at 3:00 p.m. local time, where he shot his commander and a woman believed to be a relative of the commander after a dispute, Reuters reports. An hour later, he went to the Surathampithak army base where he was stationed and killed an army guard before stealing assault weapons, at least one machine gun and roughly 800 rounds of ammunition.The gunman drove off in a stolen Humvee and stopped at a Buddhist temple as authorities chased him. He killed around nine people before driving away. A Thai police officer was also killed during the shooting spree.The shooter posted updates to Facebook during the shootings, with messages such as "No one can escape death," at 6:30 p.m.The Thai soldier also live-streamed part of his shooting rampage on Facebook, though the video has since been deleted. At least two victims died at the hospital during surgery, while others remain hospitalized, CNN reports, citing Narinrat Pitchayakamin, a Thai public health ministry official.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the shooting spree began2. The soldier shooting people at a Buddhist temple3. The soldier shooting people at a mall4. Authorities shoot and kill the soldierVOICEOVER (in English): "Reuters reports that Sergeant Major 1st Class Jakrapanth Thomma[g][h][i] made his way to his commanding officer's house in Nakhon Ratchasima, Thailand on Saturday, February 8 at 3:00 p.m. local time, where he shot his commander and a woman believed to be a relative of the commander after a dispute.""An hour later, he went to the Surathampithak army base where he was stationed and killed an army guard before stealing assault weapons, at least one machine gun and roughly 800 rounds of ammunition.""The gunman drove off in a stolen Humvee and stopped at a Buddhist temple as authorities chased him. He killed around nine people before driving away. A Thai police officer was also killed during the shooting spree.""Around 5:30 p.m., the soldier made his way to Terminal 21 shopping mall in Nakhon Ratchasima, where he began to open fire on frightened shoppers in the vicinity. At least 12 shoppers were shot dead, while dozens were injured.""Twenty minutes after the shooting, the police cordoned off two kilometers of the area around the mall.""A few hours later, Thai security forces stormed the mall and helped hundreds of shoppers escape.""The gunman escaped to the basement of the mall at 12:30 a.m., Sunday. Authorities continued to search for the soldier throughout the night. He was located in the basement in the morning at 9:05 a.m., when he was promptly shot dead by security forces."SOURCES: CBC News, CNN, Reuters, BBC News, Bangkok Post https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mass-shooting-in-thailand-soldier-goes-on-rampage-kills-multiple-people-today-2020-02-08-live-updates/https://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/08/asia/thai-soldier-shooting-dead-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-shooting-timeline/one-gunman-four-locations-29-dead-how-the-mass-shooting-in-thailand-unfolded-idUSKBN2030FQhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-shooting/soldier-kills-29-people-in-thailand-before-being-shot-idUSKBN2020TBhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-51431690https://www.bangkokpost.com/thailand/general/1853804/mass-shooter-killed-at-korat-mall-20-dead***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/10/3961201/3961201_6A25E4F60C0943DBB2325CD057A36F97_200210_3961201_Twenty_nine_dead_in_mass_shooting_in_Thailand_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation,Thailand shooting, thailand mass shooting, thai soldier, thai soldier attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961118</guid>
      <title>7-Eleven trials cashier-less store</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN7-Eleven has announced a trial of a cashier-less store in Irving, Texas starting this week. During the trial period, the store will only be open to 7-Eleven employees.Customers shopping at the store will need to download and sign up for an app then use it to check-in at the cashier-less store, according to a press release from the company.The convenience store will offer an array of products including beverages, food, groceries and also over-the-counter drugs.Once the customer has finished shopping, the app will be used to make payments and customers can view their receipt once they have exited the store.7-Eleven did not mention in its press release how long the trial is expected to last.The company had previously launched a Mobile Checkout feature which allowed customers to skip waiting in line and instead pay for products using their smartphones in selected stores.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cashier-less 7-Eleven store2. Customers will need to download an app to shop at the store3. Different products the store will offer4. The app will be used to make payments and view receiptsVOICEOVER (in English): "7-Eleven has announced a trial of a cashier-less store in Irving, Texas starting this week.""During the trial period, the store will only be open to 7-Eleven employees.""According to a press release from the company, customers shopping at the store will need to download and sign up for an app then use it to check-in at the cashier-less store.""The convenience store will offer an array of products including beverages, food, groceries and also over-the-counter drugs.""Once the customer has finished shopping, the app will be used to make payments and customers can view their receipt once they have exited the store."SOURCES: New Atlas, 7-11, Tech Crunch, 21 CBS DFWhttps://newatlas.com/good-thinking/7-eleven-trial-no-cashiers/https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/7-eleven-pilots-cashierless-store-concept-300999252.htmlhttps://techcrunch.com/2020/02/06/7-eleven-is-the-next-retailer-to-test-cashierless-stores/https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/02/05/7-eleven-tests-cashierless-store-texas/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 10:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/10/3961118/3961118_F2DFB22AE8C64A22B5144CF941C69EBD_200210_3961118_7_Eleven_trials_cashier_less_store_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 7-11, cashierless 7-11, cashierless 7-eleven, 7-11 USA, cashierless stores, convenient stores, cashierless convenient stores, cashierless checkout]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961087</guid>
      <title>NASA says a large asteroid will fly by Earth on Feb. 15</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA warned that asteroid 2002 PZ39 will approach Earth on Saturday.This asteroid is moving at a speed of nearly 55,000 km per hour relative to Earth and has a diameter of between 440 meters to 990 meters.According to NASA, should a rocky asteroid bigger than 25 meters but smaller than 1 km were to hit Earth, the meteorite would likely cause local damage to the impact area.A meteorite larger than one or two kilometers in size would be capable of worldwide effects.Business Insider reports that most asteroids occupy orbits between Jupiter and Mars, so they pose little danger to the Earth.The outlet adds that 2002 PZ39 is one of the rare exceptions.NASA considers this asteroid a near Earth object and estimates that it will miss earth by a margin of 15.2 lunar distances  or 5.8 million km  at 11:00 pm on February 15.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid 2002 PZ39's estimated velocity and size2. NASA's assessment of the damage meteor impacts could cause to Earth3. Most asteroids' orbits are between Jupiter and Mars, posing no threat to Earth4. Asteroid 2002 PZ39's expected trajectory on Feb. 15VOICEOVER (in English): "NASA warned that asteroid 2002 PZ39 will approach Earth on Saturday.""This asteroid is moving at a speed of nearly 55,000 km per hour relative to Earth and has a diameter of between 440 meters to 990 meters.""According to NASA, should a rocky asteroid bigger than 25 meters but smaller than 1 km were to hit Earth, the meteorite would likely cause local damage to the impact area.""A meteorite larger than one or two kilometers in size would be capable of worldwide effects.""Business Insider reports that most asteroids occupy orbits between Jupiter and Mars, so they pose little danger to the Earth.""The outlet adds that 2002 PZ39 is one of the rare exceptions.""NASA considers this asteroid a near Earth object and estimates that it will miss earth by a margin of 15.2 lunar distances  or 5.8 million km  at 11:00 pm on February 15."SOURCES: NASA, Center for Near Earth Object Studies, Business Insider Indiahttps://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/asteroids/overview/fastfacts.htmlhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/ca/https://www.businessinsider.in/slideshows/the-10-biggest-asteroids-that-pose-a-threat-to-earth-in-2020/only-a-few-meters-short-of-being-a-kilometre-wide-asteroid-163373-2002-pz39-will-be-third-biggest-asteroid-to-approach-earth-on-15-february-2020-one-day-after-the-worlds-valentines-celebrations-/slideshow/73054019.cms***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 09:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/10/3961087/3961087_45773D9F09A34B7A884D84D4FE7F3BB2_200210_3961087_NASA_says_a_large_asteroid_will_fly_by_Earth_on__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, asteroid, asteroids, meteor, meteors, near earth object, near miss, neo, impact, 2002 PZ39, NASA, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961649</guid>
      <title>U.S. charges four Chinese military operatives in Equifax 2017 hack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA federal grand jury charged four Chinese military officers on Tuesday for the massive hack of the credit rating giant Equifax that occurred in 2017. The four are alleged members of the People's Liberation Army's 54th Research Institute.Speaking at a press conference in Washington, U.S. Attorney General William Barr called the hack 'one of the largest data breaches in history.' Barr said the hackers stole personal information and trade secrets including data compilation and database designs.BBC reports that the hackers allegedly routed traffic through 32 servers in nearly 20 countries to conceal their location as they conducted the cyber attack, which occurred from May to June in 2017. The U.S. Department of Justice named three of the four suspects, but their whereabouts are unknown. The Washington Post quotes FBI Deputy Director David Bowdich as saying, "We can't take them into custody, try them in a court of law, and lock them up  not today, anyway."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Four Chinese military officers charged over 2017 Equifax hack 2. Hackers accessed personal information and trade secrets3. Hackers utilized servers around the world to conceal the attack's origin 4. Suspects are unlikely to be brought to trialVOICEOVER (in English): "A federal grand jury charged four Chinese military officers on Tuesday for the massive hack of the credit rating giant Equifax that occurred in 2017. The four are alleged members of the People's Liberation Army's 54th Research Institute.""Speaking at a press conference in Washington, U.S. Attorney General William Barr called the hack 'one of the largest data breaches in history.' Barr said the hackers stole personal information and trade secrets including data compilation and database designs.""BBC reports that the hackers allegedly routed traffic through 32 servers in nearly 20 countries to conceal their location as they conducted the cyber attack, which occurred from May to June in 2017.""The U.S. Department of Justice named three of the four suspects, but their whereabouts are unknown. The Washington Post quotes FBI Deputy Director David Bowdich as saying, 'We can't take them into custody, try them in a court of law, and lock them up  not today, anyway.'"SOURCES: BBC, Washington Posthttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51449778https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/justice-dept-charges-four-members-of-chinese-military-in-connection-with-2017-hack-at-equifax/2020/02/10/07a1f7be-4c13-11ea-bf44-f5043eb3918a_story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/11/3961649/3961649_C079628A618F448892F98A87DC0A29DA_200211_3961649_U_S__charges_four_Chinese_military_operatives_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Equifax, Equifax hack, Equifax breach, department of justice, fbi, people's liberation army, hackers, cyber warfare, cyber, trade secrets, 54th research institute, personal data, personal information]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961625</guid>
      <title>Arctic ice loss could lead to cold climate in Western Europe: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA NASA study says that human caused climate change is rapidly melting arctic ice and disrupting ocean currents, which could make Western Europe cooler.The new study was conducted over 12 years and published in Nature Communication.The Beaufort Gyre is a current that previously kept the Arctic waters cold and protected sea ice.However, the glut of cold fresh water is making the gyre spin stronger and faster, and the natural reversal of the spin's direction has not happened for over 10 years.Researchers say that if the westerly wind guiding the current should reverse its direction now, the cold water build up could be unleashed at all once.The cold tide may well slow down the Atlantic currents that bring warmth to Western Europe.Citing the researchers, NASA says in its news release that disruptions to the Gulf Stream would have a negative impact on ocean life and the communities that depend on them.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Human caused climate change is melting Arctic sea ice 2. Freshwater from the melt changes the Beaufort Gyre's behavior3. Build up of cold, fresh water from the gyre may disrupt Atlantic currents4. Influx of cold water harmful to ocean life and communities that depend on themVOICEOVER (in English): "A NASA study says that human caused climate change is rapidly melting arctic ice and disrupting ocean currents, which could make Western Europe cooler.""The new study was conducted over 12 years and published in Nature Communication.""The Beaufort Gyre is a current that previously kept the Arctic waters cold and protected sea ice.""However, the glut of cold fresh water is making the gyre spin stronger and faster, and the natural reversal of the spin's direction has not happened for over 10 years.""Researchers say that if the westerly wind guiding the current should reverse its direction now, the cold water build up could be unleashed at all once.""The cold tide may well slow down the Atlantic currents that bring warmth to Western Europe.""Citing the researchers, NASA says in its news release that disruptions to the Gulf Stream would have a negative impact on ocean life and the communities that depend on them."SOURCES: Nature Communications, NASAhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-020-14449-zhttps://climate.nasa.gov/news/2950/arctic-ice-melt-is-changing-ocean-currents/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/11/3961625/3961625_FA21692A414F460C8788B8C90E1C9295_200211_3961625_Arctic_ice_loss_could_lead_to_cold_climate_in_We_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Global warming, climate change, sea ice loss, ice melt, beaufort gyre, gulf stream, the arctic, arctic ocean, atlantic, ocean currents, Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation, AMOC]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961602</guid>
      <title>Somalia &amp; other east African countries threatened by locust plague</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.N. has warned that Somalia and the rest of east Africa may soon be facing a severe locust plague.A report by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations says that young locusts are threatening pastures and crops in Somalia. The insects are said to threaten more than 10 million people in the region.These young locusts are expected to mature and develop wings in the coming weeks. They are then expected to make their way to Ethiopia and Kenya.Somalia has become the first country in east Africa to declare an emergency over locust infestation, BBC News reports. Kenya and Ethiopia are already taking precautionary measures by using planes to spray pesticides to prevent a locust outbreak.The locust outbreak follows a period of unusually heavy rains and a powerful cyclone off the coast of Somalia at the end of 2019, the Associated Press reports, citing climate experts. According to the report, more rains are expected in the next few weeks. This means that the number of locusts could increase.Dominique Burgeon, the Food and Agriculture Organization's emergency and resilience director, explained another generation of the insect could now even be born in regular moisture conditions due to the high density of locusts.He said that without enough planes spraying to stop the locust swarms, the outbreak may even turn into a plague, which could take years to control.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Young locusts are threatening east Africa2. How Kenya and Ethiopia are taking precautionary measures3. The number of locusts could increase as more rains are expected4. Why a new generation of locusts could be born even in regular moisture conditionsVOICEOVER (in English): " A report by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations says that young locusts are threatening pastures and crops in Somalia.""The insects are said to threaten more than 10 million people in the region.""These young locusts are expected to mature and develop wings in the coming weeks. They are then expected to make their way to Ethiopia and Kenya.""Kenya and Ethiopia are already taking precautionary measures by using planes to spray pesticides to prevent a locust outbreak.""Citing climate experts, the Associated Press reports that the locust outbreak follows a period of unusually heavy rains and a powerful cyclone off the coast of Somalia at the end of 2019.""According to the report, more rains are expected in the next few weeks. This means that the number of locusts could increase.""Dominique Burgeon, the Food and Agriculture Organization's emergency and resilience director, explained another generation of the insect could now even be born in regular moisture conditions due to the high density of locusts."SOURCES: Associated, Press, Bloomberg, BBC News, Science Alert, Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations   https://apnews.com/3bdd3a1db7136d0e0e454f5f1f59c998https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-02/somalia-declares-locust-plague-emergency-appeals-for-fundinghttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-51348517https://www.sciencealert.com/africa-is-having-its-worst-locust-swarm-in-decades-and-the-destructive-potential-is-unprecedentedhttp://www.fao.org/3/ca7557en/ca7557en.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 09:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/11/3961602/3961602_CD69BAAEBA7E46ED8C42072144CCE025_200211_3961602_Somalia___other_east_African_countries_threatene_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Locust plague, locust plague somalia, locust plague africa, locust plague africa 2020, locust plague in east africa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962231</guid>
      <title>Russian spacecraft shadowing U.S. spy satellite: U.S. Space Force commander</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo mysterious Russian spacecraft have been shadowing a U.S. reconnaissance satellite since November, coming to as close to 100 miles at times, U.S. Space Force commander General John Raymond confirmed to Time in a report dated to Feb. 10.[b]Citing outside experts, Time reports that the U.S. KH-11 satellite is about the size of a bus. Its spying sensors are believed to be as powerful as the Hubble Space Telescope's.Citing General Raymond, Time reports that the Russians launched a Soyuz rocket in November with a payload that separated into the two stalking satellites. General Raymond says he believes the bigger satellite acted as a carrier for the small one.Satellite watcher Michael Thompson  who first broke the story in January  tweeted that the Russian orbit was cleverly designed. The orbit the pair of satellites holds allows the two to observe KH-11 from one side during daytime and the other at night.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two Russian spacecraft tail a U.S. KH-11 reconnaissance satellite2. KH-11's speculated capabilities3. Russian satellites were launched in one payload before separating4. The Russian craft orbit allows observation on either side of KH-11VOICEOVER (in English): "Two mysterious Russian spacecraft have been shadowing a U.S. reconnaissance satellite since November, coming to as close to 100 miles at times, U.S. Space Force commander General John Raymond confirmed to Time in a report dated to Feb. 10.[c]""Citing outside experts, Time reports that the U.S. KH-11 satellite is about the size of a bus and its spying sensors are believed to be as powerful as the Hubble Space Telescope's.""Citing General Raymond, Time reports that the Russians launched a Soyuz rocket in November with a payload that separated into the two stalking satellites. General Raymond says he believes the bigger satellite acted as a carrier for the small one.""Satellite watcher Michael Thompson  who first broke the story in January  tweeted that the Russian orbit was cleverly designed. The orbit the pair of satellites holds allows the two to observe KH-11 from one side during daytime and the other at night."SOURCES: Time, Michael Thompson (Twitter)https://time.com/5779315/russian-spacecraft-spy-satellite-space-force/?utm_source=twitter.com&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=social-share-article***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 13:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/12/3962231/3962231_7BE7E7C6705C4545B99481774E567A5C_200212_3962231_Russian_spacecraft_shadowing_U_S__spy_satellite__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media,KH-11, spy satellite, reconnaissance satellite, surveillance, soyuz, russian satellites, russian spacecraft, u.s. space force, u.s., russia, space, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962131</guid>
      <title>New MRI contrast agent could aid early stage cancer detection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers claim that a new MRI contrast agent could be a "game changer" for the early detection of metastasizing cancers, especially liver cancer. This study was published in Science Advances on Feb. 5.The paper focused on a form of eye cancer that can migrate to the liver during the early stages of metastasizing. Georgia State University's news release said that current tests often do not detect liver cancer before advanced stages.The research team applied the metal element gadolinium to the contrast agent's protein. This allowed the MRI to accurately detect overexpression of receptors called CXCR4 in cancerous organs, even during early stage metastasis.According to the paper, the contrast agent has been tested in mice, but the university says that the substance can identify multiple types of cancer cells and and the FDA is fast tracking human trials, which could begin in 18 months.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New MRI contrast agent may aid in early detection of metastasizing cancer 2. Current techniques does not reliably detect metastasizing cancer in early stages3. Contrast agent utilize metal element gadolinium to identify receptor overexpression4. Tests conducted with lab mice; human trials fast tracked and expected in 18 monthsVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers claim that a new MRI contrast agent could be a 'game changer' for the early detection of metastasizing cancers, especially liver cancer. This study was published in Science Advances on Feb. 5.""The paper focused on a form of eye cancer that can migrate to the liver during the early stages of metastasizing. Georgia State University's news release states that current tests often do not detect liver cancer before advanced stages.""The research team applies the metal element gadolinium to the contrast agent's protein. This allows the MRI to accurately detect overexpression of receptors called CXCR4 in cancerous organs, even during early stage metastasis.""According to the paper, the contrast agent has been tested in mice, but the university says that the substance can identify multiple types of cancer cells and the FDA is fast tracking human trials, which could begin in 18 months."SOURCES: Science Advances, Georgia State Universityhttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/6/eaav7504https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-02-method-early-stage-cancer.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 10:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/12/3962131/3962131_3D53F793E30845CF8318B34AC3140BF0_200212_3962131_New_MRI_contrast_agent_could_aid_early_stage_can_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, MRI, contrast agent, tracer agent, imaging agent, cancer detection, metastasis, metastasizing cancer, early stage metastasis liver cancer, eye cancer, metal element, gadolinium, receptors, health, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962076</guid>
      <title>Native American burial sites being blown up for Trump's border wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. government is blowing up Native American burial sites to build Trump's border wall.The Washington Post reports that construction crews have begun controlled blasting within Arizona's Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument, which is a UNESCO recognized natural reserve.According to the BBC, the project is being done to prepare for the construction of Trump's border wall system, which will see a 30-foot tall steel barrier run across 43 miles of national park land.The blasts are occurring on Monument Hill, on ground considered sacred to Native American tribes, which include the burial site for the Tohono O'odham Nation.It also includes an area that is believed to contain artifacts dating back 10,000 years.Democratic Congressman Raul D. Grijalva described the project as "sacrilegious" and says the Tohono O'odham Nation was not consulted by the government beforehand.Under the 2005 REAL ID act, the federal government has the right to waive laws that get in the way of national security. The Trump administration has since used this to waive dozens of laws, in order to construct the wall.Environmentalists are also concerned about the damage being done to the local underground aquifer, as well as to migrating wildlife in the region.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Controlled blasting within Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument2. Construction of border wall3. Blast site done on Native American burial grounds4. Environmental damage of blasts and wall constructionVOICEOVER (in English): "The Washington Post reports that construction crews have begun controlled blasting within Arizona's Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument, which is a UNESCO recognized natural reserve.""According to the BBC, the project is being done to prepare for the construction of Trump's border wall system, which will see a 30-foot tall steel barrier run across 43 miles of national park land.""The blasts are occurring on Monument Hill, on ground considered sacred to Native American tribes, which include the burial site for the Tohono O'odham Nation.""It also includes an area that is believed to contain artifacts dating back 10,000 years.""Environmentalists are also concerned about the damage being done to the local underground aquifer, as well as to migrating wildlife in the region."SOURCES: Washington Post, CBS, BBChttps://www.washingtonpost.com/immigration/2020/02/09/border-wall-native-american-burial-sites/https://www.cbsnews.com/news/organ-pipe-cactus-national-monument-blasts-arizona-national-monument-being-blown-up-for-border-wall-2020-02-07/https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51449739***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 09:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/12/3962076/3962076_6FAA0C97D40E4B0C812E059A1906DB92_200212_3962076_Native_American_burial_sites_being_blown_up_for__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Native American burial ground, Trump wall, Trump, Trump border wall, US border wall, Native Americans, Donald Trump, border wall construction, wall construction]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962036</guid>
      <title>UN: North Korea still developing nuclear, missile programs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea has continued development of its nuclear and missile programs, according to a confidential United Nations report seen by Reuters.The country conducted 13 missile tests last year and launched roughly 25 missiles. This included new short-range and submarine-launched ballistic missiles, according to the report. It mentioned that North Korea has continued to "develop infrastructure and capacity" to enhance its missile program.The U.N. report says that the country also exported tons of commodities such as coal using Chinese barges, even though North Korea has been banned from doing so since 2017. DPRK-flagged vessels would transfer over the commodities to local Chinese barges, a method known as ship-to-ship transfer, which would then deliver the goods to ports in Hangzhou Bay and the Yangtze River in China.In a statement, China called the accusations "baseless," and said that it is implementing U.N. sanctions against North Korea.According to the report, North Korea also continued to illegally import refined petroleum using the same method.The country has been allowed to import 500,000 barrels of refined petroleum under current sanctions, but the report found that North Korea exceeded the limit "many times over," between January 1 and October 31 of last year, reports Reuters. North Korea's allies, Russia and China, have both raised concerns saying that the U.N. sanctions are causing harm to civilians in North Korea, according to Reuters. The United States, France and Great Britain have all said that sanctions should not be lifted.North Korea has been sanctioned by the United Nations since 2006, Reuters reports. Members of the U.N. security council have imposed harsher sanctions against the country over the years to deprive the country of funding for its nuclear and ballistic missile programs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korea continues to develop its nuclear and missile programs amid U.N. sanctions2. North Korea conducting a missile test3. How North Korea was able to export commodities4. How the country was able to import refined petroleum VOICEOVER (in English): "North Korea has continued development of its nuclear and missile programs, according to a confidential United Nations report seen by Reuters.""According to the report, the country conducted 13 missile tests last year and launched roughly 25 missiles. This included new short-range and submarine-launched ballistic missiles.""It mentioned that North Korea has continued to 'develop infrastructure and capacity' to enhance its missile program.""The U.N. report says that the country also exported tons of commodities such as coal using Chinese barges, even though North Korea has been banned from doing so since 2017.""DPRK-flagged vessels would transfer over the commodities to local Chinese barges, a method known as ship-to-ship transfer, which would then deliver the goods to ports in Hangzhou Bay and the Yangtze River in China.""According to the report, North Korea also continued to illegally import refined petroleum using the same method.""Reuters reports that the country has been allowed to import 500,000 barrels of refined petroleum under current sanctions, but the report found that North Korea exceeded the limit 'many times over,' between January 1 and October 31 of last year."SOURCES: Reuters https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-sanctions-un-exclusive-idUSKBN20426J***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 08:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/12/3962036/3962036_8FD6454D864F4A238B0732AF35FE6A06_200212_3962036_UN__North_Korea_still_developing_nuclear__missil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, North korea, north korea sanctions, north korea breach sanctions, north korea UN report, north korea nuclear missile program, north korea missile test, north korea enhanced nuclear program]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962832</guid>
      <title>Crew on quarantined cruise ship at greater risk of infection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs quarantine on the Diamond Princess cruise ship continues, crews may be facing a greater risk of coronavirus infection.The New York Times reports that at least 219 people aboard the Diamond Princess cruise ship currently docked in Yokohama port have been infected with the novel coronavirus, or COVID-19.Those who tested positive for the virus have disembarked and been sent to local hospitals.CNN reports that passengers and crew have been quarantined on the ship since February 4.Passengers are asked to wear masks and stay in their cabins. Meals are delivered to their rooms. They are also permitted to walk the decks for a few minutes each day, but must keep a distance of at least six feet from other passengers.The ship's crew, meanwhile, continue to live and work in close proximity to each other and the passengers, which can mean potential contact with those who are infected.Harvard University professor of immunology Eric Rubin told CNN that keeping everyone on the ship poses a greater infection risk for the crew. Ten crew members who recently tested positive for the virus stayed in shared cabins and ate meals in the mess hall alongside other employees.According to the New York Times, it isn't clear how many people on the ship have the virus, because Japanese officials have only tested 439 of the 3,700 passengers for infection, reasoning that there is a shortage of testing supplies. The current quarantine period is scheduled to end on February 19, unless there are any "unforeseen developments."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People infected with coronavirus on Diamond Princess cruise ship2. How passengers are quarantine on cruise ship3. Crew continue working on ship4. Crew at greater risk of coronavirus infectionVOICEOVER (in English): "The New York Times reports that at least 219 people aboard the Diamond Princess cruise ship currently docked in Yokohama port have been infected with the novel coronavirus, or COVID-19.""Those who tested positive for the virus have disembarked and been sent to local hospitals.""CNN reports that passengers and crew have been quarantined on the ship since February 4.""Passengers are asked to wear masks and stay in their cabins. Meals are delivered to their rooms. They are also permitted to walk the decks for a few minutes each day, but must keep a distance of at least six feet from other passengers.""The ship's crew, meanwhile, continue to live and work in close proximity to each other and the passengers, which can mean potential contact with those who are infected.""Harvard University professor of immunology Eric Rubin told CNN that keeping everyone on the ship poses a greater infection risk for the crew.""Ten crew members who recently tested positive for the virus stayed in shared cabins and ate meals in the mess hall alongside other employees."SOURCES: CNN, New York Timeshttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/12/asia/princess-diamond-cruise-crew-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/10/business/coronavirus-japan-cruise-ship.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 16:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/14/3962832/3962832_66892C1F05F24B1BA81F8C9188DAB7AF_200214_3962832_Crew_on_quarantined_cruise_ship_at_greater_risk__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Diamond Princess crew, cruise ship crew, Diamond Princess, Diamond Princess quarantine, cruise ship quarantine, ship quarantine, quarantine, COVID-19, Diamond Princess cruise, Diamond Princess ship]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962639</guid>
      <title>NASA's next Mars rover will sport laser to vaporize rocks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Mars 2020 rover will sport a rock-vaporizing laser gun. According to NASA, the mast-mounted laser has a range of 7 meters and will be used for studying minerals and help looking for microbe fossils.The rover mast features the SuperCam, a next gen version of Curiosity's ChemCam. The Supercam is a cereal box-sized device that combines a camera, a laser and spectrometers into a single instrument.The rover could use the SuperCam infrared laser to superheat out-of-reach rocks. The rover would then deploy a camera to analyze the plasma and determine its chemical makeup without taking a physical sample.SuperCam also includes a green laser and a 100-nanosecond shutter optic that can identify chemical compounds on surfaces around the rover. Together, these features will help the rover to find sulfates and carbonates that would indicate the presence of liquid water on Mars.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA's Mars 2020 rover will be equipped with a laser2. Laser is a part of the miniaturized devices included in rover SuperCam3. Rover's laser vaporizes rocks into plasma for chemical analysis4. SuperCam's lasers and sensors will help find evidence of water on MarsVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Mars 2020 rover will sport a rock-vaporizing laser gun. According to NASA, the mast-mounted laser has a range of 7 meters and will be used for studying minerals and help looking for microbe fossils.""The rover mast features the SuperCam, a next gen version of Curiosity's ChemCam. The Supercam is a cereal box-sized device that combines a camera, a laser and spectrometers into a single instrument.""The rover could use the SuperCam infrared laser to superheat out-of-reach rocks. The rover would then deploy a camera to analyze the plasma and determine its chemical makeup without taking a physical sample.""SuperCam also includes a green laser and a 100-nanosecond shutter optic that can identify chemical compounds on surfaces around the rover. Together, these features will help the rover to find sulfates and carbonates that would indicate the presence of liquid water on Mars."SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7591***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 10:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/13/3962639/3962639_37CC52D8FED741C6A6A9CE1E194F7320_200213_3962639_NASA_s_next_Mars_rover_will_sport_laser_to_vapor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA, mars 2020 rover, mars rover, new mars rover, laser, lasers, minerals, fossils, microbes, microbial life, water, sulfates, sulfur, carbon, carbonates, SuperCam, mars, space exploration, science, technology, Next Animation, Next Media]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962602</guid>
      <title>New cases show novel coronavirus could spread via sewage pipes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Hong Kong woman fell victim to the new coronavirus after a man residing 10 floors directly above her unit became sick. The South Morning China Post reports on Tuesday that the new cases suggest building pipes could be a path for the virus.Citing the WHO, Live Science reports that the coronavirus which causes SARS could get into feces and infect people through leaky pipes because compromised sewage pipes could allow pathogens to move into the surrounding air.Toilets have a u-shaped drain to trap fluids and odor. However, the Washington Post reported in 2003 that faulty plumbing can cause backwash from toilets, which led to a SARS outbreak at another residential tower in Hong Kong.Citing an infectious disease expert, Live Science explains that the new virus, now named COVID-19, could in fact transmit via feces, although aerosols from coughing and sneezing are still believed to be the main infection mechanism.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two Hong Kong residents living on different floors of apartment building were infected 2. Sewage contamination is known to spread SARS, which is another coronavirus 3. Faulty plumbing could result in toilet backwash and infection4. Aerosols still believed to be novel coronavirus' primary infection mechanism VOICEOVER (in English): "A Hong Kong woman fell victim to the new coronavirus after a man residing 10 floors directly above her unit became sick. The South Morning China Post reports on Tuesday that the new cases suggest building pipes could be a path for the virus.""Citing the WHO, Live Science reports that the coronavirus which causes SARS could get into feces and infect people through leaky pipes because compromised sewage pipes could allow pathogens to move into the surrounding air.""Toilets have a u-shaped drain to trap fluids and odor. However, the Washington Post reported in 2003 that faulty plumbing can cause backwash from toilets, which led to a SARS outbreak at another residential tower in Hong Kong.""Citing an infectious disease expert, Live Science explains that the new virus, now named COVID-19, could in fact transmit via feces, although aerosols from coughing and sneezing are still believed to be the main infection mechanism."SOURCES: South Morning China Post, Live Science, World Health Organization, The Washington Posthttps://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/3049921/tsing-yi-residents-evacuated-hong-kong-healthhttps://www.livescience.com/coronavirus-spread-building-pipes.htmlhttps://www.who.int/mediacentre/news/releases/2003/pr70/en/https://www.washingtonpost.com/archive/politics/2003/04/18/in-hong-kong-apartment-tower-sars-virus-spread-through-plumbing/99bcd25f-de85-472a-b084-4f847e0dac9a/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/13/3962602/3962602_D767621CC60C4CF987A74921E8C6AC05_200213_3962602_New_cases_show_novel_coronavirus_could_spread_vi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, health, china, china news, hong kong,  hong kong news, transmission, water pipes, pipes, drainage, sewage, epidemiology, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962539</guid>
      <title>Global carbon emissions were flat last year: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report by the International Energy Agency has found that global carbon emissions flattened in 2019, following two years of increased emissions.The U.S. also decreased its carbon emissions by 2.9 percent last year.This is because advanced economies, such as Australia, Canada, Japan and South Korea, increased their use of renewable resources such as wind and solar power, according to the report. The report also found that a rise in nuclear power and a weaker demand for electricity resulted in lower carbon emissions.In comparison, usage of coal-fired plants in advanced economies last year had declined by nearly 15 percent.The report also found that carbon emissions rose sharply in southeast Asia due to an increased demand of coal. China and India were found to have moderate emissions growth in 2019 due to slower economic growth and an increase in usage of renewable energy.In a statement, Fatih Birol, the International Energy Agency executive director, said that the halt in carbon emission growth provides optimism that climate change can be tackled this decade.A separate report from the United Nations stated that global emissions would have to be reduced by 7.6 percent every year until 2030 to prevent temperatures from rising to dangerously high levels which would "increase the frequency and intensity" of climate change.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  Global carbon emissions were flat last year2. Why CO2 emissions were flat in 20193. Usage of coal-fired plants had decreased in advanced economies4. Why carbon emissions in southeast Asia rose sharplyVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report by the International Energy Agency has found that global carbon emissions flattened in 2019, following two years of increased emissions." "The U.S. also decreased its carbon emissions by 2.9 percent last year.""According to the report, this is because advanced economies, such as Australia, Canada, Japan and South Korea, increased their use of renewable resources such as wind and solar power.""The report also found that a rise in nuclear power and a weaker demand for electricity resulted in lower carbon emissions.""In comparison, usage of coal-fired plants in advanced economies last year had declined by nearly 15 percent.""The report also found that carbon emissions rose sharply in southeast Asia due to an increased demand of coal.""China and India were found to have moderate emissions growth in 2019 due to slower economic growth and an increase in usage of renewable energy."SOURCES: Technology Review, The Hill, International Energy Agency, Time, CNBC, UN Environment Program https://www.technologyreview.com/f/615182/global-carbon-dioxide-emissions-were-flat-last-year-even-as-the-economy-grew/https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/482601-us-energy-related-carbon-dioxide-emissions-lowered-in-2019-reporthttps://www.iea.org/articles/global-co2-emissions-in-2019https://www.iea.org/news/defying-expectations-of-a-rise-global-carbon-dioxide-emissions-flatlined-in-2019https://time.com/5782089/iea-emissions-energy-climate-change/https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/11/energy-related-co2-emissions-flatlined-last-year-iea-says.htmlhttps://www.unenvironment.org/news-and-stories/press-release/cut-global-emissions-76-percent-every-year-next-decade-meet-15degc***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 08:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/13/3962539/3962539_A240EA394D6A492B987BB5013CC7F639_200213_3962539_Global_carbon_emissions_were_flat_last_year__Rep_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Climate change, global warming, carbon emissions, global carbon emissions, US carbon emissions, International energy agency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962450</guid>
      <title>Study finds human coronaviruses can survive on surfaces for up to 9 days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew analysis shows that many human coronavirus strains can stay infectious on inanimate surfaces for up to 9 days.The 2019 novel coronavirus is a droplet-based infection that can be spread through direct person-to-person transmission or by touching contaminated surfaces. These include door knobs or handles, bedside tables and chairs, call buttons, and other objects around an infected patient.A report published in the Journal of Hospital Infection looked at 22 studies on different coronaviruses and found that human coronaviruses such as SARS and MERS can survive on glass, plastic, and metal surfaces for up to 9 days.According to Professor Gunter Kampf, from the Institute of Hygiene and Environmental Medicine at Germany's Greifswald University Hospital, low temperature and humidity can increase the viruses' lifespan.Fortunately, the research also found that disinfectants such as ethanol, hydrogen peroxide, or sodium hypochlorite can easily kill the viruses within just one minute.While the study focused on other types of coronaviruses like SARS and MERS, researchers predict the findings may also be applicable to the 2019-nCov.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How coronaviruses spread2. Human coronaviruses stay infectious on surfaces for 9 days3. How temperature and humidity affect coronavirus lifespan4. Disinfectants kill coronaviruses within one minuteVOICEOVER (in English): "The 2019 novel coronavirus is a droplet-based infection that can be spread through direct person-to-person transmission or by touching contaminated surfaces.""A report published in the Journal of Hospital Infection looked at 22 studies on different coronaviruses and found that human coronaviruses such as SARS and MERS can survive on glass, plastic, and metal surfaces for up to 9 days.""According to Professor Gunter Kampf, from the Institute of Hygiene and Environmental Medicine at Germany's Greifswald University Hospital, low temperature and humidity can increase the viruses' lifespan.""Fortunately, the research also found that disinfectants such as ethanol, hydrogen peroxide, or sodium hypochlorite can easily kill the viruses within just one minute."SOURCES: Journal of Hospital Infection, Forbeshttps://www.journalofhospitalinfection.com/article/S0195-6701(20)30046-3/fulltexthttps://www.forbes.com/sites/victoriaforster/2020/02/09/scientists-predict-coronavirus-may-live-for-up-to-nine-days-on-surfaces/#33dd794514e3***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/13/3962450/3962450_07897A17C8704CE4B1A975CC3B4E5629_200213_3962450_Study_finds_human_coronaviruses_can_survive_on_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Coronavirus, SARS, MERS, nCov, novel coronavirus, contaminated surfaces, disinfectants, coronavirus transmission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963270</guid>
      <title>Old mattresses used to grow plants, crops</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the University of Sheffield have found a way to use foam from abandoned mattresses to grow plants and vegetables for those living in the Zaatari refugee camp in Jordan.In a news release from the university, researcher Tony Ryan explained that the mattress foam supports the plant while water and nutrient solution are pumped into the foam to allow the plant to grow. This system is called hydroponic farming and involves plants that are supported artificially and do not use soil.According to Jordanian law, refugees aren't allowed to grow plants in the ground or build permanent structures while living in these camps.In order to allow large-scale farming, researchers built a plastic piping system and put it on a rack. The piping system has numerous openings in which recycling yogurt pots holding the mattress foam and plants are put inside. Nutrient solution is added and flows through to the plants, helping them to grow and produce crops.This gives the refugees the opportunity to grow fresh vegetables which can be used for cooking their own meals, according to the researchers. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mattress foam being used to grow plants 2. How hydroponic farming allows plants to grow3. How a plastic piping system is being used for large-scale farming4. Refugees can grow fresh vegetables in the camp which can be used to make mealsVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the University of Sheffield have found a way to use foam from abandoned mattresses to grow plants and vegetables for those living in the Zaatari refugee camp in Jordan.""In a news release from the university, researcher Tony Ryan explained that the mattress foam supports the plant while water and nutrient solution are pumped into the foam to allow the plant to grow. This system is called hydroponic farming and involves plants that are supported artificially and do not use soil.""In order to allow for large-scale farming, researchers built a plastic piping system and put it on a rack." "The piping system has numerous openings in which recycling yogurt pots holding the mattress foam and plants are put inside." "Nutrient solution is added and flows through to the plants, helping them to grow and produce crops.""According to the researchers, this gives the refugees the opportunity to grow fresh vegetables which can be used for cooking their own meals."SOURCES: BBC News, University of Sheffield https://www.bbc.com/news/av/science-environment-51466978/how-mattresses-could-solve-hungerhttps://youruniversity.group.shef.ac.uk/2019-2020/features/jordan/https://www.sheffield.ac.uk/research/features/sheffield-zaatari-and-back-feeding-world-foam***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 12:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/14/3963270/3963270_A9B1BA8F6CEE403A82C4480B1C919953_200214_3963270_Old_mattresses_used_to_grow_plants__crops_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Old mattresses, discarded mattresses, mattress foaming, mattress foam plants, growing plants with mattress foam, mattress foaming for planting, using old mattresses to grow plants, growing plants in refugee camp, Zaatari camp]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963153</guid>
      <title>Mars might have formed over longer time than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe early solar system was a chaotic place with many large-scale collisions. A new study in Science Advances argues that such collisions involving Mars could be why scientists are underestimating the red planet's age.According to the Southwest Research Institute, Martian meteorites' tungsten content are highly varied. Since tungsten migrates from a planet's mantle to its core during formation, scientists are led to believe that Mars formed rapidly in 2 to 4 million years.However, the institute's researchers say Mars is known to have experienced large collisions in its early formative history. According to their models, this would have scrambled Mars's mantle and created a heterogeneous, marbled structure.Subsequently, when later collisions on Mars sent meteorites to Earth, the debris would have contained an uneven quantity of tungsten. Using the new models, the paper's authors claim that Mars may have taken 20 million years to become fully formed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mars had large scale collisions during the solar system's early history2. Scientists previously relied on tungsten content to gauge Mars formation timescale3. Large collisions could have tungsten distribution in Mars' mantle4. Using new models and Martian meteorites, scientists estimate Mars to be much olderVOICEOVER (in English): "The early solar system was a chaotic place with many large-scale collisions. A new study in Science Advances argues that such collisions involving Mars could be why scientists are underestimating the red planet's age.""According to the Southwest Research Institute, Martian meteorites' tungsten content are highly varied. Since tungsten migrates from a planet's mantle to its core during formation, scientists are led to believe that Mars formed rapidly in 2 to 4 million years.""However, the institute's researchers say Mars is known to have experienced large collisions in its early formative history. According to their models, this would have scrambled Mars's mantle and created a heterogeneous, marbled structure.""Subsequently, when later collisions on Mars sent meteorites to Earth, the debris would have contained an uneven quantity of tungsten. Using the new models, the paper's authors claim that Mars may have taken 20 million years to become fully formed."SOURCES: Science Advances, Southwest Research Institutehttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/7/eaay2338https://phys.org/news/2020-02-hint-longer-timescale-mars-formation.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/14/3963153/3963153_0B77E50268934E6BA22DBABABFD5DA84_200214_3963153_Mars_might_have_formed_over_longer_time_than_pre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964238</guid>
      <title>Plasma from recovered patients may help treat COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese researchers say blood plasma from recovered patients may help other COVID-19 patients to survive.China National Biotec Group said it is taking plasma taken from recovered COVID-19 patients to treat those who are critically ill. The state-owned pharmaceutical made those remarks in a news release dated Feb. 13.The group claims a round of the treatment improved the patient's condition significantly after 12 to 24 hours, including reduced inflammation and improved blood oxygen levels, lymphocyte counts, and reduced viral load.Citing an unnamed expert, the group states that this plasma contains special antibodies which were used to treat COVID-19 in the critically ill.The group says the procedure was tested successfully in over 10 patients and asserts that it is the best available option for reducing mortality rates. China Daily reports the president of Wuhan's Jinyintan Hospital called for plasma donations on Feb. 13.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Blood plasma from recovered patients might be a treatment for COVID-192. Plasma treatment significantly improved conditions for the critically ill3. Special antibodies from the plasma have been clinically utilized 4. Clinical trial showed success for 10 patientsVOICEOVER (in English): "China National Biotec Group said it is taking plasma taken from recovered COVID-19 patients to treat those who are critically ill. The state-owned pharmaceutical made those remarks in a news release dated Feb. 13.""The group claims a round of the treatment improved the patient's condition significantly after 12 to 24 hours, including reduced inflammation and improved blood oxygen levels, lymphocyte counts, and reduced viral load.""Citing an unnamed expert, the group states that this plasma contains special antibodies which were used to treat COVID-19 in the critically ill.""The group says the procedure was tested successfully in over 10 patients and asserts that it is the best available option for reducing mortality rates. China Daily reports the president of Wuhan's Jinyintan Hospital called for plasma donations on Feb. 13."SOURCES: China National Biotech Group (WeChat), Bloomberg, China Dailyhttps://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?__biz=MzA5MzYyMjg3Nw==&mid=2650277425&idx=1&sn=ac0d81c6e70fd375e60ca22d7d24fa95&chksm=8857a103bf2028157e09556def05f0218c5471c1d971d344e470ea0f15e94dec50d109124aca&mpshare=1&scene=1&srcid=0214Gl4uglGbR818tq2NtkW1&sharer_sharetime=1581645361400&sharer_shareid=43bf103a1eed26107a95ebb1c7d24e37&exportkey=Aas2m1%2BUdUWarZ%2BD5Hy%2B3b4%3D&pass_ticket=D2NTBG8gJo6znvmq9j1%2BLWVAI2454ghMXv%2F6sgerpqwBc1gr3SLvRggxUoGks3YL#rdhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-14/china-seeks-plasma-from-recovered-patients-for-coronavirus-cure?sref=hBxgxhfNhttps://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202002/14/WS5e45f72aa3101282172777cb.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 10:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/17/3964238/3964238_BFD76E03C3E4480C9B9AE9A7FB6C558A_200217_3964238_Plasma_from_recovered_patients_may_help_treat_CO_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, COVID-19, novel coronavirus, wuhan virus, wuhan pneumonia, antibodies, blood plasma, outbreak, china national biotec group, wuhan, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964187</guid>
      <title>NASA to use lasers space communication</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has announced that it is building a new satellite dish as part of the Deep Space Network that would be able to communicate with far away robotic spacecrafts.The dish, named Deep Space Station-23, is expected to be completed in two and a half years.The satellite dish will be 34 meters wide and will use advanced technology, such as lasers, to transmit data to and from space. Deep Space Station-23 will operate as a radio antenna and will also be equipped with mirrors and include a special receiver for laser beams.NASA officials say this technology can be used for communicating with astronauts once they are sent to places like Mars.According to Suzanne Dodd, director of the Interplanetary Network, which manages the Deep Space Network, lasers will be able to transmit roughly 10 times more data than radio antennas from Mars to Earth.NASA currently has deep space networks in Goldstone, California; Madrid, Spain; and Canberra, Australia. This is to allow spacecraft to have continual contact with Earth while our planet rotates.As part of the Artemis program, NASA plans to launch three lunar missions by 2024 which will eventually pave way for astronauts to make their way to Mars and make human exploration of the red planet a reality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New satellite dish2. Dimensions of the new satellite dish3. How it would workVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has announced that it is building a new satellite dish as part of the Deep Space Network that would be able to communicate with far away robotic spacecrafts.""The dish, named Deep Space Station-23, is expected to be completed in two and a half years.""The satellite dish will be 34 meters wide and will use advanced technology, such as lasers, to transmit data to and from space.""Deep Space Station-23 will operate as a radio antenna and will also be equipped with mirrors and include a special receiver for laser beams.""NASA officials say this technology can be used for communicating with astronauts once they are sent to places like Mars.""According to Suzanne Dodd, director of the Interplanetary Network, which manages the Deep Space Network, lasers will be able to transmit roughly 10 times more data than radio antennas from Mars to Earth."SOURCES: NASA, Inverse https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7594&utm_source=iContact&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=nasajpl&utm_content=daily-20200211-1https://deepspace.jpl.nasa.gov/https://www.inverse.com/science/human-missions-to-mars-will-use-lasers-to-communicate-with-earth-nasa***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 08:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/17/3964187/3964187_1D657850366A4BE58683C99E8D71B312_200217_3964187_NASA_to_use_lasers_space_communication_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, space, space exploration, NASA mars mission, NASA deep space network, NASA robotic spacecraft, Artemis program, moon mission, artemis 2024, lunar mission, space, astronauts, moon, space mission, artemis mission nasa, artemis nasa, artemis 2,  Deep Space Station-23]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964135</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How the Nevada caucus works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAfter Iowa and New Hampshire comes the third nominating contest for the Democratic presidential contenders in Nevada, the "First of the West."The Nevada Independent reports that early voting for the Nevada caucus is from February 15 to 18 at over 80 sites.Voters must first check in with volunteers, whose party-purchased iPads are loaded with a PDF voter roll. After filling out a Google form and being given a voter pin, they rank their preferences on a scannable paper ballot, which is then dropped into a ballot boxDuring caucus day on February 22, voters sign in at their local precincts and must then separate into groups based on which candidate they support. Candidates who receive less than 15 percent of the vite are deemed "non-viable" and disqualified. Their supporters can either go to a different candidate or remain uncommitted.Instead of the Shadow Inc. app used in Iowa, Nevada will use a Google Forms-based caucus calculator on the iPads.According to ABC, this will calculate totals by combining caucus day and early voting data, although precinct chairs will still be required to fill out back-up paper reporting sheets. Should the state deem it necessary to conduct a recount, these sheets will serve as their paper trail.As required by the DNC, three sets of results will be reported on caucus day: raw votes from the first alignment, raw votes from the final alignment, and county delegate results.A Nevada Democratic Official told ABC that the reporting process will include a two-source verification, with data first reported through "a secure hotline to a trained operator." Either the calculator or the reporting sheet will serve as an additional source.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nevada early voting details2. Nevada early voting process3. Nevada caucus process4. Caucus mathVOICEOVER (in English): "The Nevada Independent reports that early voting for the Nevada caucus is from February 15 to 18 at over 80 sites.""Voters must first check in with volunteers, whose party-purchased iPads are loaded with a PDF voter roll. After filling out a Google form and being given a voter pin, they rank their preferences on a scannable paper ballot, which is then dropped into a ballot box""During caucus day on February 22, voters sign in at their local precincts and must then separate into groups based on which candidate they support.""Candidates who receive less than 15 percent of the vite are deemed 'non-viable' and disqualified. Their supporters can either go to a different candidate or remain uncommitted.""Instead of the Shadow Inc. app used in Iowa, Nevada will use a Google Forms-based caucus calculator on the iPads.""According to ABC, this will calculate totals by combining caucus day and early voting data, although precinct chairs will still be required to fill out back-up paper reporting sheets."SOURCES: ABC, Reuters, The Green Papershttps://abcnews.go.com/Politics/nevada-democrats-detail-reporting-tool-caucus-day-fiasco/story?id=68967246https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-nevada-tech/after-iowa-meltdown-nevada-democrats-will-use-scannable-early-voting-ballots-idUSKBN2062QBhttps://www.thegreenpapers.com/P20/NV-D***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 07:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/17/3964135/3964135_B7BD5782E6E842ABAC21876057FD974D_200217_3964135_Explainer__How_the_Nevada_caucus_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Nevada caucus, caucus explained, Nevada caucus explained, Nevada caucus 2020, caucus 2020, how the Nevada caucus works, Nevada caucus explainer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964039</guid>
      <title>USS Normandy seizes vessel with Iranian weapons in the Arabian Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. has seized yet another vessel containing Iranian-made weapons that was apparently bound for Houthi forces in Yemen.The USS Normandy was conducting maritime security operations when it stopped a stateless dhow in the Arabian Sea on Sunday, February 9, according to a statement from the U.S. Central Command.Sailors from the missile cruiser boarded the vessel in accordance with international law.They found and seized weapons onboard including 150 Dehlavieh anti-tank missiles, three surface-to-air missiles, thermal imaging weapon scopes, and components used for unmanned aerial and surface vessels.In a statement, the U.S. Central Command explained that these weapons were deemed to be of Iranian origin. These were seized as they were determined to be for Houthi fighters in Yemen, which would violate a UN Security Council Resolution. The resolution prohibits the sale, supply and or transfer of weapons to these fighters.The weapons are now in U.S. custody waiting for final disposition.The statement, which was released on Thursday, also noted that the seized weapons were "identical" to weapons seized by the USS Forrest Sherman in the Arabian Sea in November.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. USS Normandy stopping a dhow2. Officials boarding the dhow3. Weapons seized4. The weapons were determined to be for Houthi fighters in Yemen VOICEOVER (in English): "The USS Normandy was conducting maritime security operations when it stopped a stateless dhow in the Arabian Sea on Sunday, February 9, according to a statement from the U.S. Central Command.""Sailors from the missile cruiser boarded the vessel in accordance with international law.""They found and seized weapons onboard including 150 Dehlavieh anti-tank missiles, three surface-to-air missiles, thermal imaging weapon scopes, and components used for unmanned aerial and surface vessels.""In a statement, the U.S. Central Command explained that these weapons were deemed to be of Iranian origin.""These were seized as they were determined to be for Houthi fighters in Yemen, which would violate a UN Security Council Resolution." "The resolution prohibits the sale, supply and or transfer of weapons to these fighters."SOURCES: USNI News, U.S. Central Command, Stars and Stripes, Reuters https://news.usni.org/2020/02/13/video-uss-normandy-seizes-cache-of-iranian-made-weapons-in-arabian-seahttps://www.centcom.mil/MEDIA/PRESS-RELEASES/Press-Release-View/Article/2083824/us-navy-seizes-illegal-weapons-in-arabian-sea/https://www.stripes.com/news/middle-east/us-says-it-has-seized-large-cache-of-iranian-made-missiles-in-the-arabian-sea-1.618642https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran-missiles-military/u-s-warship-in-arabian-sea-seizes-suspected-iranian-weapons***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/17/3964039/3964039_27B5522D403348C99A5AB7AB41D4061F_200217_3964039_USS_Normandy_seizes_vessel_with_Iranian_weapons__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, USS Normandy, arabian sea, Iranian-made missiles, iranian dhow, USS Normandy seizes Iranian weapons at sea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964034</guid>
      <title>New Horizons flyby of Arrokoth reveals how planets are formed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew Horizons' flyby of the most distant object ever visited has revealed the secrets to how planets are formed.MIT Technology Review reports that there have been two theories for planet formation. The first more prominent theory, hierarchical accretion, is when smaller objects collide at high speeds until they form a larger structure.The second theory, called cloud collapse, is when concentrations of matter collapse or gently clump together at low speeds.NASA's New Horizons spacecraft ventured to Kuiper Belt in the outer reaches of our solar system, it conducted a flyby of an ancient planetesimal named Arrokoth.Three studies published in the journal Science analyzed the high-resolution photos of Arrokoth taken by New Horizons  and found no evidence of violent impact, indicating that there was instead a gentle accumulation of matter.Simulations based on the new data suggest that Arrokoth's two parts formed independently from the collapse of the same cloud, and eventually gently merged together.More data collected during the Arrokoth flyby has yet to be downloaded and analyzed  a task which scientists say may take another year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hierarchical accretion theory of planet formation2. Cloud collapse theory of planet formation3. New Horizons flyby of Arrokoth4. How Arrokoth is believed to have formedVOICEOVER (in English): "MIT Technology Review reports that there have been two theories for planet formation. The first more prominent theory, hierarchical accretion, is when smaller objects collide at high speeds until they form a larger structure.""The second theory, called cloud collapse, is when concentrations of matter collapse or gently clump together at low speeds.""NASA's New Horizons spacecraft ventured to Kuiper Belt in the outer reaches of our solar system, it conducted a flyby of an ancient planetesimal named Arrokoth.""Three studies published in the journal Science analyzed the high-resolution photos of Arrokoth taken by New Horizons  and found no evidence of violent impact, indicating that there was instead a gentle accumulation of matter.""Simulations based on the new data suggest that Arrokoth's two parts formed independently from the collapse of the same cloud, and eventually gently merged together."SOURCES: MIT Technology Review, BBChttps://www.technologyreview.com/s/615208/a-snowman-shaped-space-rock-is-teaching-us-how-planets-form/https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51295365***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/17/3964034/3964034_1A23C3069C114BEFB1A3C3043EF4D183_200217_3964034_New_Horizons_flyby_of_Arrokoth_reveals_how_plane_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, New Horizons, planet formation, hierarchical accretion, cloud collapse, planet formation theory, Arrokoth, planetesimal, Kuiper belt, space, space exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964720</guid>
      <title>New Airbus prototype explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAirbus unveiled a prototype for a new aircraft called MAVERICK at the Singapore Airshow on February 11.MAVERICK is an acronym for Model Aircraft for Validation and Experimentation of Robust Innovative Controls.The prototype is two meters long and 3.2 meters wide, according to a press release from the company. Airbus has yet to unveil the dimensions of a full-sized MAVERICK.The company states in the press release that MAVERICK will have a "blended wing body design," which would allow the aircraft to potentially burn up to 20 percent less fuel in comparison to traditional planes.The press release explained that MAVERICK will also have a shielded engine above its central body that will reduce aircraft noise significantly.Its design would also allow the plane to utilize different types of propulsion systems, though Airbus has yet to specify what these might be.Airbus explained the unique design will allow the aircraft to have a wide cabin layout, which would provide passengers with extra legroom and larger aisles.According to WIRED, the aircraft may accommodate fewer window seats than traditional airplanes due to its design, though this may lead to more creative seating arrangements than what are usually present in traditional planes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New MAVERICK aircraft2. Dimensions of the prototype aircraft3. Features of the aircraft4. What the interior of the plane will look likeVOICEOVER (in English): "Airbus has unveiled a prototype for a new aircraft called MAVERICK at the Singapore Airshow on February 11.""This is an acronym for Model Aircraft for Validation and Experimentation of Robust Innovative Controls.""According to a press release from the company, the prototype is two meters long and 3.2 meters wide.""Airbus has yet to unveil the dimensions of a full-sized MAVERICK.""The company states in the press release that MAVERICK will have a 'blended wing body design,' which would allow the aircraft to potentially burn up to 20 percent less fuel in comparison to traditional planes.""The press release explained that MAVERICK will also have a shielded engine above its central body that will reduce aircraft noise significantly.""Airbus explained the unique design will allow the aircraft to have a wide cabin layout, which would provide passengers with extra legroom and larger aisles."SOURCES: Popular Mechanics, Airbus, Wired, Clean Technica https://www.popularmechanics.com/flight/a30916392/maveric-airbus-concept/https://www.airbus.com/newsroom/stories/Imagine-travelling-in-this-blended-wing-body-aircraft.htmlhttps://www.airbus.com/newsroom/press-releases/en/2020/02/airbus-reveals-its-blended-wing-aircraft-demonstrator.htmlhttps://www.wired.com/story/airbus-maveric-blended-wing-jet/https://cleantechnica.com/2020/02/13/airbus-maveric-design-study-project-is-20-more-efficient-than-todays-airplanes/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 10:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/18/3964720/3964720_E1DE83CCC8774DAD92502D548ECFEC26_200218_3964720_New_Airbus_prototype_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Airbus, airbus prototype, airbus maverick, maverick, new airbus maverick, airbus next generation plane, airbus blended wing body, airbus maverick model, prototype flying wing, airbus flying wing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964442</guid>
      <title>New restrictions implemented in Hubei amid coronavirus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBeijing has now tightened restrictions across Hubei province amid the growing threat of the Wuhan virus.Residents of Hubei province have been ordered to stay at home and aren't allowed to leave unless there is an emergency, BBC News reports. The government will allow one person from each household to leave their house once every three days in order to purchase food and other essential products.Only one entrance will be kept open in residential buildings. The buildings will be guarded and only those residing in the building will be allowed to enter or leave.Pharmacies, hotels, grocery stores and medical services will be open while other businesses in Hubei province will remain closed.China has also banned the use of private cars on the streets of Hubei, though delivery vehicles carrying essential goods will be exempt from the ban.Separately, the New York Times reports, Beijing has now ordered everyone returning to the capital city to quarantine themselves for 14 days in an attempt to contain the novel coronavirus.According to CNN, the virus has already killed 1,775 people and has infected more than 71,000 people globally. 70,548 of these cases are in China. Outside of China, only five deaths have been reported: one in Hong Kong, Taiwan, Japan, the Philippines and France.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hubei residents are banned from leaving their homes unless there is an emergency2. Residential buildings will only have one entrance opened which will be guarded3. Most businesses will remain closed 4. Private cars, except delivery vehicles, are bannedVOICEOVER (in English): "BBC News reports that residents of Hubei province have been ordered to stay at home and aren't allowed to leave unless there is an emergency.""The government will allow one person from each household to leave their house once every three days in order to purchase food and other essential products.""Only one entrance will be kept open in residential buildings. The buildings will be guarded and only those residing in the building will be allowed to enter or leave.""Pharmacies, hotels, grocery stores and medical services will be open while other businesses in Hubei province will remain closed.""China has also banned the use of private cars on the streets of Hubei, though delivery vehicles carrying essential goods will be exempt from the ban."SOURCES: BBC News, New York Times, Reuters, CNN https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51523835https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/14/world/asia/beijing-quarantine-coronavirus-rules.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health/coronavirus-cases-rise-again-in-chinas-hubei-province-idUSKBN20B014https://edition.cnn.com/asia/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-02-17-20-intl-hnk/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 01:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/18/3964442/3964442_30B623D869944CDF99E91970284C9EFE_200218_3964442_New_restrictions_implemented_in_Hubei_amid_coron_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, china virus, china virus 2020, china news, china virus spreads, wuhan virus, china hubei, china hubei lockdown, china hubei restrictions, china tightens restrictions on hubei]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965278</guid>
      <title>January 2020 was the warmest in weather history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe past month was the hottest January in weather history, according to the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.Citing climate researchers, NBC reports that a jet stream trapping cold air over the Arctic might be responsible for the warm January." NOAA data shows that the US and Hawaii region, Russia, Europe, South America and Australia experienced abnormally hot weather in January. Meanwhile, sea ice has retreated in the Arctics and Antarctica.Citing the National Ice and Snow Data Center, NBC reports the jet stream over the Arctic is called the Arctic Oscillation. The jet stream is wavy during a negative phase of this. This allows cool air to go south, taking cold temperatures and rains with it.Citing the center's director Mark Serreze[a], NBC reports the AO is having a positive phase with a flat jetstream circle, which entraps the cold air over the Arctic region. Serrez says this weather phenomenon is possibly the cause of the high temperatures.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Arctic jet stream could be responsible for abnormal hot weather in January 20202. NOAA data on global temperature abnormalities in January 20203. Wavy jet stream in Arctic allow North Pole's cold airs to lower temperatures 4. Flat jet stream in the past two months trapped cold airs over the ArcticVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, the past month was the hottest January in weather history.""Citing climate researchers, NBC reports that a jet stream trapping cold air over the Arctic might be responsible for the warm January." "NOAA data shows that US and Hawaii region, Russia, Europe, South America and Australia experienced abnormally hot weather in January.""Meanwhile, sea ice has retreated in the Arctics and Antarctica.""Citing the National Ice and Snow Data Center, NBC reports the jet stream over the Arctic is called the Arctic Oscillation. "The jet stream is wavy during a negative phase of this. This allows cool air to go south, taking cold temperatures and rains with it.""Citing the center's director Mark Serreze[b], NBC reports the AO is having a positive phase with a flat jetstream circle, which entraps the cold air over the Arctic region. Serrez says this weather phenomenon is possibly the cause of the high temperatures."SOURCES: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), NBC News https://www.noaa.gov/news/january-2020-was-earth-s-hottest-january-on-recordhttps://www.nbcnews.com/science/environment/what-happened-winter-jet-stream-science-explains-unseasonable-warmth-u-n1136136***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 12:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/19/3965278/3965278_F1E6C6EA29D849AFB087778AEFA28FD6_200219_3965278_January_2020_was_the_warmest_in_weather_history_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, arctic, jet stream, flat jet stream, wavy jet stream, arctic oscillation, January 2020, hottest January, warm winter, National Ice and Snow Data Center, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965180</guid>
      <title>The Sun will someday destroy the asteroid belt before it dies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBillions of years from now, the Sun will exhaust its hydrogen fuel and enter what astronomers call the 'giant branch' phase. The Sun will grow bigger by hundreds of times, while its luminance and radiation output increase by thousands of times.Writing in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, researchers say this energy will heat up the asteroid belt and cause the asteroids to spin faster and faster until they are torn to pieces, which will happen in six billion years.Since most big asteroids are a loose collection of rocks called rubble piles, they are susceptible to this heat induced spinning, or the YORP effect. Most asteroids will be reduced until they become small homogeneous fragments.The scientists' model predicts that the Sun will collapse into a white dwarf and absorb the smashed asteroids, which pollutes the star and changes its spectra. This would explain why many white dwarfs' spectra suggest dead stars contain asteroid elements.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Sun will briefly become a giant star after it exhausts hydrogen fuel2. Radiation from the dying Sun creates the YORP effect and destroy the asteroid belt3. Most asteroids are rubble piles that are susceptible to YORP4. White dwarf stars' spectra hint that they ingested pulverized asteroid belts VOICEOVER (in English): "Billions of years from now, the Sun will exhaust its hydrogen fuel and enter what astronomers call the 'giant branch' phase. The Sun will grow bigger by hundreds of times, while its luminance and radiation output increase by thousands of times.""Writing in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, researchers say this energy will heat up the asteroid belt and cause the asteroids to spin faster and faster until they are torn to pieces, which will happen in six billion years.""Since most big asteroids are a loose collection of rocks called rubble piles, they are susceptible to this heat induced spinning, or the YORP effect. Most asteroids will be reduced until they become small homogeneous fragments.""The scientists' model predicts that the Sun will collapse into a white dwarf and absorb the smashed asteroids, which pollutes the star and changes its spectra. This would explain why many white dwarfs' spectra suggest the dead stars contain asteroid elements."SOURCES: Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, The University of Warwickhttps://academic.oup.com/mnras/article/492/2/2437/5682494https://warwick.ac.uk/newsandevents/pressreleases/supercharged_light_pulverises***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 09:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/19/3965180/3965180_660456417CAB4D6E81FFF114BCB13A13_200219_3965180_The_Sun_will_someday_destroy_the_asteroid_belt_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Sun, death, asteroid belt, yorp, yorp effect, giant branch, white dwarf, white dwarf star, rubble piles, montly notices of the royal astronomical society, university of warick, science, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965074</guid>
      <title>Iranian hackers target corporate VPN servers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report by cyber security firm ClearSky has found that hackers backed by the Iranian government have been exploiting bugs in corporate VPN servers.Over the past three years this campaign has targeted numerous companies around the world ranging from the IT sector to the oil and gas, aviation, government and security sectors. In some cases, the hackers were able to exploit vulnerabilities in a short period of time.The hackers developed and used infrastructure that would allow them to control and access their targets in the long-term, according to the report. They were able to use this technique to steal valuable information from targeted companies.Researchers said that this could also be used to spread malware such as ZeroCleare and Dustman. Both of these malware are designed to delete as much data from hacked devices as possible, according to ZDNet. ZDNet points out that the report 'dispels the notion' that Iranian cyber hackers aren't as sophisticated as hackers in Russia, China or North Korea.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hackers hacking into corporate VPN servers2. Numerous companies have been targeted3. How they targeted these servers4. How they could use this technique to spread malwareVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report by cyber security firm ClearSky has found that hackers backed by the Iranian government have been exploiting bugs in corporate VPN servers in a bid to infiltrate and plant backdoors onto devices.""Over the past three years the so-called Fox-Kitten campaign targeted numerous companies around the world ranging from the IT sector to the oil and gas, aviation, government and security sectors.""According to the report, the hackers developed and used infrastructure that would allow them to control and access their targets in the long-term.""They were able to use this technique to steal valuable information from targeted companies.""However, researchers said that this could also be used to spread malware such as ZeroCleare and Dustman.""According to ZDNet, both of these malware are designed to delete as much data from hacked devices as possible."SOURCES: Computing, ZDNet, Clear Skyhttps://www.computing.co.uk/news/4010898/iranian-hackers-vpn-backdoorshttps://www.zdnet.com/article/iranian-hackers-have-been-hacking-vpn-servers-to-plant-backdoors-in-companies-around-the-world/https://www.zdnet.com/article/iranian-hackers-deploy-new-zerocleare-data-wiping-malware/https://www.clearskysec.com/fox-kitten/https://www.clearskysec.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/ClearSky-Fox-Kitten-Campaign-v1.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/19/3965074/3965074_B32ACC5C4A16491DB41FB19B6FF5B5AE_200219_3965074_Iranian_hackers_target_corporate_VPN_servers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hackers, iranian hackers, VPN servers, VPN servers hacked, iran hacking VPN servers, iran hacking campaign, iranian APT groups]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965040</guid>
      <title>SpaceX launches another 60 Starlink satellites into orbit but fails to recover reusable rocket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpaceX successfully launched another batch of 60 Starlink satellites with a Falcon 9 rocket. Space.com reports that the mission lifted off at an airbase in Florida at 10:05 a.m. on Friday.According to SpaceX, Falcon 9 is a reusable first stage booster with nine Merlin 1D engines that put out more thrust than five Boeing 747s at full power. The payload of 60 small satellites rides atop the rocket into orbit.According to SpaceX, Starlinks are telecom satellites that feature ion thrusters for maneuvering into position and articulated solar arrays. Space.com reports the latest launch brought the Starlink constellation up to nearly 300 satellites.The launch marked the fourth time the company used a booster four times. This rocket's earlier missions include a satellite launch and two runs to replenish the International Space Station last year.However, the rocket apparently missed the drone ship Of Course I Still Love You and made a soft landing in the seas near the robotic vessel. Space.com reports that the company is hopeful that the rocket can still be retrieved, citing SpaceX.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The latest Falcon 9 launch2. Rocket engine and how it carries Starlink satellites3. Starlink satellite constellation4. The reusable rocket's previous missions5. Rocket missed the drone ship during landingVOICEOVER (in English): "SpaceX successfully launched another batch of 60 Starlink satellites with a Falcon 9 rocket. Space.com reports that the mission lifted off at an airbase in Florida at 10:05 a.m. on Friday.""According to SpaceX, Falcon 9 is a reusable first stage booster with nine Merlin 1D engines that put out more thrust than five Boeing 747s at full power. The payload of 60 small satellites rides atop the rocket into orbit.""According to SpaceX, Starlinks are telecom satellites that feature ion thrusters for maneuvering into position and articulated solar arrays. Space.com reports the latest launch brought the Starlink constellation up to nearly 300 satellites.""The launch marked the fourth time the company used a booster four times. This rocket's earlier missions include a satellite launch and two runs to replenish the International Space Station last year.""However, the rocket apparently missed the drone ship Of Course I Still Love You and made a soft landing in the seas near the robotic vessel. Space.com reports that the company is hopeful that the rocket can still be retrieved, citing SpaceX."SOURCES: SpaceX, Space.comhttps://www.spacex.com/falcon9https://www.spacex.com/sites/spacex/files/starlink_media_kit_jan2020.pdfhttps://www.space.com/spacex-starlink-4-launch-success-misses-rocket-landing.htmlhttps://www.space.com/spacex-dragon-predawn-launch-landing-success-crs17.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/19/3965040/3965040_55A59C24C9884442911F39E44481E058_200219_3965040_SpaceX_launches_another_60_Starlink_satellites_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, SpaceX, falcon 9, reusable rocket, falcon 9, rocket, first stage, dragon, starlink, satellite, satellites, constellation, megaconstellation, drone ship, elon musk, space, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965745</guid>
      <title>Swiss manufacturer to offer 3D printed chocolates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBarry Callebaut, a Swiss-based chocolate manufacturer, has announced that it will start producing 3D printed chocolate at scale in its new studio called Mona Lisa.The 3D printing studio will be able to create personalized chocolates for customers, according to a news release from the company. Clients can choose which design, shape and size they want for their chocolate.Once a design has been chosen, studio designers will then make a digital 3D prototype of the chocolate. The news release explained that the technology is capable of printing thousands of chocolate pieces at a time while retaining a "hand-made appearance."The service could be used for desserts, confectionery or pastries.The company says that the service will be available to chefs, hotels, coffee chains and restaurants in select European countries.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 3D printer with chocolate2. Using the printer to print the chocolate3. Many chocolate pieces can be printed at the same time4. What the chocolate could be used for VOICEOVER (in English): "Barry Callebaut, a Swiss-based chocolate manufacturer, has announced that it will start producing 3D printed chocolate at scale in its new studio called Mona Lisa.""According to a news release from the company, the 3D printing studio will be able to create personalized chocolates for customers.""Clients can choose which design, shape and size they want for their chocolate.""Once a design has been chosen, studio designers will then make a digital 3D prototype of the chocolate.""The news release explained that the technology is capable of printing thousands of chocolate pieces at a time while retaining a "hand-made appearance".'" "The service could be used for desserts, confectionery or pastries."SOURCES: Business Insider, Barry Callebaut, Confectionery News https://www.businessinsider.com/3d-printed-chocolate-coming-to-european-consumer-market-after-hype-2020-2https://www.barry-callebaut.com/en/group/media/news-stories/barry-callebaut-opens-worlds-first-3d-printing-studio-craft-unseenhttps://www.barry-callebaut.com/en/artisans/mona-lisa/3dstudiohttps://www.confectionerynews.com/Article/2020/02/18/Barry-Callebaut-opens-world-s-first-3D-printing-studio-to-craft-unseen-chocolate-experiences-VIDEO***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/20/3965745/3965745_7BA47560AEAC44E1844DAE12290D44E9_200220_3965745_Swiss_manufacturer_to_offer_3D_printed_chocolate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Chocolate, 3D-printed chocolate, Barry Callebaut, 3D printing, Swiss chocolatier, 3D printing food, printing chocolate]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965709</guid>
      <title>Coral reefs may lose almost all habitats by 2020: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study presented to the American Geophysicists Union says that climate warming and rising acidity will kill off nearly all coral reef habitats by 2100.Warming and rising acidity bleach coral reefs by making corals eject their symbiotic algae. Scientists expect 70 percent to 90 percent of coral reefs to disappear in the next 20 years. While some groups are trying to regrow bleached corals with transplants, the study's model shows that almost none of these projects will remain viable in 2100.The study shows that small portions of Baja California and the Red Sea will be some of the last viable sites for growing reefs in 2020, but these locations are too close to rivers to be ideal habitats.Researchers say climate warming and rising acidity are the main culprits for shrinking coral habitats because plastic pollution is so extensive that there are few places left for plastics to affect.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Warming and acidity rise to eliminate almost all coral reef habitat by 20202. Efforts to regrow reefs not expected to succeed due to habitat loss3. Remaining potential habitats are too close to rivers4. Plastic pollution a lesser threat to corals than climate change and acidityVOICEOVER (in English): "Warming and rising acidity bleach coral reefs by making corals eject their symbiotic algae. A new study presented to the American Geophysicists Union says that these processes will kill off nearly all coral reef habitats by 2100.""Scientists expect 70 percent to 90 percent of coral reefs to disappear in the next 20 years. While some groups are trying to regrow bleached corals with transplants, the study's model shows that almost none of these projects will remain viable in 2100.""The study shows that small portions of Baja California and the Red Sea will be some of the last viable sites for growing reefs in 2020, but these locations are too close to rivers to be ideal habits.""Researchers say climate warming and rising acidity are the main culprits for shrinking coral habitats because plastic pollution is so extensive that there are few places left for plastics to affect."SOURCES: American Geophysical Union https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-02/agu-wao021720.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/20/3965709/3965709_EDF7BB26BDE4441DA3F27181971D6915_200220_3965709_Coral_reefs_may_lose_almost_all_habitats_by_2020_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Coral, coral reefs, habitats, habitat, habitat loss, climate change, climate warming, climate, warming, acidity, ocean, coral bleaching, coral restoration, coral transplant, coral transplants, environment, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965693</guid>
      <title>MasterCard pushes for commuter biometrics at public transit systems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMarket Watch reports CCTV and gait analysis may come to US public transit to allow commuters to pay without using cards or passes, citing MasterCard officials working on biometric technologies with transport firms.Speaking to the outlet, MasterCard's cyber solutions president Ajay Bhalla said facial features and gait could be linked to databases for cardless payment. Those methods are less vulnerable to hacking than password authenticated accounts.MasterCard is also exploring other biometric solutions, such as using wrist bands to identify a commuter's unique heartbeat patterns, EEG, and veins on the surface of their skin to authenticate payments.Bhalla is cited as saying the way a person holds a phone, which ear they use and the manner their fingers touch buttons on their devices are all potentially useful methods for authentication.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mastercard proposes commuter biometrics at public transit2. Gait analysis and facial recognition less susceptible to hacking than passwords3. Heartbeat, EEG, vein recognition technology are being explored4. Manner of using devices are potential options for biometric identificationVOICEOVER (in English): "Market Watch reports CCTV and gait analysis may come to US public transit to allow commuters to pay without using cards or passes, citing MasterCard officials working on biometric technologies with transport firms.""Speaking to the outlet, MasterCard's cyber solutions president Ajay Bhalla said facial features and gait could be linked to databases for cardless payment. Those methods are less vulnerable to hacking than password authenticated accounts.""MasterCard is also exploring other biometric solutions, such as using wrist bands to identify a commuter's unique heartbeat patterns, EEG, and veins on the surface of their skin to authenticate payments.""Bhalla is cited as saying the way a person holds a phone, which ear they use and the manner their fingers touch buttons on their devices are all potentially useful methods for authentication."SOURCES: Market Watchhttps://www.marketwatch.com/story/mastercard-is-pioneering-new-payment-technology-that-identifies-commuters-by-the-way-they-walk-2020-02-14***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/20/3965693/3965693_C0F3E217E95B4C07896C02D09A2868DA_200220_3965693_MasterCard_pushes_for_commuter_biometrics_at_pub_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Mastercard, biometrics, public transit, bus, subway, payment, authentication, identification, commuters, commuter, gait, facial recognition, EEG, heartbeat, vein, science, technology, U.S., TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965461</guid>
      <title>Largest Chinese COVID-19 study suggests elderly, sick most at risk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese authorities have published a study of COVID-19 patients across China  the largest one done on the disease so far.According to data released by the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention, 80.9 percent of COVID-19 cases have been mild, with patients exhibiting only mild pneumonia or none at all.Thirteen point eight percent of infections were classified as severe, and 4.7 percent as critical, with the sick and elderly found to be most at risk.The study also pointed out the high risk the outbreak presented to medical workers, 1,716 of whom have been diagnosed with the disease.While men are more likely than women to get infected, children and teens under 19 are not as affected, making up just two percent of those who contracted COVID-19.Of the 44,672 confirmed cases used in the study, 1,023 had died as of February 11, which puts the crude death rate for the virus at 2.3 percent.Hubei province was found to have a much higher rate at 2.9 percent, compared to 0.4 percent for the rest of China.Patients with cardiovascular disease were found most likely to die of complications from the virus, followed by those suffering from diabetes, chronic respiratory disease, and hypertension.The report finds that the epidemic peaked in January, and that a 'downward trend' in the overall epidemic curve since February 11.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Majority of cases presented as mild, but elderly and sick most at risk2. High risk to medical workers3. COVID-19 fatality rate4. Existing illnesses that put patients at riskVOICEOVER (in English): "According to data released by the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention, 80.9 percent of COVID-19 cases have been mild, with patients exhibiting only mild pneumonia or none at all.""Thirteen point eight percent of infections were classified as severe, and 4.7 percent as critical, with the sick and elderly found to be most at risk.""The study also pointed out the high risk the outbreak presented to medical workers, 1,716 of whom have been diagnosed with the disease.""While men are more likely than women to get infected, children and teens under 19 are not as affected, making up just two percent of those who contracted COVID-19.""Of the 44,672 confirmed cases used in the study, 1,023 had died as of February 11, which puts the crude death rate for the virus at 2.3 percent.""Hubei province was found to have a much higher rate at 2.9 percent, compared to 0.4 percent for the rest of China.""Patients with cardiovascular disease were found most likely to die of complications from the virus, followed by those suffering from diabetes, chronic respiratory disease, and hypertension."SOURCES: Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention, BBC, The Telegraphhttp://weekly.chinacdc.cn/en/article/id/e53946e2-c6c4-41e9-9a9b-fea8db1a8f51https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51540981https://www.telegraph.co.uk/global-health/science-and-disease/coronavirus-new-data-china-tells-us-disease/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 02:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/20/3965461/3965461_F5A373C3A0224533A69448DC12AB64DB_200220_3965461_Largest_Chinese_COVID_19_study_suggests_elderly__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID 19, coronavirus, China CDC, China CDC study, patients at risk, COVID-19 fatality rate, Coronavirus statistics, COVID-19 statistics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966461</guid>
      <title>9 dead in far-right shooting in Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA gunman in Germany opened fire on two shisha bars in what police suspect is a racially-motivated attack.The BBC reports that around 10 p.m. Wednesday, a 43-year-old man began shooting inside the Midnight shisha bar in the city center of Hanau in Germany. He then fled by car to the Kesselstadt neighborhood about 2.5 kilometers away, and continued his attack at another shisha bar, called Arena Bar and Cafe. According to CNN, nine people were killed in the attacks, with both German and Turkish nationals being among the victims. Six others suffered injuries.The BBC reports that following the shootings, police carried out an hours-long manhunt that lasted through the night.According to the Guardian, special police force officers stormed the suspect's home at 5 a.m. local time and found the suspect dead along with another body. Police say the gunman, later identified as Tobias Rathjen. had shot his 72-year-old mother and then himself.The Bild newspaper reported that the suspect left a letter of confession, in which he expressed "extreme right wing views. He also put up a video explaining his motives, but it has since been taken down from social media sites.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman shooting inside Midnight shisha bar 2. Gunman shooting inside Arena Bar and Cafe 3. Number of casualties, police manhunt4. Gunman shooting mother and himselfVOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports that around 10 p.m. Wednesday, a 43-year-old man began shooting inside the Midnight shisha bar in the city center of Hanau in Germany.""He then fled by car to the Kesselstadt neighborhood about 2.5 kilometers away, and continued his attack at another shisha bar, called Arena Bar and Cafe.""According to CNN, nine people were killed in the attacks, with both German and Turkish nationals being among the victims. Six others suffered injuries.""The BBC reports that following the shootings, police carried out an hours-long manhunt that lasted through the night.""According to the Guardian, special police force officers stormed the suspect's home at 5 a.m. local time and found the suspect dead along with another body.""Police say the gunman, later identified as Tobias Rathjen. had shot his 72-year-old mother and then himself."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardian, CNNhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51567971https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/19/shooting-germany-hanau-dead-several-people-shisha-near-frankfurthttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/19/europe/hanau-germany-shootings-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/22/3966461/3966461_42A154AE16B94BF488A70B6BC5A1FFD9_200222_3966461_9_dead_in_far_right_shooting_in_Germany_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Germany shooting, Germany attack, Germany far right, Germany far right shooting, far right shooting, Germany terrorism]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966319</guid>
      <title>Google removes over 500 Chrome extensions containing malware</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoogle has removed hundreds of extensions for their internet browser Chrome after they were found to have malware.A joint investigation by cyber security firm Duo Security, and Jamila Kaya, an independent security researcher, has identified roughly 70 chrome extensions that contained malicious codes. The researchers notified Google after which the tech giant conducted its own analysis and found more than 500 chrome extensions that were infected with malware.According to the report, the chrome extensions would inject malicious advertisements while users are browsing a website or lead users to specific websites such as Macys, Dell, or BestBuy.In some cases, the extension would take users to a phishing page or a malware download site.Researchers said that if users weren't regularly checking their chrome extensions, the plugins were able to collect extensive data and generate revenue through the user's device.Google has since removed the malicious chrome extensions and deactivated them for users who had installed the extensions on their browser, according to ZDNet. The website reports that Google also marked these extensions as "malicious",  so users would know to not reactivate them and to get rid of them from their browser.Google did not mention how many people had been affected by the breach.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chrome extensions that had malicious codes2. How the extensions would spread malware3. These plugins had the ability to collect data and generate revenue 4. Google has since removed these extensionsVOICEOVER (in English): "A joint investigation by cyber security firm Duo Security, and Jamila Kaya, an independent security researcher, has identified roughly 70 chrome extensions that contained malicious codes." "The researchers notified Google after which the tech giant conducted its own analysis and found more than 500 chrome extensions that were infected with malware.""According to the report, the chrome extensions would inject malicious advertisements while users are browsing a website or lead users to specific websites such as Macys, Dell, or BestBuy.""In some cases, the extension would take users to a phishing page or a malware download site.""Researchers said that if users weren't regularly checking their chrome extensions, the plugins were able to collect extensive data and generate revenue through the user's device.""According to ZDNet, Google has since removed the malicious chrome extensions and deactivated them for users who had installed the extensions on their browser.""The website reports that Google also marked these extensions as "malicious",  so users would know to not reactivate them and to get rid of them from their browser."SOURCES: ZDNet, Duo Securityhttps://www.zdnet.com/article/google-removes-500-malicious-chrome-extensions-from-the-web-store/https://duo.com/labs/research/crxcavator-malvertising-2020***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 12:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/21/3966319/3966319_EF49C6D4E661408280D600B34483DCE0_200221_3966319_Google_removes_over_500_Chrome_extensions_contai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Google, google chrome extensions, google chrome extensions malicious, malware chrome extensions, malicious extensions online, Duo Security, google security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966251</guid>
      <title>Space time ripples may have clues to universe creation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists may have figured out why matter outnumbers antimatter in our universe.According to the researchers, had the two substances been created in equal amounts, they would have annihilated one another and the universe would not have existed.In a study published in Physical Review Letters, researchers say that after the big bang, the early universe must have gone through a phase that allowed neutrinos to create more matter than antimatter. This period would also have created the cosmic strings.Citing the authors, Live Science reports that cosmic strings are thin bands of energy that still thread through the universe and that the strings' formation in the early cosmos can be proven by the ripples in space time they created.Although the ripples are faint, the research team says that if their models are correct, future instruments such as NASA's future Laser Interferometer Space Antenna will be able to detect the ripples and confirm their theory.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. If matter did not outnumber antimatter, the universe would not exist2. A transition phase after big bang may explain why there is an abundance of matter3. Cosmic strings created during the phase should create ripples in space time4. Future space instruments may confirm the theory by observing the ripplesVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists may have figured out  why matter outnumbers antimatter in our universe. They say that had the two substances been created in equal amounts, they would have annihilated one another and the universe would not have existed.""In a study published in Physical Review Letters, researchers say that after the big bang, the early universe must have gone through a phase that allowed neutrinos to create more matter than antimatter. This period would also have created the cosmic strings.""Citing the authors, Live Science reports that cosmic strings are thin bands of energy that still thread through the universe and that the strings' formation in the early cosmos can be proven by the ripples in space time they created.""Although the ripples are faint, the research team says that if their models are correct, future instruments such as NASA's future Laser Interferometer Space Antenna will be able to detect the ripples and confirm their theory."SOURCES: Physical Review Letters, Live Sciencehttps://journals.aps.org/prl/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevLett.124.041804https://www.livescience.com/phase-transition-allowed-neutrinos-shuffle-matter.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 10:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/21/3966251/3966251_2B38EEE9253446DD8AF39305A7546A40_200221_3966251_Space_time_ripples_may_have_clues_to_universe_cr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media,Big bang, cosmic strings, cosmic string, space time, space time ripples, matter, antimatter, laser interference space antenna, LISA, NASA, universe, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967426</guid>
      <title>Scientists advance new theory of Earth's formation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists say the early Solar System's cosmic dust gave rise to primitive Earth over just five million years. If the Solar System's existence is compressed into 24 hours, then the proto-Earth's creation did not take more than a minute.According to the study published in Science Advances, the research team found that a type of meteorites known as CI chondrites are the closest iron isotope match to our planet and the bulk composition of the solar system itself.In a news release, the University of Copenhagen says that the Sun once possessed an accretion disk. After the young star cooled, the CI dust in the disk was allowed to settle on proto-Earth.The university says the process would not be not possible unless the earlier iron had already migrated into the proto-Earth's nascent core. That our planet's composition is similar to only one meteor type suggests it is not created from random collisions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Early Solar System's accretion disk creates proto-Earth in a five-million-years span2. Iron isotopic analysis shows CI chondrites are the best match to Earth's composition3. CI dust from the sun's former accretion disk probably settled on proto-Earth's mantle4. Randomly amalgamated Earth would not be similar only to CI chondrites VOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists say the early Solar System's cosmic dust gave rise to primitive Earth over just five million years. If the Solar System's existence is compressed into 24 hours, then the proto-Earth's creation did not take more than a minute.""According to the study published in Science Advances, the research team found that a type of meteorites known as CI chondrites are the closest iron isotope match to our planet and the bulk composition of the solar system itself.""In a news release, the University of Copenhagen says that the Sun once possessed an accretion disk. After the young star cooled, the CI dust in the disk was allowed to settle on proto-Earth.""The university says the process would not be not possible unless the earlier iron had already migrated into the proto-Earth's nascent core. That our planet's composition is similar to only one meteor type suggests it is not created from random collisions."SOURCES: Science Advances, University of Copenhagen https://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/7/eaay7604https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/02/200220130509.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/24/3967426/3967426_930757BB7F414DEE8EA886FE14F58C38_200224_3967426_Scientists_advance_new_theory_of_Earth_s_formati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Earth, proto-Earth, proto Earth, Earth formation, Earth's formation, iron isotope, iron isotopes, cosmic dust, CI chondrite, CI, meteorite, meteorites, accretion disk, Centre for Star and Planet Formation, StarPlan, University of Copenhagen, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967416</guid>
      <title>Increased methane emissions linked to fossil fuel usage: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published by the University of Rochester in Nature magazine has found that human activity has been contributing significantly to the rise of methane emissions via the use of fossil fuels.For this study, scientists collected ice cores from Greenland and melted them to measure the amount of carbon-14 isotopes that were trapped in the ice cores.Fossil methane does not contain carbon-14 as it has been trapped underground for millions of years and the isotope has decayed. Biological methane, which comes from living sources such as animals, contains carbon-14. This chemical signature allowed researchers to distinguish natural emissions from man-made emissions over a period of 200 years, from before the Industrial Revolution started in the early 18th century to the present day.Researchers found that almost all methane that was emitted to earth's atmosphere until 1870 was biological in nature.After 1870, researchers found a roughly 25 to 40 percent increase of human-produced methane emissions. This coincides with a sharp increase in the use of fossil fuels such as coal, oil and natural gas around the same period of time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rise of methane emissions due to human activity2. How researchers conducted their study3. Increased usage of fossil fuels coincided with rising emissions4. Why we should reduce fossil fuel usageVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study by the University of Rochester has found that human activity has been contributing significantly to the rise of methane emissions via the use of fossil fuels.""For this study, scientists collected ice cores from Greenland and melted them to measure the amount of carbon-14 isotopes that were trapped in the ice cores." "Fossil methane does not contain carbon-14 as it has been trapped underground for millions of years and the isotope has decayed. Biological methane, which comes from living sources such as animals, contains carbon-14.""This chemical signature allowed researchers to distinguish natural emissions from man-made emissions over a period of 200 years, from before the Industrial Revolution started in the early 18th century to the present day.""Researchers found that almost all methane that was emitted to earth's atmosphere until 1870 was biological in nature.""After 1870, researchers found a roughly 25 to 40 percent increase of human-produced methane emissions." "This coincides with a sharp increase in the use of fossil fuels such as coal, oil and natural gas around the same period of time.""Scientists linked the study to today's climate crisis and said that a reduction in fossil fuel use could lessen the threat of global warming."SOURCES: Technology Review, Nature Magazine, Science Daily via University of Rochester, Science Daily via Princeton University, The Verge https://www.technologyreview.com/f/615263/humans-are-producing-a-far-larger-share-of-methane-emissions-than-we-thought/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-1991-8.epdfhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/02/200219113746.htmhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2014/03/140327111724.htmhttps://www.theverge.com/2020/2/19/21143597/methane-greenhouse-gas-oil-underestimate-leaks***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/24/3967416/3967416_BE72423703C14A829BB7C188BFBE1C7F_200224_3967416_Increased_methane_emissions_linked_to_fossil_fue_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Methane emissions, human methane emissions, methane emissions natural gas, atmospheric methane, potent greenhouse gases, CH4 emissions, methane fossil fuel emissions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967400</guid>
      <title>North Korea mines cryptocurrency to circumvent sanctions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea is turning to cryptocurrency as a means to circumvent sanctions. In a published report, analysts at Record Future say the regime is investing in high end machines for mining Monero and the activity has increased tenfold since May 2019.Recorded Future, which has ties to the CIA, says North Korea heavily regulates internet access and allows only elite military officials to use the Web. This makes Pyongyang's cyber traffic easier to sample and analyze. North Korea also engages in cyber theft and espionage, including cryptocurrency theft, hacking enabled bank theft, and financial cybercrimes. Over the past four years, those activities generated $2 billion, a sum equal to 7 percent of North Korea's annual GDP.According to the report, North Korea has three main ways to connect to the Internet, which is via its normal allotted IP, China-based Unicom, or Russia's satellite company SatGate Holdings.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korea mines cryptocurrency to circumvent sanctions2. NK's footprint is trackable because only elite officers use the Internet 3. Pyongyang's cybercrimes generate $2 billion in revenue 4. NK make use of its own IP and telecoms companies in China and RussiaVOICEOVER (in English): "North Korea is turning to cryptocurrency as a means to circumvent sanctions. In a published report, analysts at Record Future say the regime is investing in high end machines for mining Monero and the activity has increased tenfold since May 2019.""Recorded Future, which has ties to the CIA, says North Korea heavily regulates internet access and allows only elite military officials to use the Web. This makes Pyongyang's cyber traffic easier to sample and analyze.""North Korea also engages in cyber theft and espionage, including cryptocurrency theft, hacking enabled bank theft, and financial cybercrimes. Over the past four years, those activities generated $2 billion, a sum equal to 7 percent of North Korea's annual GDP.""According to the report, North Korea has three main ways to connect to the Internet, which is via its normal allotted IP, China-based Unicom, or Russia's satellite company SatGate Holdings."SOURCES: Recorded Future, MIT Technology Reviewhttps://www.recordedfuture.com/north-korea-internet-tool/https://www.technologyreview.com/s/615262/north-koreas-ultra-secretive-ways-can-make-the-regime-easier-to-track-online/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/24/3967400/3967400_4DADE50DACEF41FE960F3AACC391B52F_200224_3967400_North_Korea_mines_cryptocurrency_to_circumvent_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Cybercrime, Internet, cryptocurrency, Monero, sanctions, cryptocurrency mining, hacking, hackers, Insikt Group, Insikt, Recorded Future, North Korea, China, Russia, U.S., TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967252</guid>
      <title>Large number of blue whales found in South Georgia waters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the British Antarctic Survey have found an increase of blue whales around the island of South Georgia near Antarctica.The whale population in South Georgia declined due to extensive hunting in the early 20th century, according to BBC News. The researchers embarked on several missions to the waters of South Georgia from January 1, 2018 to January 1, 2020 and spotted roughly 55 blue whales.Researchers used advanced acoustics to locate different whales and attached satellite tags to identify them. They also collected skin samples and flew drones over the whales to assess their body conditions.The report suggests that the whales may be returning to South Georgia waters for feeding purposes which is, in turn, impacting the reproductive rate of the whale population.According to British Antarctic Survey's website, South Georgia may have been an important place for many whale species in the past due to its influx of Antarctic krill and immense seasonal productivity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Increasing number of blue whales in South Georgia2. Why the whale population originally declined3. What researchers did on their mission to South Georgia4. Why the blue whales may be returning to South GeorgiaVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the British Antarctic Survey have found an increase of blue whales around the island of South Georgia near Antarctica.""According to BBC News, the whale population in South Georgia declined due to extensive hunting in the early 20th century.""The researchers embarked on several missions to the waters of South Georgia from January 1, 2018 to January 1, 2020 and spotted roughly 55 blue whales.""Researchers used advanced acoustics to locate different whales and attached satellite tags to identify them." "They also collected skin samples and flew drones over the whales to assess their body conditions.""The report suggests that the whales may be returning to South Georgia waters for feeding purposes which is, in turn, impacting the reproductive rate of the whale population."SOURCES: BBC News, British Antarctic Survey, Oceanographichttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51553381https://www.bas.ac.uk/project/south-georgia-right-whale-project/south-georgia-right-whale-project-whale-tracking/https://www.bas.ac.uk/project/south-georgia-right-whale-project/https://www.bas.ac.uk/blogpost/blue-whale-comeback-at-south-georgia/https://www.oceanographicmagazine.com/blue-whales-south-georgia/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 08:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/24/3967252/3967252_4523406991DA49E383A618C16A702AFA_200224_3967252_Large_number_of_blue_whales_found_in_South_Georg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, endangered blue whales, blue whales, blue whales south georgia, blue whale sighting, blue whale population, blue whale population]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967206</guid>
      <title>Two killed after Australia train derails</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Australian XPT train travelling from Sidney to Melbourne derailed on Thursday, February 20, resulting in the deaths of the train driver and co-driver. Citing Australian officials, the BBC reports that 153 passengers were on board at the time.Australia's ABC reports the rail firm found track faults in the days before the accident. Citing passengers, BBC reports the driver had announced that he would try make up for earlier delays. At 7:50 p.m., the train derailed near Wallan, a township about 45 km from Melbourne.Citing Victoria Police, ABC reports the impact killed the train driver, a 54-year-old Australian Capital Territory man, and the pilot, a 49 year old Castlemaine woman. The crash turned the engine and the first carriage on their sides.Footage and images of the aftermath show that the engine and four passenger carriages left the rails. ABC reports that 12 passengers were hospitalized, including 11 with minor injuries and one person who suffered upper torso wounds.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Sidney to Melbourne XPT carried 153 passengers2. Track faults reported prior to accident and train was running late3. Train derailed near Walla; driver, co-driver killed4. One passenger seriously injured and 11 sustained minor woundsVOICEOVER (in English): "An Australian XPT train travelling from Sidney to Melbourne derailed on Thursday, February 20, resulting in the deaths of the train driver and co-driver. Citing Australian officials, the BBC reports that 153 passengers were on board at the time.""Australia's ABC reports the rail firm found track faults in the days before the accident. Citing passengers, BBC reports the driver had announced that he would try make up for earlier delays. At 7:50 p.m., the train derailed near Wallan, a township about 45 km from Melbourne.""Citing Victoria Police, ABC reports the impact killed the train driver, a 54-year-old Australian Capital Territory man, and the pilot, a 49 year old Castlemaine woman. The crash turned the engine and the first carriage on their sides.""Footage and images of the aftermath show that the engine and four passenger carriages left the rails. ABC reports that 12 passengers were hospitalized, including 11 with minor injuries and one person who suffered upper torso wounds."SOURCES: BBC, New York Times, Australia Broadcast Companyhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-51573326https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/20/world/australia/train-crash-dead.htmlhttps://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-02-20/two-dead-in-train-derailment-melbourne-wallan/11986230***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/24/3967206/3967206_FD863AE943A7497A9BAF18D81A6FCFF6_200224_3967206_Two_killed_after_Australia_train_derails_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, train crash, train wreck, derails, derailment, express train, XPT, SIdney, Melbourne, Wallan, faulty track, faulty tracks, track faults, Australia, accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967914</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover fish parasites that do not breathe: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Henneguya salminicola is a species of parasitic blob that lives inside and feeds on the flesh of fish. The creature is the first multicellular animal discovered that does not breathe, according to a study in Proceedings of the Academy of Natural Sciences.The parasite has no mitochondrial DNA, which enables other animals to respirate. Citing the authors, Live Science reports the parasite possibly absorbs ATP energy molecules directly from infected hosts to acquire energy without using oxygen fuel.Science Live reports that H. salminicola is mostly innocuous, but related parasites have wiped out whole fisheries stocks.H. salminocla is a distant relative of the jellyfish and the microscopic parasites have evolved to lose nerves, muscles and tissue. This genetic simplicity allows the creature to reproduce quickly, an evolutionary advantage for parasites.Study co-author Dorothee Huchon is cited as saying the parasite's spores are the only part of H. salminocla that shows any complexity. The spores are able to swim with two tails, and their eye-shaped stingers can latch on to the host when needed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fish parasite Henneguya salminicola is the only multicellular animal that does not breathe2. The species lacks mitochondrial DNA that allows respiration and energy acquisition3. The parasite is related to jellyfish and is genetically simpler 4. Parasite's spores are the only sophisticated part of its biologyVOICEOVER (in English): "The Henneguya salminicola is a species of parasitic blob that lives inside and feeds on the flesh of fish. The creature is the first multicellular animal discovered that does not breathe, according to a study in Proceedings of the Academy of Natural Sciences.""The parasite has no mitochondrial DNA, which enables other animals to respirate. Citing the authors, Live Science reports the parasite possibly absorbs ATP energy molecules directly from infected hosts to acquire energy without using oxygen fuel.""H. salminocla is a distant relative of the jellyfish and the microscopic parasites have evolved to lose nerves, muscles and tissue. This genetic simplicity allows the creature to reproduce quickly, an evolutionary advantage for parasites.""Study co-author Dorothee Huchon is cited as saying the parasite's spores are the only part of H. salminocla that shows any complexity. The spores are able to swim with two tails, and their eye-shaped stingers can latch on to the host when needed."SOURCES: Proceedings of the Academy of Natural Sciences, Live Sciencehttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2020/02/18/1909907117https://www.livescience.com/first-non-breathing-animal.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 13:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/25/3967914/3967914_BC58121B2A094F288C8D99EB11FC228E_200225_3967914_Scientists_discover_fish_parasites_that_do_not_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, Henneguya salminicola, h salminicola, parasite, parasites, animal, aninals, breathe, respiration, mitochondrial genome, mitochondrial dna, dna, mitochondira, multicellular animal, multicellular animals, microorganism, multicell]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967858</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy announces first operational laser to arm destroyers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Navy has put its first laser-equipped destroyer to sea. In a news release dated Feb. 20, Sea Systems Command says the Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, or ODIN, is designed to help ships counter enemy surveillance drones.Citing the command, Military.com reports the ODIN was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer Dewey in November. An image published by the Drive shows that the laser dazzler appears to be mounted in a turret atop the deckhouse."ODIN's predecessor  the Laser Weapons System  is a 30 kilowatt laser that had been tested but never operationally fielded.Military.com reports that Iranian drones had shadowed the carrier George H.W. Bush in the Persian Gulf and the laser will stymy hostile drones' attempt to gather intelligence on U.S. warships.The outlet reports that ODIN is only one of the laser weapons planned by the service. Another weapon, a 60 to 150 kW laser which has a range of five nautical miles will likely be installed on another destroyer by 2021.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. Navy's ODIN anti-drone laser dazzler2. The first ODIN unit was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer USS Dewey3. Laser a countermeasure to surveillance drones utilized by adversaries including Iran4. U.S. Navy is developing multiple laser weapons for the fleetVOICEOVER (in English): The U.S. Navy has put its first laser-equipped destroyer to sea. In a news release dated Feb. 20, Sea Systems Command says the Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, or ODIN, is designed to help ships counter enemy surveillance drones.Citing the command, Military.com reports the ODIN was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer Dewey in November. An image published by the Drive shows that the laser dazzler appears to be mounted in a turret atop the deckhouse.ODIN's predecessor  the Laser Weapons System  is a 30 kilowatt laser that had been tested but never operationally fielded.Military.com reports that Iranian drones had shadowed the carrier George H.W. Bush in the Persian Gulf and the laser will stymy hostile drones' attempt to gather intelligence on U.S. warships.The outlet reports that ODIN is only one of the laser weapons planned by the service. Another weapon, a 60 to 150 kW laser which has a range of five nautical miles will likely be installed on another destroyer by 2021.SOURCES: Naval Sea Systems Command, Military.comhttps://www.navsea.navy.mil/Media/News/SavedNewsModule/Article/2089079/navy-leverages-workforce-delivers-c-isr-capability-rapidly-to-surface-fleet/https://www.military.com/daily-news/2020/02/21/navy-has-installed-first-drone-stopping-laser-destroyer.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 10:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/25/3967858/3967858_4BEEC33592CB497CAA82F8257EEAB696_200225_3967858_U_S__Navy_announces_first_operational_laser_to_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, ODIN, laser, lasers, directed energy weapon, directed energy weapons, anti-drone, drone, drones, UAV, UAVs, unmanned aerial vehicle, unmanned aerial vehicles, U.S. Navy, Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, defense, military, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967841</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy announces first operational laser to arm destroyers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Navy has put its first laser-equipped destroyer to sea. In a news release dated Feb. 20, Sea Systems Command says the Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, or ODIN, is designed to help ships counter enemy surveillance drones.Citing the command, Military.com reports the ODIN was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer Dewey in November. An image published by the Drive shows that the laser dazzler appears to be mounted in a turret atop the deckhouse."ODIN's predecessor  the Laser Weapons System  is a 30 kilowatt laser that had been tested but never operationally fielded.Military.com reports that Iranian drones had shadowed the carrier George H.W. Bush in the Persian Gulf and the laser will stymy hostile drones' attempt to gather intelligence on U.S. warships.The outlet reports that ODIN is only one of the laser weapons planned by the service. Another weapon, a 60 to 150 kW laser which has a range of five nautical miles will likely be installed on another destroyer by 2021.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. Navy's ODIN anti-drone laser dazzler2. The first ODIN unit was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer USS Dewey3. Laser a countermeasure to surveillance drones utilized by adversaries including Iran4. U.S. Navy is developing multiple laser weapons for the fleetVOICEOVER (in English): The U.S. Navy has put its first laser-equipped destroyer to sea. In a news release dated Feb. 20, Sea Systems Command says the Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, or ODIN, is designed to help ships counter enemy surveillance drones.Citing the command, Military.com reports the ODIN was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer Dewey in November. An image published by the Drive shows that the laser dazzler appears to be mounted in a turret atop the deckhouse.ODIN's predecessor  the Laser Weapons System  is a 30 kilowatt laser that had been tested but never operationally fielded.Military.com reports that Iranian drones had shadowed the carrier George H.W. Bush in the Persian Gulf and the laser will stymy hostile drones' attempt to gather intelligence on U.S. warships.The outlet reports that ODIN is only one of the laser weapons planned by the service. Another weapon, a 60 to 150 kW laser which has a range of five nautical miles will likely be installed on another destroyer by 2021.SOURCES: Naval Sea Systems Command, Military.comhttps://www.navsea.navy.mil/Media/News/SavedNewsModule/Article/2089079/navy-leverages-workforce-delivers-c-isr-capability-rapidly-to-surface-fleet/https://www.military.com/daily-news/2020/02/21/navy-has-installed-first-drone-stopping-laser-destroyer.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 10:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/25/3967841/3967841_08C6D8B567F44E25A84675C329914506_200225_3967841_U_S__Navy_announces_first_operational_laser_to_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, ODIN, laser, lasers, directed energy weapon, directed energy weapons, anti-drone, drone, drones, UAV, UAVs, unmanned aerial vehicle, unmanned aerial vehicles, U.S. Navy, Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, defense, military, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967763</guid>
      <title>Misleading recycling labels found on plastic products: Greenpeace</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report by Greenpeace published on February 18 has found that several companies in the U.S. are misleading consumers by adding incorrect recycling labels onto their plastic products.This includes companies such as Target, Walmart, Procter & Gamble and Nestl.After surveying 367 material recovery facilities across the U.S., Greenpeace identified only two types of plastics, PET #1 and HDPE#2, that can be processed in the U.S. These are the only types of plastic allowed to be labeled as recyclable.PET #1, or polyethylene terephthalate, includes plastic water bottles, soda bottles or peanut butter jars while HDPE#2, or High-Density polyethylene, refers to milk jars, shampoo bottles or laundry detergent containers.Researchers noted that many PET #1 and HDPE#2 plastic bottles or other containers consist of full body shrink sleeves which makes the products non-recycle too.The report found that plastics labeled PVC#3, LDPE#4, PP#5, PS#6 and others cannot be classified as recyclable as they have low acceptance by material recovery facilities and are typically sent to landfills or incinerators. These include plastics such as plastic cups, bags, plates and cutlery.Greenpeace has called for companies to eliminate single-use plastics and to invest in reusable, refillable packaging or go package-free instead.The organization has said that they will file a complaint with the Federal Trade Commission if the companies do not correct their labeling.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Greenpeace report finds that companies have misleading recycling labels on their plastic products2. The two types of plastics that can be classified as recyclable3. Which plastics should not be classified as recyclable4. Eliminating single use-plasticsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report by Greenpeace published on February 18 has found that several companies in the U.S. are misleading consumers by adding incorrect recycling labels onto their plastic products.""This includes companies such as Target, Walmart, Procter & Gamble and Nestl.""After surveying 367 material recovery facilities across the U.S., Greenpeace identified only two types of plastics, PET #1 and HDPE#2, that can be processed in the U.S. These are the only types of plastic allowed to be labeled as recyclable.""PET #1, or polyethylene terephthalate, includes plastic water bottles, soda bottles or peanut butter jars while HDPE#2, or High-Density polyethylene, refers to milk jars, shampoo bottles or laundry detergent containers.""Researchers noted that many PET #1 and HDPE#2 plastic bottles or other containers consist of full body shrink sleeves which makes the products non-recycle too.""The report found that plastics labeled PVC#3, LDPE#4, PP#5, PS#6 and others cannot be classified as recyclable as they have low acceptance by material recovery facilities and are typically sent to landfills or incinerators.""These include plastics such as plastic cups, bags, plates and cutlery.""Greenpeace has called for companies to eliminate single-use plastics and to invest in reusable, refillable packaging or go package-free instead."SOURCES: Greenpeace, EcoWatch https://www.greenpeace.org/usa/news/u-s-companies-use-misleading-recyclable-labels-on-hundreds-of-plastic-products/https://www.greenpeace.org/usa/research/report-circular-claims-fall-flat/https://www.greenpeace.org/usa/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Greenpeace-Report-Circular-Claims-Fall-Flat.pdfhttps://www.ecowatch.com/us-recycling-greenpeace-report-2645190415.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 08:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/25/3967763/3967763_789AE228D06B4A22AA2CD6AB5E94A096_200225_3967763_Misleading_recycling_labels_found_on_plastic_pro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, misleading recycling labels, Plastic products, recycling labels, misleading recycling labels on plastic products, plastic products mislabeled]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968389</guid>
      <title>Archeologists complete first ever LIDAR survey of ancient Mayan highway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArcheologists have used laser scanning to chart an ancient 100 km long Mayan highway built 13 centuries ago. They say Coba, a powerful city-state, may have built the road to invade its neighbor Yaxuna. The study was published in the Journal of Archeological Science.The University of Miami said in a news release that the study used light detection and ranging technology lasers to penetrate thick jungle vegetation and reveal the ruins beneath. The LIDAR survey mapped out the road and uncovered 8,000 structures on its path.University professor Traci Ardren is cited as saying the road did not run straight as supposed. Instead, Coba's warrior queen K'awiil Ajaw may have built the winding road to control settlements across the Yucatan Peninsula and to attack Yaxuna.Arden, who is a co-author, says the Mayan roads were an engineering marvel. Giant limestone boulders were utilized to fill uneven ground, then white plaster was applied to make the road surface. This substance is similar to Roman concrete and gave the road its name Sacbe, which comes from the Mayan word for "white way."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sacbe 1 may have been built by Coba to invade Yaxuna2. LIDAR survey penetrates vegetation to reveal ruins 3. Curving path of the road may have served Coba's geostrategic purposes4. Highway construction by ancient MayansVOICEOVER (in English): "Archeologists have used laser scanning to chart an ancient 100 km long Mayan highway built 13 centuries ago.""They say Coba, a powerful city-state, may have built the road to invade its neighbor Yaxuna. The study was published in the Journal of Archeological Science.""The University of Miami said in a news release that the study used light detection and ranging technology lasers to penetrate thick jungle vegetation and reveal the ruins beneath.""The LIDAR survey mapped out the road and uncovered 8,000 structures on its path.""University professor Traci Ardren is cited as saying the road did not run straight as supposed. Instead, Coba's warrior queen K'awiil Ajaw may have built the winding road to control settlements across the Yucatan Peninsula and to attack Yaxuna.""Arden, who is a co-author, says the Mayan roads were an engineering marvel. Giant limestone boulders were utilized to fill uneven ground, then white plaster was applied to make the road surface.""This substance is similar to Roman concrete and gave the road its name Sacbe, which comes from the Mayan word for 'white way.'"SOURCES: Journal of Archeological Science, University of Miami https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2352409X19306662?via%3Dihubhttps://news.miami.edu/stories/2020/02/modern-technology-reveals-old-secrets-about-the-great-white-maya-road.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/26/3968389/3968389_9E59E5A6536D4585BB0DB76D6BF0EEB7_200226_3968389_Archeologists_complete_first_ever_LIDAR_survey_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968376</guid>
      <title>Japan plans 2024 space mission to visit Mars' moons: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan is set to launch a robotic mission to the Martian system in 2024. The MIT Technology Review reports the mission will visit Phobos and Deimos, and recover dust samples from the former Martian moon, citing Japan's space agency JAXA.According to JAXA, the Martian Moon Exploration spacecraft, or MMX, will enter into a stable orbit to observe the two moons for a year. The MMX will utilize a NASA-funded neutron and gamma-ray spectrometer to determine the composition of these moons.The MMX will also land on Phobos and send out a small rover. The vehicle will use its equipped geological core sampler and dig 2 cm deep into the dust to retrieve samples weighing 10 grams.The mission's main goals are to investigate the two moon's origins, to find evidence that water had been present on Deimos and Phobos, and gather data on the gravitational stress that is expected to tear Phobos apart 30 to 50 million years from now.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Japan plans for 2024 Martian Moon Exploration mission2. MMX spacecraft will enter orbit and scan Deimos, Phobos3. Small rover will collect dust sample from Phobos4. MMX's scientific goals VOICEOVER (in English): "Japan is set to launch a robotic mission to the Martian system in 2024. The MIT Technology Review reports the mission will visit Phobos and Deimos, and recover dust samples from the former Martian moon, citing Japan's space agency JAXA.""According to JAXA, the Martian Moon Exploration spacecraft, or MMX, will enter into a stable orbit to observe the two moons for a year. The MMX will utilize a NASA-funded neutron and gamma-ray spectrometer to determine the composition of these moons.""The MMX will also land on Phobos and send out a small rover. The vehicle will use its equipped geological core sampler and dig 2 cm deep into the dust to retrieve samples weighing 10 grams.""The mission's main goals are to investigate the two moon's origins, to find evidence that water had been present on Deimos and Phobos, and gather data on the gravitational stress that is expected to tear Phobos apart 30 to 50 million years from now."SOURCES: Japanese Aerospace Exploration Agency, NASA, MIT Technology Reviewhttp://mmx.isas.jaxa.jp/en/mission/https://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-selects-instrument-for-future-international-mission-to-martian-moonshttps://www.technologyreview.com/f/615270/japan-will-launch-the-first-ever-sample-return-mission-from-the-martian-system/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/26/3968376/3968376_7FE1E1A8220B420887B8678ADE4A9D79_200226_3968376_Japan_plans_2024_space_mission_to_visit_Mars__mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media,Martian Moon Exploration, MMX, space mission, Martian system, Martian moons, Mars moons mission, Mars' moons, Mars, Phobos, Deimos, rover, JAXA, Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency, NASA, 2024, space, space exploration, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968261</guid>
      <title>Wildlife consumption banned in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina announced on Monday that the country has banned the consumption and trade of wildlife with immediate effect amid the ongoing Covid-19 outbreak. Hunting or transporting wild animals for eating purposes will also be prohibited under the ban. Scientists in China suspect that the new coronavirus has spread from wild animals to humans, but this has not been proven yet.This includes wild animals protected by law, terrestrial animals and terrestrial wild animals that are being raised in breeding farms, the South China Morning Post reports, citing the People's Daily. Animals such as civet cats, wild boars, deer, blue peacocks and pigeons will all be protected under the ban.According to Reuters, these wild animals can be used for medical or scientific purposes but will be subject to inspection and strict examination.Aquatic animals, livestock, poultry and other animals are exempt from the ban.China's wildlife protection laws, which was brought into effect in 1989, included loopholes that allowed consumption of wild animals and captive breeding of wildlife for commercial purposes, the South China Morning Post reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Explaining China's wildlife ban 2. Which wild animals the ban would include3. The wild animals could be used for medical or scientific studies4. Which animals are exempt from the banVOICEOVER (in English): "China announced on Monday that the country has banned the consumption and trade of wildlife with immediate effect amid the ongoing Covid-19 outbreak.""Hunting or transporting wild animals for eating purposes will also be prohibited under the ban.""Scientists in China suspect that the new coronavirus has spread from wild animals to humans, but this has not been proven yet.""Citing the People's Daily, the South China Morning Post reports that this includes wild animals protected by law, terrestrial animals and terrestrial wild animals that are being raised in breeding farms." "Animals such as civet cats, wild boars, deer, blue peacocks and pigeons will all be protected under the ban." "According to Reuters, these wild animals can be used for medical or scientific purposes but will be subject to inspection and strict examination.""Aquatic animals, livestock, poultry and other animals are exempt from the ban."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, Xinhua, Reuters, The Guardian, Global Times https://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/3052151/china-bans-trade-eating-wild-animals-battle-against-coronavirushttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2020-02/25/c_138814681.htmhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health-wildlife/china-bans-trade-consumption-of-wild-animals-due-to-coronavirus-idUSKCN20J069https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/feb/25/coronavirus-closures-reveal-vast-scale-of-chinas-secretive-wildlife-farm-industryhttps://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1180632.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/26/3968261/3968261_F56D847D0452411A85252C77B713E01F_200226_3968261_Wildlife_consumption_banned_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China wildlife ban, wildlife in china, covid-19, china covid-19, consumption of wildlife banned in china, chinese wildlife industry, china wild animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968059</guid>
      <title>WHO warns that the world should prepare for coronavirus pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe World Health Organization has warned that the world should prepare for a potential coronavirus pandemic.Outbreaks of COVID-19 have emerged in South Korea, Italy, and Iran, causing concern and prompting the WHO to say countries should be in 'a phase of preparedness' for a possible pandemic.The BBC reports that a pandemic occurs when an infectious disease easily spreads from person to person across many parts of the world.Thus far, the outbreak has been centered in China, where the virus originated. Over 77,000 people have been infected, and 2,600 have died.South Korea currently has 830 confirmed cases  the largest number outside China. Eight have died, and 7,700 troops are now quarantined after at least 13 in the military were found to be infected.Most of the country's cases are in Daegu, where clusters have been linked to a hospital and a secretive religious group.The largest number of cases in Europe  at least 229  are in Italy. To contain the outbreak, authorities have locked down several towns in the Lombardy and Veneto regions.Iran also has 61 confirmed cases, the majority of which is in the holy city of Qom.According to the BBC, cases have also been reported in Iraq, Afghanistan, Kuwait, Oman, and Bahrain, all of which involve people who came from Iran.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Potential COVID-19 pandemic2. COVID-19 cases in China3. COVID-19 cases in South Korea4. Regions in Italy on lockdown5. COVID-19 cases in IranVOICEOVER (in English): "Outbreaks of COVID-19 have emerged in South Korea, Italy, and Iran, causing concern and prompting the WHO to say countries should be in 'a phase of preparedness' for a possible pandemic.""The BBC reports that a pandemic occurs when an infectious disease easily spreads from person to person across many parts of the world.""Thus far, the outbreak has been centered in China, where the virus originated. Over 77,000 people have been infected, and 2,600 have died.""South Korea currently has 830 confirmed cases  the largest number outside China. Eight have died, and 7,700 troops are now quarantined after at least 13 in the military were found to be infected.""Most of the country's cases are in Daegu, where clusters have been linked to a hospital and a secretive religious group.""The largest number of cases in Europe  at least 229  are in Italy. To contain the outbreak, authorities have locked down several towns in the Lombardy and Veneto regions.""Iran also has 61 confirmed cases, the majority of which is in the holy city of Qom.""According to the BBC, cases have also been reported in Iraq, Afghanistan, Kuwait, Oman, and Bahrain, all of which involve people who came from Iran."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardianhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-51611422https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/24/italians-struggle-with-surreal-lockdown-as-coronavirus-cases-rise***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 02:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/26/3968059/3968059_E4B7C91617174100870C7EF935BA7074_200226_3968059_WHO_warns_that_the_world_should_prepare_for_coro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, WHO, pandemic, global pandemic, coronavirus, COVID-19, wuhan virus, coronavirus outbreak, COVID-19 outbreak]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968861</guid>
      <title>Coronaviruses adapted to transmit across mammalian species: expert</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe WHO reports the COVID-19 outbreak as of February 25 has infected 80,000 people and resulted in about 2,700 deaths, mostly in China's Hubei.Writing in a column for Quanta Magazine, U.S. epidemiologist Tara C. Smith says that SARS-CoV-2 probably transmitted from bats to pangolins to humans.However, Smith, who is a public health professor at Kent State, notes other coronaviruses are known to jump the species barrier.SARS-CoV, which caused the SARS outbreak in 2003, originated from a civet cat. A decade later, MERS-CoV would emerge from a camel to infect humans.Coronaviruses rely on surface glycoproteins for binding themselves with the receptors on the cells of their hosts to cause infections.The part of the protein that binds is called the S1 subunit. Coronaviruses possess highly varied S1s that allow them to bind with many mammalian cell receptors, including those found on the surface of human air passageways.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. COVID-19 causing coronavirus probably transmitted from bat to pangolins to humans2. MERS and SARS coronaviruses are known to have crossed the speices barrier3. Coronavirus' surface glycoprotein facilitate cross species tranmission4. This is because coronaviruses have varied surface proteinsVOICEOVER (in English): "The WHO reports the COVID-19 outbreak as of February 25 has infected 80,000 people and resulted in about 2,700 deaths, mostly in China's Hubei.""Writing in a column for Quanta Magazine, U.S. epidemiologist Tara C. Smith says that SARS-CoV-2 probably transmitted from bats to pangolins to humans.""However, Smith, who is a public health professor at Kent State, notes other coronaviruses are known to jump the species barrier.""SARS-CoV, which caused the SARS outbreak in 2003, originated from a civet cat. A decade later, MERS-CoV would emerge from a camel to infect humans.""Coronaviruses rely on surface glycoproteins for binding themselves with the receptors on the cells of their hosts to cause infections.""The part of the protein that binds is called the S1 subunit. Coronaviruses possess highly varied S1s that allow them to bind with many mammalian cell receptors, including those found on the surface of human air passageways."SOURCES: WHO, Quanta Magazinehttps://www.who.int/docs/default-source/coronaviruse/situation-reports/20200225-sitrep-36-covid-19.pdf?sfvrsn=2791b4e0_2https://www.quantamagazine.org/how-do-animal-viruses-like-coronavirus-jump-species-20200225/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 10:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/27/3968861/3968861_B1C7E362F50440B88CA40462B559C960_200227_3968861_Coronaviruses_adapted_to_transmit_across_mammali_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Coronavirus, coronaviruses, animal to human transmission, species barrier, glycoproteins, glycoprotein, novel coronavirus, SARS-CoV-2, SARS-CoV, MERS-CoV, SARS, MERS, COVID-19, COVID19, science, epidemic, pneumonia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968586</guid>
      <title>South Korean COVID-19 infections linked to secretive religious cult</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCoronavirus infection cases have surged in South Korea, with more than half linked to a religious cult whose secretive nature is said to have helped the virus spread undetected. The Korean Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported 1,146 confirmed COVID-19 infections in the country as of February 26. Majority are located in the city of Daegu and neighboring Cheongdo county, where they are centered around a hospital and the Shincheonji church of Jesus.The New York Times reports that the link to many of the cases is a 61-year-old woman known as Patient No. 31. Despite presenting a fever and sore throat, she initially refused to be tested for the virus, and attended several Shincheonji church gatherings before testing positive.Church members sit packed together on the floor during services and are not allowed to wear glasses or face masks. Citing South Korean health officials, the BBC reports that any gathering in such a confined space attended by Patient No. 31 would likely have led to more infections.Another cluster at a hospital in Cheongo has also been associated with the church. According to the New York Times, a large number of followers attended a funeral at a hall owned by the hospital. Over 100 patients and staff have since tested positive for the virus.Health officials learned that Patient No. 31 had also been in Cheongdo in early February. She told Newsis she hadn't visited the funeral or the hospital, only a public bathhouse.Shincheonji is considered a cult by many in South Korea, so members typically hide their membership from non church members. This, along with the belief that being sick is a weakness, has made it more difficult for authorities to track down those who have been infected, according to the BBC.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Infections in South Korea centered in hospital and church in Daegu2. Cases linked to infected church member 3. Church member spreading virus during service in confined space4. Cluster of infections at Cheongdo hospital5. Infected church member visiting Cheongdo bathhouseVOICEOVER (in English): "The Korean Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported 1,146 confirmed COVID-19 infections in the country as of February 26.""Majority are located in the city of Daegu and neighboring Cheongdo county, where they are centered around a hospital and the Shincheonji church of Jesus.""The New York Times reports that the link to many of the cases is a 61-year-old woman known as Patient No. 31.""Despite presenting a fever and sore throat, she initially refused to be tested for the virus, and attended several Shincheonji church gatherings before testing positive.""Church members sit packed together on the floor during services and are not allowed to wear glasses or face masks.""Citing South Korean health officials, the BBC reports that any gathering in such a confined space attended by Patient No. 31 would likely have led to more infections.""Another cluster at a hospital in Cheongo has also been associated with the church. According to the New York Times, a large number of followers attended a funeral at a hall owned by the hospital.""Over 100 patients and staff have since tested positive for the virus.""Health officials learned that Patient No. 31 had also been in Cheongdo in early February. She told Newsis she hadn't visited the funeral or the hospital, only a public bathhouse."SOURCES: KCDC, BBC, New York Times, The Guardianhttps://www.cdc.go.kr/board/board.es?mid=a30402000000&bid=0030https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-51609840https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/21/world/asia/south-korea-coronavirus-shincheonji.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/22/coronavirus-south-korea-sees-huge-jump-cases-china-hubei-wuhan-outbreak-***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 03:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/02/27/3968586/3968586_33027A7044E24792856824AA01570E53_200227_3968586_South_Korean_COVID_19_infections_linked_to_secre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19, coronavirus, South Korea infection surge, South Korea infections, South Korea virus, Daegu, Shincheonji church of Jesus, religious cult, shincheonji church]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
