<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3982007</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How soap destroys COVID-19 coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWashing your hands thoroughly with soap is one of the most effective ways to eliminate SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, from your skin, according to Taiwan's Centers for Disease Control.As detailed in a report in the New York Times, soap molecules have a hydrophilic head which is attracted to water and a hydrophobic tail that seeks to bond with lipids such as oils and fats.Coronaviruses are enveloped RNA viruses. Their key components are RNA, the virus' genetic material; proteins that allow the virus to infect cells; and a lipid envelope that coats the virus. This lipid membrane has two rings of hydrophilic heads surrounding two layers of hydrophobic tails.Soap molecules destabilize a coronavirus because their hydrophobic tails are attracted to lipids in the virus' lipid bilayer. The soap molecules stick to lipids in the bilayer and pry them apart, encapsulating them in bubbles called micelles that wash away in the lather.In addition to disrupting the lipid membrane of the virus, soap molecules also disrupt the bonds that hold the proteins, lipids and viral RNA together. They effectively pull the virus apart, and the viral particles are rinsed away in water.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Soap molecule with hydrophilic head and hydrophobic tail2. RNA, proteins and lipids are main components of SARS-CoV-2 and other enveloped RNA viruses3. Soap molecules destabilize a coronavirus' lipid bilayer4. Soap molecules pull the virus apartVOICEOVER (in English): "Soap molecules have a hydrophilic head which is attracted to water and a hydrophobic tail that seeks to bond with lipids such as oils and fats.""Coronaviruses are enveloped RNA viruses. Their key components are RNA, the virus' genetic material; proteins that allow the virus to infect cells; and a lipid envelope that coats the virus. This lipid membrane has two rings of hydrophilic heads surrounding two layers of hydrophobic tails.""Soap molecules destabilize a coronavirus because their hydrophobic tails are attracted to lipids in the virus' lipid bilayer. The soap molecules stick to lipids in the bilayer and pry them apart, encapsulating them in bubbles called micelles that wash away in the lather.""In addition to disrupting the lipid membrane of the virus, soap molecules also disrupt the bonds that hold the proteins, lipids and viral RNA together. They effectively pull the virus apart, and the viral particles are rinsed away in water."SOURCES: Taiwan Centers for Disease Control, New York Times, Smithsonian, Clinical Infectious Diseaseshttps://www.cdc.gov.tw/File/Get/HAvRHGs_EjKeROHYmzWm5whttps://www.cdc.gov.tw/En/Category/ListContent/bg0g_VU_Ysrgkes_KRUDgQ?uaid=0nAzwpXdBNIAPOvJhwrGoQhttps://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/13/health/soap-coronavirus-handwashing-germs.html?auth=login-googlehttps://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/why-washing-your-hands-so-important-anyway-180974355/https://academic.oup.com/cid/article/48/3/285/304169***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 06:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/01/3982007/3982007_FA110789F1214A58BD51A7DB617B1216_200401_3982007_Explainer__How_soap_destroys_COVID_19_coronaviru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981976</guid>
      <title>Research shows coronavirus can survive on a surgical mask for up to seven days.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research published in medRxive by medical specialists in Hong Kong shows how long SARS-CoV-2 can survive on different surfaces and in different environments.The researchers pipetted a droplet of virus culture on several surfaces including paper, tissue paper, wood, cloth, glass, a banknote, stainless steel, plastic, the inner layer of a surgical mask and the outer layer of a surgical mask.Results showed that there was no trace of the infectious virus on printing and tissue paper three hours after incubation.The infectious virus stopped being present on wood and cloth by Day 2 after incubation. Glass surfaces and banknotes had no trace of the virus by Day 4. Stainless steel and plastic surfaces had no detectable virus on their surfaces by Day 7.However, the infectious virus could still be detected on the outer layer of a surgical mask by Day 7.The research concludes that although the virus is stable in a wide range of environments, it is still vulnerable to standard disinfection methods.Previous research by American health officials and experts published in medRxiv showed that the novel coronavirus can survive in air particles for several hours and on some surfaces for up to three days.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Medical pipette with coronavirus culture2. Pipette drops a droplet of coronavirus on several surfaces3. Length of coronavirus survival on different surfaces4. Coronavirus lasts seven days on surgical masks5. Coronavirus particles in the airVOICEOVER (in English): "New research published in medRxive by medical specialists in Hong Kong shows how long SARS-CoV-2 can survive on different surfaces and in different environments.""The researchers pipetted a droplet of virus culture on several surfaces including paper, tissue paper, wood, cloth, glass, a banknote, stainless steel, plastic, the inner layer of a surgical mask and the outer layer of a surgical mask.""Results showed that there was no trace of the infectious virus on printing and tissue paper three hours after incubation.""The infectious virus stopped being present on wood and cloth by Day 2 after incubation. Glass surfaces and banknotes had no trace of the virus by Day 4. Stainless steel and plastic surfaces had no detectable virus on their surfaces by Day 7." "However, the infectious virus could still be detected on the outer layer of a surgical mask by Day 7.""The research concludes that although the virus is stable in a wide range of environments, it is still vulnerable to standard disinfection methods.""Previous research by American health officials and experts published in medRxiv showed that the novel coronavirus can survive in air particles for several hours and on some surfaces for up to three days."SOURCES: medRxiv.orghttps://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.15.20036673v2.full.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 05:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/01/3981976/3981976_D00987E9E46A4051877AFFF98893EA5F_200401_3981976_Research_shows_coronavirus_can_survive_on_a_surg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Covid-19, coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, coronavirus precautions, coronavirus covid-19]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3982355</guid>
      <title>Explainer: A complete picture of how coronavirus infects and damages the human body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCOVID-19 spreads through droplets that can be carried for up to 27 feet and land on the respiratory system, according to a study in the Journal of American Medical Association.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SARS-CoV-2 is transmitted by droplets2. Novel coronavirus targets human cell ACE2 receptors3. Mutations in spike protein enables the virus to invade cells via ACE24. The virus hijacks infected cell to reproduce5. Viral proteins and RNA are packaged into new viruses by hijacked Golgi body6. Infected cells die of biochemical distress7. Immune response triggers inflammation8. Lung infections could lead to pneumonia9. COVID-19 could spread in the blood to other major organs 10. Ventilators needed to keep some patients aliveVOICEOVER (in English): "The COVID-19 coronavirus, or SARS-CoV-2, spreads through droplets that people make when we talk, cough or sneeze. The virus can be carried for up to 27 feet and land on the respiratory system, according to a study in the Journal of American Medical Association.""A gene sequence study published in Frontiers in Medicine showed that the coronavirus targets human cells with ACE2 receptors. This means the epithelial cells in the lungs and other organs are vulnerable to the coronavirus.""The coronavirus has mutations in the spike proteins on its surface. The mutations to the receptor binding domains, or RBDs, allow the virus to use human ACE2 receptors as entry points for getting into the cell.""According to the British Society for Immunology, the virus hijacks the cell and commandeers the structures inside the cell to make more copies of itself. The infected cell's ribosomes are directed to create viral RNA and proteins.""After that, the cell's Golgi apparatus puts the proteins and RNA together and coats them in protein, which creates new copies of the coronavirus.""The biochemical distress of being hijacked by the virus eventually kills the cell, which causes damage to the infected tissue.""At the same time, the body tries to fight off the infection by sending killer T-cells. The killer cells search and destroy compromised cells. The immune system's attack on the infected part of the body leads to more tissue damage and inflammation.""Speaking to the Guardian, John Wilson, president-elect of the Royal Australasian College of Physicians and a respiratory physician, said the coronavirus infection spreads down the respiratory system and may reach the alveoli at the bottom of the lungs. This fills the lungs with liquids and inflammatory materials.""Symptoms of COVID-19 include fever, breathing difficulties and muscle pains. Citing doctors, the New York Times reports the virus may move in the blood to attack the heart, the kidneys, and the liver. Lung damage would also deprive patients of blood oxygen.""George Washington University Hospital reports that 20 percent of COVID-19 patients are symptomatic. A portion of these develop severe symptoms and become unable to breath without using ventilators or other medical devices."SOURCES: Journal of American Medical Association, Frontiers in Medicinehttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2763852?appId=scwebhttp://journal.hep.com.cn/fmd/EN/10.1007/s11684-020-0754-0https://www.immunology.org/public-information/bitesized-immunology/pathogens-and-disease/virus-replicationhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/28/what-happens-to-peoples-lungs-when-they-get-coronavirus***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 03:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/02/3982355/3982355_F96F93DB41ED495CB0294EE48B6F4FE9_200402_3982355_Explainer__A_complete_picture_of_how_coronavirus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2, COVID-19, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, Wuhan virus, Wuhan pneumonia, pneumonia, receptor binding domains, ACE2 receptor, infection, pandemic, alveoli, inflammation, explainer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3983870</guid>
      <title>France launches terrorism probe after stabbing spree in southeast town</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrench authorities have launched a terrorism probe after a knife attack killed two people and wounded five in the township of Romans-sur-Isère on April 4, Reuters reports. According to BBC News, the attack began at a tobacconist's shop in the town square.  AFP reports suspect Abdallah Ahmed-Osman, a Sudanese refugee in his 30s, stabbed the owners and a customer. After that, he attacked several more people in two other stores including a butcher's shop.Citing the butcher shop's owner, AFP reports Ahmed-Osman seized another knife and stabbed a customer, who died despite the shop owners' efforts to save the victim. The suspect then allegedly ran outside and attacked people queued up by a bakery.According to AFP, the police arrested Ahmed-Osman as he knelt in prayer while speaking in Arabic. The police arrested a second Sudanese managed 28 at Ahmed-Osman's residence and later detained a third, younger Sudanese man who also lived in the household. Texts with religious connotations were recovered.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of attack and casualties2. The suspect Abdallah Ahmed-Osman began stabbing at the town tobacconist 3. Suspect seized the second knife at a butcher store and killed a customer4. Abdallah Ahmed-Osman and two other Sudanese men at his residence arrestedVOICEOVER (in English): "French authorities have launched a terrorism probe after a knife attack killed two people and wounded five in the township of Romans-sur-Isère on April 4, Reuters reports. According to BBC News, the attack began at a tobacconist's shop in the town square.""AFP reports suspect Abdallah Ahmed-Osman, a Sudanese refugee in his 30s, stabbed the owners and a customer. After that, he attacked several more people in two other stores including a butcher's shop.""Citing the butcher shop's owner, AFP reports Ahmed-Osman seized another knife and stabbed a customer, who died despite the shop owners' efforts to save the victim. The suspect then allegedly ran outside and attacked people queued up by a bakery.""According to AFP, the police arrested Ahmed-Osman as he knelt in prayer while speaking in Arabic. The police arrested a second Sudanese man aged 28 at Ahmed-Osman's residence and later detained a third, younger Sudanese man who also lived in the household. Texts with religious connotations were recovered."SOURCES: Reuters, AFP, BBC Newshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-security/frances-anti-terror-prosecutor-probes-knife-attack-in-southeast-town-idUSKBN21M0EYhttps://www.afp.com/en/news/15/three-sudanese-arrested-over-french-terror-stabbing-doc-1qe5f62https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/france-launches-terror-probe-after-two-killed-stabbing-spree-doc-1qe3yl2http://www.rfi.fr/en/wires/20200405-three-sudanese-arrested-over-french-terror-stabbinghttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-52165522***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 12:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/06/3983870/3983870_D0EB103FC4DD403596E3A969A613ED16_200406_3983870_France_launches_terrorism_probe_after_stabbing_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Terrorism, terrorist, crime, knife attack, stabbing spree, stabbing, rampage, Abdallah Ahmed-Osman, Romans-sur-Isère, France]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984034</guid>
      <title>Asymptomatic people also responsible for virus spread</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research by health specialists from Singapore shows evidence that asymptomatic individuals infected with SARS-CoV-2 can inadvertently spread the virus.According to a new study from Singapore published in the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, medical researchers studied 243 cases of coronavirus infections that occurred in Singapore from January 23 to March 16.Out of these 243 cases, researchers detected seven clusters of cases that showed possible presymptomatic transmission of the virus. The researchers determined that 10 cases from these seven clusters were due to presymptomatic transmission.For example, a man in Cluster E had traveled to Japan from February 29 to March 8 where he may have been infected. The man later infected his housemate before showing any symptoms. Both developed symptoms on March 11.A woman in Cluster B, named Patient B1 in the paper, attended an event on February 15 where she likely came into contact with a confirmed COVID-19 patient. Nine days later she attended singing classes with another woman, Patient B2. Two days later Patient B1 developed symptoms. Patient B2 developed symptoms on February 29.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Researchers carrying out a study2. Number of presymptomatic transmission cases 3. Asymptomatic man transmits virus to roommate4. Asymptomatic woman transmits virus to classmate VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study from Singapore published in the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, medical researchers studied 243 cases of coronavirus infections that occurred in Singapore from January 23 to March 16.""Out of these 243 cases, researchers detected seven clusters of cases that showed possible presymptomatic transmission of the virus. The researchers determined that 10 cases from these seven clusters were due to presymptomatic transmission.""For example, a man in Cluster E had traveled to Japan from February 29 to March 8 where he may have been infected. The man later infected his housemate before showing any symptoms. Both developed symptoms on March 11.""A woman in Cluster B, named Patient B1 in the paper, attended an event on February 15 where she likely came into contact with a confirmed COVID-19 patient. Nine days later she attended singing classes with another woman, Patient B2. Two days later Patient B1 developed symptoms. Patient B2 developed symptoms on February 29."SOURCES:U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Preventionhttps://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/69/wr/pdfs/mm6914e1-H.pdfhttps://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/prevent-getting-sick/cloth-face-cover.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/07/3984034/3984034_D814346A93674A8B836B08597583F6E5_200407_3984034_Asymptomatic_people_also_responsible_for_virus_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, TomoNews, Covid-19, coronavirus, coronavirus symptoms, coronavirus precautions, coronavirus covid-19, coronavirus asymptomatic, asymptomatic contagiousness, covid-19  presymptomatic transmission, coronavirus  presymptomatic transmission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984646</guid>
      <title>Boris Johnson spends second night in the intensive care unit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBritish Prime Minister Boris Johnson is spending his second night in the intensive care unit at St. Thomas' Hospital in London after being admitted to the hospital on Sunday.The BBC reports Johnson was presenting symptoms of the COVID-19 coronavirus on March 27. Later that day he tested positive for the disease.By April 3, seven days after testing positive, the prime minister was still presenting symptoms while self-isolating.On April 5, he was admitted to the hospital for further examinations after his coronavirus symptoms persisted.Johnson was moved to the intensive care unit on April 6, where he has spent two nights under close medical supervision. Quoting foreign secretary and current deputy to the prime minister, Dominic Raab, the Guardian reports that Johnson has received oxygen but hasn't required invasive respiratory support.Johnson is now one of the thousands of coronavirus cases reported in the United Kingdom, and potentially one of many more to come[a].According to predictions from the Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation in Seattle, the UK is projected to have 66,000 COVID-19 deaths by August.[b]However, Neil Ferguson of Imperial College London, an epidemiologist who advises the government, told the Guardian that the model, quote, "does not match the current UK situation," explaining that the health care model used for the predictions was wrong in the case of the UK.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boris Johnson displays early symptoms of coronavirus2. Boris Johnson's symptoms persist during self-isolation3. Boris Johnson's is admitted into the hospital4. Boris Johnson under supervision in the intensive care unitVOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports British Prime Minister Boris Johnson was presenting symptoms of the COVID-19 coronavirus on March 27. Later that day he tested positive for the disease.""By April 3, seven days after testing positive, the prime minister was still presenting symptoms while self-isolating.""On April 5, he was admitted to the hospital for further examinations after his coronavirus symptoms persisted.""Johnson was moved to the intensive care unit on April 6, where he has spent two nights under close medical supervision. Quoting foreign secretary and current deputy to the prime minister, Dominic Raab, the Guardian reports that Johnson has received oxygen but hasn't required invasive respiratory support."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardian, Health Metrics and Evaluationhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-52208156https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/apr/07/boris-johnson-to-stay-in-hospital-amid-concerns-over-political-vacuumhttps://covid19.healthdata.org/united-kingdom***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 11:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/08/3984646/3984646_5821A4D4221B4798A07DD5BAE11F2CEC_200408_3984646_Boris_Johnson_spends_second_night_in_the_intensi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, boris johnson coronavirus, boris johnson covid-19, uk prime minister covid-19, boris johnson in icu, boris in icu]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984451</guid>
      <title>COVID-19 coronavirus may be transmitted by breathing: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA message to U.S. President Donald Trump's White House from the National Academies of Science, Engineering and Medicine found strong evidence in the existing scientific literature that the novel coronavirus may be spread through normal breathing. The report, issued on April 1, buttresses the argument that asymptomatic people should wear masks to reduce inadvertent transmission of the virus. In an email to Science Insider, Kimberly Prather, an aerosol chemist at the University of California, San Diego, said she was "relieved to see aerosolization is accepted.""This added airborne pathway helps explain why it is spreading so fast," she said.As late as March 27, a scientific brief from the World Health Organization stated that an analysis of more than 75,000 COVID-19 cases in China found no cases of the virus spreading through aerosols. On April 3, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reversed its previous advice on wearing masks in public, and recommended that everyone wear cloth face coverings while out in public during the pandemic.In its announcement, the CDC stressed that surgical masks or N-95 respirators must be reserved for healthcare workers and medical first responders.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Spread of SARS-CoV-2 through respiratory droplets via coughing or sneezing2. Spread of SARS-CoV-2 through aerosol droplets via breathing normally3. SARS-CoV-2 resuspended in the air by a healthcare worker4. Masks reduce presence of other kinds of human coronavirus RNA in respiratory droplets and aerosolsVOICEOVER (in English): "Until now, most global health agencies have stated the primary route of transmission for SARS-CoV-2 is through respiratory droplets, up to 1 millimeter wide, that are expelled when people cough or sneeze. These fall to the ground within 1 or 2 meters. They can also be deposited on surfaces, from where they can infect people who touch their eyes, nose or mouth.""The report by the National Academies cited previous research, including a study in the New England Journal of Medicine which found that novel coronavirus can float in aerosol droplets less than 5 microns wide for up to three hours. That study cited an earlier one from University of Nebraska Medical Center researchers which found viral RNA on hard-to-reach surfaces and in air samples more than 2 meters away from infected people.""The report also cited research from Wuhan University which found that novel coronavirus can be resuspended in the air when healthcare workers remove their personal protective equipment, clean infected floors, or otherwise operate in infected areas.""Also cited in the National Academies report was a study by University of Hong Kong researchers in Nature Medicine, which found masks reduced the detection of human coronavirus RNA  not including SARS-CoV-2  in both respiratory droplets and aerosols. That study has yet to undergo peer review."SOURCES: The National Academies of Sciences, Engineering and Medicine, Science, U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Preventionhttps://www.nap.edu/read/25769/chapter/1https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/04/you-may-be-able-spread-coronavirus-just-breathing-new-report-findshttps://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/prevent-getting-sick/diy-cloth-face-coverings.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/08/3984451/3984451_2664A6BB51AA4A91888EBD54129E53BF_200408_3984451_COVID_19_coronavirus_may_be_transmitted_by_breat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984895</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How bacteria give rain its unique scent</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research may explain why rainfall on the soil creates a unique scent in the air.According to a study published in Nature, the smell of rain is caused by geosmin, a chemical secreted by a genus of soil-dwelling bacteria called streptomyces.Writing a news release from John Innes Centre, researchers say the scent is bait for springtails, tiny 1.5mm-long arthropods.The tiny six-legged animals sport antennas to detect geosmin. As springtails are attracted to the substance, they follow the scent and eat the bacteria.By encouraging springtails to eat them, streptomyces get their spores on the arthropods and in their feces, which allows the bacteria to spread and reproduce. This mutually beneficial relationship may have endured for 450 million years.Streptomyces produce antibiotics that kill nematodes and fruit flies, but not springtails. According to the scientists, this is evidence that springtails have evolved to privilege the bacteria as a food source, which the springtails help to spread.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Streptomyces creates geosmin, the chemical responsible for the smell of rain2. Geosmin attracts springtails that eat the streptomyces 3. Streptomyces use springtails to spread their spores to reproduce4. Springtails are not affected by streptomyces's antibiotics VOICEOVER (in English): "New research may explain why rainfall on the soil creates a unique scent in the air." "According to the study published in Nature, the smell of rain is caused by geosmin, a chemical secreted by a genus of soil-dwelling bacteria called streptomyces.""Writing a news release from John Innes Centre, researchers say the scent is bait for springtails, tiny 1.5mm-long arthropods.""The tiny six-legged animals sport antennas to detect geosmin. As springtails are attracted to the substance, they follow the scent and eat the bacteria.""By encouraging springtails to eat them, streptomyces get their spores on the arthropods and in their feces, which allows the bacteria to spread and reproduce." "This mutually beneficial relationship may have endured for 450 million years.""Streptomyces produce antibiotics that kill nematodes and fruit flies, but not springtails.""According to the scientists, this is evidence that springtails have evolved to privilege the bacteria as a food source, which the springtails help to spread."SOURCES: Nature Microbiology, John Innes Centrehttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41564-020-0697-xhttps://www.jic.ac.uk/press-release/research-unearths-the-science-behind-the-smell-of-spring/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 06:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/09/3984895/3984895_C4103B898F50409FA4E69321E47DC0D8_200409_3984895_Explainer__How_bacteria_give_rain_its_unique_sce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, smell of rain, petrichor, streptomyces, bacteria, geosmin, springtails, arthropod, arthropods, spores, John Innes Centre, biology, microbiology, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985397</guid>
      <title>NASA plans lunar base camp near Moon's South Pole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA submitted its plans for a lunar base camp to the National Space Council in a 13-page report entitled "NASA's Plan for Sustained Lunar Exploration and Development" on April 2.The plans are part of NASA's Artemis program to send humans back to the Moon as early as 2024.NASA plans to build its Artemis Base Camp near the Moon's South Pole. The base camp will provide a fixed outpost for exploration and in the long term would include a landing pad and infrastructure for power, radiation shielding, and waste disposal and storage.Core elements for a sustained presence on the Moon would include a lunar terrain vehicle, for mobility around the base camp, a habitable mobility platform that would allow for longer excursions on the Moon for up to 45 days, and a fixed lunar foundation surface habitat that could house as many as four astronauts for shorter periods of time.NASA's planned Gateway outpost in lunar orbit would serve as a command and control center for operations on the Moon's surface, a rendez-vous point for spacecraft traveling to and from Earth, as well as provide living quarters and space to conduct scientific research.In an April 3 article on its website, NASA said it envisions sending four astronauts to the Gateway for a multi-month stay to simulate a trip to Mars. Later, two crew members would travel to the lunar surface and explore with the habitable mobility platform.The four astronauts would then be reunited aboard the Gateway for another multi-month stay to simulate the return trip to Earth.NASA said: "These missions will be by far the longest duration human deep-space missions in history."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Artemis Base Camp2. Lunar terrain vehicle3. Habitable mobility platform4. Lunar foundation surface habitatVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA plans to build its Artemis Base Camp near the Moon's South Pole. The base camp will provide a fixed outpost for exploration and in the long term would include a landing pad and infrastructure for power, radiation shielding, and waste disposal and storage.""A lunar terrain vehicle, or LTV, will transport crew around base. Like the Apollo program's Lunar Roving Vehicle, the LTV will be an unenclosed rover. Astronauts driving it will wear spacesuits that have been specifically designed for the Artemis program.""For exploration beyond the lunar base camp, astronauts will use a habitable mobility platform, a larger pressurized rover with living space and amenities for trips across the Moon lasting up to 45 days.""The habitable mobility platform will be the primary residence for surface missions, but a lunar foundation surface habitat at the base camp will provide a more permanent habitat for as many as four crew members on shorter surface stays."SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/nasa-outlines-lunar-surface-sustainability-concepthttps://www.nasa.gov/sites/default/files/atoms/files/a_sustained_lunar_presence_nspc_report4220final.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 07:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/10/3985397/3985397_C40F5593073F4A629568362A4ABBE65E_200410_3985397_NASA_plans_lunar_base_camp_near_Moon_s_South_Pol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985385</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How the coronavirus tricks its way into human cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study sheds light on the fundamental architecture of the coronavirus that allows the pathogen to disguise itself and get into human cells.SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, has a viral coating that is studded with spike proteins, which are the coronavirus's camouflage and infection tools.According to a preprint paper published in BioArxiv, scientists have detailed the chemical makeup of the proteins by using electron microscopy and spectrometry. The researchers identified host-derived sugars  or glycans  embedded in the envelope of the spike protein, as well as the concentration of the sugars in each location on the spike.Glycans are what viruses use for hiding from the immune system and sneaking into human cells.Writing in a news release, the researchers say SARS-CoV-2's embedded glycan defenses are thinner than those of many other viruses.This suggests the coronavirus is a "hit and run" virus that moves rapidly from one person to another.Paper co-author Max Crispin is cited as saying the study about the coronavirus's sugars is "a very encouraging message for vaccine development," and the research team is already working with partners who have designed candidate vaccines.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Scientists detail the chemical makeup of coronavirus proteins 2. Viral spike protein's embedded sugars are located and identified3. SARS-CoV-2 has less defense and is a "hit and run" a virus4. Knowledge of spike protein may lead to a vaccine VOICEOVER (in English): "SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, has a viral coating that is studded with spike proteins, which are the coronavirus's camouflage and infection tools.""According to a preprint paper published in BioArxiv, scientists have detailed the chemical makeup of the proteins by using electron microscopy and spectrometry." "The researchers identified host-derived sugars  or glycans  embedded in the envelope of the spike protein, as well as the concentration of the sugars in each location on the spike." "Glycans are what viruses use for hiding from the immune system and sneaking into human cells.""Writing in a news release, the researchers say SARS-CoV-2's embedded glycan defenses are thinner than many other viruses." "This suggests the coronavirus is a 'hit and run' virus that moves rapidly from one person to another.""Paper co-author Max Crispin is cited as saying the study about the coronavirus's sugars is 'a very encouraging message for vaccine development,' and the research team is already working with partners who have designed candidate vaccines."SOURCES: BioArxiv, University of Southampton https://www.sciencefocus.com/news/coronavirus-a-wolf-in-sheeps-clothing-tricking-its-way-into-the-human-body/https://www.southampton.ac.uk/news/2020/04/coronavirus-spike-glycan.page***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 07:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/10/3985385/3985385_70EFC7EB2051440E989C15E4E9CAFEC3_200410_3985385_Explainer__How_the_coronavirus_tricks_its_way_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus, SARS-CoV-2, COVID-19, hit and run virus, spike protein, proteins, glycans, sugars, University of Southampton, UK, science, biology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986278</guid>
      <title>How the coronavirus came to Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a report from Euractiv in collaboration with Reuters, Germany's Patient Zero was a Chinese woman working at the Shanghai branch of Webasto Group, a German car parts supplier. The woman's parents visited her from Wuhan before she left for Germany to attend meetings at the company's headquarters.In order to trace back the origin of the spread, doctors looked into the records of staff meetings and interviewed employees.Through the information they gathered, they found that the first German person infected by the Chinese woman was sitting next to her during a meeting on January 20.Evidence showed that the fourth person to be infected, or case #4, had been in regular contact with the Chinese woman. On January 22, case #4 sat back to back with a co-worker at the office canteen, where they shared a salt shaker. Researchers believe this is when the coworker became the fifth person to be infected.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese woman brings coronavirus into Germany2. Researchers trace back string of infections 3. First German case of coronavirus4. Fourth case spreads the virus through a saltshakerVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report from Euractiv in collaboration with Reuters, Germany's Patient Zero was a Chinese woman working at the Shanghai branch of Webasto Group, a German car parts supplier. The woman's parents visited her from Wuhan before she left for Germany to attend meetings at the company's headquarters.""In order to trace back the origin of the spread, doctors looked into the records of staff meetings and interviewed employees.""Through the information they gathered, they found that the first German person infected by the Chinese woman was sitting next to her during a meeting on January 20.""Evidence showed that the fourth person to be infected, or case #4, had been in regular contact with the Chinese woman. On January 22, case #4 sat back to back with a co-worker at the office canteen, where they shared a salt shaker. Researchers believe this is when the coworker became the fifth person to be infected."SOURCES: Euractive/Reutershttps://www.euractiv.com/section/coronavirus/news/pass-the-salt-how-coronavirus-came-to-germany-and-how-it-was-traced/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 10:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/13/3986278/3986278_1CCA2E1C12AE4C009973098CE20804BE_200413_3986278_How_the_coronavirus_came_to_Germany_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus in germany, coronavirus, covid-19, coronavirus germany, SARS-CoV-2, COVID-19, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, Wuhan virus, Wuhan pneumonia, pneumonia, COVID-19 virus, COVID-19 pandemic, webasto]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986236</guid>
      <title>NASA concept would turn Moon crater into a giant telescope</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA is funding an early-stage concept to build a giant telescope in a crater on the far side of the moon through its NASA Innovative Advanced Concepts program, the space agency announced on April 7.At a kilometer in diameter, the Lunar Crater Telescope would be the largest filled-aperture radio telescope in the Solar System.Its location on the Moon's far side would isolate the telescope from electromagnetic interference from Earth, as well as allow it to observe longer wavelengths that are blocked by the Earth's ionosphere.This would allow scientists to observe fingerprints left by the Big Bang as the universe expanded exponentially in less than a trillionth of a second after it came into existence.NASA has given the project $125,000 for a nine-month study of the concept. Other projects that received funding from the NASA Innovative Advanced Concepts program include a lunar landing pad and a robotic explorer for Saturn's moon Enceladus. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lunar Crater Telescope would be located on the Moon's far side2. Robots deploy wire mesh and suspend telescope's receiver in lunar crater3. The Moon would shield the telescope from electromagnetic radiation and the ionosphere4. Telescope could observe fingerprints left by the Big BangVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA is funding an early-stage concept to build a giant telescope in a crater on the far side of the moon through its NASA Innovative Advanced Concepts program, the space agency announced on April 7.""The proposal for the Lunar Crater Telescope would use robots to hoist a wire mesh with a receiver suspended over a crater. At a kilometer in diameter, it would be the largest filled-aperture radio telescope in the Solar System.""The telescope's location on the Moon's far side would physically isolate it from electromagnetic interference caused by human activity, as well as allow it to observe longer wavelengths that are blocked by the Earth's ionosphere.""This would allow scientists to observe fingerprints left by the Big Bang as the universe expanded exponentially in less than a trillionth of a second after it came into existence."SOURCES: NASA, Nature https://www.nasa.gov/directorates/spacetech/niac/2020_Phase_I_Phase_II/lunar_crater_radio_telescope/https://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-selects-early-stage-technology-concepts-for-new-continued-studyhttps://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-017-08941-8***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 08:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/13/3986236/3986236_F8DB9EF8834E4EEBBED1328086A55313_200413_3986236_NASA_concept_would_turn_Moon_crater_into_a_giant_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986226</guid>
      <title>Nearly 600 sailors on the U.S. Navy aircraft carrier Theodore Roosevelt test positive for COVID-19: Pentagon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOLDA total of 585 sailors on the U.S. Navy aircraft carrier Theodore Roosevelt tested positive for COVID-19, the Navy said in a statement dated April 12. This figure represents 12 percent of the ship's 4,800 crew and an uptick of about 170 cases in three days.Speaking to a news conference at the Pentagon on April 9, the Joint Chiefs of Staff's General John Hyten said one of the carrier's sailors with COVID-19 was found unresponsive in their isolation room and transferred to the ICU on Guam Island.According to the Navy's statement, 3,967 sailors of the ship have moved ashore, and 92 percent of the crew have been tested as of April 12.The U.S. Navy operates 11 aircraft carriers. According to National Public Radio, at least three of the advanced warships have reported COVID-19 cases onboard, which raises troubling questions about the fleet's military readiness.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A total of 585 sailors on USS Theodore Roosevelt have tested positive for COVID-192. One sailor has been admitted to an ICU on Guam Island3. About 92 percent of the ship's crew have been tested4. Three out of 11 U.S. Navy carriers have reported COVID-19 casesVOICEOVER (in English): "A total of 585 sailors of the Navy's carrier Theodore Roosevelt tested positive for COVID-19, reads the Navy's statement dated April 12. This figure represents 12 percent of the ship's 4,800 crew and an uptick of about 170 cases in three days.""Speaking to a news conference at the Pentagon on April 9, the Joint Chiefs of Staff's General John Hyten said one of the carrier's sailors with COVID-19 was found unresponsive in their isolation room and transferred to the ICU on Guam Island.""According to the Navy's statement, 3,967 sailors of the ship have moved ashore, and 92 percent of the crew have been tested as of April 12.""The U.S. Navy operates 11 aircraft carriers. According to National Public Radio, at least three of the advanced warships have reported COVID-19 cases onboard, which raises troubling questions about the fleet's military readiness."SOURCES: U.S. Navy, USNI News, ABC News, National Public Radio, USA Todayhttps://navylive.dodlive.mil/2020/03/15/u-s-navy-covid-19-updates/Sitive-for-covid-19https://news.usni.org/2020/04/09/carrier-roosevelt-sailor-in-intensive-care-after-testing-positive-for-covid-19https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/10-percent-carriers-crew-4800-coronavirus/story?id=70066250https://www.npr.org/2020/04/09/831266852/with-warship-coronavirus-cases-rising-concerns-over-military-readinesshttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/04/09/coronavirus-navy-denies-covid-19-cases-board-uss-nimitz-aircraft-carrier/5122778002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/13/3986226/3986226_A851671A79884653AA447974121C858E_200413_3986226_Nearly_600_sailors_on_the_U_S__Navy_aircraft_car_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus, U.S. Navy, US Navy, USN, USS, Theodore Roosevelt, aircraft carrier, Crozier, Modly, Guam, pandemic, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986513</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus may attack the brain and nervous system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study of COVID-19 patients in the Chinese city of Wuhan, from where the pandemic originated, found coronavirus could lead to serious neurological complications in perhaps as many as one third of all patients.In the study of 214 hospitalized COVID-19 patients in Wuhan published in the journal JAMA Neurology on April 10, researchers reported more than 35 percent had neurological complications, including decreased levels of cognition, stroke, and muscle damage.Separately, France's National Union of Dermatologists-Venereologists, or SNDV, said in an April 6 press release that certain skin dermatological conditions may possibly be associated with Covid-19 infection.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Wuhan, China on a map2. Neurological complications in COVID-19 patients in Wuhan study3. 36.4 of patients in study had neurologic symptoms, while 45.5 percent of those with severe infections showed neurologic manifestations4. Common manifestations of COVID-195. Reports indicate COVID-10 patients may experience anosmia, hyposmia, and dysgeusia6. France on a map7. Possible dermatological symptoms of COVID-1 include pseudo-frostbite, hives, and rednessVOICEOVER (in English): "A study of COVID-19 patients in the Chinese city of Wuhan, from where the pandemic originated, found coronavirus could lead to serious neurological complications in perhaps as many as one third of all patients.""In the study of 214 hospitalized COVID-19 patients in Wuhan, researchers reported more than 35 percent had neurological complications, including decreased levels of cognition, stroke, and muscle damage.""Their findings, published in the journal JAMA Neurology on April 10, found 36.4 percent of those studied had neurologic symptoms. Among patients with more severe infections, 45.5 percent showed neurologic manifestations.""Not all patients with these symptoms exhibited common manifestations of the disease, namely a sore throat, dry cough, and diarrhea.""The news comes after previous reports that many COVID-10 patients experience anosmia, or the loss of smell; hyposmia, a reduced sense of smell; and dysgeusia, the distortion of the sense of taste." "These reported symptoms may indicate other ways in which the coronavirus could affect the brain.""Separately, France's National Union of Dermatologists-Venereologists, or SNDV, has reported that certain skin dermatological conditions may possibly be associated with Covid-19 infection." "In an April 6 press release, the organization said these symptoms include appearance of pseudo-frostbite of the extremities, transient hives, and sudden onset of persistent, sometimes painful redness."SOURCES: JAMA Neurology, Le Syndicat national des dermatologues-venereologues, American Academy of Otolaryngology-Head and Neck Surgery, ENT UKhttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/2764549https://www.syndicatdermatos.org/communique/communique-de-presse-06-04-20-covid19-et-peau/https://www.entnet.org/content/aao-hns-anosmia-hyposmia-and-dysgeusia-symptoms-coronavirus-diseasehttps://www.entuk.org/sites/default/files/files/Loss%20of%20sense%20of%20smell%20as%20marker%20of%20COVID.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/14/3986513/3986513_A5C19FEAC428433F9C5555465360F1FC_200414_3986513_Coronavirus_may_attack_the_brain_and_nervous_sys_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, symptoms of coronavirus, symptoms of covid-19, coronavirus animation, covid-19 animation, SARS-CoV-2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986481</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus may attack the brain and nervous system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study of COVID-19 patients in the Chinese city of Wuhan, from where the pandemic originated, found coronavirus could lead to serious neurological complications in perhaps as many as one third of all patients.In the study of 214 hospitalized COVID-19 patients in Wuhan, researchers reported more than 35 percent had neurological complications, including decreased levels of cognition, stroke, and muscle damage.Their findings, published in the journal JAMA Neurology on April 10, found 36.4 percent of those studied had neurologic symptoms. Among patients with more severe infections, 45.5 percent showed neurologic manifestations.Separately, France's National Union of Dermatologists-Venereologists, or SNDV, has reported that certain skin dermatological conditions may possibly be associated with Covid-19 infection.In an April 6 press release, the organization said these symptoms include appearance of pseudo-frostbite of the extremities, transient hives, and sudden onset of persistent, sometimes painful redness.The organization recommended that patients with skin conditions of these types consult a dermatologist to rule out the possibility of COVID-19.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Wuhan, China on a map2. Neurological complications in COVID-19 patients in Wuhan study3. 36.4 of patients in study had neurologic symptoms, while 45.5 percent of those with severe infections showed neurologic manifestations4. Common manifestations of COVID-195. Reports indicate COVID-10 patients may experience anosmia, hyposmia, and dysgeusia6. France on a map7. Possible dermatological symptoms of COVID-1 include pseudo-frostbite, hives, and rednessVOICEOVER (in English): "A study of COVID-19 patients in the Chinese city of Wuhan, from where the pandemic originated, found coronavirus could lead to serious neurological complications in perhaps as many as one third of all patients.""In the study of 214 hospitalized COVID-19 patients in Wuhan, researchers reported more than 35 percent had neurological complications, including decreased levels of cognition, stroke, and muscle damage.""Their findings, published in the journal JAMA Neurology on April 10, found 36.4 percent of those studied had neurologic symptoms. Among patients with more severe infections, 45.5 percent showed neurologic manifestations.""Not all patients with these symptoms exhibited common manifestations of the disease, namely a sore throat, dry cough, and diarrhea.""The news comes after previous reports that many COVID-10 patients experience anosmia, or the loss of smell; hyposmia, a reduced sense of smell; and dysgeusia, the distortion of the sense of taste." "These reported symptoms may indicate other ways in which the coronavirus could affect the brain.""Separately, France's National Union of Dermatologists-Venereologists, or SNDV, has reported that certain skin dermatological conditions may possibly be associated with Covid-19 infection." "In an April 6 press release, the organization said these symptoms include appearance of pseudo-frostbite of the extremities, transient hives, and sudden onset of persistent, sometimes painful redness."SOURCES: JAMA Neurology, Le Syndicat national des dermatologues-venereologues, American Academy of Otolaryngology-Head and Neck Surgery, ENT UKhttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/2764549https://www.syndicatdermatos.org/communique/communique-de-presse-06-04-20-covid19-et-peau/https://www.entnet.org/content/aao-hns-anosmia-hyposmia-and-dysgeusia-symptoms-coronavirus-diseasehttps://www.entuk.org/sites/default/files/files/Loss%20of%20sense%20of%20smell%20as%20marker%20of%20COVID.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/14/3986481/3986481_320CBB3D1D5D4CDA868A18C5E1B95E96_200414_3986481_Coronavirus_may_attack_the_brain_and_nervous_sys_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, symptoms of coronavirus, symptoms of covid-19, coronavirus animation, covid-19 animation, SARS-CoV-2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986921</guid>
      <title>New theory may explain how mystery space object Oumuamua came into being: astronomers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in Nature suggests the tidal forces that formed Oumuamua may have caused its erratic behavior.Since its discovery in 2017, the cigar-shaped space object has flummoxed scientists with its odd shape and acceleration movements that gravity effects cannot explain.Writing in a news release, researchers say that Oumuamua's parent body or bodies may have had a close encounter with a host star.They say computer models show the tidal forces from stars could rip the parent body apart and turn the original object into an elongated field of debris.The fragments may have then melted under the intense heat near the star before condescending again to form the strange cigar shape of Oumumua.Additionally, water-ice could be trapped under Oumuamua's surface. As the object makes its passage through the solar system, the ice could be vaporized and converted to thrust, which gives Oumuamua its gravity-defying accelerations.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Space object Oumuamua has dry surface and unusual acceleration patterns2. Oumuamua's precursor body may have been torn apart by a star's tidal forces3. Fragments near the star were heated and then coalesced into an elongated shape4. Water trapped in Oumamua may have vaporized to cause accelerationVOICEOVER (in English): "Since its discovery in 2017, the cigar-shaped space object Oumuamua has flummoxed scientists with its odd shape and acceleration movements that gravity effects cannot explain." "A new study published in Nature now suggests the tidal forces that formed Oumuamua may have caused its erratic behavior.""Writing in a news release, researchers say that Oumuamua's parent body or bodies may have had a close encounter with a host star.""They say computer models show the tidal forces from stars could rip the parent body apart and turn the original object into an elongated field of debris.""The fragments may have then melted under the intense heat near the star before condescending again to form the strange cigar shape of the Oumumua.""Additionally, water-ice could be trapped under Oumuamua's surface. As the object makes its passage through the solar system, the ice could be vaporized and converted to thrust, which gives Oumuamua its gravity-defying accelerations."SOURCES: Nature Astronomy, Phys.orghttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-020-1065-8https://phys.org/news/2020-04-formation-theory-mysterious-interstellar-oumuamua.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/15/3986921/3986921_BB01AE0FFBCD4D41921CA79C77AAFBF8_200415_3986921_New_theory_may_explain_how_mystery_space_object__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Oumuamua, tidal force, tidal forces, tidal disruption, solar system, interstellar object, oumuamua interstellar object,  National Astronomical Observatories, Chinese Academy of Sciences,  University of California Santa Cruz, Harvard, alien spacecraft, astronomy, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986869</guid>
      <title>New ozone hole found above the Arctic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have discovered an unusually large hole in the ozone layer above the Arctic.  According to observations from the European Space Agency, a new ozone hole has been spotted above the Arctic. The hole covers less than 1 million square kilometers. The Antarctic hole, on the other hand, can extend to around 20 to 25 million square kilometers.The ESA explains that during this polar winter, strong westerly winds from the polar vortex trapped cold air over the North Pole.When the polar winter ended, the heat from the first sunlight over the Arctic triggered ozone depletion, causing this unusual mini-hole to form.This type of ozone hole formation is different from that of the Antarctic ozone hole which appears every year due to extremely cold temperatures and pollution derived from human activity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Size of the new ozone hole over the Arctic2. Polar vortex and strong winds in the Arctic3. Sunlight triggers ozone depletion4. Antarctic ozone hole formationVOICEOVER (in English): "According to observations from the European Space Agency, a new ozone hole has been spotted above the Arctic. The hole covers less than 1 million square kilometers. The Antarctic hole, on the other hand, can extend to around 20 to 25 million square kilometers.""The ESA explains that during this polar winter, strong westerly winds from the polar vortex trapped cold air over the North Pole.""When the polar winter ended, the heat from the first sunlight over the Arctic triggered ozone depletion, causing this unusual mini-hole to form.""This type of ozone hole formation is different from that of the Antarctic ozone hole which appears every year due to extremely cold temperatures and pollution derived from human activity."SOURCES: European Space Agency, Nature.comhttp://www.esa.int/Applications/Observing_the_Earth/Copernicus/Sentinel-5P/Unusual_ozone_hole_opens_over_the_Arctichttps://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-020-00904-w***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 06:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/15/3986869/3986869_6DAA675484EF48A098079A3D6E65244D_200415_3986869_New_ozone_hole_found_above_the_Arctic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, new ozone hole, ozone hole, arctic ozone hole, north pole ozone hole, ozone depletion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987417</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus has mutated into three variants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the University of Cambridge and Germany have used RNA analysis to identify three types of COVID-19 that evolved during the early stages of the pandemic. This study is published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.Citing the team, the University of Cambridge writes in a news release that COVID-19 type A is the "original human virus genome" from the Chinese city of Wuhan.Mutated versions of type A were discovered in U.S. nationals who reportedly lived in Wuhan. Large numbers of type A virus were also seen in patients living in the U.S. and Australia.Strangely, the dominant variant in Wuhan was type B, which was prevalent across East Asia, but did not spread much beyond the region. This means either a complex founding event happened in Wuhan, or some factors had resisted type B outside East Asia."Type C is the main COVID-19 variant in Europe. The presence of type C was detected in early cases from France, Italy, Sweden and England, yet this variant was absent in samples from patients in Mainland China.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. RNA analysis identifies three types of COVID-19 during the pandemic's early stages2. Type A, the original human virus genome, was detected in Wuhan, the U.S. and Australia3. Type B was the dominant strain in Wuhan and prevalent in East Asia4. Type C was the main variant of COVID-19 in EuropeVOICEOVER (in English): "The coronavirus is mutating rapidly and the pathogen has already developed into three main branches as of March 4 2020, according to a UK-German study.""Researchers from the University of Cambridge and Germany have used RNA analysis to identify three types of COVID-19 that evolved during the early stages of the pandemic. This study is published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.""Citing the team, the University of Cambridge writes in a news release that COVID-19 type A is the 'original human virus genome' from the Chinese city of Wuhan. Mutated versions of type A were discovered in U.S. nationals who reportedly lived in Wuhan. Large numbers of type A virus were also seen in patients living in the U.S. and Australia.""Strangely, the dominant variant in Wuhan was type B, which was prevalent across East Asia, but did not spread much beyond the region. This means either a complex founding event happened in Wuhan, or some factors had resisted type B outside East Asia.""Type C is the main COVID-19 variant in Europe. The presence of type C was detected in early cases from France, Italy, Sweden and England, yet this variant was absent in samples from patients in Mainland China.""Researchers also traced the first infections in Italy to Germany and Singapore, both of which had patients with the C variant of the coronavirus."SOURCES: Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, University of Cambridgehttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2020/04/07/2004999117https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-04/uoc-cgn040820.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/16/3987417/3987417_763A19BE2A88411E8F9254EE80A787A1_200416_3987417_Coronavirus_has_mutated_into_three_variants_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, SARS-CoV-2, COVID-19, pandemic, rapid mutation, RNA analyses, genetic network analysis, evolutionary paths, types of coronavirus, the University of Cambridge, Wuhan, UK, Germany]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987303</guid>
      <title>Singapore may have flattened the curve on coronavirus: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to Singapore's The Strait Times, COVID-19 has an infection number between 2 and 3 globally, meaning each patient infects two or three more people.The newspaper reports the infection number in the city-state has dropped to 1 since the government-ordered lockdown on April 8, citing Alex Cook, associate professor of public health at the National University of Singapore.By limiting exposure to carriers, social distancing could slow the spread of COVID-19, even if the biological factors remain hard to tackle.Cook was cited as saying Singapore's confirmed cases have risen to 1,481 as of April 7.However, he claims most were imported and Singapore should be able to control the disease if the nation shuts its borders.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Singapore may have succeeded in flattening the COVID-19 curve 2. Social distancing can be helpful even in the absence of vaccines or anti-virals3. COVID-19 capable of asymptomatic transmission4. Coronaviruses could spread by respiratory droplets to a distance of 2 meter5. The virus that causes COVID-19 could survive 7 days on stainless steel and plastic6. Singapore closed workplaces and schools7. Public health expert proposes Singapore to close borders VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Singapore's The Strait Times, COVID-19 has an infection number between 2 and 3 globally, meaning each patient infects two or three more people." "Citing a public health expert, the newspaper reports the infection number in the city-state has dropped to 1 since the government-ordered lockdown on April 8.""According to Alex Cook, associate professor of public health at the National University of Singapore, epidemics have biological and social factors."By limiting exposure to carriers, social distancing could slow the spread of COVID-19, even if the biological factors remain hard to tackle.""According to a study published by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, COVID-19 has been difficult to contain partly because asymptomatic carriers are already infectious."Writing in a report, the National Academies of Science states previous reports suggest breathing could spread coronaviruses to a distance of 2 meters, as evidenced by viral RNA residues.""Yet another study published in medRxive suggests the virus that causes COVID-19 could survive on printing and tissue paper for less than 3 hours, but 2 days on wood and cloth, 4 days on glass and banknotes, and 7 days on plastics and stainless steel.""The Strait Times reports Singapore has shuttered workplaces and closed public schools to let students study remotely, as part of its policies designed to contain the epidemic dubbed 'circuit breaker measures.'""Cook was cited as saying Singapore's confirmed cases have risen to 1,481 as of April 7.""However, he claims most of the cases were imported and Singapore should be able to control the disease if the nation shuts its borders."SOURCES: The Strait Times, Center for Disease Control and Prevention, The National Academies of Sciences, medRxiv.orghttps://www.straitstimes.com/singapore/health/how-circuit-breaker-measures-help-to-prevent-spread-of-virus-as-scientists-race-forhttps://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/69/wr/pdfs/mm6914e1-H.pdfhttps://www.nap.edu/read/25769/chapter/1https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.15.20036673v2.full.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 06:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/16/3987303/3987303_4952187AF058486A8456A5BFE315D9EC_200416_3987303_Singapore_may_have_flattened_the_curve_on_corona_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation, Next Media, coronavirus, COVID-19, reproduction number, social distancing, Singapore]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987215</guid>
      <title>Taiwan to roll out social distancing app</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan is working on a social distancing app that people can download on a voluntary basis to help prevent the spread of the coronavirus, a cabinet official said on April 11.In an article published by Taiwan's Central News Agency, Chien Hung-wei, director of the Executive Yuan's Department of Cyber Security, said the social distancing app uses Bluetooth to keep track of when the user gets close to other people. The app will issue an alert each time the user gets too close to someone else. It will also provide data on how often the user came too close to others during each day. Chien said the app's primary purpose is to provide users with information about crowded places so that they can avoid them.The app is currently being tested and will be released within the next two weeks. Use of the app will be voluntary. Data will be encrypted and saved in the user's device and will not be collected to track the user's movements, Chien said.Social distancing guidelines from Taiwan's Central Epidemic Command Center advise people to stay at least one meter apart outdoors and 1.5 meters apart indoors.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Social distancing app uses Bluetooth2. App issues an alert when the user gets too close to someone else and shows how many times this happens each day3. App shows users where large groups are gathering4. Social distancing guidelines from Taiwan's Central Epidemic Command CenterVOICEOVER (in English): "The Taiwanese social distancing app uses Bluetooth to keep track of when the user gets close to other people. Data will be encrypted and saved in the user's device and will not be collected to track the user's movements.""The app will issue an alert each time the user gets too close to someone else. It will also provide data on how often the user came too close to others during each day.""According to the Taiwanese government, the app's primary purpose is to provide users with information about crowded places so that they can avoid them.""Social distancing guidelines from Taiwan's Central Epidemic Command Center advise people to stay at least one meter apart outdoors and 1.5 meters apart indoors."SOURCES: Central News Agency (Taiwan)https://www.ocac.gov.tw/ocac/subsites2/pages/detail.aspx?site=af324ca7-bd1a-4f98-b704-6eec80ba4054&nodeid=4608&pid=16133105***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 02:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/16/3987215/3987215_69C002FF74EF4DADA959A6F4B1E87246_200416_3987215_Taiwan_to_roll_out_social_distancing_app_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19 Taiwan, geolocation, mass surveillance, Taiwan coronavirus, coronavirus, SARS-CoV-2, social distancing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987928</guid>
      <title>China using health tracking mobile system to curtail the spread of coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANApps from Chinese tech giants Alibaba and Tencent will now host a new health code system that uses QR codes to indicate the health status of citizens, according to a report from CNN.This is part of an effort to contain the spread of coronavirus now that businesses are reopening in the country. Alipay launched the new system on February 11.Chinese nationals have to input their national identity number or passport number along with their phone number into the system. Citizens also have to share their travel history and list what symptoms they may be experiencing.After the information is officially verified, citizens are assigned a colored QR code depending on their health status. Green QR codes mean you are safe, yellow QR codes mean you came in contact with a sick person and red means you cannot go out in public.Several businesses in China are now placing QR codes outside their venues so clients and customers can scan and show their health status codes to employees before entering a business.Oh, and how many people are under this system? Well, according to state-run Science and Technology Daily, Tencent's health code system has been in use in more than 300 cities since March.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tencent and Alibaba host health system on their apps2. Information gathered by the apps3. Colored-QR code system used 4. System being used outside a restaurantVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report from CNN, apps from Chinese tech giants Alibaba and Tencent will now host a new health code system that uses QR codes to indicate the health status of citizens. This is part of an effort to contain the spread of coronavirus now that businesses are reopening in the country. Alipay launched the new system on February 11.""Chinese nationals have to input their national identity number or passport number along with their phone number into the system. Citizens also have to share their travel history and list what symptoms they may be experiencing.""After the information is officially verified, citizens are assigned a colored QR code depending on their health status. Green QR codes mean you are safe, yellow QR codes mean you came in contact with a sick person and red means you cannot go out in public.""Several businesses in China are now placing QR codes outside their venues so clients and customers can scan and show their health status codes to employees before entering a business."SOURCES: CNN, The Guardian, ZDnethttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/04/15/asia/china-coronavirus-qr-code-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/06/more-scary-than-coronavirus-south-koreas-health-alerts-expose-private-liveshttps://www.zdnet.com/article/coronavirus-contact-tracing-apps-what-are-the-privacy-concerns/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/17/3987928/3987928_1AECE34FCCBE47C58D26E70B27CF3A55_200417_3987928_China_using_health_tracking_mobile_system_to_cur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus china, covid19 china, covid-19 china, tencent, alibaba, china health system, china health code system, health code system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987712</guid>
      <title>Researchers find longest animal ever recorded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a press release from the Schmidt Ocean Institute, researchers found a new submarine creature off the coast of Australia while aboard the Falkor research ship. The team completed twenty 4,500 meter dives and totaled over 181 hours of deep-sea exploration using a remotely operated submarine called SuBastian.During this expedition, the marine specialists spotted a type of string-like sea creature called siphonophore Apolemia. Scientists estimated that its outer ring is roughly 46 meters long. Logan Mock-Bunting, a spokesperson for the Schmidt Ocean Institute, told Newsweek that although exact measurements are pending, its length could be over 119 meters long.Siphonophores are related to corals and jellyfish. They are an entity made up of a connected colony of cloned zooids that work as a team to keep the siphonophore alive.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Area researched / Falkor research ship2. Remotely operated submarine SuBastian3. Siphonophore Apolemia found in deep sea4. Close up of zooidsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a press release from the Schmidt Ocean Institute, researchers found a new submarine creature off the coast of Australia while aboard the Falkor research ship." "The team completed twenty 4,500 meter dives and totaled over 181 hours of deep-sea exploration using a remotely operated submarine called SuBastian.""During this expedition, the marine specialists spotted a type of string-like sea creature called siphonophore Apolemia. Scientists estimated that its outer ring is roughly 46 meters long. Logan Mock-Bunting, a spokesperson for the Schmidt Ocean Institute, told Newsweek that although exact measurements are pending, its length could be over 119 meters long." "Siphonophores are related to corals and jellyfish. They are an entity made up of a connected colony of cloned zooids that work as a team to keep the siphonophore alive."SOURCES: Schmidt Ocean Institute. Science Alert, Newsweekhttps://schmidtocean.org/new-species-discovered-during-exploration-of-abyssal-deep-sea-canyons-off-ningaloo/https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-filmed-the-longest-known-stringy-stingy-thingy-floating-in-the-oceanhttps://www.newsweek.com/otherworldly-150-foot-long-string-like-organism-deep-sea-millions-interconnected-clones-1496512***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/17/3987712/3987712_62AAF10171044B05951E6A230FBE6EDA_200417_3987712_Researchers_find_longest_animal_ever_recorded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, new sea animals, deep sea creatures, Siphonophores, ROV SuBastian, Schmidt Ocean Institute Siphonophores, Schmidt Ocean Institute, deep sea animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988741</guid>
      <title>At least 17 killed in worst mass shooting in recent Canadian history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA man disguised as a police officer killed at least 17 people across Nova Scotia this weekend in one of the deadliest mass shootings in Canadian history, Canada's National Post reports.Canadian police said the suspect set fires and shot at people while dressed as a Royal Canadian Mounted Police officer and driving what looked like a Royal Canadian Mounted Police cruiser.The 12-hour rampage ended Sunday morning in a standoff at a gas station outside Halifax when the suspect was caught by the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. Police confirmed in a press conference Sunday evening that he was dead.Among those people killed was Constable Heidi Stevenson, a 23-year veteran of the Nova Scotia RCMP.The suspect has been identified as 51-year-old Gabriel Wortman. According to reports, he was a denturist who collected old police cruisers and other police memorabilia.The spree was the worst mass shooting in Canada in 30 years, surpassing the death toll of the 1989 Ecole Polytechnique massacre in Montreal.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of Portapique, Nova Scotia on a map2. Suspect disguised himself as a Royal Canadian Mounted Police officer3. Suspect drove what looked like an RCMP cruiser and later a silver Chevrolet SUV4. At least 17 killed including RCMP Constable Heidi StevensonVOICEOVER (in English): "The suspect shot and killed at least 17 people in several locations across Nova Scotia. Several bodies were found in Portapique, a rural town about 130 kilometers north of Halifax. More bodies were found at other locations.""The suspect has been identified as 51-year-old Gabriel Wortman, a denturist who collected old police cruisers and other police memorabilia." "The spree began Saturday night. Authorities say Wortman disguised himself as a police officer at one point and drove what looked like a Royal Canadian Mounted Police cruiser.""He later switched to a small silver Chevrolet Tracker SUV.""Among the 17 people killed was Constable Heidi Stevenson, a 23-year veteran of the Nova Scotia RCMP."SOURCES: Global News, National Post, Globe and Mail, SOURCES: National Post, Globe and Mail, CTV Newshttps://nationalpost.com/news/canada/nova-scotia-shooting-rcmphttps://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-nova-scotia-mass-shooter-was-a-denturist-with-an-obsession-for/https://globalnews.ca/news/6838880/rcmp-active-shooter-portapique-n-s/https://youtu.be/bVeJ27gtDz4https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/nova-scotia-shooting-rcmphttps://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-nova-scotia-mass-shooter-was-a-denturist-with-an-obsession-for/https://globalnews.ca/news/6838880/rcmp-active-shooter-portapique-n-shttps://atlantic.ctvnews.ca/just-unbelievable-neighbours-of-nova-scotia-shooting-suspect-shocked-by-news-1.4903021/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 07:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/20/3988741/3988741_C06E300162D54871A0A8BC51993C48D8_200420_3988741_At_least_17_killed_in_worst_mass_shooting_in_rec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988708</guid>
      <title>NASA discovers 'most similar planet to Earth' ever found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of scientists has discovered an Earth-size exoplanet in the habitable or "Goldilocks" zone of its star while reviewing old data from the Kepler Space Telescope, according to a press release from NASA.The planet, Kepler-1649c, is located 300 light-years from Earth in the constellation of Cygnus and "is most similar to Earth in size and estimated temperature" of all the exoplanets discovered by Kepler.Kepler-1649c is 1.06 times the size of Earth and orbits a small red dwarf star once every 19.5 Earth days, from which it receives 75 percent of the amount of light Earth receives from the Sun. Scientists made the discovery while analyzing old data from Kepler. They found that previous searches with a computer algorithm had misidentified Kepler-1649c as a false positive. "Out of all the mislabeled planets we've recovered, this one's particularly exciting," said Andrew Vanderburg, a researcher at the University of Texas at Austin and lead author of the paper published on April 15 in the Astrophysical Journal Letters. "If we hadn't looked over the algorithm's work by hand, we would have missed it.""In terms of size and likely temperature, this is the most similar planet to Earth that has ever been found with Kepler," said co-author Jeff Coughlin at the SETI Institute. "It's incredible to me that we just found it now, seven years after data collection stopped on the original Kepler field."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Kepler-1649c and size comparison with Earth2. Kepler-1649 orbits the red dwarf Kepler-1649 from which it receives 75 percent of the amount of light Earth receives from the Sun3. Kepler-1649c's orbital period and location within its star's habitable zone4. Depiction of the orbits of Kepler-1649c and Kepler-1649b along with a speculated third planetVOICEOVER (in English): "Among all the exoplanets discovered by the Kepler spacecraft thus far, Kepler-1649c is most similar to Earth in size and estimated surface temperature." "The planet is just 1.06 times the size of Earth and it may share similar surface temperatures since it receives 75 percent of the amount of light Earth receives from the Sun, though it orbits a red dwarf star, which may be prone to frequent flare-ups.""Kepler-1649c orbits the red dwarf so closely that a year on Kepler-1649c lasts only 19.5 Earth days. But it lies within the star's Goldilocks Zone, where temperatures are neither too hot nor too cold for liquid water to exist on the planet.""Kepler-1649c has a neighboring planet, Kepler-1649b. Kepler-1649c circles the red dwarf nine times for every four times the inner planet orbits. This nine-to-four ratio is rare, and may indicate the presence of another planet, which scientists have not observed because it may be too small or have an orbital tilt that makes it hard to find."SOURCES: NASA Jet Propulsion Laboratory, SETI Institute, The Astrophysical Journal Letters, NASA Exoplanet Archivehttps://www.nasa.gov/press-release/earth-size-habitable-zone-planet-found-hidden-in-early-nasa-kepler-datahttps://www.seti.org/press-release/dedicated-team-scientists-discover-habitable-zone-earth-size-planet-kepler-datahttps://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/2041-8213/ab84e5https://exoplanetarchive.ipac.caltech.edu/docs/intro.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 06:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/20/3988708/3988708_7341EFCAC845442985DAA2D9A2C4EDCD_200420_3988708_NASA_discovers__most_similar_planet_to_Earth__ev_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Kepler-1649c, planet, NASA, new planets, kepler space telescope, earth like planets, exoplanet, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988678</guid>
      <title>Uranus's ionized gas leak seen for the first time by Voyager 2 decades ago: NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWriting in the Geophysical Research Letters, NASA says a review of Voyager 2's old data from 1986 showed that Uranus vented a giant blob of gas into space. This pocket of ionized gas, a plasma structure called plasmoid, was 400 km across and 200 km long.According to NASA's news release, Uranus is special in that it spins almost on its side "like a pig on a spit roast," while the axis of its magnetic field is offset from the spin by 60 degrees. This gives the planet's magnetic field an odd wobble that scientists cannot model.As solar winds blasted Uranus, the bombardment pinched gas off from the far end of the field. The resulting leak was then accidentally discovered by NASA researchers who were reviewing the old magnetic data.In the new research, scientists dialed up the reading's resolution to make a data point every two seconds. They spotted a blip in the readings that indicated the planet was making a plasmoid.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Voyager 2 flew past Uranus in 1986 just as the planet was venting a plasmoid 2. Uranus spins sideways and has a magnetic field axis 60 offset degrees from spin 3. Solar winds blow planetary magnetic fields backward and pinch off gas on the far side4. Researchers accidentally discovered the plasmoid when revisiting Voyager 2 dataVOICEOVER (in English): "Writing in the Geophysical Research Letters, NASA says a review of Voyager 2's old data from 1986 showed that Uranus vented a giant blob of gas into space." "This pocket of ionized gas, a plasma structure called plasmoid, was 400 km across and 200 km long.""According to NASA's news release, Uranus is special in that it spins almost on its side 'like a pig on a spit roast,' while the axis of its magnetic field is offset from the spin by 60 degrees.""This gives the planet's magnetic field an odd wobble that scientists cannot model.""As solar winds blasted Uranus, the bombardment pinched gas off from the far end of the field.""The resulting leak was then accidentally discovered by NASA researchers who were reviewing the old magnetic data.""In the new research, scientists dialed up the reading's resolution to make a data point every two seconds." "They spotted a blip in the readings that indicated the planet was making a plasmoid."SOURCES: Geophysical Research Letters, NASAhttps://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1029/2019GL083909https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2020/revisiting-decades-old-voyager-2-data-scientists-find-one-more-secret/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/20/3988678/3988678_71122BF597EB40A392F601C3271E01E1_200420_3988678_Uranus_s_ionized_gas_leak_seen_for_the_first_tim_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Uranus, gas leak, gas vent, plasmoid, plasma, plasma structure, ionized gas, atmosphere, magnetic field, magnetosphere, solar winds, Voyager 2, NASA, space, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989548</guid>
      <title>SpaceX set to launch astronauts to the International Space Station on May 27: NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. will send two astronauts to the International Space Station on a SpaceX rocketship from U.S. soil after an 11 year hiatus, according to NASA, NASA will launch two astronauts to the International Space Station from Florida's Kennedy Space Center, according to the New York Times.Citing a tweet by NASA Administer Jim Bridenstine, the New York Times reports a Falcon 9 rocket will be utilized for the mission scheduled May 27.The Falcon 9 rocketship features a reusable second stage with nine Merlin engines.The New York Times reports NASA's Douglas Hurley and Robert Behnken will pilot the ship from the Dragon spacecraft mounted atop the first stage that will push the capsule to orbit.The reusable first stage has one Merlin engine and it is capable of reactivating multiple times during the flight to orbit, according to SpaceX.The Dragon spacecraft will jettison the first stage and fairings before unfurling its solar array, according to NASA.The Dragon spacecraft has completed multiple supply missions to the ISS and completed its most recent run in March.According to Space.com, Demo-2 will be the first mission for Dragon to dock itself, instead of relying on robotic arm capture.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Demo-2 mission to the ISS scheduled for launch from Kennedy Space Center2. SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket's reusable first stage3. Space X Flacon 9's unusual second stage4. Dragon spacecraft to self-dock with the ISSVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA will launch two astronauts to the International Space Station from Florida's Kennedy Space Center, according to the New York Times.""Citing a tweet by NASA Administer Jim Bridenstine, the Times reports a Falcon 9 rocket will be utilized for the mission scheduled May 27.""The Falcon 9 rocketship features a reusable second stage with nine Merlin engines." "The New York Times reports NASA's Douglas Hurley and Robert Behnken will pilot the ship from the Dragon spacecraft mounted atop the first stage that will push the capsule to orbit.""According to SpaceX, the reusable first stage has one Merlin engine and it is capable of reactivating multiple times during the flight to orbit." "According to NASA, the Dragon spacecraft will jettison the first stage and fairings before unfurling its solar array.""The Dragon spacecraft has completed multiple supply missions to the ISS and completed its most recent run in March.""According to Space.com, Demo-2 will be the first mission for Dragon to dock itself, instead of relying on robotic arm capture."SOURCES: New York Times, Space.com, SpaceX (Twitter)https://www.nytimes.com/2020/04/17/science/spacex-nasa-crew-dragon.htmlhttps://www.space.com/spacex-crew-dragon-nasa-astronauts-demo-2-launch-date.html https://www.space.com/spacex-dragon-space-station-arrival-crs-20.htmlhttps://twitter.com/spacex/status/585875717000310784***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 10:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/22/3989548/3989548_F296A86EE77F486EA4979A986E873775_200422_3989548_SpaceX_set_to_launch_astronauts_to_the_Internati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, SpaceX, Demo-2, Falcon 9, International Space Station, ISS, Dragon spacecraft, first stage, second stage, reusable, solar arrays,  Douglas Hurley, Robert Behnken, space, science, technology, Kennedy Space Center, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989499</guid>
      <title>Death toll from Canada mass shooting rises to 19: police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Royal Canadian Mounted Police say the death toll from the Nova Scotia mass shooting that occurred from Saturday to Sunday has risen to 19.Citing the Royal Canadian Mounted Police, the National Post reports that 51-year-old suspect Gabriel Wortman had masqueraded as a police constable and utilized various firearms in the killing spree.The police did not disclose the type of weapons used.The 12-hour rampage started in the rural town of Portapique on Saturday evening. Wortman initially drove a detailed replica of a mounted police cruiser.The suspect committed murders at no fewer than 16 locations before being cornered and shot dead by police at a gas station near Halifax. By that time, he had obtained another silver SUV via unknown means.As multiple buildings and cars were set ablaze, possibly by Wortman, the RMCP say they are still recovering and counting the dead.The police say the crimes "appear to be, at least in part, very random in nature," but added that Wortman did have a connection with some victims.Constable Heidi Stevenson, a 23-year veteran of the Nova Scotia RCMP; elementary school teacher Lisa McCully; and the suspect Wortman were among the 19 slain, a number the police say will almost certainly increase. RCMP Constable Chad Morrison was shot in a confrontation with the suspect but he is currently recovering at home.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mass shooting suspect impersonated a police officer and used various firearms 2. Suspect drove a replica police cruiser and at least one other vehicle3. Buildings and cars were set ablaze by shooter4. Death toll is likely to increase VOICEOVER (in English): "Citing the Royal Canadian Mounted Police, the National Post reports that 51-year-old suspect Gabriel Wortman had masqueraded as a police constable and utilized various firearms in the killing spree." "The police did not disclose the type of weapons used.""The 12-hour rampage started in the rural town of Portapique on Saturday evening. Wortman initially drove a detailed replica of a mounted police cruiser." "The suspect committed murders at no fewer than 16 locations before being cornered and shot dead by police at a gas station near Halifax. By that time, he had obtained another silver SUV via unknown means.""As multiple buildings and cars were set ablaze, possibly by Wortman, the RMCP say they are still recovering and counting the dead.""The police say the crimes, quote, 'appear to be, at least in part, very random in nature,' but added that Wortman did have a connection with some victims." "Constable Heidi Stevenson, a 23-year veteran of the Nova Scotia RCMP; elementary school teacher Lisa McCully; and the suspect Wortman were among the 19 slain, a number the police say will almost certainly increase." "RCMP Constable Chad Morrison was shot in a confrontation with the suspect but he is currently recovering at home."SOURCES: National Post, Globe and Mail, Washington Post, BBChttps://nationalpost.com/news/canada/nova-scotia-shooting-victims-what-we-know-about-those-killed-in-the-worst-mass-shooting-in-canadian-historyhttps://nationalpost.com/news/canada/nova-scotia-shooting-rcmphttps://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-senseless-tragedy-at-least-18-dead-in-nova-scotia-shooting-rampage/https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/the_americas/nova-scotia-shootings-trudeau-gun-control-wortman-rcmp/2020/04/20/dbc54d40-829e-11ea-81a3-9690c9881111_story.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-52346447***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 08:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/22/3989499/3989499_1FBADD627E5341CB98594F313F52D69B_200422_3989499_Death_toll_from_Canada_mass_shooting_rises_to_19_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Canada mass shooting, Canada shooting, Nova Scotia mass shooting, Nova Scotia shooting, Royal Canadian Mounted Police, worst mass shootings in Canadian history]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989348</guid>
      <title>American black and brown minorities worst hit during coronavirus pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMinorities in the United States are being disproportionately affected by the spread of coronavirus due to economic disparities and lack of data collection.According to Politico, black and brown American communities are being heavily affected by the spread of coronavirus in the U.S. In addition, not enough information on the spread in these communities is being collected, affecting efforts to ameliorate the situation.Five Florida counties stated that African American and Latino patients infected with coronavirus are being hospitalized and, at times, dying at faster rates than white patients.According to a statement from Louisiana Governor John Bel Edwards, a little more than 70 percent of COVID-19 deaths in the state were from African American patients.However, not all information related to the testing and treatment of these minorities is being released, making it difficult for authorities to provide proper help to curtail the spread of the virus in these communities.Fewer individuals belonging to these groups have access to health insurance, further exacerbating the lack of information.Data collected by doctors at the universities of Virginia and Pittsburgh, in collaboration with data-tracking firm Rubix, indicate that although thousands of individuals belonging to these minorities presented symptoms of coronavirus, they were not receiving testing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lack of information of COVID-19 infections among minorities2. Minorities affected in Florida and Louisiana3. Lack of data regarding effect of coronavirus on minorities4. Minorities presenting symptoms are not being testedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Politico, black and brown American communities are being heavily affected by the spread of coronavirus in the U.S. On top of that, not enough information on the spread in these communities is being collected, affecting efforts to ameliorate the situation.""Five Floridian counties stated that African American and Latino patients infected with coronavirus are being hospitalized and, at times, even dying at faster rates than white patients.""According to a statement from Louisiana Governor John Bel Edwards, a little more than 70 percent of COVID-19 deaths in the state were from African American patients.""However, not all information related to the testing and treatment of these minorities is being released, making it difficult for authorities to provide proper help to curtail the spread of the virus in these communities.""Also, fewer individuals belonging to these groups have access to health insurance, further exacerbating the lack of information.""Moreover, data collected by doctors at the universities of Virginia and Pittsburgh, in collaboration with data-tracking firm Rubix, indicate that although thousands of individuals belonging to these minorities presented symptoms of coronavirus, they were not receiving testing."SOURCE: Politicohttps://www.politico.com/news/2020/04/20/minority-cases-coronavirus-197203https://www.politico.com/news/2020/04/06/coronavirus-demographics-170353  ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/22/3989348/3989348_9076408986F9493EB69FF46B590B4042_200422_3989348_American_black_and_brown_minorities_worst_hit_du_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Covid-19, coronavirus, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus and minorities, african american, latino,  african american people, african american communities, latino communities, latino people]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3990345</guid>
      <title>Inflammation in toes could be a symptom of coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmerican health professionals have observed a new potential coronavirus symptom that appears in the toes of those infected.According to USA Today, some health professionals treating COVID-19 have noticed purple and blue lesions on the toes of coronavirus patients. This symptom is now being referred to as 'COVID toes' and can often be observed in patients with severe flu or viral pneumonia.Ebbing Lautenbach, chief of infectious disease at the University of Pennsylvania's School of Medicine, told USA Today that the symptom could be an inflammatory reaction to an infection in an individual's feet, or a clot in the toes' blood vessels.Lautenbach said patients exhibiting this symptom tend to be children or young adults who are otherwise asymptomatic and would probably test negative for COVID-19 as the infection is in its early stages.However, Susan Wilcox, Massachusetts General Hospital's chief of critical care for the emergency department, told USA Today that she mostly observed 'COVID toes' in the most severe cases she was treating.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Close up of toe inflammation in patients' toes 2. Possible causes of toe inflammation3. Asymptomatic children with toe inflammation4. Hospitalized patient showing coronavirus symptomsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to USA Today, some health professionals treating COVID-19 have noticed purple and blue lesions on the toes of coronavirus patients. This symptom is now being referred to as 'COVID toes' and can often be observed in patients with severe flu or viral pneumonia.""Ebbing Lautenbach, chief of infectious disease at the University of Pennsylvania's School of Medicine, told USA Today that the symptom could be an inflammatory reaction to an infection in an individual's feet, or a clot in the toes' blood vessels.""Lautenbach said patients exhibiting this symptom tend to be children or young adults who are otherwise asymptomatic and would probably test negative for COVID-19 as the infection is in its early stages.""However, Susan Wilcox, Massachusetts General Hospital's chief of critical care for the emergency department, told USA Today that she mostly observed 'COVID toes' in the most severe cases she was treating."SOURCES: USA Todayhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/04/21/coronavirus-covid-toes-may-symptom-covid-19-young-people/2994930001/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 07:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/24/3990345/3990345_9B85BBBE7AD64DC5A05BA5EB20C92B38_200424_3990345_Inflammation_in_toes_could_be_a_symptom_of_coron_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Covid toes, coronavirus, covid19, covid 19, covid-19, symptoms of covid 19, symptoms of coronavirus, symptoms of covid-19, coronavirus animation, covid-19 animation, coronavirus update, SARS-CoV-2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3990278</guid>
      <title>Massive asteroid to pass near Earth on April 29</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA huge asteroid classified as "potentially hazardous" by NASA will streak past our planet on April 29, accordoing to NASA's Asteroid Watch.Asteroid 52768, also known as 1998 OR2, is estimated by NASA to be between 1.8 to 4.1 kilometers wide. It takes Asteroid 1998 OR2 three years and eight months to orbit our Sun. Its journey takes it near Jupiter at its furthest point, but just outside Earth's farthest distance from the Sun on its closest approach.On April 29 it will pass Earth at a distance that is more than 16 times the average distance between Earth and the Moon.According to NASA's Center for Near-Earth Object Studies, as of April 21, some 22,582 near-Earth objects had been discovered. The latest data on the center's website shows that 9,085 of these were 140 meters or larger in size, and 902 were estimated to be larger than one kilometer.By comparison, the Chicxulub asteroid that wiped out the dinosaurs is estimated to have been 11 to 81 kilometres in diameter.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Asteroid 1998 OR2 near Earth2. Estimated size of 1998 OR23. Orbit of 1998 OR24. Closest distance of 1998 OR2 to EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "A huge asteroid classified as 'potentially hazardous' by NASA is barreling toward Earth at speeds of 31,320 kilometers per hour and will streak past our planet on April 29.""Asteroid 52768, also known as 1998 OR2, is estimated by NASA to be between 1.8 to 4.1 kilometers wide. That makes it roughly the size of Midtown Manhattan.""It takes Asteroid 1998 OR2 three years and eight months to orbit our Sun. Its journey takes it near Jupiter at its furthest point, but just outside Earth's farthest distance from the Sun on its closest approach.""According to NASA's Asteroid Watch, on April 29 it will pass Earth at a distance that is more than 16 times the average distance between Earth and the Moon."SOURCES: NASA, NASA Asteroid Watch, NASA Center for Near-Earth Object Studies https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/asteroidwatch/https://twitter.com/AsteroidWatchhttps://www.nasa.gov/planetarydefense/did-you-knowhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/stats/totals.htmlhttps://www2.jpl.nasa.gov/sl9/back2.htmlhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/stats/size.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/five-years-after-the-chelyabinsk-meteor-nasa-leads-efforts-in-planetary-defense***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 05:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/24/3990278/3990278_C68C1AB9B9BF41D88273DF965847D015_200424_3990278_Massive_asteroid_to_pass_near_Earth_on_April_29_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991336</guid>
      <title>Oxford starts human trials on COVID-19 vaccine: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe University of Oxford has initiated human trials for the first COVID-19 vaccine in Europe, according to the BBC.Citing the university, BBC reports on April 23 that the experimental COVID-19 vaccine takes the coronavirus's genetic material and inserts the substance into adenoviruses that are responsible for the common cold.The cold viruses are weakened so that they cannot grow inside the human body after injection.The modified viruses should make the human cells produce the same spike proteins that stud the surface of the coronaviruses and teach the immune system to recognize COVID-19.When vaccine recipients actually encounter the coronavirus, their bodies' immune system would then be able to identify the threat and scramble antibodies and killer T cells to fight off the infection.At the time of report, two volunteers have received the shot, out of around 800 recruited for the first phase human trial.Citing the doctors, the BBC reports potential side effects include headache, fever and muscle pains a couple of days after the injection.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Experimental vaccine utilizes neutralized adenoviruses 2. Vaccine induces the body to produce coronavirus spike proteins3. The immune system learns to recognize and fight the coronavirus4. Potential side effects include headache, fever and muscle painsVOICEOVER (in English): "Citing the University of Oxford, the BBC reports on April 23 that the experimental COVID-19 vaccine takes the coronavirus's genetic material and inserts the substance into adenoviruses that are responsible for the common cold.""The cold viruses are weakened so that they cannot grow inside the human body after injection." "The modified viruses should make the human cells produce the same spike proteins that stud the surface of the coronaviruses and teach the immune system to recognize COVID-19.""When vaccine recipients actually encounter the coronavirus, their bodies' immune system would then be able to identify the threat and scramble antibodies and killer T cells to fight off the infection.""At the time of report, two volunteers have received the shot, out of around 800 recruited for the first phase human trial.""Citing the doctors, the BBC reports potential side effects include headache, fever and muscle pains a couple of days after the injection."SOURCES: BBChttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-52394485***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 10:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/27/3991336/3991336_D2F4729454C043658EBECCAC5663C7C1_200427_3991336_Oxford_starts_human_trials_on_COVID_19_vaccine___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, vaccine, human trials, first phase human trials, neutralized virus, common cold virus, common cold viruses, adenovirus, adenoviruses, genetic modification, recombinant vaccine, University of Oxford, U.K.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991522</guid>
      <title>Hot exoplanet atmosphere can vaporize metals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUsing the Extreme Precision Spectrometer, or EXPRES, a team of multinational scientists were able to look more closely into the environment of MASCARA-2 b, a large, scorching hot gaseous planet in our galaxy, Yale News reports.MASCARA-2 b is a gas giant twice the size of Jupiter located 140 parsecs, or 4.3 quadrillion kilometers, away from Earth.MASCARA-2 b is just 8 million kilometers away from its sun, making its atmosphere reach temperatures of more than 1726.6 degrees Celsius.Further observations using the EXPRES spectrogram indicate that the gas giant contains small quantities of gaseous iron, magnesium and chromium.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Scientist using EXPRES tool to observe MASCARA-2 b2. Distance between MASCARA-2 b and Earth3. Temperature on MASCARA-2 b4. Vaporized metals found on MASCARA-2 bVOICEOVER (in English): "Using the Extreme Precision Spectrometer, or EXPRES, a team of multinational scientists were able to look more closely into the environment of MASCARA-2 b, a large, scorching hot gaseous planet in our galaxy, Yale News reports.""MASCARA-2 b is a gas giant twice the size of Jupiter located 140 parsecs away from Earth  that's the equivalent of 4.3 quadrillion kilometers or 2.68 quadrillion miles.""MASCARA-2 b is just 8 million kilometers or 5 million miles away from its sun, making its atmosphere reach temperatures of more than 1726.6 degrees Celsius or 3,140 degrees Fahrenheit.""Further observations using the EXPRES spectrogram indicate that the gas giant contains small quantities of gaseous iron, magnesium and chromium."SOURCES: Yale Newshttps://news.yale.edu/2020/04/22/yales-expres-looks-skies-scorching-distant-planet***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/28/3991522/3991522_C0E3DA97974544028E2812757ACA1F33_200428_3991522_Hot_exoplanet_atmosphere_can_vaporize_metals_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, exoplanet, space weather, space research, weird weather, extreme weather, weird weather, extreme weather, MASCARA-2 b, mascara2b,  Extreme Precision Spectrometer, EXPRES]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992047</guid>
      <title>White House official says new research shows sunlight, humidity help kill coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDirect sunlight and high humidity can kill the coronavirus in minutes, according to new research announced on April 24 by a senior U.S. official in a press conference with President Donald Trump.A summary of research from the Department of Homeland Security found that when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity, the coronavirus' half-life, or rate of decay, was 18 hours on a nonporous surface. When humidity was raised to 80 percent, the halflife fell to six hours. When sunlight was added, the half-life dropped to just two minutes. When the virus was aerosolized in droplets that hang in the air, its half-life was one hour when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity. When sunlight was added to the equation, its half-life was only one-and-a-half minutes. The new research was announced to reporters at the White House by William Bryan, science and technology advisor to the Department of Homeland Security secretary.The study, which was carried out by the National Biodefense Analysis and Countermeasures Center in Maryland, has not yet been released for review and is still awaiting external evaluation.Bryan's summary of the research leaves many questions unanswered, such as the intensity and wavelength of the ultraviolet light used in the experiment.In a statement sent to CNN, the Illuminating Engineering Society, a non-profit industry group, said, "Ultraviolet disinfecting 'wands' or other ultraviolet products for residential use  as they are inadequately proven and unregulated  may pose a safety hazard and are unlikely to provide the protection expected."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of coronavirus2. Half-life of coronavirus on non-porous surfaces at 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity3. Coronavirus' half-life on non-porous surfaces when humidity is increased and sunlight is added4. Coronavirus' half-life in aerosols at 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity5. Coronavirus' half-life in aerosols when sunlight is addedVOICEOVER (in English): "Direct sunlight and high humidity can kill the coronavirus in minutes, according to new research announced on April 24 by a senior U.S. official.""A summary of research from the Department of Homeland Security found that when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit, or 21 to 24 degrees Celsius, with 20 percent humidity, the coronavirus' half-life, or rate of decay, was 18 hours on a nonporous surface.""When humidity was raised to 80 percent, the halflife fell to six hours. When sunlight was added, the half-life dropped to just two minutes.""When sunlight was added to the equation, its half-life was only one-and-a-half minutes." SOURCES: White House, NPR, New York Post, CNN, Reutershttps://www.whitehouse.gov/briefings-statements/remarks-president-trump-vice-president-pence-members-coronavirus-task-force-press-briefing-31/https://www.npr.org/2020/04/24/844562958/coronavirus-updates-president-signs-bill-clarifI have NT$1,000 in coupons for you for Labor Day. Please sign the form on my desk when you get the chance.ies-disinfectant-suggestionhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/04/25/health/uv-coronavirus-lamps/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-trump/sunlight-heat-and-humidity-weaken-coronavirus-u-s-official-says-idUSKCN2253SA***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 07:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/29/3992047/3992047_4E0BC24064D848EB9FDF847B9779EB68_200429_3992047_White_House_official_says_new_research_shows_sun_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus animation, Trump, covid-19 animation, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus, sunlight, Donald Trump, humidity, half-life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991937</guid>
      <title>White House official says new research shows sunlight, humidity help kill coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDirect sunlight and high humidity can kill the coronavirus in minutes, according to new research announced on April 24 by a senior U.S. official in a press conference with President Donald Trump.A summary of research from the Department of Homeland Security found that when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity, the coronavirus' half-life, or rate of decay, was 18 hours on a nonporous surface. When humidity was raised to 80 percent, the halflife fell to six hours. When sunlight was added, the half-life dropped to just two minutes. When the virus was aerosolized in droplets that hang in the air, its half-life was one hour when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity. When sunlight was added to the equation, its half-life was only one-and-a-half minutes. The new research was announced to reporters at the White House by William Bryan, science and technology advisor to the Department of Homeland Security secretary.The study, which was carried out by the National Biodefense Analysis and Countermeasures Center in Maryland, has not yet been released for review and is still awaiting external evaluation.Bryan's summary of the research leaves many questions unanswered, such as the intensity and wavelength of the ultraviolet light used in the experiment.In a statement sent to CNN, the Illuminating Engineering Society, a non-profit industry group, said, "Ultraviolet disinfecting 'wands' or other ultraviolet products for residential use  as they are inadequately proven and unregulated  may pose a safety hazard and are unlikely to provide the protection expected."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of coronavirus2. Half-life of coronavirus on non-porous surfaces at 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity3. Coronavirus' half-life on non-porous surfaces when humidity is increased and sunlight is added4. Coronavirus' half-life in aerosols at 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity5. Coronavirus' half-life in aerosols when sunlight is addedVOICEOVER (in English): "Direct sunlight and high humidity can kill the coronavirus in minutes, according to new research announced on April 24 by a senior U.S. official.""A summary of research from the Department of Homeland Security found that when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit, or 21 to 24 degrees Celsius, with 20 percent humidity, the coronavirus' half-life, or rate of decay, was 18 hours on a nonporous surface.""When humidity was raised to 80 percent, the halflife fell to six hours. When sunlight was added, the half-life dropped to just two minutes.""When sunlight was added to the equation, its half-life was only one-and-a-half minutes." SOURCES: White House, NPR, New York Post, CNN, Reutershttps://www.whitehouse.gov/briefings-statements/remarks-president-trump-vice-president-pence-members-coronavirus-task-force-press-briefing-31/https://www.npr.org/2020/04/24/844562958/coronavirus-updates-president-signs-bill-clarifI have NT$1,000 in coupons for you for Labor Day. Please sign the form on my desk when you get the chance.ies-disinfectant-suggestionhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/04/25/health/uv-coronavirus-lamps/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-trump/sunlight-heat-and-humidity-weaken-coronavirus-u-s-official-says-idUSKCN2253SA***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 02:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/29/3991937/3991937_820D8C0A69834F08BCBB356F4AD21CEC_200429_3991937_White_House_official_says_new_research_shows_sun_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus animation, Trump, covid-19 animation, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus, sunlight, Donald Trump, humidity, half-life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991919</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus threatens U.S. meat supply</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe spread of coronavirus among employees in meat factories is forcing several meat production plants in the U.S. to shut down.A report by the Associated Press explains that efforts from the meat industry in the United States to curtail the spread of the virus among their employees have resulted in slower meat production which will eventually result in less meat in the market and higher prices for the meat that is available.Pork production has been the most affected. According to the report, 15 of America's largest pork-packaging plants are responsible for 60 percent of all processed pork produced in the U.S.This means that when one shuts down, overall pork production is severely affected. As of last week, pork processing capacity has dropped 25 percent.The Associated Press reports the U.S. Department of Agriculture expects beef to rise in price by between one to two percent, poultry by 1.5 percent and pork between two and three percent.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fewer employees working on-site due to the coronavirus2. Pig industry most harshly affected3. Meats will see a slight increase in pricesVOICEOVER (in English): "A report by the Associated Press explains that efforts from the meat industry in the United States to curtail the spread of the virus among their employees have resulted in slower meat production which will eventually result in less meat in the market and higher prices for the meat that is available.""Pork production has been the most affected. According to the report, 15 of America's largest pork-packaging plants are responsible for 60 percent of all processed pork produced in the U.S." "This means that when one shuts down, overall pork production is severely affected. As of last week, pork processing capacity has dropped 25 percent.""The Associated Press reports the U.S. Department of Agriculture expects beef to rise in price by between one to two percent, poultry by 1.5 percent and pork between two and three percent."SOURCES: Associated Presshttps://apnews.com/cb9fd324e9e3276dd56075a78223b7bb***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 01:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/29/3991919/3991919_BCFD320E090D4B89A6419A35E86AFD58_200429_3991919_Coronavirus_threatens_U_S__meat_supply_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, united states, covid-19 in united states, meat production, meat industry]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992496</guid>
      <title>Migrating sea turtles find empty U.S. beaches, a rare chance to thrive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThousands of sea turtles are currently migrating to nesting grounds on beaches across the southeastern United States, just in time to enjoy a rare break from human interference as coronavirus lockdowns keep people indoors.Experts interviewed by CBS News expect sea turtles to thrive amid the lack of human activity and pollution as beaches are deserted thanks to stay-at-home orders. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sea turtle swimming in the ocean2. Beaches void of crowds and debris see increase in sea turtle nests3. Number of species of sea turtles, changes hatchling will live to adulthood4. Animals and human threats to sea turtlesVOICEOVER (in English): "Thousands of sea turtles are currently migrating to nesting grounds on beaches across the southeastern United States, just in time to enjoy a rare break from human interference as coronavirus lockdowns keep people indoors.""Experts interviewed by CBS News expect sea turtles to thrive amid the lack of human activity and pollution as beaches are deserted thanks to stay-at-home orders. CBS cited a University of Florida study conducted in 2016 which found that removing detritus from the beach can increase the number of nests by as much as 200 percent.""There are seven existing species of sea turtles. Nearly all are endangered, three of them critically. Out of every 1,000 hatchlings, only one survives to adulthood, CBS Miami reports, citing the Loggerhead Marinelife Center in Juno Beach Florida." "Sea turtle hatchlings are preyed on by dogs, seabirds, raccoons, crabs and fish, while adult sea turtles face numerous threats from humans, including microplastics, fishing gear, human development along the ocean, boat strikes, global warming, and trade in sea turtle shells and sea turtle eggs."SOURCES: CBS News, Miami Herald, University of Florida, WWFhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/sea-turtles-are-finally-thriving-now-that-people-are-stuck-indoors-2020-04-18/https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article242134506.htmlhttps://news.ufl.edu/articles/2016/05/study-proves-removing-beach-debris-increases-sea-turtle-nests.htmlhttps://www.worldwildlife.org/species/sea-turtlehttps://wwf.panda.org/knowledge_hub/endangered_species/marine_turtles/asian_marine_turtles/our_solutions/turtle_trade/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 04:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/30/3992496/3992496_5A383328E92246F099A5F902BA5C2784_200430_3992496_Migrating_sea_turtles_find_empty_U_S__beaches__a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sea turtles, environment, coronavirus, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992453</guid>
      <title>Ocean ecosystems changing due to shift in ocean currents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to research published in the journal Geophysical Research Letters, scientists have discovered significant changes in the Atlantic Ocean's ecosystem that might have been caused by shifts in ocean circulation.To examine changes in the ecosystem, researchers used a plastic tube to take samples from sediments in the ocean floor. Scientists then studied the fossil plankton available in newer and older sediments.Results show that changes in the ocean's water circulation have caused a decline in cold water plankton and a rise in warm water species in southern Iceland as the flow of warm water has overtaken cold waters.Scientists who participated in the study believe that these shifts have caused some fish species, such as mackerel, to travel northward.Results also showed that warm water is now reaching the Arctic. Scientists note that this could be aggravating the melting of sea ice there. The shift in the direction of the warm water currents could also affect key fisheries in the U.S. and Canada.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Atlantic Ocean circulation2. Extraction and examination of ocean sediments3. Reduction of cold water plankton and movement of mackerel fish4. Melting sea ice and impact on fisheriesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to research published in the journal Geophysical Research Letters, scientists have discovered significant changes in the Atlantic Ocean's ecosystem that might have been caused by shifts in ocean circulation.""In order to examine changes in the ecosystem, researchers used a plastic tube to take samples from sediments in the ocean floor. Scientists then studied the fossil plankton available in newer and older sediments.""Results show that changes in the ocean's water circulation have caused a decline in cold water plankton and a rise in warm water species in southern Iceland as the flow of warm water has overtaken cold waters.""Scientists who participated in the study believe that these shifts have led to some fish species, such as mackerel, to travel northward.""Results also showed that warm water is now reaching the Arctic. Scientists note that this could be aggravating the melting of sea ice there. The shift in the direction of the warm water currents could also affect key fisheries in the U.S. and Canada."SOURCES: Geophysical Research Letters, The Conversationhttps://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1029/2020GL087577https://theconversation.com/seabed-fossils-show-the-ocean-is-undergoing-a-change-not-seen-for-10-000-years-136804***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 01:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/04/30/3992453/3992453_1B844B25EB0E4FE0AA41CE813CC99B96_200430_3992453_Ocean_ecosystems_changing_due_to_shift_in_ocean__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, climate change, plankton, oceanography, paleoclimate, marine ecology, fossils, seabed fossils, atlantic ocean, ocean circulation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992818</guid>
      <title>Locust plague and coronavirus threaten food security in East Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEast African countries could be facing a food crisis as waves of locusts have hit crops in the region since the end of 2019, according to a report by the Globe and Mail. A third wave of the insects is expected to hatch and spread in June and July.Just one locust can travel 150 kilometers in 24 hours and is capable of eating its own weight in crops each day.A small swarm of locusts, which would be around 40 to 80 million, can cover about a square kilometer and eat the same amount of food consumed by 35,000 humans in a day.On top of crops being impacted by the waves of locust plagues, Stephanie Hanson, senior vice-president of One Acre Fund, told the Center for Strategic and International Studies that farmers' incomes have also been affected due to restrictions put in place during the pandemic, which limit their capacity to sell food in local markets.The pandemic has also made it difficult for farmers to get rid of the locusts. Hanson noted that pilots in Kenya who fly pesticide aircraft are required to land at local airports before the national curfew is lifted.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Swarm of desert locusts in East African farmland2. Amount of damage locusts can make in crops3. Local farmers affected due to virus4. Regulations put in place due to the coronavirus affecting fight against locust plagueVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report by the Globe and Mail, East African countries could be facing a food crisis as waves of locusts have hit crops in the region since the end of 2019. A third wave of the insects is expected to hatch and spread in June and July.""Just one locust can travel 150 kilometers in 24 hours and is capable of eating its own weight in crops each day.""A small swarm of locusts, which would be around 40 to 80 million, can cover about a square kilometer and eat the same amount of food consumed by 35,000 humans in a day.""On top of crops being impacted by the waves of locust plagues, Stephanie Hanson, senior vice-president of One Acre Fund, told the Center for Strategic and International Studies that farmers' incomes have also been affected due to restrictions put in place during the pandemic, which limit their capacity to sell food in local markets.""The pandemic has also made it difficult for farmers to get rid of the locusts. Hanson noted that pilots in Kenya who fly pesticide aircraft are required to land at local airports before the national curfew is lifted."SOURCES: The Globe and Mail, Deutsche Welle, The New Humanitarianhttps://www.theglobeandmail.com/world/article-second-wave-of-locusts-causing-havoc-in-east-africa/https://www.dw.com/en/severe-hunger-threatens-africa-during-covid-19-lockdowns/a-53212565https://www.thenewhumanitarian.org/feature/2020/04/28/locusts-Africa-Kenya-Uganda-Ethiopia-Somalia***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 02:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/05/01/3992818/3992818_69F6EF169E6C4955A59315EEAC06D40F_200501_3992818_Locust_plague_and_coronavirus_threaten_food_secu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coronavirus, east africa, food, environment, africa coronavirus, food and agriculture, coronavirus animation, east africa locusts, east africa locust plague, locust plague, food shortage, coronavirus curfew]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
