<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3431608</guid>
      <title>US-STORM-HARVEY-ARKEMA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEBlasts rocked a flooded Crosby, Texas chemical plant on Thursday.According to Reuters, 15 Harris County Sheriff's deputies had to be treated in hospital after investigating the explosions.The plant makes organic peroxides, a compound found in commonplace everyday household items. Some of these require refrigeration and if they aren't cooled, they can catch fire.Arkema Group, the facility owner, had been expecting a fire or explosion. Flooding from Hurricane Harvey had knocked out the facility's power and this meant its cooling systems weren't refrigerating volatile substances. Prior to the explosion on Thursday, the company told the Texan Tribune there wouldn't be any long term impact and that environmental damage would be minimal.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of area impacted by plant and explosion2. Depiction of flooding3. Chemical compound made by plantVOICEOVER (in English): "Fears of an explosion at a storm ravaged Crosby, Texas chemical facility prompted evacuation of 300 people from the area surrounding it earlier this week.""Blasts were heard at the facility on Thursday.""The Arkema group anticipated an explosion after flooding from Hurricane Harvey had cut power to their chemical cooling and emergency systems.""The chemical plant makes organic peroxides, a compound found in commonplace everyday items. "Some of the substances are volatile and will catch fire if they aren't refrigerated."SOURCES: Reuters, Chron.com, Arkema Americas, NBC News, Texas Tribune https://www.reuters.com/article/us-storm-harvey-arkema-idUSKCN1BA2LFhttp://www.chron.com/news/houston-texas/texas/article/New-explosions-expected-at-Crosby-chemical-plant-12163386.php#photo-14026137http://www.arkema-americas.com/en/social-responsibility/incident-page-2/https://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/hurricane-harvey/harvey-danger-major-chemical-plant-near-houston-likely-explode-facility-n797581https://www.texastribune.org/2017/08/30/crosby-chemical-plant-could-explode-due-harvey-flooding/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 05:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/01/3431608/3431608_85D6B28B5B244BBEB34669EE5471AD0E_170901_3431608_US_STORM_HARVEY_ARKEMA_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/107/9C1/1079C1B0AB3C43B89BC9798F72F7E509_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, chemical plant explosion, hurricane harvey, texas, flooding chemical plant, arkema group, crosby, texas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3431515</guid>
      <title>Pet turtles blamed for multistate Salmonella outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEPet turtles are blamed for causing an outbreak of human Salmonella infections in 13 U.S. states.Thirty-seven people from 13 states have been infected with Salmonella Agbeni linked with pet turtles. Sixteen people have been hospitalized but no deaths have been reported.According to the CDC, all turtles can carry Salmonella bacteria even if they look healthy and clean. The bacteria can even end up in the water they swim in.Kissing the pet turtles or place them near mouths can contaminate human bodies with the bacteria.The FDA has banned selling and distributing turtles with shells less than 4 inches long as pets since 1975. The CDC also recommends that households with young children should not keep turtles or reptiles as pets.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Salmonella outbreak in 13 states2. Turtle carry Salmonella bacteria; bacteria found in water3. Bacteria transmits from turtle to humanVOICEOVER (in English): "Thirty-seven people from 13 states have been infected with Salmonella Agbeni linked with pet turtles.""According to the CDC, all turtles can carry Salmonella bacteria even if they look healthy and clean. The bacteria can even end up in the water they swim in.""Kissing the pet turtles or place them near mouths can contaminate human bodies with the bacteria."SOURCES: CDC, Washington Posthttps://www.cdc.gov/salmonella/agbeni-08-17/index.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/animalia/wp/2017/08/30/why-your-adorable-pet-turtle-may-make-your-child-sick/?utm_term=.9fc00220ff20***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/01/3431515/3431515_3CB47EC74DAB4B459F3FF2051578E13D_170901_3431515_Pet_turtles_blamed_for_multistate_Salmonella_out_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0A2/E5C/0A2E5CDA396540A8B4D183AC0B5A3669_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, salmonella outbreak, pet turtles salmonella, salmonella bacteria, multistate salmonella outbreak, health, cdc warning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3433753</guid>
      <title>Firefighters battle largest Los Angeles fire in history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEGovernor Jerry Brown declared a state of emergency in Los Angeles County on Sunday as firefighters continued to battle a 5,900-acre brush fire north of downtown Los Angeles. The fire, which began on Friday, has forced people out of their homes and shut down an interstate, CNN reported. The declaration will make sure state and federal assistance will be provided as fast as possible, according to the L.A. Times. Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti already said the blaze was the biggest in the city's history in terms of acreage, the L.A. Times reported.  Garcetti said on Saturday that 300 homes in Burbank and 180 houses in Los Angeles received evacuation orders, according to CNN. So far the fire has destroyed three homes in Tujunga, while two firefighters had to be taken to the hospital for dehydration. The blaze was only 15% contained by Sunday, with more than 1,000 firefighters now on scene.There are 206 fire engines and nine helicopters dedicated to battling the blaze, Los Angeles Fire Department Chief Ralph Terrazas said at a Sunday press conference, according to CNN.The blaze is believed to have been started by fireworks, according to the California Department of Forestry and Fire Protection. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Firefighters battling fire by freeway2. 25% of the fire is contained, with over 1,000 firefighters on scene3. Over 200 fire engines and nine helicopters have been deployed4. 300 homes evacuated in Burbank, 180 homes in L.A., 3 homes destroyed and 2 firefighters treated for dehydrationVOICEOVER (in English): "Governor Jerry Brown declared a state of emergency in Los Angeles County on Sunday as firefighters continued to battle a 5,900-acre brush fire near Burbank." "The blaze was 25% contained by Sunday night, with more than 1,000 firefighters from across California currently on scene.""According to the L.A. fire chief, there are over 200 fire engines and nine helicopters dedicated to battling the fire.""Three hundred homes in Burbank and 180 homes in Los Angeles received evacuation orders. Three houses have been destroyed by fire, while two firefighters have been treated for dehydration."  SOURCES: CNN, L.A. Timeshttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/02/us/los-angeles-wildfire/index.htmlhttp://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-wildfire-los-angeles-20170903-story.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/04/3433753/3433753_05C8CB27C3554F2A8C662E25CB4CB794_170904_3433753_Firefighters_battle_largest_Los_Angeles_fire_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AC3/5BC/AC35BC17347D45AFA01DD81F491E51E3_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Los Angeles, Los Angeles brush fire, Los Angeles La Tuna brush fire, La Tuna Brush fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3433616</guid>
      <title>North Korea conducts most powerful nuclear test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENorth Korea conducted its sixth and most powerful nuclear test at the underground Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility on Sunday.According to the U.S. Geological Survey, the underground explosion resulted in a 6.3 magnitude earthquake. Estimates put its explosive yield at 120 kilotons, reported 38 North.There is speculation this weekend's test bomb will form the warhead component of the Hwasong-14, North Korea's inter-continental ballistic missile. This ICBM can reportedly hit Alaska.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of underground nuclear test at Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility2. Depiction of earthquake on world map from Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility3. Comparison of N Korea test bomb against the Hirisohima Little Boy bom, and B61-12. 4. Range of N Korea's Hwasong 14 ICBM.VOICEOVER (in English): "On Sunday September 3, North Korea conducted its sixth and most powerful nuclear test at the underground Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility.""According to the U.S. Geological Survey, the underground explosion resulted in a 6.3 magnitude earthquake. Estimates put its explosive yield at 120 kilotons.""For comparison, the Little Boy bomb dropped on Hiroshima in 1945 had a yield of 15 kilotons.""The recent North Korean test was eight times stronger than that.""But it's just over a third of the power of the recently tested U.S. remote controlled nuclear bomb, the B61-12. That holds a maximum yield of 340 kilotons.""There is speculation this weekend's test bomb will form the warhead component of the Hwasong-14, North Korea's inter-continental ballistic missile.""This ICBM can reportedly hit Alaska."SOURCES: 38 North, U.S. Geological Survey, CNN, JamesMartinCNS / Sketchfab, Twitter @ISNJHhttp://www.38north.org/2017/09/nuke090317/https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us2000aert#executivehttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/03/asia/north-korea-nuclear-test-explainer/index.htmlhttps://sketchfab.com/models/f12664b12b4e43bab9460d141055fb1bhttps://twitter.com/ISNJH***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 07:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/04/3433616/3433616_A433572733BD4AF39F95A4287AB9DD27_170904_3433616_North_Korea_conducts_most_powerful_nuclear_test_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/650/390/650390D7D40D497CB627453350BCFA0C_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, North korea missile test latest, hwasong 14, dprk, kim jong un, north korea nuclear missile, n korea explained, missile test, donald trump]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3433578</guid>
      <title>'Selfie' app designed to detect signs of pancreatic cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers at the University of Washington have developed a smartphone app that could detect the early signs of pancreatic cancer by analyzing users' selfies.Bilirubin is a bile pigment produced when the liver breaks down old red blood cells. One of the symptoms of pancreatic cancer is jaundice, caused by an accumulation of bilirubin in the body."The eyes are a really interesting gateway into the body -- tears can tell you how much glucose you have, sclera can tell you how much bilirubin is in your blood," Shwetak Patel, senior author of the study and a professor in computer science and engineering at the University of Washington said in a statement quoted by Medical Daily.The BiliScreen app is used in conjunction with a 3D printed box that controls light exposure for the eye, or with paper glasses that helps calibrate color.After the user has taken a selfie, the app's computer vision algorithms and machine learning tools can spot even the slightest increase in bilirubin levels in the sclera.The app is designed to help people get early treatment if needed, however it cannot replace a blood test.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bilirubin found in bile2. Jaundice and pancreatic cancer 3. App uses with 3D printed box or paper glasses; user takes selfie4. App shows bilirubin levels in the scleraVOICEOVER (in English): "Bilirubin is a bile pigment produced when the liver breaks down old red blood cells.""One of the symptoms of pancreatic cancer is jaundice, caused by an accumulation of bilirubin in the body.""The BiliScreen app is used in conjunction with a 3D printed box that controls light exposure for the eye, or with paper glasses that helps calibrate color.""After the user has taken a selfie, the app's computer vision algorithms and machine learning tools can spot even the slightest increase in bilirubin levels in the sclera."SOURCES: University of Washington, Medical Dailyhttps://ubicomplab.cs.washington.edu/publications/biliscreen/http://www.medicaldaily.com/selfie-app-detects-pancreatic-cancer-measuring-bilirubin-levels-eyes-421801***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 06:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/04/3433578/3433578_5AAD60F358D9486C807BB1FA1538B992_170904_3433578__Selfie__app_designed_to_detect_signs_of_pancrea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/774/FB4/774FB47F7E8D45C89F0EF7763C8F7A7D_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, biliscreen app selfie, selfie app detects pancreatic cancer, medical app, pancreatic cancer, cancer treatment, cancer screening, cancer detection app, medical, university of washington]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3434484</guid>
      <title>Burnout spectators scorched after car ignites gasoline</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEOver a dozen people were seriously wounded after a car ignited fuel during a burnout competition in Adelaide, Australia on Sunday.Friction from the tyres ignited the fuel, causing fire to spew from the wheels. According to Australian newspaper The Gold Coast Bulletin, 14 people were hospitalized. One person was critically wounded, according to Adelaide newspaper the Advertiser.Organisers of the Red CentreNats competition stopped the event immediately after the incident. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of how to perform a burnout maneuver2. Depiction of smoke resulting from tyre after burnout maneuver3. Depiction of car about to perform burnout maneuver near spectators4. Depiction of car igniting gasoline near spectatorsVOICEOVER (in English): "To perform a burnout, drivers typically first engage the handbrake to lock the wheels and then push on the gas to accelerate.""The wheel rotates at speed in a stationary position. The friction from the ground warms they tyre, creating smoke.""Over a dozen spectators were injured at a car competition in Australia at the weekend, when a vehicle performed a burnout over fuel on the track.""Friction from the tyres ignited the fuel, causing fire to spew from the wheels. One person was critically injured, while others received serious burns."SOURCES: Gold Coast Bulletin, Facebook / Fk The Epa (Video of incident), CNN, Adelaide Now, http://www.goldcoastbulletin.com.au/news/national/no-way-for-spectators-to-escape-fire/news-story/df46bbe578cf283e8840a4d07fb00948https://m.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=691864584341317&id=261131674081279http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/news/south-australia/monday-pulse-two-men-airlifted-to-adelaide-after-nt-drag-race-burnout/news-story/a655865a19c068ed03ff51738e2f39d1http://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/04/asia/australia-car-race/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 09:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/05/3434484/3434484_BB35325BBE0E492C8CE4916233352452_170905_3434484_Burnout_spectators_scorched_after_car_ignites_ga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CCB/356/CCB356BF0CAB491A89496414C565A23D_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ...]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3434477</guid>
      <title>Intermediate-mass black hole may be hiding in the Milky Way</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew evidence has been found backing the existence of a mid-sized black hole, which was long-theorized to be the middle ground between single star black holes, and supermassive ones found in galaxy centers.According to a the National Astronomical Observatory of Japan, a team led by Keio University professor Tomoharu Oka discovered a peculiar gas cloud called CO-0.40-0.22 near the center of the Milky Way that contained gas moving at vastly different velocities.This, along with faint radio waves coming from the center of the cloud, suggest the presence of a black hole a hundred thousand times the mass of our Sun.The radio signals detected from the cloud are similar to those produced by Sagittarius A, the supermassive black hole at the center of our galaxy.The Japanese team hypothesized that the midsized or intermediate-mass black hole was formed from the core of a dwarf galaxy that had previously been absorbed into the Milky Way.Scientists have long believed that giant black holes grow, in part, from the merger of small ones. So the discovery is especially significant since it's the clearest evidence yet of a black hole mass in between the two size extremes.The team's findings have been published in the journal Nature Astronomy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Molecular gas cloud found near center of Milky Way2. Radio signals from center of cloud indicate intermediate-sized black hole3. Intermediate-sized black hole possibly formed from core of a dwarf galaxy absorbed by the Milky WayVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers in Japan discovered a peculiar gas cloud near the center of the Milky Way that contained gas that moved at vastly different velocities.""This, along with faint radio waves coming from the center of the cloud, suggest the presence of a black hole a hundred thousand times the mass of our Sun.""The Japanese team hypothesized that the mid-sized or intermediate-mass black hole was formed from the core of a dwarf galaxy that had previously been absorbed into the Milky Way."SOURCES: National Astronomical Observatory of Japan, Science, The Guardianhttps://www.nao.ac.jp/en/news/science/2016/20160115-nro.htmlhttp://www.sciencemag.org/news/2017/09/long-rumored-midsized-black-hole-may-be-hiding-out-milky-wayhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/sep/04/supermassive-black-hole-discovered-near-heart-of-the-milky-way***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 09:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/05/3434477/3434477_6463BC8B6FAF40BD93161AE169D76B04_170905_3434477_Intermediate_mass_black_hole_may_be_hiding_in_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/348/05C/34805C68042B4244A01BDC0463ECFA43_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, black hole, Milky way, midsize black hole, intermediate mass black hole, space, singularity, galaxy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3434314</guid>
      <title>The weapons in North Korea's arsenal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEExperts are assessing North Korea's military capabilities amid heightened tensions on the Korean peninsula following further ballistic missiles tests by Pyongyang.North Korea is believed to have more than 1,000 missiles of varying ranges, according to the Telegraph. Military service is mandatory in North Korea for men and women, and the army has more than a million troops.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korean missiles and potential range2. North Korean nuclear weapons capability3. North Korean chemical and biological weapons4. North Korean military and equipment5. North Korean cyber warfare capabilityVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Telegraph, North Korea is believed to have more than 1,000 missiles of varying ranges.""North Korea's short- and long-range missiles can strike South Korea and Japan. Washington says Pyongyang is also developing a missile that will be capable of reaching the continental United States.""North Korea is estimated to have enough plutonium to build as many as six nuclear bombs.""Experts say it will take North Korea up to 10 years to fit a nuclear warhead to a missile capable of reaching the U.S." "North Korea is believed to be able to make most kinds of chemical weapons. South Korea says the DPRK also has biological weapons, but it is unclear if they are ready for the battlefield.""Military service is mandatory in North Korea for men and women, and the army has more than a million troops.""The army relies on outdated Soviet tanks.""The navy has more than 70 submarines and three frigates.""Most North Korean air force planes are outdated Chinese fighter jets, although it does have a small number of more modern, Russian-built jets."  "The cyber warfare threat from North Korea is centered around an organisation called Bureau 121, which boasts up to 6,000 hackers. Most of its attacks are targeted at South Korea."SOURCES: The Telegraph, Council on Foreign Relationshttp://bit.ly/2wWmV8f http://on.cfr.org/2rVfKGp  ***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/05/3434314/3434314_C74A534D56C04DF8AA88CC543902248C_170905_3434314_The_weapons_in_North_Korea_s_arsenal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/443/56F/44356F1A223D43BB84721E4D292790BC_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kim jong un, north korea, north korea news, north korea missile, dprk, north korea military, north korea military power, north korea nuclear weapons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3434241</guid>
      <title>The aftermath of Hurricane Harvey</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEHurricane Harvey may have left Texas, but the damage it brought on Houston and other areas is still ever-present.USA Today reports that Harvey may be the most expensive natural disaster to hit the U.S., with damage estimated at $190 billion, or a 1% hit to the GNP.Gas prices have risen in the wake of Hurricane Harvey, as several oil refineries on the Gulf Coast were incapacitated by the storm.Texans also face significant health risks from contact with floodwaters, which are potentially contaminated with bacteria from compromised wastewater facilities, and chemicals from toxic Superfund sites, according to the Washington Post.Public water systems are likewise affected, and have rendered thousands of people with no access to safe drinking water. Residents are being advised to boil water before drinking, or to just use bottled water.Massive flooding in homes and businesses may also cause mold growth, which in turn may exacerbate existing health issues.Relief efforts are pouring in, but even so, the state's road to recovery looks to be long and slow, especially as floods in some parts of the state have yet to subside.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flooded oil refineries lead to high gas prices2. Floodwaters potentially contaminated with bacteria, toxic chemicals3. No access to safe drinking water4. Mold outbreak in flooded homesVOICEOVER (in English): "Gas prices have risen in the wake of Hurricane Harvey, as several oil refineries on the Gulf Coast were incapacitated by the storm.""Texans also face significant health risks from contact with floodwaters, which are potentially contaminated with bacteria from compromised wastewater facilities, and chemicals from toxic Superfund sites.""Public water systems are likewise affected, and have rendered thousands of people with no access to safe drinking water. Residents are being advised to boil water before drinking, or to just use bottled water.""Massive flooding in homes and businesses may also cause mold growth, which in turn may exacerbate existing health issues."SOURCES: Washington Post, CNN, New York Times, USA Todayhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-nation/wp/2017/09/03/trump-administration-wants-to-tie-harvey-recovery-aid-to-debt-ceiling-legislation/?utm_term=.f955fccdb3e8http://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/03/us/houston-texas-flood-aftermath/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/02/us/one-week-after-harvey-texas-residents-exhausted-still-stranded.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/weather/2017/08/30/harvey-costliest-natural-disaster-u-s-history-estimated-cost-160-billion/615708001/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 05:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/05/3434241/3434241_C7BB7F36257E4D1FB9A73AC6998E91A5_170905_3434241_The_aftermath_of_Hurricane_Harvey_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/762/061/7620610D187549BF983B39FE529F93A7_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hurricane harvey, hurricane, houston, texas, flood, flooding, floodwater, bacteria, toxic chemical, superfund, gas prices, mold, black mold, flood damage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3435174</guid>
      <title>How are hurricanes categorized?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAs Irma makes its way towards the eastern U.S., it has now been upgraded from a tropical storm to a Category 5 hurricane. Hurricanes are classified into five categories using the Saffir-Simpson scale, with the highest number representing the most powerful storm. Hurricanes are categorized based on wind speed. The wind speed is measured from an unobstructed area at a point 33 feet (10 meters) above the ground for one minute, according to the National Hurricane Center. The higher the category, the stronger the winds, and the more damage to be expected. Storms moving less than 38 mph are classified as a tropical depression, while those moving between 39 to 73 mph are considered tropical storms. In a Category 1 hurricane, wind speeds blow between 74 to 95 mph. Downed power lines, broken tree limbs, and minor home damage can be expected. With a Category 2 hurricane, wind speeds are between 96 to 110 mph. There can be "extensive damage" to houses and trees, while power outages can last for days or weeks. A Category 3 has wind speeds from 111 to 129 mph and the potential to cause "devastating damage" to roof decking and gable ends. In a Category 4 hurricane, wind speeds range from 130 to 156 mph and have the ability to cause "catastrophic damage," with the possibility of leaving areas uninhabitable for weeks to months. The last is a Category 5, which has wind speeds of 157 mph and over. During a Category 5, there's a "high percentage" that a home can be totally destroyed.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How wind speed in measured2. Damage caused by a Category 1 and Category 2 hurricane3. Damage caused by a Category 3 and Category 4 hurricane4. Damage caused by a Category 5 hurricane VOICEOVER (in English): "Hurricanes are classified into five categories based on wind speed. Wind speed is measured at a point 33 feet above the ground for one minute.""In a Category 1, wind speeds are between 74 to 95 mph with minor home damage to be expected. With a Category 2 hurricane, wind speeds are between 96 to 110 mph.""A Category 3 has wind speeds between 111 to 129 mph and has the potential to cause devastating damage. A Category 4 has wind speeds between 130 and 156 mph.""The last is a Category 5, which has wind speeds of 157 mph and over. During a Category 5, there's a high percentage homes can be totally destroyed." SOURCES: National Hurricane Centerhttp://www.nhc.noaa.gov/aboutsshws.phphttp://www.nhc.noaa.gov/pdf/sshws.pdf***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 07:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/06/3435174/3435174_79DE73339CBE4EBA8ED0C80634E507A9_170906_3435174_How_are_hurricanes_categorized__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A8/576/1A8576CAF0EB4822BBC01BC3AE5ACB3C_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hurricane Irma, hurricane categories, category 5 hurricane, hurricane categories explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3435121</guid>
      <title>Radio signals detected from distant galaxy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAstronomers last month reported detections of radio bursts from a far away galaxy.Writing in the Astronomer's Telegram, scientists reported 15 fast radio bursts detected from a dwarf galaxy some 3 billion light years from our own. Scientists suggest the bursts may have come from a magnetar, which is a rotating neutron star with a strong magnetic field. Researchers also speculate that the bursts may originate from alien laser technology used to propel and power spacecraft, like wind powers sails on a ship, according to a University of California, Berkeley news release. That theory is similar to Breakthrough Starshot, an initiative aimed at propelling nanocraft to Proxima Centauri with Earth-based lasers.Whatever they came from, researchers say that those signals began travelling from their galaxy over 10 billion years ago, when ours wasn't even 2 billion years old.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of dwarf galaxy and Milky Way2. Depiction of magnetar star3. Depiction of laser technology similar and Breakthrough Starshot4. Depiction of Alien radio signal VOICEOVER (in English): "Writing in the Astronomer's Telegram, scientists reported 15 fast radio bursts detected from a dwarf galaxy some 3 billion light years from our own.""Scientists suggest the bursts may have come from a magnetar, which is a rotating neutron star with a strong magnetic field.""Researchers also speculate that the bursts may originate from alien laser technology used to propel and power spacecraft, like wind powers sails on a ship .""That theory is similar to Breakthrough Starshot, an initiative aimed at propelling nanocraft to Proxima Centauri with Earth-based lasers.""Whatever they came from, researchers say that those signals began travelling from their galaxy over 10 billion years ago, when ours wasn't even 2 billion years old."  SOURCES: The Astronomer's Telegram, UC Berkeley, Geek Wirehttp://www.astronomerstelegram.org/?read=10675http://news.berkeley.edu/2017/08/30/distant-galaxy-sends-out-15-high-energy-radio-bursts/https://www.geekwire.com/2017/alien-hunting-breakthrough-listen-project-tracks-strange-series-15-radio-bursts/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 06:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/06/3435121/3435121_05BC0E826D4842E7907E1B25A1ED0583_170906_3435121_Radio_signals_detected_from_distant_galaxy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A07/103/A0710339235C49E8ABEE890D8E6B043C_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, alien radio broadcast, alien radio waves, alien life found, proxima centauri, laser technology, laser propulsion, alien technology, nanocraft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3435018</guid>
      <title>Japan planning for possible evacuation of 60,000 from South Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEJapan has started planning for a possible evacuation of the 60,000 Japanese citizens currently living in or visiting South Korea as tensions on the Korean Peninsula continue to rise. There are currently around 38,000 Japanese living in South Korea, while about 19,000 are tourists or short-term visitors, the Nikkei Asian Review reported. Tokyo is proposing four contingency plans: limit nonessential travel to South Korea, discourage all travel to South Korea, advise all Japanese to evacuate and encourage them to take shelter in place, according to the Nikkei Asian Review.In the event of smaller military skirmishes between the Koreas, Tokyo would discourage all travel to South Korea, while concurrently urging citizens to leave using commercial aircraft.   During a shelter in place scenario, Japan would need to work with Seoul. For example, if South Korean airports were taken out, the Japanese embassy would advise citizens to stay in place or seek safer shelter further south. South Korea has agreed to give Japanese in the country access to safes zones, such as designated subway stations, churches and shopping centers, a source told the Nikkei Asian Review. Tokyo has provided its citizens with over 900 such facilities. In the event flying is not an option, Japanese citizens could return by sea from the port city of Busan. Japan is currently in talks with the U.S. to have American forces transport evacuees to Busan.   In response to Pyongyang's sixth nuclear test, Japan and the U.S. are looking to increase economic pressure on North Korea through an oil embargo and other measures.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Japanese residents and tourists in South Korea being evacuated to Japan2. Japan has four contingency plans in place 3. Japanese nationals have access to 900 designated safe zones in South Korea4. Busan port could send Japanese citizens back by sea VOICEOVER (in English): "Tokyo is preparing four contingency plans in the event 60,000 Japanese citizens  38,000 residents and 19,000 tourists  need to be evacuated from South Korea because of conflicts with North Korea.""Depending on the severity of the situation, Japan plans to limit nonessential travel to South Korea, discourage all travel to South Korea, advise all Japanese to evacuate or encourage them to take shelter in place." "During a shelter-in-place scenario where airports are no longer an option, Seoul has agreed to give Japanese nationals access to over 900 designated safe zones." "Depending on the circumstances, Japanese citizens could also have to return by sea from the port city of Busan. Japan is currently in talks with the U.S. to have American forces transport evacuees to Busan."   SOURCES: Nikkei Asian Reviewhttps://asia.nikkei.com/Spotlight/Pyongyang-provocation/Japan-prepping-for-evacuation-of-tens-of-thousands-in-South-Korea***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 04:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/06/3435018/3435018_488ACD50AF89474DBD113D3AB84EDF16_170906_3435018_Japan_planning_for_possible_evacuation_of_60_000_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/00E/FDF/00EFDFA9BFAD4CFCAB59E0A008CEF85C_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, North Korea, Japan evacuation plans, South Korea, Japan South Korea evacuation plan, North Korea nuclear test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3436095</guid>
      <title>Facebook discovers Russia-funded misinformation campaign</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFacebook says that is has uncovered a Russian-funded campaign to spread divisive social and political messages over its network. The company said $100,000 was spent on around 3,000 ads over a two-year period that ended in May 2017, the BBC reported. The advertisements did not support any particular candidate, but focused on immigration, race and equal rights. The ads directed people to 470 accounts that were spreading false news or were in breach of company policies, Facebook said in a blog post.The accounts have all been shut down, according to Alex Stamos, Facebook's chief security officer. Facebook believes, though it cannot verify, that the accounts in question belonged to the Internet Research Agency, a pro-Russian group based in St. Petersburg. The campaign was discovered as part of Facebook's internal investigation after it was criticized for allowing the spread of fake news on the site in the lead up to the 2016 U.S. presidential election."We looked for ads that might have originated in Russia, even those with very weak signals of a connection and not associated with any known organized effort."This was a broad search, including, for instance, ads bought from accounts with U.S. IP addresses but with the language set to Russian  even though they didn't necessarily violate any policy or law."In this part of our review, we found approximately $50,000 in potentially related ad spending on roughly 2,200 ads."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Facebook discovering 3,000 ads in violation of company policy2. Ads directing users to 470 fake accounts3. Facebook using IP addresses and language settings to identify suspicious accounts 4. Ads focused on immigration, race and equal rightsVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook says around 3,000 ads worth $100,000 ran on their network over a two-year period, ending in May 2017, adding that the purpose of the ads were to spread divisive social and political messages." "The ads directed people to 470 accounts that were spreading false news or were in breach of company policies and have since been shut down.""As part of an internal investigation on how Facebook could have been used to influence the last U.S. election, the company found ads that were bought from U.S. IP addresses, but with their language set to Russian." "The advertisements did not support any particular candidate, but focused on immigration, race and equal rights." SOURCES: BBC, Facebookhttp://www.bbc.com/news/technology-41182519https://newsroom.fb.com/news/2017/09/information-operations-update/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 09:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/07/3436095/3436095_3A2436BCECF7458AABBD4158F084685A_170907_3436095_Facebook_discovers_Russia_funded_misinformation__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2E0/76C/2E076C49D51243009E7A755CB6D2A972_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Facebook, Russian hacking, Russia-funded misinformation campaign, Facebook ads, Facebook internal investigation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3436062</guid>
      <title>Rare disorder discovered after boy's heart stops while eating a hot dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA report in the medical journal Pediatric describes how a 9-year-old boy's heart stopped beating after he began eating a hot dog in Istanbul, Turkey.He was later resuscitated.Choking can lead to cardiac arrest in children, but in this case medical staff found the hotdog stimulated the boy's vagus nerve, which in turn triggered an abnormal rhythm that caused his heart to stop.Upon further investigation and an electrocardiogram, he was found to have a rare life-threatening heart rhythm condition known as Brugada Syndrome.The child was later implanted with a defibrillator to help regulate the abnormal heart rhythms via electrical impulses.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Child suffering heart stoppage after eating hot dog2. Stimulated vagus nerve signaling heart3. Brugada Syndrome electrocardiogram pattern 4. Implanted cardioverter defibrillatorVOICEOVER (in English): "A report in the medical journal Pediatric describes how a 9-year-old boy's heart stopped beating after he began eating a hot dog in Istanbul, Turkey.""He was later resuscitated.""Choking can lead to cardiac arrest in children, but in this case medical staff found the hotdog stimulated the boy's vagus nerve, which in turn triggered an abnormal rhythm that caused his heart to stop.""Upon further investigation and an electrocardiogram, he was found to have a rare life-threatening heart rhythm condition known as Brugada[a] Syndrome.""The child was later implanted with a defibrillator to help regulate the abnormal heart rhythms via electrical impulses."SOURCES: Pediatrics, CNN, Mayo Clinic http://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/early/2017/09/04/peds.2016-2485http://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/06/health/hot-dog-cardiac-arrest-brugada-syndrome/index.htmlhttp://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/brugada-syndrome/basics/definition/con-20034848***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 09:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/07/3436062/3436062_89C9D9DBFC424F06BF67682B5E9D2457_170907_3436062_Rare_disorder_discovered_after_boy_s_heart_stops_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E8C/70D/E8C70DE10A9142FC952B8AF0BFDE5497_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Brugada syndrome, hot dog stops heart, hot dog, cardiac arrest, heart stops beating]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3436051</guid>
      <title>83% of tap water around the world contaminated with plastic fibers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEPlastic has not only been polluting the seas and oceans, but also most of the world's tap water, according to a new study.According to an investigation by Orb Media, scientists tested water samples from a dozen countries on five different continents, and found that 83% contained microscopic plastic fibers.The U.S. had the highest contamination rate at 94%, while Europe fared better at 72%.The microscopic fragments are believed to be from clothes, plastic waste, tire dust, microbeads, and paint that have been flushed into water systems.Synthetic fibers shed from clothes and carpets have also been known to contaminate the air and eventually make it to waterways.Microplastics have been known to contain toxic chemicals, which could be released into the body when ingested.Many studies have explored the impact of microscopic plastic particles on marine life, but none so far have focused directly on human health.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 83% of the world's tap water found to have microscopic plastic fibers2. Plastic particles flushed into water systems 3. Synthetic fibers shed into the atmosphere4. Plastic fibers potentially dangerous when ingestedVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists tested water samples from a dozen countries on five different continents, and found that 83% contained microscopic plastic fibers.""The microscopic fragments are believed to be from clothes, plastic waste, tire dust, microbeads, and paint that have been flushed into water systems.""Synthetic fibers shed from clothes and carpets have also been known to contaminate the air and eventually make it to waterways.""Microplastics have been known to contain toxic chemicals, which could be released into the body when ingested."SOURCES: Orb Media, The Guardianhttps://orbmedia.org/stories/Invisibles_plastics/multimediahttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/sep/06/plastic-fibres-found-tap-water-around-world-study-reveals***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 09:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/07/3436051/3436051_FB5B4DAA8F1549FAA1A489A9123B8431_170907_3436051_83__of_tap_water_around_the_world_contaminated_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/38C/B24/38CB24688EE145E38B288A93D7B5A431_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, plastic pollution, tap water, contaminated water, contaminated tap water, microplastics, plastic fiber, microscopic plastics, plastic, pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3436008</guid>
      <title>Zika virus could help cure deadly brain cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Zika virus caused an epidemic of microcephaly in South America, but now scientists say it may be the key to defeating a deadly and hard-to-treat form of brain cancer.According to a press release from the Washington University School of Medicine, glioblastoma is an aggressive brain cancer typically treated using surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation. But cancer stem cells often survive the treatment, and go on to produce new tumors.The ability to create new cells is also seen in neuroprogenitor cells, which Zika targets and destroys. This prompted scientists to hypothesize that it may also be able to target glioblastoma stem cells.Scientists infected tumors with one of two Zika virus strains, and found that both destroyed stem cells while bypassing other tumor cells.Mice were then injected with either a saltwater placebo or Zika virus cells. Researchers found that those infected with Zika had smaller tumors two weeks later.Mutations were also introduced into the Zika cells as an additional safety feature, rendering them still able to destroy cancer stem cells, but also easier to eliminate from the host body.The findings indicate that Zika infection can be used to complement conventional treatment to eradicate the cancer. But though promising, the research still has a long way to go before it can be safely given the green light for human trials.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Standard treatment kills glioblastoma tumor but not stem cells; tumor recurs2. Zika virus targets neuroprogenitor cells, which work like cancer stem cells 3. Tumor infected with Zika; Zika killed cancer stem cells but avoided other tumor cells 4. Brain tumors shrunk in mice injected with Zika virus cells5. Scientists mutating Zika cells that will be easier for body's healthy cells to defeatVOICEOVER (in English): "Glioblastoma is typically treated using surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation. But cancer stem cells often survive the treatment, and go on to produce new tumors.""The ability to create new cells is also seen in neuroprogenitor cells, which Zika targets and destroys. This prompted scientists to hypothesize that it may also be able to target glioblastoma stem cells.""Scientists infected tumors with one of two Zika virus strains, and found that both destroyed stem cells while bypassing other tumor cells.""Mice were then injected with either a saltwater placebo or Zika virus cells. Researchers found that those infected with Zika had smaller tumors two weeks later.""Mutations were also introduced into the Zika cells as an additional safety feature, rendering them still able to destroy cancer stem cells, but also easier to eliminate from the host body."SOURCES: Washington University School of Medicine, UC San Diego Healthhttps://medicine.wustl.edu/news/zika-virus-kills-brain-cancer-stem-cells/https://health.ucsd.edu/news/releases/Pages/2017-09-05-zika-virus-targets-and-kills-glioblastoma.aspx***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 08:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/07/3436008/3436008_F85950137D21440DB53769FDAD80E2FC_170907_3436008_Zika_virus_could_help_cure_deadly_brain_cancer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8E1/E1B/8E1E1B9F8803455B961648A4B7C5891F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, glioblastoma, brain cancer, brain tumor, zika virus, cancer, cancer stem cells, tumor, cancer treatment, cancer cure]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3435979</guid>
      <title>Paper-thin Brane Craft to clean space debris</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA has awarded $500,000 for the development of an innovative new spacecraft that promises to get rid of orbital trash.According to a press release from the Aerospace Corporation, space debris in the form of spent rocket parts, old satellites, shrapnel and other items are accumulating around Earth's orbit, which may make collisions more common.To address this issue, NASA is looking to Aerospace's Brane Craft, a light, 3 foot-by-3 foot spacecraft that's thinner than human hair.When deployed, the Brane Craft moves toward a piece of debris and wraps itself around the item. It then fires its thrusters and pushes back toward the Earth.The spacecraft eventually lowers itself and the debris down to the atmosphere, where both are incinerated.The Brane Craft is intended to be light and cheap enough that it can be sacrificed at the end of a cleaning mission.But it may also have other applications beyond just collecting trash. The spacecraft is extremely fuel-efficient, making it fully capable of travelling long distances, perhaps to explore and mine asteroids or other space rocks.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Earth's orbit crowded with space debris 2. Brane Craft as thin as a strand of human hair3. Brane Craft wraps around space junk4. Brane Craft drags junk to be incinerated in Earth's atmosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "Space debris in the form of spent rocket parts, old satellites, shrapnel and other items are accumulating around Earth's orbit, which may make collisions more common.""To address this issue, NASA is looking to the Brane Craft, a light, 3 foot-by-3 foot spacecraft that's thinner than human hair.""When deployed, the Brane Craft moves toward a piece of debris and wraps itself around the item. It then fires its thrusters and pushes back toward Earth.""The spacecraft eventually lowers itself and the debris down to the atmosphere, where both are incinerated."SOURCES: Aerospace, NASAhttp://www.aerospace.org/news/highlights/brane-craft-proposal-wins-2017-nasa-innovative-advanced-concepts-phase-ii-award/https://www.nasa.gov/directorates/spacetech/niac/2017_Phase_I_Phase_II_Brane_Craft***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 08:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/07/3435979/3435979_8A9E7A1311BA47F48B4B16498BC81B06_170907_3435979_Paper_thin_Brane_Craft_to_clean_space_debris_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/371/3A4/3713A4A129CA40F9B9008E05225A4E35_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, brane craft, spacecraft, NASA, space junk, space debris, aerospace, space pollution, trash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3435717</guid>
      <title>What a military response against North Korea could look like</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA Washington Examiner commentary suggests that the U.S. would likely deploy large groups of its navy and air force to Japan, Okinawa and Guam.A Stratfor analyst told Business Insider that they they'd also possibly maneuver submarines and ships closer to the North and target nuclear facilities through airstrikes.Helicopter-deployed buoys would listen for North Korean submarines, which could be destroyed by more advanced American underwater craft.Experts also reckon that the U.S. would not invade, but rather defend South Korea as the North Korean army charges the border. This scenario would also see U.S. special forces parachuting into strategic locations around Pyongyang for surgical strikes.If, in the extremely unlikely scenario  North Korea hits Guam or another U.S. territory or ally  with a nuclear strike, the U.S. has the option to respond via land, sea or air. Most agree that the resulting American retaliation would lay waste to Pyongyang and kill thousands, if not millions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Potential American ship movements and air strikes on North Korea2. Depiction of underwater warfare between North Korea and the USA3. Depiction of ground force skirmishes 4. Scenario showing U.S. response to North Korean nuclear strike on Guam VOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. would likely deploy large groups of its navy and air force to Japan, Okinawa and Guam to bolster military presence there.""A Stratfor analyst told Business Insider that they they'd also possibly maneuver submarines and ships closer to the North and target nuclear facilities through airstrikes.""Helicopter-deployed buoys would listen for North Korean submarines, which could be destroyed by more advanced American underwater craft.""Experts reckon that the U.S. would not invade, but rather defend South Korea as the North Korean army charges the border.""This scenario would also see U.S. special forces parachuting into strategic locations around Pyongyang for surgical strikes.""If, in the extremely unlikely scenario  North Korea strikes Guam or another U.S. territory or ally  with a nuclear strike , the U.S. has the option to respond via land, sea or air.""Most agree that the resulting American retaliation would lay waste to Pyongyang and kill thousands, if not millions."SOURCES: Business Insider, Washington Examiner, National Interest, Global Security, CNNhttp://www.businessinsider.com/us-preemptive-strike-north-korea-2017-3/#first-a-decision-would-need-to-be-made-1http://www.globalsecurity.org/wmd/world/dprk/other_nuke.htmhttp://www.washingtonexaminer.com/how-would-the-us-retaliate-if-north-korea-attacked-guam/article/2631144http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/what-a-us-nuclear-strike-on-north-korea-would-look-like/article/2630856http://nationalinterest.org/blog/the-buzz/what-would-happen-if-north-korea-fired-nuclear-weapon-20205?page=showhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/04/politics/north-korea-nuclear-test-us-military-options/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 02:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/07/3435717/3435717_332F001316D841DC9AD68233CDDA1FAF_170907_3435717_What_a_military_response_against_North_Korea_cou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9CF/4BF/9CF4BF8D5FAE4EF3844C258A51E2C94B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dprk v usa, North korea, usa, kim jong un, donald trump, north korea usa who would win, south korea vs north korea, kim jong un vs donald trump, News]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3437099</guid>
      <title>Equifax data breach exposes personal data of 143 million U.S. consumers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENearly half of the United States has been impacted by a massive cyber security incident at one of the three largest credit agencies in the country.NBC reports that credit reporting agency Equifax has announced that it suffered a massive data breach which compromised the personal information of 143 million Americans.Stolen data included names, social security numbers, addresses, and birthdays. Credit card numbers of 209,000 consumers were also taken, along with the dispute documents of 182,000 others.These personal details may well be used to engage in fraud and identity theft schemes, which Equifax was ironically in the business of protecting people from.Hackers reportedly accessed the data in mid-May through a web vulnerability, and maintained access until July 29.The data breach extends beyond the U.S., with Equifax saying data from people in Canada and the UK may have also been exposed.Likewise, people who aren't customers of Equifax may also be affected, since the firm obtains information from credit card companies, banks, and other sources to determine a person's credit score.The company is currently cooperating with the FBI, which is investigating the incident. They're also working with an independent security firm for extra protection.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Equifax data breach exposed personal information of 143 million Americans2. Personal data, credit card numbers, dispute documents stolen3. Hackers accessed data from mid-May to July4. Equifax customers in Canada, UK potentially affectedVOICEOVER (in English): "Credit reporting agency Equifax has announced that it suffered a massive data breach which compromised the personal information of 143 million Americans.""Stolen data included names, social security numbers, addresses, and birthdays. Credit card numbers of 209,000 consumers were also taken, along with the dispute documents of 182,000 others.""Hackers reportedly accessed the data in mid-May through a web vulnerability, and maintained access until July 29.""The data breach extends beyond the U.S., with Equifax saying data from people in Canada and the UK may have also been exposed."SOURCES: NBC, CNBChttps://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/massive-equifax-data-breach-could-impact-half-u-s-population-n799686https://www.cnbc.com/2017/09/07/credit-reporting-firm-equifax-says-cybersecurity-incident-could-potentially-affect-143-million-us-consumers.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/08/3437099/3437099_4BE5176B2CB84BE784ABD1EF116F1419_170908_3437099_Equifax_data_breach_exposes_personal_data_of_143_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ED0/F4A/ED0F4AA0D9B84EADB9E01A846EA14D01_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, equifax, data breach, cyber theft, cyber security threat, cyber security, hackers, hacking, data leak, identity theft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3436865</guid>
      <title>Sun storm discharges strongest solar flare since 2006</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA massive storm over the sun on Wednesday discharged the strongest solar flare in ten years.The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration says the X9.3 flare caused high frequency radio blackouts and navigational issues over the sunlit part of Earth.According to NASA, solar flares take place when magnetic energy built up within the sun's atmosphere is suddenly released.They impact everything on the electromagnetic spectrum, from radio waves to X-rays.[a] The energy released is equivalent to millions of 100-megaton nuclear bombs exploding at the same time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Solar flare happening on sun.2. A closer look at the solar flare and how it impacted Earth3. Explanation of solar flares 4. Depiction of 100 megaton bomb explosion.VOICEOVER (in English): "A massive storm over the sun on Wednesday discharged the strongest solar flare in ten years.""The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration says the X9.3 flare caused high frequency radio blackouts and navigational issues over the sunlit part of Earth.""According to NASA, solar flares take place when magnetic energy built up within the sun's atmosphere is suddenly released.""They impact everything on the electromagnetic spectrum, from radio waves to X-rays.[b]""The energy released is equivalent to millions of 100-megaton nuclear bombs exploding at the same time."SOURCES: NOAA, SPACE, NATIONAL GEOGRAPHIC, NASAhttp://www.swpc.noaa.gov/news/r3-x13-flare-radio-blackout-observed-7-sep-1436-utchttps://www.space.com/38057-sun-unleashes-decades-strongest-solar-flare.htmlhttp://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/09/sun-solar-flare-strongest-auroras-space-science/https://hesperia.gsfc.nasa.gov/sftheory/frame1.htm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 08:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/08/3436865/3436865_F92488F1727949268778DB28410FB873_170908_3436865_Sun_storm_discharges_strongest_solar_flare_since_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A4/3F4/1A43F42A3E7645E9A4FB94CC8F7FF142_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, solar flare, x9 solar flare, solar flare radio effect, nasa, noaa, space weather]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3436784</guid>
      <title>How to prepare for a hurricane evacuation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAs Hurricane Irma makes its way toward the eastern U.S., residents have been preparing for the worst. In the event of an evacuation, here's what you can do to prepare, according to the New York Times.Before leaving the house, make sure to pack an emergency kit with money, medication, a portable radio, flashlights and at least three days' worth of food and water. Designate a meeting spot with your family in case you get separated. Mobile phones may or may not work in affected areas. Make sure to photograph or scan important documents such as licenses, social security cards, passports, prescriptions and tax statements. Upload images online, so that you have backup copies. Store the documents in fireproof, watertight containers or bring them with you. The Food and Drug Administration suggests turning your refrigerator to the coldest setting, so that if the power goes out, items can stay cold longer. Even with no power, a freezer can stay cold for about 48 hours. Double check that dangerous chemicals like bleach, ammonia and drain cleaners are securely stored. Move electronics and small appliances as high up as possible. And lastly, clear the yard and board up your windows. Move or dispose of anything that could become a projectile if left on the ground.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Items that should be included in emergency kits  2. Family meeting a designated point3. Important documents should be photographed and backed up4. Windows should be boarded up and the yard cleared of debrisVOICEOVER (in English): "In the event of an evacuation, here's what you can do to be prepared. Pack an emergency kit with money, medications, a portable radio, flashlights and at least three days' worth of food and water." "Designate a meeting spot with your family in case you get separated. Mobile phones may or may not work in affected areas." "Photograph or scan important documents such as licenses, social security cards, passports, prescriptions and tax statements. Upload images online. Store documents in fireproof, watertight containers or bring them with you.""Clear the yard and board up windows. Move or dispose of anything that could become a projectile if left on the ground." SOURCES: New York Timeshttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/07/climate/hurricane-irma-evacuation-tips.html?src=twr***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 07:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/08/3436784/3436784_C76F2197C3244081A8474A34444306E3_170908_3436784_How_to_prepare_for_a_hurricane_evacuation_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/83B/758/83B758C4E6C749A6B7E4F7C8B876031F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hurricane Irma, Hurricane Irma evacuations, evacuation preparation, emergency kit, hurricane evacuations]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3436758</guid>
      <title>Antarctic seabed life almost doubles in ocean warming experiment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA team of British and American scientists investigating the impact of ocean-warming found that the amount of Antarctic seabed life doubled after a temperature increase of 1 degree Celsius.Researchers placed heated panels on the seabed near the UK's Rothera Research Station on the Antarctic Peninsula, according to a press release from the British Antarctic Survey.The panels heated the water a few millimeters above them for a year, with researchers checking in and photographing the area periodically.Researchers found that the amount of sea life there had doubled after a rise of 1-degree Celsius.But after increase of 2 degrees Celsius, only certain species continued to grow. Encrusting bryozoan grew almost twice as fast under under the experimental warmer conditions.Results of the study were published in the journal, Current Biology.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of heaters underwater in Antarctica.2. Depiction of area heaters warmed3. Depiction of marine life growing4. Depiction of encrusting byrzoanVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists placed heated panels on the seabed near the UK's Rothera Research Station on the Antarctic Peninsula.""The panels heated the water a few millimeters above them for a year, with researchers checking in and photographing the area periodically" "Researchers found that the amount of sea life there had doubled after a rise of 1-degree Celsius.""But after increase of 2 degrees Celsius, only certain species continued to grow.""The encrusting bryozoan grew almost twice as fast under under the experimental warmer conditions."SOURCES: Current Biology, British Antarctic Surveyhttp://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(17)30952-1https://www.bas.ac.uk/media-post/antarctic-marine-life-may-grow-faster-in-a-warming-world/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 06:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/08/3436758/3436758_19D53529030E479480B0F1C99EC4B355_170908_3436758_Antarctic_seabed_life_almost_doubles_in_ocean_wa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D0A/4C4/D0A4C4BC8BB84B8B9AA383FB44B6A5AF_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, climate change, ocean warming, antarctica, global warming, marine life, biodiversity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3438925</guid>
      <title>U.S. 'nuke sniffer' aircraft used to measure radiation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe United States and Japan have both deployed "nuke sniffing" aircraft following North Korea's sixth and most powerful nuclear test.On September 3, the DPRK conducted a weapons test at the underground Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility, with the explosion resulting in a 6.3 magnitude earthquake.According to Stars and Stripes, a U.S. WC-135 Constant Phoenix was deployed from Offutt Air Force Base in Nebraska, landing at Okinawa's Kadena Air Base on September 5.Commonly referred to as a "nuke sniffer", the aircraft uses external flow-through devices to collect air particles on filter paper, measuring them onboard for radioactivity.The nuke sniffers are also equipped to collect whole air samples inside holding spheres, to be analyzed later on the ground.The North's nuclear test likewise prompted Japan to send three T-4 jets to collect dust and air samples for radiation testing.Japanese C-130 transport planes will also be checking for airborne radioactive gases, though the risk of the underground tests releasing toxic radiation is generally low, according to 9news.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korea underground nuclear test 2. US deploys WC-135 aircraft to Okinawa3. Air particles collected via filter tested for radioactivity onboard aircraft4. Whole air samples collected in holding spheres5. Japanese T-4 jets deployed to collect samples for radiation testingVOICEOVER (in English): "On September 3, the DPRK conducted a weapons test at the underground Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility, with the explosion resulting in a 6.3 magnitude earthquake.""A U.S. WC-135 Constant Phoenix was deployed from Offutt Air Force Base in Nebraska, landing at Okinawa's Kadena Air Base on September 5.""Commonly referred to as a 'nuke sniffer', the aircraft uses external flow-through devices to collect air particles on filter paper, measuring them onboard for radioactivity.""The nuke sniffers are also equipped to collect whole air samples inside holding spheres, to be analyzed later on the ground.""The North's nuclear test likewise prompted Japan to send three T-4 jets to collect dust and air samples for radiation testing."SOURCES: Stars and Stripes, Military.com, 9news, 38Northhttps://www.stripes.com/news/nuke-sniffer-ballistic-recon-aircraft-deploy-to-okinawa-amid-rising-tensions-with-n-korea-1.486700#.WbXrhoiGOUkhttp://www.military.com/equipment/wc-135-constant-phoenixhttp://www.9news.com.au/world/2017/09/04/08/52/japanese-jets-sweep-skies-on-search-for-deadly-north-korean-radioactive-materialhttp://www.38north.org/2017/09/punggye090517/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 09:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/11/3438925/3438925_A25C1DC8071B4292B5D9214C9DCD6165_170911_3438925_U_S___nuke_sniffer__aircraft_used_to_measure_rad_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D3A/D11/D3AD112BD64D4B9B8D76D29216A36DEA_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nuke sniffer, WC-135, WC135, constant phoenix, radioactive fallout, nuclear fallout, radioactive test, north korea, hydrogen bomb, nuclear testing, Kawasaki T4, T4 jet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3438796</guid>
      <title>What is a storm surge?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA storm surge is an enormous mound of water that accumulates and is pushed ashore by hurricane winds. It is one of the deadliest and most destructive threat from a hurricane, according to ABC News Storm surges are responsible for around half of hurricane deaths since 1970, according to the National Hurricane Center, USA Today reported. The National Weather Service only started issuing storm surge alerts this hurricane season. About 1,000 miles of coastline from Tampa Bay to parts of South Carolina could experience a storm surge. Forecasters warn of a 10- to 15-foot surge in the Naples area and 5 to 8 feet around Tampa, ABC News reported. Storm surge watches and warnings are not included with hurricane alerts because hurricane winds and storm surges don't always occur at the same place or same time, said Rick Knabb, former director of the hurricane center, USA Today reported. During a storm surge, people should evacuate, while for wind warnings, they can stay in place as long as the structures is stable and away from flood-risk areas, Knabb added. A "storm surge watch" is issued when there's a chance of flooding, while a "warning" is issued when flooding is expected. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How a storm surge is formed2. Forecasted levels of storm surge around Florida3. Storm surge watches and warnings are separate from hurricane warnings4. The difference between a storm surge watch and storm surge warningVOICEOVER (in English): "A storm surge is an enormous mound of water that accumulates and is pushed ashore by hurricane winds.""About 1,000 miles of coastline from Tampa Bay to parts of South Carolina could experience a storm surge. Forecasters warn of a 10- to 15-foot surge in the Naples area and 5 to 8 feet around Tampa."  "Storm surge watches and warnings are not included with hurricane alerts because hurricane winds and storm surges don't always occur at the same place or same time.""A 'storm surge watch' is issued when there's a chance of flooding, while a 'warning' is issued when flooding is expected." SOURCES: USA Today, ABC News***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 07:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/11/3438796/3438796_D085A07C58EF4AEB905823E5B9853B88_170911_3438796_What_is_a_storm_surge__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EFC/41B/EFC41BE257DB486BBA2C9017D2BE23CE_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hurricane Irma, storm surge, storm surge explainer, storm surge warning, storm surge watch]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3440112</guid>
      <title>Cities compete to host new Amazon HQ</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAmazon has announced it was looking to build a second headquarters in North America, setting up a bidding war amongst U.S. states and Canadian provinces.The online retailer will reportedly spend north of $5 billion on the project that could employ up to 50,000 people over two decades, reported the New York Times.Potential American cities for Amazon's so-called HQ2 include Los Angeles, San Francisco, Salt Lake City, Austin, Dallas, Denver, Detroit, Memphis, Atlanta, Baltimore, Boston, Washington D.C and  New York.In Canada, Toronto and Vancouver are speculated to be in the running as well.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Amazon's current HQ2. Amazon's plans for new HQ3. American cities in the running4. Canadian cities in runningVOICEOVER (in English): "Amazon has announced it was looking to build a second headquarters in North America, setting up a bidding war amongst U.S. states and Canadian provinces.""The online retailer will reportedly spend north of $5 billion on the project that could employ up to 50,000 people over two decades.""Potential American cities for Amazon's so-called HQ2 include Los Angeles, San Francisco, Salt Lake City, Austin, Dallas, Denver, Detroit, Memphis, Atlanta, Baltimore, Boston, Washington D.C and  New York.""North of the border, in Canada, Toronto and Vancouver are reportedly in the running as well."SOURCES: New York Times, Fort Worth Star-Telegramhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/07/technology/amazon-headquarters-north-america.html?referer=https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/09/09/upshot/where-should-amazon-new-headquarters-be.htmlhttp://www.star-telegram.com/news/business/article171867197.htmlhttp://www.star-telegram.com/news/business/article171726862.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 23:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/13/3440112/3440112_27CB099B9B3C411A852F39275FA8DB1D_170913_3440112_Cities_compete_to_host_new_Amazon_HQ_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B7D/431/B7D431EB798C494CAC1FE62B9A57E09C_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Amazon new headquarters, new amazon hq, amazon head quarters, News, amazon, jeff bezos, where is amazon new hq]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3439557</guid>
      <title>Hurricane Irma sets weather records</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEDespite recently being downgraded to a tropical storm, Hurricane Irma broke several meteorological records as it rampaged through the Caribbean and Florida.CNBC reports that Irma began as a tropical storm, but quickly strengthened to a hurricane in the middle of the Atlantic. It generated the most accumulated cyclone energy by a tropical cyclone ever recorded  more than 18 entire hurricane seasons since 1966.Irma clocked in 185 mile-per-hour winds for 37 hours, which is the longest time a tropical cyclone has maintained winds of that intensity.It was the strongest storm to hit the Leeward Islands, the first Category 5 hurricane to hit the Bahamas since 1992, and Cuba since 1924.It's also the first major hurricane to make landfall in Florida since Wilma in 2005.The hurricane prompted the largest evacuation in the Bahamas, with 5,000 leaving the islands. Some 6.3 million Floridians were also instructed to evacuate.With Irma and Harvey just days apart, 2017 also marks the first time the U.S. was hit by two category-4 hurricanes in one season. The combined cost of damage brought about by the storms may also be one of country's most expensive.Hopefully though, the worst is over, especially since experts say September 10 marks the peak of this year's Atlantic hurricane season.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hurricane Irma strengthened to massive 70,000 square mile hurricane in the Atlantic2. Hurricane Irma maintained 185mph winds for 37 hours3. Hurricane Irma prompted largest evacuation in Bahamas, Florida4. Damage from Hurricanes Irma and Harvey combined may be the US' most costlyVOICEOVER (in English): "Irma began as a tropical storm, but quickly strengthened to a hurricane in the middle of the Atlantic. It generated the most accumulated cyclone energy by a tropical cyclone ever recorded  more than 18 entire hurricane seasons since 1966.""Irma clocked in 185 mile-per-hour winds for 37 hours, which is the longest time a tropical cyclone has maintained winds of that intensity.""The hurricane prompted the largest evacuation in the Bahamas, with 5,000 leaving the islands. Some 6.3 million Floridians were also instructed to evacuate.""With Irma and Harvey just days apart, 2017 also marks the first time the U.S. was hit by two category-4 hurricanes in one season. The combined cost of damage brought about by the storms may also be one of country's most expensive."SOURCES: CNBC, The Telegraphhttps://www.cnbc.com/2017/09/11/here-are-some-of-the-records-hurricane-irma-set.htmlhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/11/hurricane-irma-numbers-records-storm-has-blown-away/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 08:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/12/3439557/3439557_2F4D2094B374412DA8E61F24DE7F44E2_170912_3439557_Hurricane_Irma_sets_weather_records_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/535/009/535009CEFB234739BF95FAACBB4EE337_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hurricane irma, irma, tropical storm, hurricane harvey, natural disaster, hurricane, florida, bahamas, caribbean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3439344</guid>
      <title>Blood clot risk linked to height</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETaller people might be at more risk of suffering a blood clot, according to new research.The Swedish study investigated multi-generational data from over 2.5 million siblings of varying heights. It was published in the journal Circulation: Cardiovascular Genetics.Women shorter than 155 centimeters  or 5 feet, 1 inch  were at lower risk  of suffering a blood clot, as were men shorter than 160 centimeters  or 5 feet, 2 inches. Women taller than 185 centimeters  or 6 feet, 1 inch  and men taller than 190 centimeters  or 6 feet, 2 inches, were at a higher risk.Deadly blood-clotting usually occur in the lower half of the body, but can also take place in the brain and lungs.The lead researcher of the study suggests that height should be included in risk assessment for blood clots, just as other factors, such as weight. However, exactly how height and blood clots are correlated remains unknown. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study overview2. Differences of clot risk across height groups 3. Where blood clots can form4. Height and obesity factorsVOICEOVER (in English): "A Swedish study investigated multi-generational data from over 2.5 million siblings of varying heights.""Women shorter than 155 centimeters  or 5 feet, 1 inch  were at lower risk  of suffering a blood clot, as were men shorter than 160 centimeters  or 5 feet, 2 inches.""Women taller than 185 centimeters  or 6 feet, 1 inch  and men taller than 190 centimeters  or 6 feet, 2 inches, were at a higher risk.""Deadly blood-clotting usually occur in the lower half of the body, but can also take place in the brain and lungs.""The lead researcher of the study suggests that height should be included in risk assessment for blood clots, just as other factors, such as weight."SOURCES: Circulation: Cardiovascular Genetics, American Heart Association, CNN, Centers for Disease Control and Preventionhttp://circgenetics.ahajournals.org/content/10/5/e001651http://newsroom.heart.org/news/can-height-increase-risk-for-blood-clots-in-veins?preview=5e0ahttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/06/health/blood-clots-health-risk-height-study/index.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/ncbddd/dvt/facts.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 02:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/12/3439344/3439344_480CE6661F5D429CB2B260874731E729_170912_3439344_Blood_clot_risk_linked_to_height_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5C4/813/5C4813FBD52846AF9D0D542246C91734_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tall people problems, taller people blood clots, blood clot risk, blood clots, health risk of blood clots]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3440341</guid>
      <title>Enormous fatberg found blocking London sewer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA 250-meter long fatberg weighing 130 tons has been discovered blocking a sewer line in London. The huge mass of congealed fat, wet wipes, diapers, oil and condoms formed in a sewer tunnel in Whitechapel, the BBC reported. Thames Water officials said it was one of the biggest blockages they had seen before and that it would take three weeks to remove, according to the BBC.Fatbergs form when people put things they shouldn't down toilets and sinks. The fatberg weighs as much as 10.5 school buses, or a blue whale.The length of the fatberg is actually 6 meters longer than the 244-meter Tower Bridge. Workers began removing the mass this week. Eight workers will use high-pressure hoses to break up the mass, then suck up the pieces into trucks and then transport the waste to a recycling station. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The fatberg in the sewer tunnel2. Fatbergs are congealed masses of fat, oil, diapers, wet wipes, sanitary napkins3. The weight and length of the fatberg4. Workers removing the fatbergVOICEOVER (in English): "A 250-meter long fatberg weighing 130 tons has been discovered blocking a sewer line in Whitechapel, London." "A fatberg is a giant mass of congealed fat, oils, wet naps, diapers, sanitary napkins and other things that should not be flushed down the toilet or washed down the sink."  "The fatberg weighs as much as 10.5 school buses or a blue whale. The length of the fatberg is actually 6 meters longer than the 244-meter Tower Bridge." "Eight workers will use high-pressure hoses to break up the mass, then suck up the pieces into trucks and then transport the waste to a recycling station."SOURCES: BBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-london-41238272***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 07:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/13/3440341/3440341_6615A0F103A64722B4692FCB56F199C5_170913_3440341_Enormous_fatberg_found_blocking_London_sewer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/69D/F98/69DF983AEAC54A34890925EBC875991A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  fatberg, fatberg blocking sewer, fatberg formation, fatberg London sewer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3440272</guid>
      <title>UN passes new sanctions on North Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENorth Korea is facing a new round of sanctions, after the United Nations Security Council unanimously approved the decision on Monday.The New York Times reports that in the wake of the North Korean regime's latest and largest nuclear weapons test on September 3, the UN adopted a U.S.-drafted resolution aimed at preventing the country from fueling and funding its weapons program.The resolution will restrict oil imports into the North by prohibiting the sale of natural gas and setting a 2-million-barrel-a-year cap on petroleum products.There will be a ban on textile exports, which are North Korea's second-biggest exports, earning the country nearly $760 million in 2016.New measures will also be put in place to prohibit North Koreans from working overseas, cutting off the $500 million in revenue generated by heavily taxing 93,000 citizens sent abroad to work.The original resolution pushed for a full oil embargo, and included an asset freeze and travel ban for North Korean leader Kim Jong Un. These were removed after negotiations between the U.S. and China. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New UN sanctions after North Korea nuclear test2. Restrictions on oil imported into North Korea3. Ban on North Korean textile exports4. Measures prohibiting North Koreans from working abroadVOICEOVER (in English): "In the wake of the North Korean regime's latest and largest nuclear weapons test September 3, the UN adopted a U.S.-drafted resolution aimed at preventing the country from fueling and funding its weapons program.""The resolution will restrict oil imports into the North by prohibiting the sale of natural gas and setting a 2-million-barrel-a-year cap on petroleum products.""There will be a ban on textile exports, which are North Korea's second-biggest exports, earning the country nearly $760 million in 2016.""New measures will also be put in place to prohibit North Koreans from working overseas, cutting off the $500 million in revenue generated by heavily taxing 93,000 citizens sent abroad to work."SOURCES: New York Times, CNN, BBChttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/11/world/asia/us-security-council-north-korea.htmlhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/11/politics/north-korea-un-security-council-vote/index.htmlhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-41235157***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 05:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/13/3440272/3440272_91BA5CCF47AD4619BF2F1BAEE28AB47E_170913_3440272_UN_passes_new_sanctions_on_North_Korea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EF9/355/EF935579D0CE4B56A6E9DB6D78578B8B_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, north korea, un, un sanctions, north korea weapons, nuclear test, nuclear weapons, oil imports, textile exports, kim jong un, un security council]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3440252</guid>
      <title>Trans-Pacific Russia, Japan rail bridge plans visualized</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONERail passengers on the Trans-Siberian Express may soon be able to travel from London, across Europe and Russia, and beyond to Japan under new plans from Moscow.The plan involves the construction of a bridge or tunnel between Russia and Sakhalin, and from there, a bridge to the Japanese island of Hokkaido, reports the Siberian Times. The bridge between Japan and Russia would reportedly be 28 miles in length across the Pacific Ocean.The project is nicknamed "A Bridge Across History", as the two countries never signed a peace treaty after the end of World War II, reports Conde Nast Traveler.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tran-Siberian route on globe, connecting to Japan2. Map showing proposed links between Russia and Japan3. Depiction of bridge construction on ocean4. Depiction of passengers aboard the trainVOICEOVER (in English): "Rail passengers on the Trans-Siberian Express may soon be able to travel from London, across Europe and Russia, and beyond to Japan under new plans from Moscow.""The plan involves the construction of a bridge or tunnel between Russia and Sakhalin, and from there, a bridge to the Japan's Hokkaido island.""The bridge between Japan and Russia would reportedly be 28 miles in length across the Pacific Ocean.""The journey from Hokkaido to Tokyo takes around 4 hours via bullet train."SOURCES: Siberian Times, Conde Nast Travelerhttp://siberiantimes.com/business/investment/news/russia-offers-a-bridge-across-history-to-connect-tokyo-to-the-trans-siberian-railway/https://www.cntraveler.com/story/the-trans-siberian-railway-will-eventually-connect-london-to-tokyo***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 05:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/13/3440252/3440252_45E9A3E2676E47B4B37FAD231C35E0AE_170913_3440252_Trans_Pacific_Russia__Japan_rail_bridge_plans_vi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C1F/C7C/C1FC7C29F94A4FF095624E3D127E1E8E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Russia japan bridge, mega rail project, bridge across pacific, Mega projects, russia japan, hokkaido, sakhalin, russian mega projects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3440121</guid>
      <title>Rural Alabama plagued by sewage problems, hookworm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEHookworm, disease that is typically associated with developing nations, has been found to be plaguing poor areas in the southern U.S.According to a press release from the Baylor College of Medicine, 34.5% of 55 stool samples taken from Alabama's Lowndes County tested positive for a species of hookworm called Necator americanus.Households in the county are poor and lack basic sanitation, with waste often discarded in the backyard. Residents exposed to the raw sewage may become infected with hookworm, which enters the human body through the feet.The parasitic worm attaches itself to the walls of the small intestine, sucking the host's blood and causing anemia, weight loss, impaired mental function, and stunted growth in children.The disease is a problem even for those who can afford to install their own septic tanks.Sewage problems run rampant in Alabama's Black Belt region. The area's loamy soil prevents water from draining into the ground, and heavy rains often cause septic systems to overflow or back up.Parasitic infections like hookworm are treatable with medication, but unless sanitation conditions improve, people will just get re-infected with the disease.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 34.5% of stool samples tested in Alabama tested positive for hookworm2. Inadequate sewage system creates environment for hookworm3. Hookworm attaches to the small intestine, causes anemia, weight loss, mental impairment4. Alabama Black Belt region unsuitable for septic tanks, often backs up and overflowsVOICEOVER (in English): "34.5% of stool samples taken from Alabama's Lowndes County tested positive for a species of hookworm called Necator americanus.""Households in the county are reportedly poor and lack basic sanitation, with waste often discarded in the backyard. Residents exposed to the raw sewage may become infected with hookworm, which enters the human body through the feet.""The parasitic worm attaches itself to the walls of the small intestine, sucking the host's blood, which in turn causes anemia, weight loss, impaired mental function, and stunted growth in children.""The disease is a problem even for those who can afford to install their own septic tanks.""Sewage problems run rampant in Alabama's Black Belt region. The area's loamy soil prevents water from draining into the ground, and heavy rains often cause septic systems to overflow or back up."SOURCES: Baylor College of Medicine, The Guardianhttps://www.bcm.edu/news/school-of-tropical-medicine/hookworm-poverty-sanitation-alabamahttps://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2017/sep/05/hookworm-lowndes-county-alabama-water-waste-treatment-poverty***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 00:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/13/3440121/3440121_0BEC8C1CC18A4CAE907729B1EBFD1601_170913_3440121_Rural_Alabama_plagued_by_sewage_problems__hookwo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4ED/44C/4ED44C5037EA4FD487136B6C4FFC1B41_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hookworm, worm, parasite, disease, poverty, sewage, raw sewage, sewage problems, sewer line, septic system, septic tank, anemia, iron deficiency, black belt, lowndes county, alabama]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441356</guid>
      <title>Boeing awarded $600 million Air Force One contract</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. Air Force has contracted Boeing to begin design work on presidential aircraft.According to an Air Force news release,  the U.S. government purchased two Boeing 747-8 jetliners as part of their plan to develop a new Air Force One aircraft.Under the contract, Boeing will design modifications for the 747-8s.  These will reportedly include an executive interior, meeting rooms, medical facilities and other features of the current presidential aircraft.According to Reuters, the planes were previously ordered by Transaero, a now defunct Russian Airline. According to Defense One, the design will also need to have defensive countermeasures, including a hardened exterior capable of withstanding electromagnetic pulse from nuclear explosions.The Air Force plans to spend around $3.2 billion on the next presidential aircraft, reported Defense One.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New aircraft purchased2. Previous order of aircraft3. Design modifications for new aircraft4. Aircraft in airVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Air Force has purchased two Boeing 747-8 jetliners as part of their plan to develop a new Air Force One aircraft.""The planes were previously ordered by Transaero, a now defunct Russian Airline.""Under the contract, Boeing will design modifications for the 747-8s.""These will reportedly include an executive interior, meeting rooms, medical facilities and other features of the current presidential aircraft.""The design will also need to have defensive countermeasures, including a hardened exterior capable of withstanding electromagnetic pulse from nuclear explosions."SOURCES: U.S. Air Force, Reuters, Defense One, Los Angeles Times, http://www.af.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/1309352/af-awards-contract-to-begin-designing-next-air-force-one-aircraft/http://www.defenseone.com/business/2017/08/russian-air-force-one-boeing-trump-747/139872/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-airforceone/boeing-wins-u-s-air-force-contract-to-modify-next-presidential-aircraft-idUSKCN1BO1UKhttp://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-air-force-one-contract-20170913-story.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 11:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/14/3441356/3441356_C29732934C5E42C187FDCC684F641CCB_170914_3441356_Boeing_awarded__600_million_Air_Force_One_contra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D9E/449/D9E449F4249D4437A8BA326EEC3BCE89_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, us air force one, air force one, air force 1, new air force 1, boeing air force one, air force one cost, air force one upgrade]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441349</guid>
      <title>U.S. Air Force battles mosquitoes after Hurricane Harvey</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETexas officials asked the U.S. Air Force to spray coastal regions of the state in order to combat swarming mosquitoes in the aftermath of Hurricane Harvey. U.S. Air Force C-130 cargo planes started spraying insecticides over three eastern Texas counties during the weekend and plan to expand to other counties over the following weeks, said officials from the Texas Department of State Health Services (DSHS), Reuters reported. The C-130 cargo planes flew from an air force base in San Antonio and joined two smaller planes. About 1.85 million acres have been treated as of Tuesday, the department said. The plan is to spray 6 million acres in total.  Officials hope the spraying will prevent mosquito-borne illnesses as well as protect emergency response workers and residents from swarms during cleanup efforts.The Air Force is using an organophosphate insecticide called naled, according to Quartz. Naled acts as a neurotoxin that targets adult mosquitoes, according to Newsweek. The health department sprays about 16 million acres a year with the insecticide. It is frequently used after disasters to deal with mosquitoes. Health officials urged residents to dispose of standing water, use repellant and wear long-sleeved clothing outdoors. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. C-130 spraying insecticide2. C-130 spraying Naled 3. Officials hope spraying will prevent spread of Zika, West Nile and protect disaster workers and residents4. Residents disposing of standing water, using repellant and wearing long-sleeved clothingVOICEOVER (in English): "U.S. Air Force C-130 cargo planes have started spraying insecticides over three eastern Texas counties and plan to expand to other areas over the next two weeks in an attempt to combat mosquitoes." "According to Texas health officials, about 1.85 million acres have been treated with the organophosphate insecticide Naled as of Tuesday. The plan is to spray 6 million acres in total." "Officials hope spraying will prevent mosquito-borne illnesses, such as Zika and West Nile Virus, as well as protect disaster workers and residents from swarms during cleanup efforts.""Health officials also urged residents to dispose of standing water, use repellant and wear long-sleeved clothing outdoors." SOURCES: Reuters, Newsweek, Quartzhttp://news.trust.org/item/20170912180035-zvnkehttp://www.newsweek.com/texas-hurricane-harvey-mosquitoes-us-air-force-664397https://qz.com/1075935/swarmed-with-mosquitoes-after-harvey-texas-calls-in-the-us-air-force/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/14/3441349/3441349_5BDE9C00C15842EFA0D459703791FE72_170914_3441349_U_S__Air_Force_battles_mosquitoes_after_Hurrican_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5AB/529/5AB529B0579E432B840603D118FF310E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hurricane Harvey, US Air Force, Harvey clean up, mosquito-borne illnesses, Zika, West Nile Virus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441239</guid>
      <title>Biggest ever wind farm to be built off British coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEDanish energy firm DONG will construct the largest ever wind farm off the British coast over the next 5 years.The wind farm is to be built 90 miles of the British coast. When completed in 2022, the wind farm will have a capacity of some 1.4 gigawatts.According to DONG, that's enough energy to power some 1.3 million British homes.The project is expected to create 2,000 jobs over its duration.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of new wind farm2. Depiction of wind turbines being constructed3. Number of British homes that can be poweredVOICEOVER (in English): "The world's largest wind farm is set to be built 90 miles of the British coast by Danish energy firm DONG. ""When completed in 2022, the wind farm will have a capacity of some 1.4 gigawatts.""According to DONG, that's enough energy to power some 1.3 million British homes."SOURCES: DONG Energy, BBC, Reutershttp://www.dongenergy.com/en/media/newsroom/news/articles/170911_announcement_uhttp://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-41228969https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-renewables-dong-energy/denmarks-dong-wins-uk-contract-to-build-worlds-largest-offshore-wind-farm-idUKKCN1BM0R1***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 09:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/14/3441239/3441239_7A0097C76F834D60BFC26B591ED0E637_170914_3441239_Biggest_ever_wind_farm_to_be_built_off_British_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/014/CBF/014CBF1FD92F489D99778EE490D2EAFA_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, TomoNews, News, mega projects, wind farm, biggest wind farm, wind farm renewables, planet earth, DONG energy, DONG uk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441116</guid>
      <title>Symptoms of a silent heart attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEHeart attacks may not always be defined by crushing chest pains, and can sometimes strike with little to no symptoms.The BBC reports that a heart attack, or a myocardial infarction, occurs when a clot blocks the flow of blood and oxygen to the heart, which damages or kills heart muscle cells. The most common symptom of this is pain or discomfort in the chest area.But research has found that at least 45% of attacks are "silent", occurring with less intense symptoms, and thus undetected. Silent myocardial infarctions have been known to strike men more than women.Symptoms are often mistaken for other conditions, and include fatigue, dizziness, nausea, and pain in the neck, jaw and arm.Silent heart attacks are usually identified using an electro or echocardiogram, which detects damaged heart tissue, according to Harvard Medical School.Patients who have suffered a silent attack are at a higher risk of having a second one, or succumbing to sudden cardiac arrest.Doctors stress the importance of getting checked even if the symptoms may not seem serious. At the end of the day, it's better to be safe than sorry.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Blocked blood supply to the heart results in a heart attack; associated with chest pain2. 45% of heart attacks are silent3. Symptoms of a silent heart attack 4. Heart damage detected using electrocardiogram or echocardiogramVOICEOVER (in English): "A heart attack, or a myocardial infarction, occurs when a clot blocks the flow of blood and oxygen to the heart, which damages or kills heart muscle cells. The most common symptom of this is pain or discomfort in the chest area.""But research has found that at least 45% of attacks are 'silent', occurring with less intense symptoms, and thus go undetected. Silent myocardial infarctions have been known to take place in men more than women.""Symptoms are often mistaken for other conditions, and include fatigue, dizziness, nausea, and pain in the neck, jaw and arm.""Silent heart attacks are usually identified using an electro or echocardiogram, which detects damaged heart tissue"SOURCES: Harvard Medical School, BBChttps://www.health.harvard.edu/heart-health/the-danger-of-silent-heart-attackshttp://www.bbc.com/future/story/20170912-can-you-have-a-heart-attack-and-not-realise-it***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 07:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/14/3441116/3441116_3859B5EA09804F3DAF985089D6616695_170914_3441116_Symptoms_of_a_silent_heart_attack_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AB5/2D6/AB52D6C42470453D8DF7DD614CF4C83E_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, heart attack, silent heart attack, silent killer, SMI, silent myocardial infarction, blood clot, heart, heart health, heart disease, pain, symptoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441090</guid>
      <title>Inside Japan's new luxury train</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe ultra-luxury Shiki-Shima Train hit Japanese tracks at the beginning of May and is already fully booked until 2018.The service, operated by East Japanese Railway Company, chauffeurs passengers around North-East Japan on multi-day trips.According to information on the train operator's website, it's 17 suites can accommodate 34 passengers. Prospective passengers need to apply online to join the journey. Ticket cost upwards of $6,000 per person.The train travels at 110 kilometers per hour  3 times slower than the Shinkansen, better known as Japan's "bullet train".The Shiki-Shima comprises 10 cars. These include 1 car for deluxe and Shiki-Shima suite passengers, 5 cars for regular suite , 2 observatory cars, a lounge car and a dining room.It's observatory cars allow passengers to sit back and take in panoramic views of the Japanese countryside.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Passenger boarding the Shiki-Shima train, depicted from a first-person perspective2. Depiction of train travelling through Japanese countryside, with map of Japan highlighting area train travels in3. The Shiki-Shima travelling overnight4. The speed of the Shiki-Shima compared to the Shinkansen train5. Breakdown of train6. Depiction of the observatory car7. The interior of a suite8. The interior of the dining room and lounge carsVOICEOVER (in English): "The Shiki-Shima Train debuted in Japan in May of this year.""The service, operated by East Japanese Railway Company, chauffeurs passengers around northeastern Japan on up to almost 1,300-kilometer round trips." "The train departs Tokyo's Ueno station and guests sleep on board overnight.""The Shiki-Shima travels at 110 kilometers per hour  three times slower than the Shinkansen, Japan's famous bullet train.""The 10-carriage train includes five standard suite cars, one car for a deluxe suite and the Shiki-Shima suite, two observatory cars for viewing, and two cars for lounging and dining." "Observatory cars allow passengers to take in panoramic views of the Japanese countryside.""The train can accommodate 34 passengers in its 17 suites."  "The Shiki-Shima's dining and lounge cars also allow guests to view the scenery outside. The train's appearance and interior decoration was designed by Ken Okuyama." SOURCES: https://www.jreast.co.jp/shiki-shima/en/http://www.telegraph.co.uk/luxury/travel/shiki-shima-japan-luxury-train-journey-launch-rates-route/http://www.cntraveler.com/story/japans-new-shiki-shima-luxury-train-is-already-sold-out-until-2018https://www.theguardian.com/world/gallery/2017/may/03/japan-luxurious-shika-shima-sleeper-train-in-pictureshttp://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-luxurytrain-idUSKBN17Y19H***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 07:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/14/3441090/3441090_18B80D247C9A4C6FBE002641A2E46B2A_170914_3441090_Inside_Japan_s_new_luxury_train_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DD7/320/DD7320E7D42A4A06AC471F23849BBBE4_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Luxury train, shiki shima train, japan, ueno, luxury trains of the world, ultra luxury, travel in japan, japan east railway company]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3440948</guid>
      <title>Study claims AI can identify sexuality</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers from Stanford University are facing backlash this week after developing an artificial intelligence that they say can identify sexuality based on profile photosCritics worry the technology could be replicated by governments of countries where gay people are prosecuted.The AI was used as part of a study that was to be published in the Journal of Personality and Social Psychology. It is currently being held for review regarding ethical concerns, reported Science Alert.The AI scanned publicly available photos from dating websites to identify whether the image's subject was gay or not. In total, it looked at 130,741 images. It proved more effective than the study's human judges. On the whole, the AI was able to identify gay women with 74% accuracy and gay men with 81% accuracy.Researchers say the AI was able to do this by looking at transient features, such as nose shape and hair style. It only looked at white people aged between 18 and 40.The Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation and Human Rights Campaign called for people to debunk it, citing multiple flaws in the study.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study overview2. Accuracy of study against human judges3. Facial features AI looked at4. Countries where gay people are prosecutedVOICEOVER (in English): "The AI scanned publicly available photos from dating websites to identify whether the image's subject was gay or not. In total, it looked at 130,741 images.""It proved more effective than the study's human judges. On the whole, the AI was able to identify gay women with 74% accuracy and gay men with 81% accuracy.""Researchers say the AI was able to do this by looking at transient features, such as nose shape and hair style. It only looked at white people aged between 18 and 40.""Critics of the study worry the technology could be replicated by governments of countries where gay people are prosecuted."SOURCES: Open Society Foundation, GLAAD, Stanford researchers' response (Google Doc link), Guardian/ILGA, ScienceAlert, New York Posthttps://osf.io/zn79k/https://www.glaad.org/blog/glaad-and-hrc-call-stanford-university-responsible-media-debunk-dangerous-flawed-reporthttps://docs.google.com/document/d/1UuEcSNFMduIaf0cOWdWbOV3NORLoKWdz3big4xuk7Z4/edithttps://www.theguardian.com/news/datablog/2013/oct/15/state-sponsored-homophobia-gay-rightshttps://www.sciencealert.com/here-s-what-s-really-going-on-with-that-study-saying-ai-can-detect-your-sexual-orientationhttp://nypost.com/2017/09/12/researchers-face-backlash-from-lgbtq-groups-over-ai-study/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 02:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/14/3440948/3440948_AA697D3006A9497C8760122DA15BCBE5_170914_3440948_Study_claims_AI_can_identify_sexuality_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4F0/440/4F0440773B094C57A892C1096CC4F78C_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Gay bot, ai, gaydar study, real life gaydar, gaydar, stanford]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3440908</guid>
      <title>San Diego power washes its streets to fight deadly Hepatitis A outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAt least 16 people have died and more than 400 have been hospitalized following an outbreak of the deadly hepatitis A virus in "America's Finest City".According to the San Diego County Health and Human Services Agency, the Hepatitis A virus is spread through contact with a fecally contaminated environment, or person to person. It attacks the liver, and can be fatal.Roughly two-thirds of those infected are homeless and/or drug users.NBC San Diego reports that to combat the spread of the disease, city crews have begun powerwashing the streets with a bleach solution known to kill the virus. Street spraying has been scheduled three times a week, every other week.Officials have already set up hand washing stations in areas where the homeless congregate, and deployed an additional 40 around the county.Free vaccinations are also available and recommended to anyone frequenting downtown. Hepatitis A vaccines work by prompting the body to produce antibodies against the disease.San Diego's precautionary efforts are modelled after those implemented in Los Angeles, where it proved effective.In addition to street-spraying, installing hand-washing stations and administering vaccines, city officials are also looking into providing more bathroom access downtown.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hepatitis A spread via contact with contaminated environment, person; attacks liver2. San Diego power washing streets with bleach to kill Hepatitis A virus3. Hand washing stations set up around San Diego4. Vaccinations recommended to prevent infectionVOICEOVER (in English): "The Hepatitis A virus in San Diego is spread through contact with a fecally contaminated environment, or person to person. It attacks the liver, and can be fatal.""To combat the spread of the disease, city crews have begun powerwashing the streets with a bleach solution known to kill the virus.""Officials have already set up hand washing stations in areas where the homeless congregate, and deployed an additional 40 around the county.""Free vaccinations are also available and recommended to anyone frequenting downtown. Hepatitis A vaccines work by prompting the body to produce antibodies against the disease."SOURCES: San Diego County, NBC San Diego, CBS 8http://www.sandiegocounty.gov/content/sdc/hhsa/programs/phs/community_epidemiology/dc/Hepatitis_A.htmlhttp://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/San-Diego-Begins-Power-Washing-Streets-to-Fight-Hepatitis-A-443868103.htmlhttp://www.cbs8.com/story/36341357/spraying-the-streets-to-stop-the-outbreak-of-hepatitis-a***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/14/3440908/3440908_CEA6D450A66C4033AB2DEA4A2AA72450_170914_3440908_San_Diego_power_washes_its_streets_to_fight_dead_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B4E/9F6/B4E9F68AF3EB4D218D1CD4F76338810B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hepatitis A, hepatitis, liver, liver disease, hepatitis outbreak, san diego, homeless, vaccine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3442214</guid>
      <title>SpaceX and Boeing pushing 'new space race' for NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA says it may soon be able to launch astronauts from U.S. soil to the International Space Station. Important project milestones are coming up for NASA's two commercial crew partners: Boeing and SpaceX, according to AP. Several flight tests, including manned missions, are slated for 2018.Boeing is working on the CST-100 Starliner. The spacecraft is designed to send up to seven astronauts to the space station. Three Starliners are currently in production, with one planned to carry astronauts next year.SpaceX, which has flown cargo missions to the space station with its Dragon spacecraft,  plans to use the Dragon 2 to send astronauts to space. The Dragon 2 is the latest version of SpaceX's Dragon capsule model, which can carry seven astronauts.   Boeing and SpaceX must show that both of their systems are ready to start regular flights to the space station in order to meet NASA's requirements. SpaceX has its first test flight set for February, while Boeing's launch is planned for June. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The CST-100 Starliner and the Dragon 22. The CST-100 Starliner can seat up to 7 astronauts3. The CST-100 Starliner being launched by an Atlas rocket4. The Dragon 2 heading towards the ISS5. The Dragon 2 can seat 7 astronautsVOICEOVER (in English): "Important project milestones are coming up for NASA's two commercial crew partners Boeing and SpaceX, with several flight tests, including manned missions, slated for 2018." "Boeing is working on the CST-100 Starliner. The spacecraft can seat up to seven and is meant to send astronauts to the space station.""Three Starliners are currently in production, with one planned to carry astronauts next year. The pressurized vessel can be reused 10 times.""SpaceX, which has flown cargo missions to the ISS with its Dragon spacecraft, plans to use the Dragon 2 to send astronauts to space." "The Dragon 2 is the latest version of SpaceX's capsule model. It's designed to seat seven astronauts." SOURCES: Associated Press, NASAhttp://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/private-companies-drive-space-race-nasa-center-49505922http://www.nasa.gov/exploration/commercial/crew/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 11:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/15/3442214/3442214_DF1B82AFF3354ED496D03256702CBE3B_170915_3442214_SpaceX_and_Boeing_pushing__new_space_race__for_N_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EC7/34B/EC734B6E1C2D44C2913A8FBC51C08702_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, NASA, International Space Station, SpaceX Dragon 2, Boeing CST-100 Starliner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441818</guid>
      <title>Longer bouts of sitting linked to higher risk of death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEHealth experts have long warned against the perils of sitting all day, but a new study suggests the length of time spent inactive in between bouts of movement also matters.According to the study published in Annals of Internal Medicine, hip-mounted accelerometers measured physical inactivity in nearly 8,000 Americans aged 45 years and older, for a period of 10 days. Researchers found that the participants were sedentary for 12.3 hours out of a 16-hour waking day.When measuring bout length, it was discovered that subjects who sat for longer periods at a time were more likely to have died at the end of the study period than those with shorter sitting spells.Findings indicate that moving around for every 30 consecutive minutes of inactivity may significantly decrease the risk for death.The study did not explain how sitting increases early death, but experts suggest inactivity exposes the body to higher blood glucose levels, which leads to problems like diabetes, heart disease, or stroke.Prolonged sitting may also weaken the abdominal muscles, hip flexors, and glutes.It could also lead to a lack of circulation in the legs, potentially resulting in blood clots forming in the veins  a condition known as deep vein thrombosis.Alas, working out after a long day of sitting in an office chair may not necessarily undo its ill effects. The best way to lengthen your lifespan, it seems, is to move about as often as you can.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Americans monitored over 10 days sedentary for 12.3 hours in a 16-hour day 2. More accumulated sitting time, and longer bouts of sitting linked to higher risk of death3. Movement breaks for every 30 minutes of sitting reduces risk of death4. Prolonged inactivity can lead to higher blood glucose levels5. Prolonged sitting weakens abdominals, hip flexors, glutes6. Sedentary behavior can lead to deep vein thrombosis VOICEOVER (in English): "Hip-mounted accelerometers measured physical inactivity in nearly 8,000 Americans aged 45 years and older, and found that they were sedentary for 12.3 hours out of a 16-hour waking day.""When measuring bout length, it was discovered that subjects who sat for longer periods at a time were more likely to have died at the end of the study period than those with shorter sitting spells.""Findings indicate that moving around for every 30 consecutive minutes of inactivity may significantly decrease the risk for death.""The study did not explain how sitting increases early death, but experts suggest inactivity exposes the body to higher blood glucose levels, which leads to problems like diabetes, heart disease, or stroke.""Prolonged sitting may also weaken the abdominal muscles, hip flexors, and glutes.""It could also lead to a lack of circulation in the legs, potentially resulting in blood clots forming in the veins  a condition known as deep vein thrombosis."SOURCES: Annals of Internal Medicine, CNN, Los Angeles Timeshttp://annals.org/aim/article/2653704/patterns-sedentary-behavior-mortality-u-s-middle-aged-older-adultshttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/09/11/health/sitting-increases-risk-of-death-study/index.htmlhttp://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-sitting-death-risk-20170911-story.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 04:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/15/3441818/3441818_C411B07EC75F481B833DF16A9EAEA5A3_170915_3441818_Longer_bouts_of_sitting_linked_to_higher_risk_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/54E/7D0/54E7D0C9492D43E9AE659D3E973BE51A_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, prolonged sitting, sitting, sedentary behavior, sedentary, movement, exercise, blood glucose, blood sugar, deep vein thrombosis, weak muscles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441811</guid>
      <title>Tattoo ink could leave behind metals that affect immune system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETattoo ink may leave microscopic particles that can circulate in the immune system and end up in the lymph nodes, a new study finds.   Scientists wanted to determine the effect tattoos had within the body, particularly the lymph nodes, the Atlanta Journal-Constitution reported. The study, published in Scientific Reports, examined lymph nodes and skin samples from deceased donors: four with tattoos and two with no tattoos, according to Smithsonian Magazine. Using X-ray fluorescence to identify ink particles and Fourier transform infrared spectroscopy to detect biomolecular changes in surrounding tissue, scientists found traces in the subjects with tattooes and none in the lymph nodes of the non-tattooed subjects.   They discovered stained lymph nodes in two of the subjects, one with blue ink and one with green. Researchers found elevated levels of metals including aluminum, chromium, iron, nickel and copper in the nodes and skin. The study concluded contamination could lead to chronic enlargement of the lymph nodes and long-term exposure to toxic compounds. The scientists say the next step will be to study what particular health effects ink particles may cause.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tattoo ink particles traveling to lymph nodes2. The study looked at deceased subjects with and without tattoos3. Some of the tattooed subjects had elevated levels of metals4. Contamination could lead to enlarged lymph nodesVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study finds tattoo ink may leave microscopic particles that can circulate in the immune system and end up in the lymph nodes.""Scientists examined deceased individuals with tattoos and deceased individuals without tattooes using X-ray fluorescence to identify ink particles. They also used Fourier transform infrared spectroscopy to detect biomolecular changes in the surrounding tissue." "Researchers found elevated levels of metals including aluminum, chromium, iron, nickel and copper in the lymph nodes and skin in some of the tattooed subjects.""The study concluded contamination could lead to chronic enlargement of the lymph nodes and long-term exposure to toxic compounds." SOURCES: Atlanta Journal-Constitution, Smithsonian Magazine, Scientific Reportshttp://www.ajc.com/news/world/can-your-tattoos-leave-behind-toxic-ink-that-could-affect-your-immune-system/RKwiPm26OmZehlRLejFOEL/http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/tattoos-can-be-much-more-skin-deep-180964881/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-11721-z***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 04:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/15/3441811/3441811_0D030324632A40E084691FA5BA6DEB31_170915_3441811_Tattoo_ink_could_leave_behind_metals_that_affect_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/769/E8C/769E8C7F6E284AF7AD9683EF10C0530B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tattoo ink, tattoo ink toxic metal, tattoo ink immune system, tattoo ink lymph nodes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3441795</guid>
      <title>Cassini headed for final Saturn plunge mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA's Cassini spacecraft is now on course for its last mission that will see it dive and disintegrate into Saturn's atmosphere on Friday. Cassini has been traveling around Saturn and its moons for 13 years, but it is finally running out of fuel, so NASA wants the probe disposed of properly, Space.com reported.The probe sped within 73,974 miles (119,049 kms) of Titan on Sept. 11 in a flyby meant to lower the spacecraft's orbit enough to ensure it will crash into Saturn's atmosphere, NASA officials said, according to Space.com. The main purpose of this last mission is to make sure that Cassini does not contaminate the moons of Titan or Enceladus with Earth microbes. Scientists think the two moons could possibly support life. Enceladus has an ocean of liquid water underneath its icy shell, as well as hydrothermal hot spots in the ocean.Titan is also believed to have a subsurface water ocean. The moon also has lakes and seas of hydrocarbons on its surface.     Once Cassini enters Saturn's thick atmosphere, it will take approximately five to six minutes for the probe to fall apart and melt. During its last dive, the probe will be sending data back to Earth in real time for researchers to analyze.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cassini probe traveling towards Saturn2. Cassini's final flight path 3. The purpose of the mission is to ensure Cassini doesn't contaminate Saturn's moons4. Cassini burning up in Saturn's atmosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Cassini spacecraft is now on course for its last mission that will see it dive and disintegrate into Saturn's atmosphere on Friday." "The probe sped around Titan on Sept. 11 in a flyby meant to lower the spacecraft's orbit enough to ensure it will crash into Saturn's atmosphere on Sept 15.""The main purpose of the mission is to make sure Cassini does not contaminate the moons of Titan or Enceladus  both of which scientists believe could support life  with Earth microbes.""Once Cassini enters Saturn's thick atmosphere, it will take approximately five to six minutes for the probe to fall apart and melt. During its final dive, the craft will be sending data back to Earth in real time for researchers to analyze."SOURCES: Space.com, Vergehttps://www.space.com/38124-cassini-saturn-plunge-titan-goodbye-kiss.htmlhttps://www.space.com/36537-cassini-s-grand-finale-saturn-orbits-astrodynamics-explained-video.htmlhttps://www.theverge.com/2017/9/11/16266304/nasa-cassini-spacecraft-saturn-enceladus-titan-end-of-mission***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 04:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/15/3441795/3441795_3292098A46174A40BFE2148650E61A5E_170915_3441795_Cassini_headed_for_final_Saturn_plunge_mission_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FB2/A9D/FB2A9DCEEE314A6D86B21FC9CD41991F_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Cassini space probe, Cassini spacecraft, NASA Cassini probe, Cassini Grande Finale]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3443100</guid>
      <title>'Messaging Extraterrestrial Intelligences' will attempt to contact alien life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA group known as Messaging Extraterrestrial Intelligences, or METI, will in 2018 attempt to message alien life.According to CNET, most concur the message should consist of physics and math as these are forms of knowledge aliens likely hold in common with humanity.However, many scientists, including Stephen Hawking, worry that such a message could put Earth in danger.Previous attempts to communicate with alien civilizations have included sending out the formula for alcohol, and Craigslist advertisements, reported CNET.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of astronomers 2. Depiction of radio telescope sending message consisting of math and physics3. Depiction of threat to Earth4. Depiction of radio telescope sending Craigslist advertisements and alcohol formulaVOICEOVER (in English): "A group known as Messaging Extraterrestrial Intelligences, or METI, will in 2018 attempt to message alien life.""According to CNET, most concur the message should consist of physics and math as these are forms of knowledge aliens likely hold in common with humanity.""However, many scientists, including Stephen Hawking, worry that such a message could put Earth in danger.""Previous attempts to communicate with alien civilizations have included sending out the formula for alcohol, and Craigslist advertisements."SOURCES: CNET, News.com.auhttps://www.cnet.com/news/next-year-scientists-will-send-messages-to-search-for-aliens/http://www.news.com.au/technology/science/space/a-group-called-messaging-extraterrestrial-intelligence-are-about-to-step-up-the-call-to-et/news-story/d4b25a99f84c1b85f8229c212afe6e12***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 01:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/17/3443100/3443100_8E8A4518C064487E9E5CCE68A924B303_170917_3443100__Messaging_Extraterrestrial_Intelligences__will__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DB7/C28/DB7C2899CDF84A76BFACDE1E95BEDA17_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, meti, contacting aliens, speak to aliens, alien communication, alien communication attempt, stephen hawking aliens]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3443096</guid>
      <title>India begins work on Japanese bullet train</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEIndia has started building a high-speed train system with the help of Japanese technology and finance.  The network will stretch 508 kms from Ahmedabad to the financial center of Mumbai, and was announced Thursday by Prime Minister Narendra Modi, the Guardian reported. The country plans to invest $19 billion to construct the new bullet train line. Japan will fund more than 80 percent of the project, over $14 billion, by providing a 0.1 percent interest loan to be repaid over the next 50 years. The line is expected to be finished by 2023 and will cut travel time between the two cities down to three hours from the current eight. The Modi administration claims that the project will create 36,000 jobs in India, according to the Guardian. The bullet train can carry 750 passengers at an average speed of 250 kph, with a top speed of 320 kph. Analysts say constructing the bullet train will give a boost to infrastructure development in India's quickly-developing western industrial region and help with economic growth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The proposed bullet train line between Ahmedabad and Mumbai2. The bullet train will take 3 hours compared to the current 8 hours between the two cities3. The exterior and interior of the bullet train4. The bullet train traveling down the tracksVOICEOVER (in English): "India has begun construction on its first Japanese bullet train line which will stretch 508 kms from the city of Ahmedabad to the financial center of Mumbai on the country's western coast."  "The line is expected to be finished by 2023 and will cut travel time between the two cities down to three hours from the current eight.""The new train will be able to carry 750 passengers at an average speed of 250 kph, with a top speed of 320 kph." "India plans to invest $19 billion in the new line. Japan will fund over $14 billion of the project, with a 0.1 percent interest loan to be repaid over the next 50 years."SOURCES: The Guardian, Al Jazeera, The Independenthttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/14/india-starts-work-on-its-first-bullet-train-linehttp://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/india-invest-17bn-japanese-bullet-trains-170914122827892.htmlhttp://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/india-bullet-train-japan-mumbai-ahmedabad-city-narendra-modi-shinzo-abe-a7946321.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/17/3443096/3443096_D679C31935134DF7AEBB86C352AF7AA2_170917_3443096_India_begins_work_on_Japanese_bullet_train_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/61B/9B0/61B9B0E3E6044DDEA88B349874BA679C_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, India bullet train, India high-speed train, Japan India bullet train, Indian Railways, Shinkansen Technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3444049</guid>
      <title>MIT develops tech that can pack several vaccine doses into one injection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Massachusetts Institute of Technology has developed a drug delivery method that packs multiple doses in a single injection, and could soon make multi-shot vaccines a thing of the past.According to the MIT News Office, engineers used biodegradable polymers used in implants, sutures, and prosthetic devices, and pressed them into silicone molds to form tiny cups each measuring 400 micrometers across.The cups are filled with vaccine and covered with a lid made from the same polymer. Heat is applied to fuse the cup and lid together, sealing the vaccine inside.Varying its chemical makeup allows the polymers to degrade at specific times, though all are delivered simultaneously via a single injection.Inside the body, the vaccine is released once the cup degrades. Lab tests on mice showed the polymer cups successfully releasing their payload in 9, 20, and 41 days, without prior leakage.Researchers say the new technology could benefit patients in developing nations, who are often unable to travel frequently to health care facilities to complete their shots.It may also allow newborns to be given an injection carrying one or two year's worth of vaccines, minimizing stressful, tear-filled doctor's visits for kids and parents alike.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Polymer turned into tiny cups using silicone mold2. Polymer cups filled with vaccine, lid sealed using heat3. Vaccine cups injected into the body4. Cups break down and release vaccine at different times  VOICEOVER (in English): "Biodegradable polymers used in implants, sutures, and prosthetic devices, were pressed into silicone molds to form tiny cups each measuring 400 micrometers across.""The cups are filled with vaccine and covered with a lid made from the same polymer. Heat is applied to fuse the cup and lid together, sealing the vaccine inside.""Varying its chemical makeup allows the polymers to degrade at specific times, though all are delivered simultaneously via a single injection.""Inside the body, the vaccine is released once the cup degrades. Lab tests on mice showed the polymer cups successfully releasing their payload in 9, 20, and 41 days, without prior leakage."SOURCES: Massachusetts Institute of Technology News Officehttp://news.mit.edu/2017/one-vaccine-injection-could-carry-many-doses-0914***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 11:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/18/3444049/3444049_5A2EE865F4BE4808B54A3E58D4B377D2_170918_3444049_MIT_develops_tech_that_can_pack_several_vaccine__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/32C/A5B/32CA5BF1ABF74EBA831EB233631F8ADE_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, vaccine, injection, polymer cup, vaccine cup, timed vaccine, technology, MIT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3443955</guid>
      <title>Researchers finds fungus that can break down plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new study published in the journal Environmental Pollution discusses a fungus that breaks down plastic materials.A group of researchers from the Kunming Institute of Botany in China found aspergillus [a]tubingensis[b], a common soil fungus, at a dump in Pakistan. Under laboratory conditions it was shown to break down plastic in weeks, not years.The fungus used its roots to break apart the plastic, but its effectiveness was found to be influenced by other factors such as temperature and pH levels.Aspergillus tubingensis was previously found in patients with lung conditions such as cystic fibrosis, according to a 2016 study in the journal Medical Mycology.RUNDOWN SHOWS:  1. Common components of plastic2. Fungus in garden 3. Fungus examined in lab4. Depiction of plastic garbage being cleanedVOICEOVER (in English): "Plastic is not easily biodegradable and can take thousands of years to decompose.""A group of researchers found aspergillus [c]tubingensis[d], a common soil fungus, at a dump in Pakistan. "Under laboratory conditions it was shown to break down plastic in weeks, not years." "The fungus used its roots to break apart the plastic, but its effectiveness was found to be influenced by other factors such as temperature and pH levels.""Aspergillus tubingensis has been previously found in patients with lung conditions such as cystic fibrosis.""Researchers say that tweaking these could pave the way for fungi to be used in waste treatment plants, or in soils impacted by plastic."SOURCES: Environmental Pollution (Science Direct), Medical Mycology, Agroforestry World, Futurismhttp://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0269749117300295?showall%3Dtrue%26via%3Dihubhttps://academic.oup.com/mmy/article/54/5/459/2579167/Aspergillus-tubingensis-a-major-filamentous-fungushttp://blog.worldagroforestry.org/index.php/2017/09/12/scientists-find-fungus-appetite-plastic-rubbish-dump/https://futurism.com/researchers-find-a-fungus-that-can-break-down-plastic-in-weeks/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 10:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/18/3443955/3443955_23C113C032894C788799EAA612DF2DBB_170918_3443955_Researchers_finds_fungus_that_can_break_down_pla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F61/9EF/F619EF5E185F4BDEBDF946EE90F0F090_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, plastic eating fungus, aspergillus tubingensis,environmental pollution, mycology, kunming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3443929</guid>
      <title>Mexloop hyperloop design could connect 42 million people in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new Hyperloop system being proposed by Mexican consortium Mexloop could reduce traveling time between Mexico City and Guadalajara to 38 minutes.Mexloop's design is one of the 10 winners of the Hyperloop One Global Challenge, Inhabitat reported.The Hyperloop would connect 42 million people in four major cities in Central Mexico: Mexico City, Quertaro, Len and Guadalajara.The proposed system would stretch 330 miles, and would take about 38 minutes the travel the entire route.Stations would be located close to airports, rail freight hubs and train stations in order to maximize transportation infrastructure efficiency, according to Hyperloop One. Mexloop says the Hyperloop would help the economy as well as ease traffic congestion. According to Mexloop, a Hyperloop system would only be two thirds of the cost of a high speed rail system. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The proposed Mexloop system 2. Hyperloop trip would take 38 minutes from Mexico City to Guadalajara3. Mexloop stations would be built near airports and train stations4. The Hyperloop system would be  of what a high speed system would costVOICEOVER (in English):  "Mexican consortium Mexloop is proposing a 330-mile hyperloop system that would connect four cities in Central Mexico: Mexico City, Quertaro, Len and Guadalajara." "The trip would take about 38 minutes compared to the current six hours it now takes to drive between the two cities." "Stations would be located close to airports, rail freight hubs, and train stations in order to maximize transportation infrastructure efficiency.""According to Mexloop, a hyperloop system would only be two thirds of the cost of a high speed rail system." SOURCES: Inhabitat, Hyperloop Onehttp://inhabitat.com/winning-mexloop-hyperloop-design-could-connect-42m-people-in-new-megalopolis/https://hyperloop-one.com/blog/how-hyperloop-could-transform-mexicos-megaregion***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 09:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/18/3443929/3443929_D668D9280FC045659E0CA13FB16A7F4A_170918_3443929_Mexloop_hyperloop_design_could_connect_42_millio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/18C/6B8/18C6B868428943988C9341C396307153_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Mexloop, Hyperloop One, Mexloop Hyperloop design, Hyperloop One pod, Hyperloop system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3443842</guid>
      <title>Human health also at risk from third-hand smoke</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMost people are familiar with the ill effects of first and second hand smoking on the body, but a new study has found that even third-hand exposure to tobacco smoke poses a health risk.According to a study published in Clinical Science, third-hand smoke comes from exhaled cigarette residue getting absorbed into surfaces, causing toxins to accumulate in like clothing, curtains, carpets, and furniture.Bystanders can be exposed to the toxins through skin absorption, with children especially vulnerable since they are in close contact with household surfaces.Researchers found that mice exposed to sections of fabric imbued with third-hand smoke were found to have liver damage after just one month. They suffered further molecular damage to both the liver and brain after two to six months.The exposure also increased insulin resistance in the mice, and upped the release of the stress hormone epinephrine, making them prone to type-2 diabetes and immune fatigue.Though the research was conducted on animals, it nevertheless draws attention to the dangers of cigarette smoke even on a third-hand basis.Further studies should investigate the effects on humans, and possibly determine what effect long-term exposure will have on the body.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Residue from cigarette smoke absorbed into clothing, furniture, carpets, surfaces2. Liver and brain damage in mice exposed to third-hand smoke fabrics 3. Insulin resistance; increased stress hormones lead to immune fatigue4. Third-hand smoke potentially harmful to children and older adultsVOICEOVER (in English): "Third-hand smoke comes from exhaled cigarette residue being absorbed into surfaces, causing toxins to accumulate in clothing, curtains, carpets, and furniture.""Bystanders can be exposed to the toxins through skin absorption, with children especially vulnerable since they are often in close contact with household surfaces.""Mice exposed to sections of fabric imbued with third-hand smoke were found to have liver damage after just one month. They suffered further molecular damage to both the liver and brain after two to six months.""The exposure also increased insulin resistance in the mice, and upped the release of the SOURCES: Clinical Science, University of California-Riversidehttp://www.clinsci.org/content/131/19/2409https://ucrtoday.ucr.edu/48710***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 08:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/18/3443842/3443842_D1B4F9B1CF8046B391B827E9800A0086_170918_3443842_Human_health_also_at_risk_from_third_hand_smoke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D9F/A84/D9FA8485193E447085D2EB87762EAC0F_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, third hand smoke, smoking, cigarette smoke, toxins, liver damage, brain damage, animal study, mice experiment, diabetes, immune fatigue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3443710</guid>
      <title>3,000 Swedish commuters using implanted microchips to pay for train tickets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAround 3,000 Swedish commuters have had biometric microchips implanted in their hands in order to pay for train tickets. Swedish rail company SJ first introduced the alternative pay option in June, according to BBC. Commuters who elect to have the RFID chip implanted under their skin are able to have their ticket loaded onto the device. The implants use Near Field Communication technology similar to contactless credit cards or mobile payments. When activated by a reader device a few centimeters away information can be transferred between the them using magnetic field induction. The train conductor then scans the microchip with a smartphone to complete the ticket transaction. The rail company does not implant the chip for customers. People need to have the procedure done own their own. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Commuter getting chip implanted 2. Ticket data being transferred to chip implant3. The chip implant uses Near Field Communication technology to complete ticket transactions4. Train conductor scanning a commuter's chip implantVOICEOVER (in English): "Around 3,000 Swedish commuters have had biometric microchips implanted in their hands in order to pay for train tickets." "Commuters who elect to have the RFID chip implanted under their skin are able to have their tickets loaded onto the device."  "The implants use Near Field Communication technology similar to contactless credit cards or mobile payments. When activated by a reader device a few centimeters away information can be transferred between the them using magnetic field induction." "The train conductor then scans the microchip with a smartphone to complete and verify the ticket transaction." SOURCES: BBC, Independent http://www.bbc.com/news/av/technology-41178142/rail-company-accepts-tickets-on-a-microchip-in-your-handhttp://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/sj-rail-train-tickets-hand-implant-microchip-biometric-sweden-a7793641.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/18/3443710/3443710_3184BF54AAB54BEB97757C9C24A671CB_170918_3443710_3_000_Swedish_commuters_using_implanted_microchi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/995/5D5/9955D551AC5E478089A1474EBFD12F2E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, RFID hand implants, RFID chip implants, Sweden RFID commuters, train commuters chip implants]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3443672</guid>
      <title>Shrinking Asian glaciers could lead to massive water shortages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEWith asian glaciers facing a massive melt by the end of the century, millions of people are at risk of water shortages  and it's all thanks to global warming.According to the World Wildlife Fund, the high mountains of Asia lie in a region surrounding the Tibetan plateau, and contains the largest store of permanent ice outside the North and South poles.Meltwater feeds into major rivers like the Indus, Yangtze, and Mekong and are used for drinking, hydroelectric power, and irrigation.Reuters reports that researchers from Utrecht University predict that Asian high mountain glaciers will lose a third of their mass by 2100 if the global temperature rises 1.5 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels. If temperatures increase 3.5, 4, or 6 degrees, losses could reach 49, 51, and  65%, respectively.Glacial loss could affect the region's water supply and lead to shortages. At the same time, accelerated melting could trigger intense flooding, especially when combined with climate change-induced heavy rains and super typhoons.High-warming scenarios carry worse consequences, including massive sea-level rise, floods, droughts, loss of species, and even disease.The only way to avoid such a dismal future is by minimizing global temperature rise, and for that, we need to double, even triple efforts to combat climate change.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ice store in Asian high mountains2. Meltwater feeds into river systems, used for drinking, farming, electricity3. Asian glaciers to lose a third of their mass in 2100 if global temps rise by 1.54. Water shortages, potentially catastrophic floodingVOICEOVER (in English): "The high mountains of Asia lie in a region surrounding the Tibetan plateau, and contains the largest store of permanent ice outside the North and South poles.""Meltwater feeds into major rivers like the Indus, Yangtze, and Mekong and are used for drinking, hydroelectric power, and irrigation.""Scientists predict that Asian high mountain glaciers will lose a third of their mass by 2100 if the global temperature rises 1.5 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels. If temperatures increase 3.5, 4, or 6 degrees, losses could reach 49, 51, and  65%, respectively.""Glacial loss could affect the region's water supply and lead to shortages. At the same time, accelerated melting could trigger intense flooding, especially when combined with climate change-induced heavy rains and super typhoons."SOURCES: Reuters, AFP (via South China Morning Post)https://www.reuters.com/article/us-asia-climate-water/millions-at-risk-of-water-shortages-as-asian-glaciers-melt-study-idUSKCN1BP2EBhttp://www.scmp.com/news/asia/article/2111086/asias-glaciers-will-melt-sharply-global-warming-centurys-end-climate-study***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/18/3443672/3443672_05682924C0DA4F068650C771B0E423C4_170918_3443672_Shrinking_Asian_glaciers_could_lead_to_massive_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F93/9E6/F939E6B078F54C199C12BA1292F03F9E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, climate change, global warming, asian glaciers, melting glaciers, glaciers, glacial melt, high mountain glaciers, water shortage, paris agreement]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3444844</guid>
      <title>Enormous Antarctic iceberg now adrift at sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA massive iceberg around the size of Delaware has broken off from Antarctica and is now floating out to sea.Recent satellite photos show the A68 iceberg appearing to move away from the Larsen C ice shelf, the Independent reported. The iceberg is over 2200 sq miles, weighs approximately a trillion tons and has a volume twice that of Lake Erie, according to Scientific American. Professor Stef Lhermitte, of Delft University in the Netherlands posted the images on Twitter with a caption, "After some initial back-and-forth movement, Larsen C's iceberg A68 seems on drift now." Experts now believe the iceberg will float northeast and slowly make its way out into the open seas of the Southern Ocean, Business Insider reported. Scientists are concerned that A68 could break up into smaller pieces and then drift into shipping lanes. Pieces too small to track by satellite could pose major risks to passing ships.    Some researchers have said the calving of the iceberg was a normal event, not caused by global warming, according to the Independent.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The A68 iceberg is the size of Delaware2. A68 is over 2200 sq miles, weighs about 1 trillion tons and has a volume twice that of Lake Erie3. A68 breaking up into smaller pieces 4. A cargo ship approaching smaller icebergs in open ocean VOICEOVER (in English): "A massive iceberg around the size of Delaware that had broken off from Antarctica is now floating out into the Weddell Sea.""Recent satellite photos show the A68 iceberg appearing to move away from the Larsen C ice shelf. It's over 2,200 square miles, weighs about 1 trillion tons and has a volume twice that of Lake Erie.""Experts say the iceberg will break up into smaller pieces and float northeast as it makes its way out into the open waters of the Southern Ocean.""Scientists are concerned the smaller pieces could then drift into shipping lanes. Pieces too small to track by satellite could pose major risks to passing ships."    SOURCES: Independent, Business Insider, Scientific Americanhttp://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/antarctic-iceberg-a68-larsen-c-ice-shelf-quarter-size-wales-drifting-out-sea-a7950746.htmlhttp://uk.businessinsider.com/larsen-c-iceberg-satellite-pictures-2017-8/#deimos-1-and-deimos-2-follow-similar-orbits-and-work-together-to-image-the-same-spots-on-the-ground-in-medium-and-very-high-resolution-1https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/5-things-to-know-about-the-trillion-ton-iceberg/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 11:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/19/3444844/3444844_85FD4929E13643D188ACE078BF8EBBDB_170919_3444844_Enormous_Antarctic_iceberg_now_adrift_at_sea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4DC/534/4DC5344D746E438AA6049AEA93CD18F8_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, A68 iceberg, Larsen C ice shelf, Antarctica, A68 iceberg adrift]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3444763</guid>
      <title>North Korean missile launch prompts Japan, U.S. and South Korea military drills</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAircraft from the U.S., Japanese and South Korean air forces were involved in military drills this week in response to the North Korean missile launch over Japan on Sept. 14. According to a U.S. Pacific Command news release, 4 American F35Bs and 2 B1-B bombers, along with 4 Korean F15s and 4 Japanese F2s flew in sequential military drills this week.South Korean and American aircraft dropped live munitions at the Pilsung training range in South Korea.The exercises were conducted in response to North Korea's missile launch over Japan on September 14, according to the news release. Japanese and American aircraft flew over waters near the south west coast of Japan.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of American, South Korean and Japanese aircraft involved2. Depiction of military drill in South Korea3. Depiction of South Korean and American aircraft flying4. Depiction of military drills near JapanVOICEOVER (in English): "Four American F35Bs and two B1-B bombers, along with four Korean F15s and four Japanese F2s flew in sequential military drills this week.""South Korean and American aircraft dropped live munitions at the Pilsung training range in South Korea.""According to U.S. Pacific Command, the exercises were conducted in response to North Korea's missile launch over Japan on September 14.""The Japanese and American aircraft flew over waters near the south west coast of Japan." SOURCES: U.S. Pacific Command, Reutershttp://www.pacom.mil/Media/News/News-Article-View/Article/1314000/japanese-korean-and-us-aircraft-conduct-show-of-force-in-response-to-north-kore/http://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles/korean-peninsula-draws-range-of-military-drills-in-show-of-force-against-north-korea-idUSKCN1BT0CK***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 10:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/19/3444763/3444763_0222C809061B49FCB43546A9FB44929F_170919_3444763_North_Korean_missile_launch_prompts_Japan__U_S___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/735/FA9/735FA978A37440649F51F36C6380F642_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, North korea missile test, us air force, japan air force, south korean air force, kim jong un]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3444625</guid>
      <title>Venus' mysterious night side revealed for the first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFor the first time ever, scientists are studying Venus' mysterious night side, and have found that it's vastly different from its day side.It takes Venus 225 days to revolve around the sun, and 243 days to fully rotate on its axis. As a result, "night" and "day" on the planet last a longer time than on Earth.So far, the day side has been studied extensively, but the night side has been notoriously difficult to observe, until now.According to the European Space Agency, Venus' atmosphere consists of strong winds blowing 60 times faster than the planet's rotation. This super-rotation has been assumed to be uniform in both sides, but new data from the Venus Express spacecraft shows the winds are more chaotic and irregular on the night side.Night side clouds formed large, wavy, filament-like patterns not seen in day clouds, and are dominated by stationary waves, which remain still and do not move with the atmosphere.Stationary waves were thought to form specifically over steep, mountainous areas, but were recently detected in the planet's southern hemisphere - an area with low elevation. The waves were likewise assumed to be rising up through the cloud from the surface, but were mysteriously missing from the lower and intermediate cloud levels.Scientists have yet to explore what this means, but will likely need to come up with new, updated models of Venus to help them figure it out.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Venus' revolution and rotation2. Super-rotation on Venus' surface3. Stationary waves4. Mountains believes to cause stationary wavesVOICEOVER (in English): "It takes Venus 225 days to revolve around the sun, and 243 days to fully rotate on its axis. As a result, 'night' and 'day' on the planet last a longer time than on Earth.""Venus' atmosphere consists of strong winds blowing 60 times faster than the planet's rotation. This super-rotation has been assumed to be uniform in both sides, but new data shows the winds are more chaotic and irregular on the night side.""Night side clouds formed large, wavy, filament-like patterns not seen in day clouds, and are dominated by stationary waves, which remain still and do not move with the atmosphere.""Stationary waves were thought to form specifically over steep, mountainous areas, but were recently detected in the planet's southern hemisphere - an area with low elevation. SOURCES: Nature, European Space Agencyhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-017-0187http://sci.esa.int/venus-express/59498-venus-mysterious-night-side-revealed/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 07:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/19/3444625/3444625_210B93C3064845308AAC8FDE1DFD41EB_170919_3444625_Venus__mysterious_night_side_revealed_for_the_fi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/55D/1AC/55D1AC819D8843459B76215D8F7A93DF_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, venus, night side, planets, solar system, outer space, milky way, astronomy, european space agency, venus express]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3444590</guid>
      <title>Gravity on gas giants may have thrown water to Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A study published in the journal Icarus, suggest that Earths water is a simple byproduct of giant planet growth.During the formation of gas giants such as Saturn or Jupiter, they enter a period of rapid growth. This destabilized nearby water-rich space rocks known as planetesimals, bringing them into the planetary orbit.Next, the gravity there would have propelled these to the inner or outer solar system.The researchers speculate some were sent in an inward direction, toward some early form of Earth and seeded it with water.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of water on Earth from space.2. Depiction of how planetesimals interact with Jupiter and Saturn3. Overview of planetesimal movement from Jupiter and Saturn]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 06:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/19/3444590/3444590_262362584CE84814BCC2B4B276DB38FB_170919_3444590_Gravity_on_gas_giants_may_have_thrown_water_to_E_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/300/5F2/3005F24A6FF54FF29C83E3C0CA1C6ABD_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,News,where did water come from in the universe,did water come from space,planetesimals,water,h20,origin of water]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3444434</guid>
      <title>Colorado route chosen for Hyperloop One project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEHyperloop One announced Colorado would be one of the 10 finalists in its global competition to identify the best potential Hyperloop routes.  The Colorado Department of Transportation is working with the Hyperloop company to carry out a feasibility study for the proposed route between Cheyenne, Denver and Pueblo, Techcrunch reported.The feasibility study could cost up to $1 million and take years to complete, CBS 4 reported. The proposed route would stretch 360 miles and link 10 urban centers around the state, with the potential to connect over 4,800,000 people, according to Techcrunch. A Hyperloop trip from Denver to Pueblo would take 15 minutes, while Denver to Fort Collins would only take 9 minutes. Denver to Vail would also be 9 minutes. Three other U.S. routes were chosen by Hyperloop as finalists: Chicago-Columbus-Pittsburgh, Miami-Orlando and Dallas-Laredo-Houston. Hyperloop One plans for its first functional prototypes to be running as early as 2020.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Passengers boarding a Hyperloop One passenger pod2. The proposed Rocky Mountain Hyperloop routes3. A Hyperloop passenger pod traveling through a Hyperloop tube4. The US has four proposed routesVOICEOVER (in English): "Hyperloop One has announced that Colorado is one of the 10 finalists in its global competition to identify the best potential Hyperloop routes.""The proposed route would stretch 360 miles and link 10 urban centers around the state, with the potential to connect over 4.8 million people.""A Hyperloop trip from Denver to Pueblo would take 15 minutes, while Denver to Fort Collins would only take 9 minutes. Denver to Vail would also be 9 minutes." "Hyperloop One also selected three other U.S. routes as finalists: Chicago-Columbus-Pittsburgh, Miami-Orlando and Dallas-Laredo-Houston."SOURCES: CBS 4, 9 News, Techcrunch  http://denver.cbslocal.com/2017/09/14/hyperloop-travel-cdot/http://www.9news.com/mobile/article/news/local/colorado-route-selected-for-hyperloop-project/474823111https://techcrunch.com/2017/09/14/hyperloop-one-and-colorado-to-conduct-hyperloop-feasibility-study/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 03:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/19/3444434/3444434_09466FE1B70F45A0A1E3C140CE35677D_170919_3444434_Colorado_route_chosen_for_Hyperloop_One_project_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/446/2B7/4462B72628944AFDB61AA848ADA6ED0C_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hyperloop, Hyperloop Colorado, Hyperloop One, Hyperloop One Global Challenge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3445446</guid>
      <title>More than 100 people killed in Mexico earthquake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA 7.1 magnitude earthquake killed more than 100 people in central Mexico on Tuesday.According to the Los Angeles Times, 44 buildings collapsed and 30 people were killed in Mexico City. Millions are currently without power.Soldiers, police officers and firefighters, as well as residents are working to save people from damaged buildings.Earlier this month an 8.1 magnitude earthquake killed 98 people in south Mexico.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of earthquake2. Depiction of destroyed home3. Depiction of rescuers working to save peopleVOICEOVER (in English): "A 7.1 magnitude earthquake killed at least 138 people in central Mexico on Tuesday and left millions without power.""According to the Los Angeles Times, 44 buildings collapsed and 30 people were killed in Mexico City.""Soldiers, police officers and firefighters, as well as residents are working to save people from damaged buildings."SOURCES: Reuters, Los Angeles Timeshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-quake-usgs/strong-quake-near-mexico-city-kills-more-than-138-idUSKCN1BU2IJhttp://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-mexico-earthquake-20170919-story.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 08:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/20/3445446/3445446_FCA335292FDC4FE381B7DAFC379E1887_170920_3445446_More_than_100_people_killed_in_Mexico_earthquake_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BCF/677/BCF677634EE94D5F8077ECA01C81A1AB_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mexico earthquake 2017, earthquake in mexico, central mexico, mexico city, natural disaster, earthquakes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3445415</guid>
      <title>Parasites impact global salmon supply</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEParasites infestations at salmon farms across the world are causing prices of the fish to surge.According to an Associated Press report on ABC, parasitic sea lice have infected salmon farms in Canada, Scotland, Norway, the United States and Chile.Once a parasite infects the salmon, it becomes inedible. Previously, salmon were fed a pesticide to defend against the sea lice. This was effective until 2009, when the lice began to overcome it and spread internationally.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of fish farm and infestation locations2. Depiction of louse on salmon3. Depiction of fish farm getting infectedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Associated Press, parasitic sea lice have infected salmon farms in Chile, the United States, Canada, Scotland and Norway.""Once a parasite infects the salmon, it becomes inedible.""Previously Salmon were fed a pesticide to defend against the sea lice. "This was reportedly effective until 2009, when the lice began to overcome it and spread globally."SOURCES: ABC (Associated Press), Newsweekhttp://abcnews.go.com/Lifestyle/wireStory/lice-salmon-parasite-plagues-global-industry-49922377http://www.newsweek.com/no-more-salmon-sushi-if-parasitic-sea-lice-have-their-way-667215***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 07:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/20/3445415/3445415_2BF6D5FC82144BA6A598C108817FBE2E_170920_3445415_Parasites_impact_global_salmon_supply_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B70/7F8/B707F8E4A8C94A6FB3C3A3E12A7DFADD_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sea louse, sea lice, salmon lice, salmon demand, salmon prices, salmon louse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3445401</guid>
      <title>New state-of-the-art NFL helmet designed to lower risk of concussions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThis NFL season about 70 players are wearing a new state-of-the-art helmet designed to lower the risk of concussions. The Vicis Zero1, which sells for $1,500, was specifically designed to soften the blows NFL players take to their heads during games, CNN Money reported. The NFL and NFL Players Association have tested dozens of different helmet concepts in recent years with the Vicis ranking highest in safety, according to CNN Money. The helmet is made of four different protective layers. The outer shell is made from flexible thermoplastic that compresses to absorb shock, then rebounds, much like a car bumper. Next is a layer of more than 500 polymer columns that can twist and move laterally, reducing the impact of rotational acceleration, a major cause of concussions, the Washington Post reported.  Underneath that is a hard inner shell that helps prevent skull fractures and brain hemorrhages. Below that is a layer of memory foam to provide the player comfort.  About half of NFL teams have put in orders for the Vicis helmet. NFL players get to choose the helmet they wear from an approved NFL list.  The NFL has been looking to address concussions, especially as the league as faced increasing scrutiny. Medical experts and players are concerned that repeated concussions increase the likelihood of developing chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE), a degenerative brain disease.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A player wearing a Vicis helmet 2. The flexibility of the outer helmet layer3. The layer of polymer columns absorbing multiple hits4. The hard inner shell and memory foam around player's headVOICEOVER (in English): "The Vicis Zero1 was specifically designed to soften the blows NFL players take to their heads during games.""The helmet is made of four different protective layers. The outer shell is made from flexible thermoplastic that compresses to absorb shock, then rebounds, much like a car bumper." "Next is a layer of  more than 500 polymer columns that can twist and move laterally, reducing the impact of rotational acceleration, a major cause of concussions.""Underneath that is a hard inner shell that helps prevent skull fractures and brain hemorrhages. Below that, a layer of memory foam provides the player comfort."  SOURCES: CNN Money, CNBC, Washington Post http://money.cnn.com/2017/09/16/news/companies/vicis-nfl-helmet-concussions-safety/index.htmlhttps://www.cnbc.com/2017/09/10/the-nfl-calls-vicis-zero1-helmets-the-safest-yet.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/high-tech-helmets-designed-to-lower-risk-of-concussions-make-nfl-debut/2017/09/11/a18c2c34-973c-11e7-87fc-c3f7ee4035c9_story.html?utm_term=.fba99663182e***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/20/3445401/3445401_557B28EBE10E4BF4ACC29A4076B8B556_170920_3445401_New_state_of_the_art_NFL_helmet_designed_to_lowe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3C5/754/3C575435DB2C43E7A75014B31A21FA96_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, NFL Vicis Zero1 helmet, Vicis Zero1 helmet, Vicis helmet, NFL concussions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3445231</guid>
      <title>Dubai to operate world's largest concentrated solar power project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Dubai government has approved an extension to the world's largest single-site solar farm. The government has given the green light to a 700-MW addition to the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Solar Park, New Atlas reported. The solar park is located about 50 kms south of Dubai, with the first phase inaugurated back in 2013, according to New Atlas. It currently has 2.3 million photovoltaic solar panels with a 200-MW capacity. Capacity is expected to grow to 5,000 MW by 2030. Developers say the park will eventually cover 214 sq km with a 260-m solar tower taking center stage.The solar plant produces power by using lenses and reflectors to concentrate sunlight in order to heat fluids, which then in turn produce steam to drive a turbine. An advantage to this type of solar system is that it's more flexible because energy can be stored as heat and used as needed. A drawback is that they are more expensive than photovoltaic solar plants. Construction of the new extension is set to begin in 2020. The contract was awarded to a consortium of Saudi Arabia's ACWA Power and Shanghai Electric.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A concentrated solar power receiver tower and surrounding solar panels2. Capacity is expected to grow to 5,000 MW by 20303. The 260-m tall solar tower4. How a concentrated solar power plant works5. Concentrated solar power plants are more flexible and more expensive than photovoltaic solar plantsVOICEOVER (in English): "The Dubai government has given the green light to a 700-MW addition to the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Solar Park.""It currently has 2.3 million photovoltaic solar panels with a 200-MW capacity. Capacity is expected to grow to 5,000 MW by 2030." "Developers say the park will eventually cover 214 sq kms with a 260-m solar tower taking center stage.""The solar plant produces power by using lenses and reflectors to concentrate sunlight in order to heat fluids, which then in turn produce steam to drive a turbine." "The advantage of this type of solar system is that it's more flexible because energy can be stored as heat and used as needed. A drawback is that they are more expensive than photovoltaic solar plants." SOURCES: New Atlashttp://newatlas.com/dubai-worlds-largest-solar-park/51382/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 01:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/20/3445231/3445231_9618161F8EFF49F7BC60009530C3212C_170920_3445231_Dubai_to_operate_world_s_largest_concentrated_so_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6D4/908/6D49089F27864E84915D68FF938458EC_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Concentrated Solar Power plant, Concentrated Solar Power, Dubai, Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Solar Park]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3446214</guid>
      <title>Scientists locate Italian supervolcano's magma source</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists have located the magma source of an Italian supervolcano that's considered one of the most dangerous in the world.Campi Flegrei is a volcanic caldera to the west of Naples which last erupted in 1538, but was responsible for a series of small earthquakes in the 1980s, according to a new study published in Scientific Reports.Researchers have long puzzled about where the caldera's magma was coming from, and have now pinpointed the location of a hot zone about 4 kilometers under the nearby city of Pozzuoli.From 1982 and 1984, rising gas and magma caused ground in the crater to swell, but was prevented from rising to the surface by a deep rock formation. The magma instead spread out laterally, causing minor earthquakes.The caldera has grown hotter since, and with pressure building, scientists fear it could soon erupt and put the entire region at risk.Volcanologists cannot say for sure what the scale of any future eruption could be, and are closely monitoring Campi Flegrei.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Camp Flegrei volcanic caldera2. Hot zone located under the city of Pozzuoli3. Potential eruption in the 1980s blocked by a rock formation; magma spread out, causing small earthquakes4. Temperature rising, pressure building within caldera could result in a massive eruptionVOICEOVER (in English): "Campi Flegrei is a volcanic caldera to the west of Naples which last erupted in 1538, but was responsible for a series of small earthquakes in the 1980s.""Researchers who have long puzzled about where the caldera's magma was coming from, have now pinpointed the location of a hot zone about 4 kilometers under the nearby city of Pozzuoli.""From 1982 and 1984, rising gas and magma caused ground in the crater to swell, but was prevented from rising to the surface by a deep rock formation. The magma instead spread out laterally, causing minor earthquakes.""The caldera has grown hotter since, and with pressure building, scientists fear it could soon erupt and put the entire region at risk."SOURCES: Scientific Reports, University of Aberdeenhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-08192-7https://www.abdn.ac.uk/news/11141/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 08:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/21/3446214/3446214_52FEDC45DD7D4D72AF7772CA346FDD89_170921_3446214_Scientists_locate_Italian_supervolcano_s_magma_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DA1/2C9/DA12C9B182804767863EA552CD04B66B_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, campi flegrei, volcano, volcanic eruption, supervolcano, magma, eruption, magma reservoir, earthquake, natural disaster, pozzuoli, naples]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3447397</guid>
      <title>Nerf guns can cause eye injuries, say doctors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEDoctors at a London eye hospital are warning against the dangers of nerf guns, after at least three people reportedly suffered serious injuries from getting hit in the eye.CBS reports that nerf guns are toys that shoot soft foam projectiles. Legitimate replacement bullets are recommended and widely available, but generic ones are cheaper. They're also harder, and have more potential to cause injury.Nerf video tutorials abound online, with some giving instructions on how to modify the toy gun to make it shoot faster and farther.According to three cases reported in the British Medical Journal, patients who were hit in the eye reportedly complained of blurred vision and pain.Doctors soon discovered their eyes were inflamed, and blood was pooling in the anterior chamber. Both the cornea and retina had also developed swelling.Fortunately, after being given eyedrops, their sight returned to normal after a few weeks.Such eye trauma may not always lead to permanent vision loss, but could result in a long-term condition like glaucoma. Experts recommend wearing safety glasses to minimize the danger.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Harder Nerf gun projectiles can damage the eye2. Victims' symptoms include eye pain and blurred vision3. Eye inflammation and pooling of blood in the back of the eye4. Doctors recommend protective eyewear when playing with Nerf gunsVOICEOVER (in English): "Nerf guns are toys that shoot soft foam projectiles. Official replacement bullets are widely available, but generic ones are cheaper. They're also harder, and have more potential to cause injury.""Patients who were hit in the eye with Nerf projectiles reportedly complained of blurred vision and pain.""Doctors later discovered their eyes were inflamed, and blood was pooling in the anterior chamber. Both the cornea and retina had also developed swelling.""Such eye trauma may not always lead to permanent vision loss, but could result in a long-term condition like glaucoma. Experts recommend wearing safety glasses to minimize the danger."SOURCES: British Medical Journal, CBS, BBChttp://casereports.bmj.com/content/2017/bcr-2017-220967https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nerf-guns-can-cause-serious-eye-damage-doctors-warn/http://www.bbc.com/news/health-41307816***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/22/3447397/3447397_E073902F60F140BA8FACF2FAD0E6D1C4_170922_3447397_Nerf_guns_can_cause_eye_injuries__say_doctors_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/690/075/6900753FE64B4723B72A1956913524C5_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nerf gun, nerf, eye damage, eye injury, toy gun, uveitis, hyphema, safety glasses, safety]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3447299</guid>
      <title>CCleaner malware targeted tech firms</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA Windows utility tool meant to clean and optimize PCs has instead exposed hundreds of thousands to malicious software.According to a report from Cisco's Talos Intelligence research team, hackers embedded malware into the CCleaner software, exposing nearly 700,000 to an attack.The compromised CCleaner version was distributed between August 15 and September 12, and taken down shortly after it was discovered.Data from the malware's seized command and control center shows it specifically targeted high-profile tech firms. It scanned and profiled infected machines, and sent system information to an external server.If a system met the malware's requirements, a second payload would be deployed to create a backdoor which the attackers could use to spy and steal company intel.Researchers examining the malware describe it as complex and sophisticated, evidenced by the fact that it went undetected for weeks.Though a partial list of affected companies was released, there's no news yet on the damage the malware may have caused.Avast, the company that owns CCleaner, says it's working with authorities to identify the perps and other servers they used in the attack.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Malware embedded in CCleaner software infects 700,000 computers2. Malware targeted tech companies, retrieved computer system information 3. Second payload deployed to selected computers creates backdoor that allows spying, information stealingVOICEOVER (in English): "Hackers were found to have embedded malware into the CCleaner software, exposing nearly 700,000 to an attack.""Data from the malware's seized command and control center shows it specifically targeted high-profile tech firms. It scanned and profiled infected machines, and sent system information to an external server.""If a system met the malware's requirements, a second payload would be deployed to create a backdoor which the attackers could use to spy and steal company intel."SOURCES: Talos Intelligencehttp://blog.talosintelligence.com/2017/09/avast-distributes-malware.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 12:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/22/3447299/3447299_F6682216605D41518DC6A20831236AB2_170922_3447299_CCleaner_malware_targeted_tech_firms_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F15/3CD/F153CDDDD0194DF8BE93058D6A204F82_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, malware, CCleaner, hacker, hacked, data breach, tech companies, malicious software, supply chain malware, Avast]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3446985</guid>
      <title>Body's 'bad fat' could be transformed into brown fat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe body's "bad fat" could be made to transform into brown fat by blocking specific proteins, researchers have found. The majority of fat in the body is unhealthy "white" tissue found around the waist, hips and thighs, the Guardian reported.  Smaller amounts of "brown" fat located around the neck and shoulders are packed with mitochondria that generate heat by burning up excess calories. Scientists from the Washington University School of Medicine found a way to turn white fat into "beige" fat, a healthier fat with some weight loss capabilities, in lab mice. "Our research suggest that by targeting a protein in white fat, we can convert bad fat into a fat that fights obesity," Dr. Irfan Lodhi said. Beige fat was discovered in adults in 2015 and found to behave like brown fat. Researchers found that by blocking the PexRAP protein in mice, white fat was transformed into calorie burning beige fat. Lodhi's team says the next step is to find a safe way to block the PexRAP protein in humans.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of white fat throughout body2. Location of mitochondria packed brown fat throughout body3. Researchers were able to transform white fat into beige fat in lab miceVOICEOVER (in English): "The majority of fat in the body is unhealthy "white" tissue found around the waist, hips and thighs.""Smaller amounts of "brown" fat located around the neck and shoulders are packed with mitochondria that generate heat when burning up excess calories." "Scientists have found a way to turn white fat in lab mice into "beige" fat, a healthier fat with some weight loss capabilities by blocking the PexRAP protein." SOURCES: Guardian, Cell Reportshttps://www.theguardian.com/society/2017/sep/19/bodys-bad-fat-could-be-altered-to-combat-obesity-say-scientistshttp://www.cell.com/cell-reports/fulltext/S2211-1247(17)31219-6***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 08:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/22/3446985/3446985_8FD86D8BEC384EC78089B0ADF82B51DB_170922_3446985_Body_s__bad_fat__could_be_transformed_into_brown_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/263/A69/263A691CCB1D4A5492458003A3F2DC8D_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, white fat, brown fat, beige fat, PexRAP protein]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3446972</guid>
      <title>NASA spacecraft to slingshot around Earth on Friday</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA's OSIRIS-Rex spacecraft will fly by Earth on Friday as part of its mission to investigate the Bennu asteroid.According to the space agency, OSIRIS-Rex will slingshot around Earth, and in doing so, use the planet's orbit to get a 8,500 mile per hour speed boost to help it on its journey to Bennu.The Bennu asteroid was discovered in 1999. Its 500m height is taller than Taipei 101, one of the tallest buildings in the world. NASA believes investigation of it may lead to a deeper understanding of some of the universe's most fundamental questions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of spacecraft2. Depiction of spacecraft doing slingshot around Earth3. Overview of asteroid4. The spacecraft touching down on the asteroidVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's OSIRIS-Rex spacecraft will fly-by Earth on Friday as part of its mission to investigate the Bennu asteroid.""The spacecraft will slingshot around Earth and use the planet's orbit to get a 8,500 mile per hour speed boost to help it on its way to Bennu.""The Bennu asteroid was discovered in 1999. Its 500m height is taller than Taipei 101, one of the tallest buildings in the world. NASA believes investigation of it may lead to a deeper understanding of some of the universe's most fundamental questions."SOURCES: NASA, Popular Mechanicshttps://www.nasa.gov/osiris-rex/https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2017/asteroid-bound-spacecraft-to-slingshot-past-earthhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B5suKnZxCpIhttp://www.popularmechanics.com/space/solar-system/news/a28291/nasa-spacecraft-approaches-earth-for-gravity-slingshot/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 08:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/22/3446972/3446972_905BB764163E432992E85571AD1EC924_170922_3446972_NASA_spacecraft_to_slingshot_around_Earth_on_Fri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CAE/266/CAE266E07E354D03B047FF9588F2C74D_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nasa spacecraft, gravitational slingshot, osiris-rex, bennu asteroid, gravitational slingshot animation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3446953</guid>
      <title>UK invests $88m in major US physics experiment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe UK pledged an $88 million investment toward the U.S. government's yet to be completed subterranean particle physics experiment this week.The Deep Underground Neutrino Experiment, also known as DUNE, begins at the Long Baseline Neutrino Facility at the Fermilab in Illinois. It ends 800 miles away at the Sanford Underground Research Facility in South Dakota.When finished, it will produce the world's highest-intensity neutrino beam using the Fermilab's proton accelerator.This beam will travel westward through the Earth's mantle to South Dakota where scientists will gather data on the neutrino particles.Scientists believe the DUNE project could lead to a deeper understanding of these weightless subatomic particles and how the universe came to be.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Distance laboratories involved in DUNE2. Depiction of DUNE3. Depiction of neutrino beam4. Depiction of neutrino particleVOICEOVER (in English): "The Deep Underground Neutrino Experiment, also known as DUNE, begins at the Long Baseline Neutrino Facility at the Fermilab in Illinois." "It ends 800 miles away at the Sanford Underground Research Facility in South Dakota.""The UK pledged an $88 million investment toward the yet to be completed project.""When finished, it'll produce the world's highest-intensity neutrino beam using the Fermilab's proton accelerator.""This beam will travel westward through the Earth's mantle to South Dakota where scientists will gather data on the neutrino particles."Scientists believe the DUNE project could lead to a deeper understanding of these weightless subatomic particles and how the universe came to be." SOURCES: Fermilab, Indiana University, The White House http://lbnf.fnal.govhttp://www.indiana.edu/~rcapub/v30n2/neutrino.shtmlhttps://www.whitehouse.gov/blog/2017/09/20/united-states-and-united-kingdom-sign-landmark-science-and-technology-agreement***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 08:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/22/3446953/3446953_A873DC002D4F45D786F79EC4D7F1E7A0_170922_3446953_UK_invests__88m_in_major_US_physics_experiment_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2D9/603/2D9603B164D9443197F0AEAE6A478512_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, fermilab, fermilab uk investment, dune project, deep underground neutrino experiment, DUNE, neutrinos, what are neutrinos, sanford lab, surf lab]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3446807</guid>
      <title>'Gloomy' octopuses more social than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe "gloomy" octopus is widely thought to be an antisocial creature, but new research may change this thinking.A study published in the journal Marine and Freshwater Behaviour and Physiology details the discovery of a site close to Jervis Bay, Australia that is occupied by 15 of these octopuses. Scientists observed complex social behavior in the creatures, including, mating, mate defense, as well as eviction from the site and exclusion of some from the group.The study provides scientists with a deeper understanding of one of nature's most difficult to study creatures.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of octopus swimming2. Location of site3. Depiction of octopus behaviorVOICEOVER (in English): "The octopus tetricus, more commonly known as the "gloomy" octopus, is widely thought to be antisocial." "This thinking may soon change." "New research has found a site in close to Jervis Bay on Australia's east coast occupied by 15 of the octopuses.""Scientists observed complex social behavior in the creatures, including, mating, mate defense, as well as eviction from the site and exclusion of some from the group."SOURCES:  Marine and Freshwater Behaviour and Physiology, Smithsonian Magazine http://www.tandfonline.com/eprint/SuKqGmXPA8zJdrkjkSRE/fullhttp://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/octopus-city-observed-180964936/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 03:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/22/3446807/3446807_0C5C159731B54F05B85C2BD060E6782F_170922_3446807__Gloomy__octopuses_more_social_than_previously_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DB1/F1F/DB1F1F8A78F54732B38F38D4A6F7437F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, octopus city, octopus, octopus city australia, gloomy octopus, octopus behaviour, jervis bay]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3448903</guid>
      <title>Trump administration unveils new travel restrictions on visitors from eight countries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Trump administration has unveiled an updated travel ban that blocks certain foreign nationals from entering the country.According to the proclamation released by the White House, beginning October 18, new U.S. travel restrictions will be implemented for visitors from eight countries  an expansion of the controversial travel ban that took effect in January.The original ban included Iraq, Iran, Syria, Somalia, Yemen, Sudan, and Libya. Iraq and Sudan have been removed, while North Korea, Chad, and Venezuela were added to the list.The new rules vary per country, but will not affect legal permanent residents, nor those who already hold a valid U.S. visa.Restrictions on Venezuela focus on government officials and their families.Despite not being included in the ban, Iraqi citizens will reportedly face enhanced scrutiny when visiting the country, reports Reuters.In justifying the ban, officials claim other governments had met U.S. requests for biometric passports or information on terrorists and criminals, but that the eight banned countries failed to do the same.Trump's initial travel ban has been widely criticized for religious discrimination, but despite the addition of non-Muslim nations into the new ban, critics believe it is still, essentially, a Muslim ban.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New travel restrictions on visitors from eight countries2. Original travel ban restrictions3. Specific restrictions on Venezuela, Iraq4. Banned countries failed to comply with U.S. requestsVOICEOVER (in English): "Beginning October 18, new U.S. travel restrictions will be implemented for visitors from eight countries  an expansion of the controversial travel ban that took effect in January.""The original ban included Iraq, Iran, Syria, Somalia, Yemen, Sudan, and Libya. Iraq and Sudan have been removed, while North Korea, Chad, and Venezuela were added to the list.""Restrictions on Venezuela focus on government officials and their families.""Despite not being included in the ban, Iraqi citizens will reportedly face enhanced scrutiny when visiting the country.""In justifying the ban, officials claim other governments had met U.S. requests for biometric passports or information on terrorists and criminals, but that the eight banned countries failed to do the same."SOURCES: The White House, Washington Post, Reutershttps://www.whitehouse.gov/the-press-office/2017/09/24/enhancing-vetting-capabilities-and-processes-detecting-attempted-entryhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-administration-changes-travel-ban-countries/2017/09/24/1fef7cfe-a140-11e7-ade1-76d061d56efa_story.html?utm_term=.347f749b89a2http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-trump-proclamation/trump-slaps-travel-restrictions-on-north-korea-venezuela-in-sweeping-new-ban-idUSKCN1BZ13Y?il=0***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 09:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/25/3448903/3448903_9DF73D6520D24B108A1844CCF0329777_170925_3448903_Trump_administration_unveils_new_travel_restrict_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E16/718/E16718965B384C058FCDB1E30553DD78_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, travel ban, travel restrictions, trump ban, donald trump, travel, passport, white house]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3448800</guid>
      <title>Far right surges in Germany election</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEGerman chancellor Angela Merkel has secured her fourth term as Germany's leader, despite massive gains by the country's far-right.According to the BBC, Angela Merkel's CDU-CSU coalition won with 33 percent of the vote, while the social democrats took around 20 percent and the far right AfD secured 13 percent.The result will likely see a governing coalition between Merkel's conservatives and the fourth place Free Democrats, reported the BBC.The election saw the heavily anti-migrant Alternative for Germany, or AfD, take third place in the vote. They want to close Europe's borders, install identity checks in Germany and ban minarets. The party also believes Germany isn't compatible with Islam.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of results 2. Depiction of future government3. Explanation of the AfDVOICEOVER (in English): "Angela Merkel's conservative coalition won with 33 percent of all votes, the social democrats took 20 percent while the far right Alternative for Germany party surged to 13 percent.""The result will likely see a governing coalition between conservatives and the fourth place Free Democrats.""The election saw the heavily anti-migrant AfD take third place in the vote. "They want to close Europe's borders, install identity checks in Germany and ban minarets. "They believe Germany isn't compatible with Islam."SOURCES: BBC, Sydney Morning Herald,http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-41376577http://www.smh.com.au/world/who-is-the-afd-alternative-for-germany-party-20170925-gyo0v5.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 07:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/25/3448800/3448800_0E3A5F48ECD24B60B29CA5F5DD39AC57_170925_3448800_Far_right_surges_in_Germany_election_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DB6/56F/DB656F75E85E467385C75294ED03D050_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, germany election, what is afd, afd, alternative for germany, germany elections, Berlin, germany election 2017, democratic systems]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3448710</guid>
      <title>Study uses sunlight to change carbon dioxide into ethanol</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists at the Berkeley Lab in California have developed technology that can convert carbon dioxide into ethanol using sunlight.The research was published in the journal, Energy & Environmental Science. The study employed low amounts of solar energy in a copper-silver nanocoral cathode to produce the ethanol."Reducing CO2 to a hydrocarbon end product like ethanol or ethylene can take up to 5 volts, start to finish," explained the study's lead author Gurudayal in a Berkeley Lab news release. "Our system reduced that by half while maintaining the selectivity of products."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of story2. Depiction of photosynthesis3. Depiction of carbon dioxide transforming to ethanolVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists at the Berkeley Lab in California have developed technology that can convert carbon dioxide into ethanol using sunlight.""This process is known as artificial photosynthesis.""During photosynthesis, plants use light from the sun to create food and oxygen.""Low amounts of solar energy were used in a copper-silver nanocoral cathode to produce ethanol."SOURCES: Energy & Environmental Science, Berkeley Lab, Popular Mechanicshttp://pubs.rsc.org/en/content/articlelanding/2017/ee/c7ee01764b#!divAbstracthttp://newscenter.lbl.gov/2017/09/18/solar-fuel-system-recycles-co2-for-ethanol-ethylene/http://www.popularmechanics.com/science/green-tech/news/a28311/co2-into-ethanol-with-sun/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 05:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/25/3448710/3448710_529F12D49E0D473194CBFFACADF53CC9_170925_3448710_Study_uses_sunlight_to_change_carbon_dioxide_int_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C4A/78C/C4A78C624CC54047BAFCA0AABB9D0E20_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, turning co2 into oxygen, artificial photosynthesis, co2 to h2o, carbon dioxide to ethanol, carbon dioxide]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3449558</guid>
      <title>Five Asian countries contribute to 60% of all plastic waste in the ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAccording to a study from Ocean Conservancy called Stemming the Tide, 55-60% of plastic polluting the oceans comes from five countries: China, Indonesia, Philippines, Thailand, Vietnam.Uncollected and mismanaged waste on land accounts for about 80% of the 8 million metric tons of trash that flow into the oceans each year.Environmental organization Greenpeace claims corporations are also at fault for selling products in single-use plastic packaging, especially in so-called 'sachet economies' like the Philippines.Various studies have shown that plastic pollution negatively impacts marine animals, and may be indirectly affecting humans through the food chain.Fortunately, improving waste management practices in the five countries can result in a 45% reduction of global plastic waste leakage by 2025.In tackling plastic pollution, everyone has a role to play. From governments and big conglomerates to the people on the street  every bit helps. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 60% of plastic in the ocean comes from five Asian countries2. 80% of ocean plastic comes from uncollected or mismanaged waste on land3. Plastic's harmful effect on marine animals and humans4. Better waste management can reduce global plastic waste leakage by 45%VOICEOVER (in English): "A study from Ocean Conservancy estimates that 55-60% of plastic polluting the oceans comes from five countries: China, Indonesia, Philippines, Thailand, Vietnam.""Uncollected and mismanaged waste on land accounts for about 80% of the 8 million metric tons of trash that flow into the oceans each year.""Various studies have shown that plastic pollution negatively impacts marine animals, and may be indirectly affecting humans through the food chain.""Fortunately, improving waste management practices in the five countries can result in a 45% reduction of global plastic waste leakage by 2025."SOURCES: Ocean Conservancy, Greenpeace, Plastic Pollutershttps://oceanconservancy.org/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/full-report-stemming-the.pdfhttp://www.greenpeace.org/international/en/press/releases/2017/Nestle-Unilever-PG-among-worst-offenders-for-plastic-pollution-in-Philippines-in-beach-audit/http://www.plasticpolluters.org/how-does-plastic-end-ocean***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 07:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/26/3449558/3449558_137C87F49A61439D92FECE3EE6F5E667_170926_3449558_Five_Asian_countries_contribute_to_60__of_all_pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/060/3FC/0603FC42B81041C884EEBF55C483068C_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, plastic, plastic pollution, plastic waste, trash, plastic trash, ocean pollution, ocean plastic, water pollution, china, indonesia, philippines, thailand, vietnam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3449371</guid>
      <title>Microsoft and Facebook's 4,000-mile-long deep sea data cable is complete</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMicrosoft, Facebook and Spanish telecommunications giant Telxius have just completed work on a massive continent-to-continent underwater cable.According to a Microsoft news release, the Marea undersea cable is comprised of eight pairs of fiber optic cables, encircled by copper, a layer of hard-plastic and a waterproof coating. The subsea cable stretches over 4,000 miles from the U.S. east coast at Virginia Beach, to Spain's north coast at Bilbao. When laying the cable, engineers had to account for an average depth of 11,000 feet and hazards including coral reefs, earthquake zones and active volcanoes.The cable can transmit a maximum of 160 terabits per second. That's the equivalent of 71 million streaming high definition videos.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of cable's length on globe, from Virginia Beach, USA to Bilbao Spain.2. Depiction of boat laying cable and hazards 3. Depiction of cable being constructed with different layers on ocean floor4. Depiction of cable transmitting data and couple watching high definition videoVOICEOVER (in English): "The subsea cable stretches over 4,000 miles from the U.S. east coast at Virginia Beach, to Spain's north coast at Bilbao.""When laying the cable, engineers had to account for an average depth of 11,000 feet and hazards including coral reefs, earthquake zones and active volcanoes.""According to Microsoft, the Marea undersea cable is comprised of eight pairs of fiber optic cables, encircled by copper, a layer of hard-plastic and a waterproof coating.""The cable can transmit a maximum of 160 terabits per second. That's the equivalent of 71 million streaming high definition videos."SOURCES: Microsoft, Popular Mechanics, Cables 24https://news.microsoft.com/features/microsoft-facebook-telxius-complete-highest-capacity-subsea-cable-cross-atlantic/http://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/infrastructure/a28324/microsoft-facebook-complete-historic-undersea-cable/http://cables24.com/en/blog/5_marea-optical-fiber-submarine***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 02:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/26/3449371/3449371_487958CDAE654B11A1E7AEC9F98B7DAC_170926_3449371_Microsoft_and_Facebook_s_4_000_mile_long_deep_se_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BAF/4E1/BAF4E132AB0D4E3BB844C73BE9CE1897_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, deep sea cables, subsea cable, marea cable, microsoft, facebook, telxius]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3449364</guid>
      <title>How would a hydrogen bomb explosion affect the Pacific Ocean?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAs the war of words between the United States and North Korea continues to escalate, Pyongyang hinted last week that it may test a hydrogen bomb in the Pacific Ocean. "It could be the most powerful detonation of an H-bomb in the Pacific," Foreign Minister Ri Yong-ho told reporters at the United Nations General Assembly in New York, the Atlantic reported. If a hydrogen bomb did hit the Pacific, it would detonate with a blinding flash, while producing a massive mushroom cloud. The immediate fallout would depend on the height of detonation.  The initial blast would instantly kill most fish and marine life in the blast area.  The explosion would send radioactive particles flying through the air and into the water. Wind also has the potential to carry the particles hundreds of miles. The smoke created at the strike zone could potentially block the sun, hurting organisms that utilize photosynthesis. Radiation would lead to severe health problems for surrounding aquatic life. Humans could also be affected if radioactive fallout reaches land. Particles could contaminate air, water and soil. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hydrogen bomb mushroom cloud2. Marine life in the blast zone would be killed instantly3. Radioactive particles in the water and air4. Hydrogen bomb blast blocking out the sun and spreading radioactive particlesVOICEOVER (in English): "If a hydrogen bomb did hit the Pacific, it would detonate with a blinding flash, while producing a massive mushroom cloud. The immediate fallout would depend on the height of detonation."  "The initial blast would instantly kill most fish and marine life in the blast area."  "The explosion would send radioactive particles flying through the air and into the water. Wind also has the potential to carry the particles hundreds of miles." "The smoke created at the strike zone could potentially block out sunlight, hurting organisms that utilize photosynthesis. Radiation would lead to severe health problems for surrounding aquatic life." SOURCES: The Atlantichttps://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2017/09/north-korea-bomb-pacific-ocean/540825/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 02:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/26/3449364/3449364_FCC52665FF5843368F03B9AE2B2CD5C2_170926_3449364_How_would_a_hydrogen_bomb_explosion_affect_the_P_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0CE/5FE/0CE5FE4683B94129B1BB89A2AD5ADB44_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, North Korea, Hydrogen bomb, Hydrogen bomb test, Hydrogen bomb test Pacific Ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3450547</guid>
      <title>Japanese turbines harvest wave energy to generate electricity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEJapanese researchers have come with special technology that can not only capture energy from waves, but also help protect coastlines.According to the Okinawa Institute of Science and Technology, a team led by Professor Tsumoru Shintake plans to set up energy-harvesting turbines near tetrapods, which are concrete structures placed along the shore to weaken the force of incoming waves and prevent erosion.The turbine has five flexible blades modelled after dolphin fins. It's supported by a stem that's anchored to the sea floor with mooring cables, which, like the blades, is flexible and can bend under pressure.Inside the turbine head is a magnet electric generator, which transforms wave energy into electricity. The electricity is sent back to the shore via cables, to feed into the grid.Using turbines on just 1% of Japan's coastline can generate roughly 10 gigawatts of energy, equivalent to about 10 nuclear power plants.Apart from tetrapods, the turbines can also harness electricity near coral reefs.They're built to be safe for marine life, with blade speed carefully calibrated so that any animals caught in them can escape unharmed.The team is currently preparing to install two half-scale model turbines that will power LEDs as part of a commercial demonstration.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Turbines placed in front of tetrapods on shoreline to harvest energy2. Turbine blades flexible, modelled after dolphin fins; stem bends under pressure3. Magnet electric generator turns ocean wave energy into electricity, sends it to electric grid via cables4. Turbines on 1% of Japan's shore generates as much energy as 10 nuclear power plantsVOICEOVER (in English): "A team from Okinawa plans to set up energy-harvesting turbines near tetrapods, which are concrete structures placed along the shore to weaken the force of incoming waves and prevent erosion.""The turbine has five flexible blades modelled after dolphin fins. It's supported by a stem that's anchored to the sea floor with mooring cables, which, like the blades, is flexible and can bend under pressure.""Inside the turbine head is a magnet electric generator, which transforms wave energy into electricity. The electricity is sent back to the shore via cables, to feed into the grid.""Using turbines on just 1% of Japan's coastline can generate roughly 10 gigawatts of energy, equivalent to about 10 nuclear power plants."SOURCES: Okinawa Institute of Science and Technologyhttps://www.oist.jp/news-center/news/2017/9/20/sustainable-future-powered-sea***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/27/3450547/3450547_03C40F0CDD264AAC83D96E6AA9B393F6_170927_3450547_Japanese_turbines_harvest_wave_energy_to_generat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CDA/D9A/CDAD9AF2522C4BCFB25194F7611B5976_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, turbine, wave energy, wave energy converter, electricity, energy, sustainable energy, energy source, japan, tetrapods, shore erosion, erosion, okinawa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3450310</guid>
      <title>Prototype construction begins on Trump's border wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEConstruction began on prototype designs for a border wall in a fenced-off area in Otay Mesa on Tuesday. Eight different designs will be constructed over the next 30-days, the San Diego Union-Tribune reported. Four of the prototypes will be concrete, while the other four will be made of various materials. All of the walls will be between 18 to 30 feet high and 30 feet long, according to the San Diego Union-Tribune. Six contractors from across the country have been chosen to build the prototypes. Bids for the prototypes ranged from $300,000 to $500,000. The construction site is about 1.5 miles east of Erico Fermi Drive. It is several miles east of the Otay Mesa Port of Entry, reported the San Diego Union-Tribune. The border wall project is underway despite lack of congressional funding. Estimates for the cost of the border wall have ranged up to $38 billion. The Department of Homeland Security is planning to pay for the prototypes with internal funds taken from other programs. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The construction site 2. Four prototypes will be made of concrete, four will be made of various materials3. The prototypes will be 18 to 30 feet in height and 30 feet long4. Bids for the prototypes ranged from $300,000 to $500,000VOICEOVER (in English): "Construction began on eight different border wall prototype designs in Otay Mesa on Tuesday. Contractors now have 30 days to complete their walls." "Four of the prototypes will be concrete, while the other four will be made of various materials.""All of the walls will be between 18 to 30 feet high and 30 feet long.""Six contractors from around the country were picked to build the prototypes. Their bids ranged from $300,000 to $500,000."SOURCES: San Diego Union-Tribune, NPRhttp://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/sd-me-border-begins-20170926-story.htmlhttp://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2017/09/26/553786714/contractors-begin-building-prototypes-for-trump-s-border-wall***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 07:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/27/3450310/3450310_B92D4F297E474C71B08DF8AC608EEE9C_170927_3450310_Prototype_construction_begins_on_Trump_s_border__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1B1/9D4/1B19D4AED6634E449D283BE8FB25D5FC_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Trump border wall, border wall prototypes, Otay Mesa border wall, border wall construction]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3451225</guid>
      <title>Scientists complete 8-month isolation mission simulating life on Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA team of scientists have finally returned to civilization after completing a NASA-funded isolation experiment to simulate life on Mars.NASA reports that the six-person HI-SEAS Mission V crew lived in a dome on the Mars-like landscape of Hawaii's Mauna Loa volcano for eight months.The dome was equipped with a kitchen, bathroom, common area, and six individual bedrooms. Though not confined to the inside, the crew were required to don spacesuits whenever they went outside.While in the habitat, the crew conducted scientific research, equipment testing, and resource tracking. They also had to learn to prepare food using dehydrated and shelf-stable ingredients.Communications with the outside were subject to a delay of 20 minutes  the same amount of time it takes for signals to reach Mars from Earth.To better understand the psychological impacts of a long-term space mission, they were fitted with sensors that gauged their moods and monitored interactions with other members.The mission is the fifth in a series of six studies designed to help NASA select crews that can do well on an expedition to the red planet. The sixth and final HI-SEAS mission will also last for eight months and is slated to begin in January 2018.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Crew spends 8 months isolated in a dome in Hawaii to simulate life on Mars2. Crew had to wear hazmat suits when going out3. 20 minute communication delay with outside world4. Crew fitted with sensors to track moods and interaction with other membersVOICEOVER (in English): "The six-person HI-SEAS Mission V crew lived in a dome on the Mars-like landscape of Hawaii's Mauna Loa volcano for 8 months.""The dome was equipped with a kitchen, bathroom, common area, and six individual bedrooms. Though not confined to the inside, the crew were required to don spacesuits whenever they went outside.""Communications with the outside were subject to a delay of 20 minutes - the same amount of time it takes for signals to reach Mars from Earth.""To better understand the psychological impacts of a long-term space mission, they were fitted with sensors that gauged their moods and monitored interactions with other members."SOURCES: NASA, University of Hawaii, USA Todayhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/hi-seas-team-completes-8-month-isolation-missionhttps://www.hawaii.edu/news/2017/09/17/fifth-uh-simulated-mars-mission-is-in-the-books/https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2017/09/15/psychology-experiment-kept-six-nasa-subjects-isolated-mars-volcano-8-months/669940001/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/28/3451225/3451225_874BBE87B2554D15AC06676D758071D5_170928_3451225_Scientists_complete_8_month_isolation_mission_si_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0AC/C9E/0ACC9E13378145CCA7D462710E21350D_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mars, life on mars, isolation, experiment, space, simulation, psychology, mauna loa, hawaii, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3451206</guid>
      <title>How hackers hack ATMs remotely</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEJapanese cybersecurity firm Trend Micro has published a white paper detailing how hackers can remotely control ATMS.According to Trend Micro, cybercriminals target banking staff with phishing emails. If a worker accesses the email, this allows the hacker to steal their identity. The hacker then uses the stolen digital credentials to enter the banking network where they begin to comb it for data on their target.This is known as lateral movement. The hack is commonly seen in places where banks' main networks and ATM networks are not separated. Once that data is acquired, the hacker gains access to ATMs. They then order machines to dispense so-called "jackpot" amounts of cash to standby mules, waiting to collect.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of hacker hacking to bank worker's computer via phishing email 2. Depiction of hacker accessing banking network with stolen credentials3. Depiction of hacker ordering ATM to dispense cash and mule collecting itVOICEOVER (in English): "First, cybercriminals target banking staff with phishing emails. If a worker accesses the email, this allows the hacker to steal their identity.""The hacker then uses the stolen digital credentials to enter the banking network where they begin to comb it for data on their target.""This is known as lateral movement. The hack is commonly seen in places where banks' main networks and ATM networks are not separated.""Once said data is acquired, the hacker gains access to ATMs." "They then order machines to dispense so-called "jackpot" amounts of cash to standby mules, waiting to collect."SOURCES: Trend Microhttp://blog.trendmicro.com/trendlabs-security-intelligence/an-elaborate-atm-threat-crops-up-network-based-atm-malware-attackshttp://blog.trendmicro.com/attack-machines-lucrative-business-atm-malware/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 08:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/28/3451206/3451206_18459ED32BAF44408ADBED42B2E82A88_170928_3451206_How_hackers_hack_ATMs_remotely_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/339/C08/339C08C51B55497BB95C7BEE88953DCC_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ATM Hack, New ATM hack, ATM hack 2017, trend micro, ATMs, ATM cyber security, Trend Micro, cyber theft, ATM, Virtual skimming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3450993</guid>
      <title>NASA investigating effects of space radiation on human body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEOne of NASA's biggest challenges in designing a mission to Mars is how to protect astronauts on the long journey through space.NASA's Human Research Program is researching how space radiation affects the human body."One of our biggest challenges on a mission to Mars is protecting astronauts from radiation," said NASA Space Radiation Element Scientist Lisa Simonsen, reported Science Daily. "You can't see it; you can't feel it. You don't know you're getting bombarded by radiation."Space radiation has enough energy to violently collide with nuclei that make up spacecraft shielding and human tissue, according to Science Daily.The collisions cause both the shielding nuclei and space radiation to break-up into several different types of new particles known as secondary radiation.NASA is currently investigating the effects of galactic cosmic rays (GCRs) on the human body.One of the main difficulties is that it's hard to simulate space radiation on Earth. Lab doses of radiation could be stronger and given for a shorter time than actual conditions in space.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Astronaut being exposed to solar radiation2. Space radiation colliding with spacecraft and human tissue nuclei3. Secondary radiation created from space radiation and shielding nuclei collisions4. A supernovaVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Human Research Program is currently researching how space radiation affects the human body." "Space radiation has enough energy to violently collide with nuclei that make up spacecraft shielding and human tissue.""The collisions cause both the shielding nuclei and space radiation to break-up into several different types of new particles known as secondary radiation." "NASA is currently focusing on the effects of galactic cosmic rays (GCRs) on the human body. GCRs that come from supernovas outside the solar system are the most harmful to the body. " SOURCES: Science Dailyhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/09/170922090932.htm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 05:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/28/3450993/3450993_A07BAF3EF9474AE9BEB6A96A8A3E7D39_170928_3450993_NASA_investigating_effects_of_space_radiation_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/29A/F6A/29AF6A7DC7BF402CBCBA0E53795C7E67_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, NASA, space radiation, NASA Mars mission, NASA Human Research Program, galactic cosmic rays]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3450984</guid>
      <title>NASA investigating effects of space radiation on human body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEOne of NASA's biggest challenges in designing a mission to Mars is how to protect astronauts on the long journey through space.NASA's Human Research Program is researching how space radiation affects the human body."One of our biggest challenges on a mission to Mars is protecting astronauts from radiation," said NASA Space Radiation Element Scientist Lisa Simonsen, reported Science Daily. "You can't see it; you can't feel it. You don't know you're getting bombarded by radiation."Space radiation has enough energy to violently collide with nuclei that make up spacecraft shielding and human tissue, according to Science Daily.The collisions cause both the shielding nuclei and space radiation to break-up into several different types of new particles known as secondary radiation.NASA is currently investigating the effects of galactic cosmic rays (GCRs) on the human body.One of the main difficulties is that it's hard to simulate space radiation on Earth. Lab doses of radiation could be stronger and given for a shorter time than actual conditions in space.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Astronaut being exposed to solar radiation2. Space radiation colliding with spacecraft and human tissue nuclei3. Secondary radiation created from space radiation and shielding nuclei collisions4. A supernovaVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Human Research Program is currently researching how space radiation affects the human body." "Space radiation has enough energy to violently collide with nuclei that make up spacecraft shielding and human tissue.""The collisions cause both the shielding nuclei and space radiation to break-up into several different types of new particles known as secondary radiation." "NASA is currently focusing on the effects of galactic cosmic rays (GCRs) on the human body. GCRs that come from supernovas outside the solar system are the most harmful to the body. " SOURCES: Science Dailyhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/09/170922090932.htm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 05:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/28/3450984/3450984_77BC31C88E8E4D5487A4E4AB988F5E0D_170928_3450984_NASA_investigating_effects_of_space_radiation_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/960/4BE/9604BE1D667B48D89A66A5B58F94E9FA_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, NASA, space radiation, NASA Mars mission, NASA Human Research Program, galactic cosmic rays]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3450893</guid>
      <title>Heartbeat could be used as passcode for smartphone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers at the University of Buffalo have developed a new biometric tool that scans your heart to unlock your phone or log onto your computer.Scientists have designed a system that uses a low-level Doppler radar to identify the shape and size of a person's heart, Gadgets Now reported. The system needs eight seconds to record the shape and person's heartbeat. It then continuously monitors the person's presence. Researchers claim the system poses no health risks as the radar system uses very little power. It is a passive, non-contact device, so people don't have to spend time authenticating themselves.The heart scanner works on individuals up to a distance of 30 meters (98 ft). The team now says they will work on shrinking down the system so it can be installed onto computer keyboards and smartphones.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Heart can work as a passcode for phone or computer2. System uses low-level Doppler radar to identify size and shape of heart3. The system takes 8 seconds to record size and shape of heart4. The system works up to a distance of 30 metersVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at the University of Buffalo have developed a new biometric tool that scans your heart to unlock your phone or log onto your computer.""The system that uses a low-level Doppler radar to identify the shape and size of a person's heart.""The system needs eight seconds to record the shape and person's heartbeat. It then continuously monitors the person's presence." "The heart scanner continuously monitors individuals up to a distance of 98 ft."SOURCES: Gadgets Nowhttp://www.gadgetsnow.com/tech-news/forget-face-scans-or-fingerprints-your-heart-could-be-your-new-passcode/articleshow/60844509.cms***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 02:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/28/3450893/3450893_1B4737657A5C47BB9DE393181BC172D1_170928_3450893_Heartbeat_could_be_used_as_passcode_for_smartpho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/719/298/7192982ADDD94E1E95BEC575071C49FB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, heart phone passcode, heart computer passcode, biometric tool, biometric heart tool]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3450885</guid>
      <title>Massive iceberg breaks off glacier in Antarctica</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA massive iceberg broke apart from of the Pine Island Glacier in Antarctica this week.The break has scientists worried that Pine Island Glacier's behavior might be changing, reported Weather.com.The area that broke apart is said to be 4.5 times the size of New York's Manhattan island.Loss of ice from the glacier contributes to a 1 millimeter rise in the world's oceans, every eight years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of land fracturing 2. Depiction of iceberg splitting from space3. Scale of iceberg against ManhattanVOICEOVER (in English): "This week an iceberg broke apart from the Pine Island Glacier in Antarctica.""Loss of ice from the glacier contributes to a 1 millimeter rise in the world's oceans every eight years.""The part that broke apart is said to be 4.5 times the size of New York's Manhattan island."SOURCES: Weather.com, Professor Stef Lhermitte,https://weather.com/science/environment/news/antarctica-iceberg-pine-island-glacierhttps://twitter.com/StefLhermitte***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 02:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/28/3450885/3450885_950B6BA679374928AAE2FD25E472B89A_170928_3450885_Massive_iceberg_breaks_off_glacier_in_Antarctica_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C27/B6A/C27B6A059A684A8FA4D6907189965695_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, iceberg breaking off glacier, icebergs, manhattan iceberg, antarctica, iceberg melting, new iceberg, super iceberg]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3452169</guid>
      <title>British Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn calls for tax on robots</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONECalls from the British Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn to publicly manage automation this week have led to speculation he is looking to tax robots, but how would that work?Replacing workers with robots, means less salary and more profit for businesses, but also less taxes on salary for the state to collect. Any robot tax would likely need to fill this gap in public finances.The Institute for Fiscal Studies estimates that the British government will collect 716.5 billion for the tax year 2016 to 2017. According to the IFS figures 43.1 percent, or 308.6 billion, of this is contributed by the 30 million people in the British workforce.Separately, a PWC study estimates that 10 million British workers may lose their jobs to automation. If permanent, and not counting the amount the government may save from automation, this would lead to a shortfall of 92.6 pounds, or 30%, in what the British state collects.A flat robot tax may help fill this gap. However, calls for automation to help people live comfortably via state-provided benefits  such as a universal income  may well see automation taxes rise. Such a move would likely scare off private industry from investing in the United Kingdom.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of truck driver being replaced by automation2. Depiction of amount of amount the British workforce contributed in taxes during 2016 and 2017, according to the IFS 3. Depiction of supermarket checkout being automated4. Depiction of robot worker being taxed and helping elderly lady into bedVOICEOVER (in English): "Replacing workers with robots, means less salary and more profit for businesses, but also less taxes on salary for the state to collect.""Any robot tax would likely need to fill this gap in public finances.""The Institute for Fiscal studies estimates that the British government will collect 716.5 billion pounds for the tax year 2016 to 2017."43.1 percent, or 308.6 billion pounds, of this is contributed by the 30 million people in the British workforce.""Separately, a PWC study estimates that 10 million British workers may lose their jobs to automation.""If permanent, and not counting the amount the government may save from automation, this would lead to a shortfall of 92.6 billion pounds, or 30%, in what the British state collects.""A flat robot tax may help fill this gap. "However, calls for automation to help people live comfortably via state-provided benefits  such as a universal income  may well see automation taxes rise."SOURCES: British Labour Party, Institute For Fiscal Studies, Office for National Statistics, The Guardian http://press.labour.org.uk/https://www.ifs.org.uk/bns/bn09.pdfhttps://www.ons.gov.uk/employmentandlabourmarket/peopleinwork/employmentandemployeetypes/bulletins/uklabourmarket/february2016https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/24/millions-uk-workers-risk-replaced-robots-study-warns***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 11:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/29/3452169/3452169_E298CCE65A1D457991DE82C8D9886B41_170929_3452169_British_Labour_leader_Jeremy_Corbyn_calls_for_ta_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4D9/930/4D9930166F7B4391B51BB230E1473FB7_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  taxing robots, robot tax, jeremy corbyn, automation tax, auto tax, taxing machines, labour conference, technology tax]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3451951</guid>
      <title>Earth's strange composition may be due to planetary collisions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETwo new studies published in the journal Nature may have shed some light on how Earth's strange chemical make-up came to be.The Washington Post reports that the solar system began some 4.6 billion years ago as a swirling disk of gas and dust. This all came together to form rocks, planetesimals, and eventually, full-sized planets.Scientists have long been puzzled by the difference in composition between Earth and the meteorites believed to have formed it. The answer, it seems, lies in Earth's explosive history.Early Earth often collided with other planetary bodies, with the impact generating enough heat to turn rocks into either magma or hot vapor. One study, led by a University of Bristol geochemist, calculated that planet lost 40 percent of its mass from this process.A second study, from Oxford University, combined Earth rock with volatile elements such as gold, silver, and zinc oxide, and heated it to 1,300 degrees Celsius. After cooling the rock, they discovered that the volatile elements had evaporated.This same vapor loss was found in samples from Mars and the asteroid Vesta, suggesting that the phenomenon occurs in similar-sized bodies.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Formation of the solar system2. Earth's composition different from ancient meteorites3. Collision generated heat, turned rock into magma or vapor4. Volatile elements evaporated when combined with basalt rock, then heatedVOICEOVER (in English): "Our solar system began some 4.6 billion years ago as a swirling disk of gas and dust. This all came together to form rocks, planetesimals, and eventually, full-sized planets.""But scientists have long been puzzled by the difference in composition between Earth and the meteorites believed to have formed it. The answer, it seems, lies in Earth's explosive history.""Early Earth often collided with other planetary bodies, with the impact generating enough heat to turn rocks into either magma or hot vapor. One study estimates the planet lost 40 percent of its mass from this process.""A second study combined earth rock with volatile elements such as gold, silver, and zinc oxide, and heated it to 1,300 degrees Celsius. After cooling the rock, they discovered that the volatile elements had evaporated."SOURCES: Washington Post, Space, International Business Timeshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/speaking-of-science/wp/2017/09/27/how-earths-hellish-birth-deprived-us-of-silver-and-gold/?utm_term=.33998b788cb9https://www.space.com/38276-earth-composition-building-blocks-collisions.htmlhttp://www.ibtimes.com/earth-mars-formation-involved-planetary-body-collisions-vaporized-rock-silicate-2594498***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 07:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/29/3451951/3451951_20EFBDF3A2214E9D8B4EC02E2523B3A3_170929_3451951_Earth_s_strange_composition_may_be_due_to_planet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/288/A96/288A96F62D9F4AD19D54BA993F7F0858_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  space, earth formation, accretion, planetary accretion, planet formation, earth composition, outer space, meteorites, chondrites]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3451794</guid>
      <title>Football players may be able to be diagnosed for CTE before death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers may have found a way to diagnose chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE) in football players while they are still alive. CTE is a progressive brain disease caused by repeated trauma to the head. It usually shows up years after taking repeated blows to the head, and can lead to symptoms like confusion, depression, aggression, memory retention, and other forms of cognitive degeneration, according to Quartz. Currently, CTE can only be diagnosed through an autopsy. Researchers have found that people who had CTE displayed abnormal clusters of the tau protein throughout the brain.Doctors believe the tau protein is responsible for killing off neurons.  Researchers at Boston University wanted to look for other markers in people suffering from CTE. Scientists found that people with CTE showed elevated levels of the protein CLL11 in both spinal fluid and the blood around the brain in the skull. They believe the CLL11 protein helps the smallest blood vessels in the brain move oxygen. Higher levels of CLL11 could mean these blood vessels are leaking, which may lead to CTE symptoms. The team at Boston University is now working with a biotech company to develop a blood test to detect CLL11 and diagnose living players. More research still needs to be conducted on the CLL11 protein to confirm it isn't linked with other kinds of neurodegenerative diseases. There's no cure for CTE, but early diagnosis could give players a chance to mitigate the disease.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Football players running into each other2. Players with CTE have elevated levels of CLL11 protein3. Football players with elevated levels of CLL11 protein4. Researchers working on a blood test to identify the CLL11 proteinVOICEOVER (in English): "CTE is a progressive brain disease caused by repeated trauma to the head. It usually shows up years after taking repeated blows." "Currently, CTE can only be diagnosed through an autopsy. Researchers at Boston University wanted to look for other markers and found people with CTE had elevated levels of the protein CLL11 in both spinal fluid and blood around the brain." "Researchers believe the CLL11 protein helps the smallest blood vessels in the brain transport oxygen. Higher levels of CLL11 could mean these blood vessels are leaking, which may lead to CTE symptoms." "The team at Boston University is now working with a biotech company to develop a blood test to detect CLL11 and diagnose living players." SOURCES: Quartz, Plos Onehttps://qz.com/1088571/scientists-may-be-able-to-test-nfl-players-for-cte-while-theyre-alive/http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0185541***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 04:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/09/29/3451794/3451794_0A19D22B83AF49A0A57D7978099E21F2_170929_3451794_Football_players_may_be_able_to_be_diagnosed_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C98/ABF/C98ABF0C9DCE4A43B06B53FFAF97BD59_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, CTE, CTE diagnosis, chronic traumatic encephalopathy, CTE football player, CTE symptoms, football concussions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
