<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3900311</guid>
      <title>Bridge collapses in Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwanese authorities are looking into what may have caused the sudden collapse of a bridge in northeastern Taiwan.CNA reports that an oil tanker truck had been driving over the Nanfangao Bridge in Taiwan's Yilan County when the structure abruptly gave way.The collapse caused the oil truck to plunge six stories down and catch fire. Three fishing vessels beneath the bridge were crushed, with at least 9 people falling overboard.The Taiwanese truck driver was rescued from the cab of the truck, and taken to the hospital. Liberty Times reports that he sustained multiple fractured ribs, head trauma, a damaged kidney, a ruptured spleen, and a broken leg.He regained consciousness Tuesday afternoon, and is slated for an operation on Friday. Doctors say they are optimistic about his condition.At least 11 Indonesian and Filipino fishermen were also injured in the incident but have been rescued. According to Apple Daily, four fishermen were found dead, while two more remain missing.Focus Taiwan reports that the cause of the collapse is still being investigated, there is speculation that the cables holding the structure up had rusted from exposure to the ocean air, rain, and wind.Yilan County had been besieged by heavy rain and strong winds from Typhoon Mitag a day earlier, and been hit by a 3.8-magnitude earthquake early Tuesday. Officials have yet to determine whether either of these was a factor in the incident.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nanfangao bridge collapse in Yilan2. Oil tanker truck falls and catches fire, fishing vessels crushed by bridge 3. Number of injured, dead, and missing4. Possible cause of the bridge collapseVOICEOVER (in English): "CNA reports that an oil tanker truck had been driving over the Nanfangao Bridge in Taiwan's Yilan County when the structure abruptly gave way.""The collapse caused the oil truck to plunge six stories down and catch fire. Three fishing vessels beneath the bridge were crushed, with at least 9 people falling overboard.""The Taiwanese truck driver was rescued from the cab of the truck, and taken to the hospital. "At least 11 Indonesian and Filipino fishermen were also injured in the incident but have been rescued.""According to Apple Daily, four fishermen were found dead, while two more remain missing.""Focus Taiwan reports that the cause of the collapse is still being investigated, there is speculation that the cables holding the structure up had rusted from exposure to the ocean air, rain, and wind."SOURCES: CNA, Focus Taiwan, Liberty Timeshttps://www.cna.com.tw/news/firstnews/201910015004.aspxhttp://focustaiwan.tw/news/asoc/201910010003.aspxhttp://focustaiwan.tw/news/asoc/201910020001.aspxhttps://news.ltn.com.tw/news/society/breakingnews/2933429 ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 16:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/03/3900311/3900311_9E2BF56EDD214AEB93DFB33CBDD1A149_191003_3900311_Bridge_collapses_in_Taiwan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, taiwan bridge collapse, bridge collapse, nanfangao bridge collapse, nanfangao bridge, taiwan bridge, suspension bridge, oil tanker truck]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900307</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk unveils interplanetary plans for Starship spacecraft</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANElon Musk has unveiled plans for SpaceX's new Starship spacecraft.Space.com reports that during an annual update in Boca Chica, Texas, Elon Musk displayed the 160-foot tall Starship MK1, the first full-size Starship prototype, which contains three methane-fueled Raptor engines.The final Starship vehicle will be mounted atop the Super Heavy booster. The entire stack will be 387 feet tall and contain six Raptor engines, with space for up to 37.According to Musk, this new version will be able to carry up to 100 people to destinations in space like the Moon or Mars, or around Earth.Instead of carbon fiber, the Starship spacecraft will be made of 301 stainless steel, which gets stronger as the temperature drops.The material's higher melting point also makes the vehicle more resilient during reentry into the Earth's atmosphere.According to Space.com, the Starship rocket will be the same one to launch Japanese billionaire Yusaku Maezwa and others on a lunar tourism mission in the 2020s."Musk plans to launch the MK1 on an uncrewed 20-kilometer test flight in the next month or so. MK2 is already under construction at the company's Cape Canaveral facility, while building plans MK3 and MK4 will be underway shortly after.The short-term goal, according to Musk, is to reach orbit in less than six months. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Starship MK1 and final starship vehicle on Super Heavy booster2. Starship's future interplanetary missions3. Stainless steel spacecraft more suitable for cold space and fiery reentry4. Starship lunar tourism missionVOICEOVER (in English): "Space.com reports that during an annual update in Boca Chica, Texas, Elon Musk displayed the 160-foot tall Starship MK1, the first full-size Starship prototype, which contains three methane-fueled Raptor engines.""The final Starship vehicle will be mounted atop the Super Heavy booster. The entire stack will be 387 feet tall and contain six Raptor engines, with space for up to 37.""According to Musk, this new version will be able to carry up to 100 people to destinations in space like the Moon or  Mars, or around Earth.""Instead of carbon fiber, the Starship spacecraft will be made of 301 stainless steel, which gets stronger as the temperature drops.""The material's higher melting point also makes the vehicle more resilient during reentry into the Earth's atmosphere.""According to Space.com, the Starship rocket will be the same one to launch Japanese billionaire Yusaku Maezwa and others on a lunar tourism mission in the 2020s."SOURCES: Space.com, SpaceXhttps://www.space.com/elon-musk-unveils-spacex-starship-2019-update.htmlhttps://www.space.com/spacex-starship-reach-orbit-six-months.htmlhttps://www.spacex.com/starship***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/03/3900307/3900307_4A9AB535ECC948C9BA6699A6090EEA91_191003_3900307_Elon_Musk_unveils_interplanetary_plans_for_Stars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, SpaceX, Starship, Starship MK1, MK1, Starship spacecraft, Elon Musk, spaceflight, Mars rocket, moon rocket, space rocket]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900247</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protester shot with live round</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA high school student involved in anti-government protests in Hong Kong was shot in the chest by police during clashes with authorities. The BBC reports that the incident came as thousands of people demonstrated in defiance of a protest ban for the 70th anniversary of Communist rule in China. According to the BBC, although people have been shot with rubber bullets in previous protests, this marks the first time live ammunition has been used.Reuters reports that Hong Kong police confirmed that an officer opened fire at a protester, saying he was acting in self-defense. A police statement said, "a large group of rioters was attacking police officers in Tsuen Wan.""Police officers warned them, but they were still attacking police. A police officer's life was seriously endangered. In order to save his and other officers' lives, they fired at the attacker."According to Reuters, a clip posted to social media shows the 18-year-old protester swing a baton at a policeman, brushing his right arm. The officer then fires a round into the protester's chest as he stumbles over another policeman and falls on his back. According to the BBC, the man has been undergoing surgery and his condition is not known. Police say he was hit "near his left shoulder."According to Hong Kong police, in addition to the bullet fired at the young protester,  five other live rounds were fired at various locations on Tuesday.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Police officer approaching protesters with gun drawn2. Protester attacking police officer3. Police officer shooting protester4. HK protestsVOICEOVER (in English): "A high school student involved in anti-government protests in Hong Kong was shot in the chest by police during clashes with authorities.""According to Reuters, a clip posted to social media shows the 18-year-old protester swing a baton at a policeman, brushing his right arm." "The officer then fires a round into the protester's chest as he stumbles over another policeman and falls on his back." "According to the BBC, the man has been undergoing surgery and his condition is not known. Police say he was hit 'near his left shoulder.'""According to Hong Kong police, in addition to the bullet fired at the young protester,  five other live rounds were fired at various locations on Tuesday."  SOURCES: Reuters, BBChttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-anniversary-hongkong-shooting/dramatic-footage-captures-moment-when-hong-kong-protester-shot-idUSKBN1WG46Ghttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-49891403***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 14:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/02/3900247/3900247_44DB492D9A2B47A5AB7594CF6CE6CBDA_191002_3900247_Hong_Kong_protester_shot_with_live_round_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong protester shot, Hong Kong protester shot live round, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899966</guid>
      <title>Light-powered RFID tags could soon power internet of things devices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from Massachusetts Institute of Technology have published a study detailing the use of photovoltaic powered sensors on radio-frequency identification, or RFID tags, to power internet of things devices.Thin film perovskite cells were added onto the RFID tags to function as energy harvesters, according to an MIT news release. These cells are able to power sensors in the RFID tag in sunny and dimmer indoor light conditions.MIT researchers say the sensors could potentially function for months or even years at a time, depending on the environment's moisture and heat condition.The scientists explained in the news release that their goal was to create inexpensive internet sensors that would not require the use of batteries or any other outside power source.The study, published in the journals Advanced Functional Materials and IEEE Sensors, found that the sensors were able to transmit data for extended amounts of time at five times the distance of traditional RFID tags.This technology could be used to track cargo in supply chains, monitor soil and monitor the amount of energy used by building equipment.Researcher Ian Matthew from the university's Department of Mechanical Engineering said in the news release that RFID tag prototype was only able to monitor the temperature.He explained that researchers plan to add more sensors integrated with perovskite cells  to the RFID tag to monitor humidity, pressure, vibration and even pollution levels.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. RFID tags with photovoltaic sensors being used to power a device2. How the sensors work3. Data being transmitted by the sensor4. What this technology could be used forVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from Massachusetts Institute of Technology have published a study detailing the use of photovoltaic powered sensors on radio-frequency identification, or RFID tags, to power internet of things devices.""According to an MIT news release, thin film perovskite cells were added onto the RFID tags to function as energy harvesters.""These cells are able to power sensors in the RFID tag in sunny and dimmer indoor light conditions.""MIT researchers say the sensors could potentially function for months or even years at a time, depending on the environment's moisture and heat condition.""The study, published in the journals Advanced Functional Materials and IEEE Sensors, found that the sensors were able to transmit data for extended amounts of time at five times the distance of traditional RFID tags.""This technology could be used to track cargo in supply chains, monitor soil and monitor the amount of energy used by building equipment."SOURCES: New Atlas, MIT, Advanced Functional Materials, IEEE Sensorshttps://newatlas.com/technology/mit-light-powered-rfid-tags-internet-of-things/http://news.mit.edu/2019/photovoltaic-rfid-sensors-iot-0927https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/adfm.201904072https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/xpl/RecentIssue.jsp?punumber=7361***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 05:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/02/3899966/3899966_76C3BB0DDA0C4EAEBA2DE661C285E6D5_191002_3899966_Light_powered_RFID_tags_could_soon_power_interne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, RFID, RFID tag, light-powered RFID, RFID technology, MIT RFID technology, internet of things, RFID internet of things, light-powered sensor for  internet of things, perovskite cells, internet-connected sensors, internet of things devices, photovoltaic RFID tag, Photovoltaic-powered sensors, RFID-based devices]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899866</guid>
      <title>Students exposed to polluted air on exam day receive lower grades</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the London School of Economics has found that students exposed to polluted air before taking their exams end up receiving lower scores.For the study, 2,418 students in the Greater London urban area were tested taking a total of 11,443 exams over a period of several weeks. Researchers found that a one unit increase of PM 10 levels indoors resulted in a 0.055 to 2.230 percentage point decrease in student test scores.The study explained that particle pollution is classified as "inhalable coarse particles" or PM 10, and "fine particles," or PM 2.5, on the basis of their size.Particles larger than 2.5 micrometers and smaller than 10 micrometers in diameter are referred to as PM, 10 while particles that are 2.5 micrometers or smaller in diameter are called PM 2.5.The study tested indoor air pollution levels in exam rooms and found PM 10 levels above 75 micrograms per cubic meter. This was able to reduce a student's test score by 3.41 percentage points.The World Health Organization's limit for PM 10 is 50 micrograms per cubic meter.Sefi Roth, a researcher from the London School of Economics who was involved with the study, told the Times of London that students should limit their outdoor activity on polluted days and try to take the less polluted route to school, the Irish Post reports. A separate study examining the impact of PM 2.5 on Israeli students also found a significant decline in student performance.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Air pollution affecting students test results2. How much air pollution affected a student while they took exams3. Air pollution levels found in a classroom4. Ways to avoid air pollutionVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the London School of Economics has found that students exposed to polluted air before taking their exams end up receiving lower scores.""For the study, 2,418 students in the Greater London urban area were tested taking a total of 11,443 exams over a period of several weeks.""Researchers found that a one unit increase of PM 10 levels indoors resulted in a 0.055 to 2.230 percentage point decrease in student test scores.""The study tested indoor air pollution levels in exam rooms and found PM 10 levels above 75 micrograms per cubic meter. This was able to reduce a student's test score by 3.41 percentage points.""The Irish Post reports, Sefi Roth, a researcher from the London School of Economics who was involved with the study, told the Times of London that students should limit their outdoor activity on polluted days and try to take the less polluted route to school."SOURCES: The Irish Post, The Times, Sefi Roth Twitter, London School of Academics, World Health Organization, American Economic Associationhttps://www.irishpost.com/news/students-exposed-pollution-exams-get-worse-grades-according-new-study-171921https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/breathing-polluted-air-on-exam-day-can-lower-students-grades-ls3vrv8w5https://twitter.com/Sefi_Roth_http://personal.lse.ac.uk/roths/JMP.pdfhttps://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/ambient-(outdoor)-air-quality-and-healthhttps://pubs.aeaweb.org/doi/pdfplus/10.1257/app.20150213***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 02:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/02/3899866/3899866_04D28882FF144E959A077E75C14997DF_191002_3899866_Students_exposed_to_polluted_air_on_exam_day_rec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  pollution, air pollution, air pollution UK, pollution linked to grades, pollution grades, pollution academics, pollution linked to getting worse grades, students pollution school, students pollution grades]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899861</guid>
      <title>Manhattan's tallest office tower to open in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe One Vanderbilt tower is set to become the tallest office tower in Midtown, Manhattan with a height of 1,401 feet once it completes construction and opens in 2020.The project is being helmed by American architectural firm Kohn Pedersen Fox Associates.The skyscraper will include a total of 1.7 million square feet of office space which spreads across 58 floors, according to the architectural firm's website. The building will consist of 42 elevators and 5 escalators.The tower's exterior will be lined with a glass facade while the building's top part will be made of four interlocking volumes that rise towards the sky.The overall shape of the tower is meant to complement the Empire State and Chrysler buildings in the area, according to Kohn Pedersen Fox Associates. The skyscraper will include a 30,000 square-foot amenity floor complete with outdoor garden terraces as well as a dining area. A pedestrian plaza will also be added to the bottom of the skyscraper.The architectural firm stated on its website that the building is aiming for LEED certification of sustainability as well as WELL certification for a building's health and well-being.The company did not detail which sustainable features the tower would include.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The One Vanderbilt Tower appears2. The building's office space, elevators and escalators3. The tower's exterior4. The tower's amenity floorVOICEOVER (in English): "The One Vanderbilt tower is set to become the tallest office tower in Midtown, Manhattan with a height of 1,401 feet once it completes construction and opens in 2020.""The project is being helmed by American architectural firm Kohn Pedersen Fox Associates.""According to the architectural firm's website, the skyscraper will include a total of 1.7 million square feet of office space which spreads across 58 floors.""The building will consist of 42 elevators and 5 escalators.""The tower's exterior will be lined with a glass facade while the building's top part will be made of four interlocking volumes that rise towards the sky.""The skyscraper will include a 30,000 square-foot amenity floor complete with outdoor garden terraces as well as a dining area.""A pedestrian plaza will also be added to the bottom of the skyscraper."SOURCES: New Atlas, Schindler, Kohn Pedersen Fox Associates, One Vanderbilt, Skyscraper Center, Curbed New Yorkhttps://newatlas.com/architecture/kpf-one-vanderbilt-tops-out/https://www.schindler.com/com/internet/en/media/behind-the-scenes/customer-projects/2018/one-vanderbilt.htmlhttps://www.kpf.com/projects/one-vanderbilthttps://www.kpf.com/current/news/kpf-designed-one-vanderbilt-tops-out-in-midtown-manhattanhttps://www.onevanderbilt.com/#mainhttps://www.skyscrapercenter.com/building/one-vanderbilt/15833https://ny.curbed.com/2019/9/19/20873336/midtown-east-new-york-one-vanderbilt-construction***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 02:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/02/3899861/3899861_18957685378140278ECFD804E9B38DFF_191002_3899861_Manhattan_s_tallest_office_tower_to_open_in_2020_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, new york architecture, manhattan architecture, crystalline skyscraper, One Vanderbilt skyscraper, crystalline skyscraper new york, one vanderbilt tower, one vanderbilt nyc, one vanderbilt spire, one vanderbilt manhattan, one vanderbilt new york, new york skyscrapers, manhattan skyscrapers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900734</guid>
      <title>Plastic waste in remote Atlantic island likely from Chinese ships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report has found a 15 percent increase of plastic waste on a remote Atlantic island called Inaccessible Island, and it's likely being dumped by Chinese merchant ships.The researchers examined plastic bottles that washed ashore on the island in 1984, 2009 and in 2018. Most of the plastic waste that drifted to the island during the 1980s was from South America, according to their findings. In 2009, plastic debris from Asia surpassed the amount of plastic waste from South America, and by the year 2018, researchers said, 75 percent of the plastic debris originated from Asia, with most made in China.Around 90 percent of the bottles discovered by researchers had been manufactured in the past two years. This means the plastic could not have been carried by ocean currents from Asia as that would take roughly three to five years to wash ashore.This indicates that marine merchant ships dispose of plastic bottles into the ocean rather than disposing it at trash cans at ports, AFP reports, citing the study. The authors noted that the number of Chinese marine ships has steadily increased in the Atlantic Ocean since the 1990s.Peter Ryan, one of the authors involved with the study, told AFP that the plastic waste is not coming from land, adding that, "It's inescapable that it's from ships."More than eight million tons of plastic are dumped into the oceans every single year, 50 percent of which are single use plastics, according to non-profit organization Plastic Oceans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Plastic waste on Inaccessible Island2. Results the report found in 1984, 2009 and 20183. 90 percent of the plastic bottles were manufactured in the past two years4. Merchant ships disposing of plastic into the oceanVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report has found a 15 percent increase of plastic waste on a remote Atlantic island called Inaccessible Island, and it's likely being dumped by Chinese merchant ships.""The researchers examined plastic bottles that washed ashore on the island in 1984, 2009 and in 2018.""According to their findings, most of the plastic waste that drifted to the island during the 1980s was from South America.""In 2009, plastic debris from Asia surpassed the amount of plastic waste from South America, and by the year 2018, researchers said, 75 percent of the plastic debris originated from Asia, with most made in China.""Around 90 percent of the bottles discovered by researchers had been manufactured in the past two years. This means the plastic could not have been carried by ocean currents from Asia as that would take roughly three to five years to wash ashore.""Citing the study, AFP reports that this indicates that marine merchant ships dispose of plastic bottles into the ocean rather than disposing it at trash cans at ports.""The authors noted that the number of Chinese marine ships has steadily increased in the Atlantic Ocean since the 1990s."SOURCES: Phys.org, Proceedings of the National Academy of Science, Sustainability Times, AFP, Plastic Oceanshttps://phys.org/news/2019-09-ocean-plastic-ships.htmlhttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2019/09/24/1909816116https://www.sustainability-times.com/environmental-protection/study-inaccessible-islands-plastic-trash-comes-from-ships/https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/ocean-plastic-waste-probably-comes-ships-report-says-doc-1kv8e91https://plasticoceans.org/the-facts/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 12:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/03/3900734/3900734_A619C9670A814C519CF66A1A7494F41C_191003_3900734_Plastic_waste_in_remote_Atlantic_island_likely_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic pollution, plastic waste, plastic waste in oceans, ocean plastic pollution, plastic waste in the ocean, plastic pollution in the ocean, plastic in ocean, ocean plastic waste, south atlantic ocean, south atlantic ocean plastic waste, plastic pollution from ships, plastic polluting the oceans, plastic waste ships, plastic debris from ship]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900702</guid>
      <title>North Korea tests new submarine-launched missile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPyongyang claims it successfully test-launched a new type of submarine missile.North Korea's state news agency KCNA has released images of what it says is a new type of submarine-launched missile.According to the agency, the projectile was fired in vertical mode in the waters near Wonsan Bay on Wednesday.The SLBM, or submarine-launched ballistic missile, is called Pukguksong-3. Reuters reports that it uses solid fuel and is nuclear-capable missile to be tested since November 2017. According to the BBC, it is capable of flying up to 1,900 kilometers.South Korean officials say that during the Wednesday test, the missile flew 450 kilometers before landing in the East Sea.The Pukguksong-3 also reached an altitude of 910 kilometers before landing  nearly twice as high as the International Space Station.The BBC reports that Pyongyang has carried out 10 missile tests this year, but have only fired short range projectiles.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korea test launches Pukguksong-3 2. Pukguksong-3 submarine-launched ballistic missile3. Distance and trajectory of Pukguksong-3 launch4. Altitude of Pukguksong-3 during launchVOICEOVER (in English): "North Korea's state news agency KCNA has released images of what it says is a new type of submarine-launched missile."According to the agency, the projectile was fired in vertical mode in the waters near Wonsan Bay on Wednesday.""The SLBM, or submarine-launched ballistic missile, is called Pukguksong-3. Reuters reports that it uses solid fuel and is nuclear-capable missile to be tested since November 2017.""According to the BBC, it is capable of flying up to 1,900 kilometers.""South Korean officials say that during the Wednesday test, the missile flew 450 kilometers before landing in the East Sea.""The Pukguksong-3 also reached an altitude of 910 kilometers before landing  nearly twice as high as the International Space Station."SOURCES: Reuters, BBChttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles/north-korea-says-successfully-tested-new-submarine-launched-ballistic-missile-kcna-idUSKBN1WH2GShttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49915224***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 11:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/03/3900702/3900702_C2D5F7D2E1D541978966984B23113B1A_191003_3900702_North_Korea_tests_new_submarine_launched_missile_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea missile, submarine launched missile, north korea submarine missile, submarine ballistic launch missile, SLBM, ballistic missile, Pukguksong-3, Pukguksong 3, Pukguksong missile, pyongyang, kim jong un]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3901170</guid>
      <title>More than half of European native trees risk extinction: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report published by the International Union for Conservation of Nature has found that approximately 58 percent of Europe's native trees are at risk of going extinct.The report said trees such as crimean rowan and the mountain ash has been assessed as threatened, while the horse chestnut tree species is deemed to be vulnerable due to the leaf-miner moth, an invasive species from the Balkans, which is causing a decline. Other species facing extinction in the European continent includes terrestrial molluscs, bryophytes and shrubs. These are threatened by the loss of agriculture, a reduction of wildlife area, climate change and invasive species.A news release by the International Union for Conservation of Nature explains that a decline in terrestrial molluscs species would be dire as they are vital for soil regeneration, nutrient recycling and producing oxygen. The report says 2,469 species of terrestrial molluscs, which are endemic to the European continent, risk extinction.A decline in Europe's ecosystem is due to a number of factors including forest fires, logging and urban development.Luc Bas, director of the organization's European regional office, said in a statement that the report shows the alarming plight of the "overlooked, undervalued species that form the backbone of Europe's ecosystems and contribute to a healthy planet."He went on to say that humans need to lessen their impact on the ecosystem and prioritize these species.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Percentage of Europe's trees that are at risk of going extinct2. Threatened tree species3. Other species facing extinction in Europe4. Why Europe's ecosystem is decliningVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report published by the International Union for Conservation of Nature has found that approximately 58 percent of Europe's native trees are at risk of going extinct.""The report said trees such as crimean rowan and the mountain ash has been assessed as threatened, while the horse chestnut tree species is deemed to be vulnerable due to the leaf-miner moth, an invasive species from the Balkans, which is causing a decline." "Other species facing extinction in the European continent includes terrestrial molluscs, bryophytes and shrubs." "These are threatened by the loss of agriculture, a reduction of wildlife area, climate change and invasive species.""A decline in Europe's ecosystem is due to a number of factors including forest fires, logging and urban development."SOURCES: International Union for Conservation of Nature, Inhabitat, The Guardian, CNN, BBC Newshttps://www.iucnredlist.org/https://www.iucn.org/news/species/201909/over-half-europes-endemic-trees-face-extinctionhttps://portals.iucn.org/library/node/48512https://inhabitat.com/more-than-half-of-europes-native-trees-face-extinction/https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/sep/27/more-than-half-of-native-european-trees-face-extinction-warns-studyhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/09/27/europe/europe-native-trees-extinction-scli-intl-scn/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-49838650***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 09:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/04/3901170/3901170_163D6D7CADD841E3B391B8686F34E248_191004_3901170_More_than_half_of_European_native_trees_risk_ext_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  europe, trees extinction europe, endemic trees europe, native european tree species, europe's endemic tree species threatened with extinction, tree species in europe, native european trees face extinction, ash tree, elm tree, rowan tree, horse chestnut tree europe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3901007</guid>
      <title>New bionic limb use electrodes, sensors for sensation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology Zurich, or ETH Zurich, and several other European universities collaborated to create a leg neuroprosthesis that sends sensory information to nerves in amputees' leg stump.A study published in Science Translational Medicine detailed the researchers' findings.The sensorized prosthetic was tested on three different amputees as they conducted different activities such as walking up and down the stairs with and without the neuroprosthesis. The study found that the sensorized bionic prosthetic allowed the participants to successfully feel obstacles underneath their foot, prevented them from falling and allowed them to walk faster.Scientists implanted tiny electrodes into the amputees' residual nerves and placed an insole with sensors under the bionic foot as well as sensors above the prosthetic knee. Signals were then sent to the residual nerves as the person walked. The nerves were able to send sensory information to the amputees' brain, allowing them to feel their knee, heel and the rest of their foot as they walked.In a press release from ETH Zurich, researchers explained that this technology improves the health of amputees as it would reduce phantom pain in their limb and improve their walking ability.The scientists noted that the study was limited as there were only three participants and said that more volunteers as well as in-home assessments were needed to provide a stronger assessment to the study's findings.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The new bionic limb and the limb sending information to nerves in the leg stump2. The prosthetic being tested3. Results of the tests4. Electrodes being put into residual nerves, soles with sensors and sensors above the prosthetic knee5. Signals being sent from the sole to the residual nerves6. Sensory information being sent from the residual nerve to the brain VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology Zurich, or ETH Zurich, and several other European universities collaborated to create a leg neuroprosthesis that sends sensory information to nerves in amputees' leg stump.""A study published in Science Translational Medicine detailed the researchers' findings.""The sensorized prosthetic was tested on three different amputees as they conducted different activities such as walking up and down the stairs with and without the neuroprosthesis." "The study found that the sensorized bionic prosthetic allowed the participants to successfully feel obstacles underneath their foot, prevented them from falling and allowed them to walk faster.""Scientists implanted tiny electrodes into the amputees' residual nerves and placed an insole with sensors under the bionic foot as well as sensors above the prosthetic knee.""Signals were then sent to the residual nerves as the person walked.""The nerves were able to send sensory information to the amputees' brain, allowing them to feel their knee, heel and the rest of their foot as they walked."SOURCES: Medical Xpress, Science Daily, Science Translational Medicine, Medpage Todayhttps://m.medicalxpress.com/news/2019-10-leg-amputees-nerve-stimulating-prosthesis-real.htmlhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/10/191002144243.htmhttps://stm.sciencemag.org/content/11/512/eaav8939https://www.medpagetoday.com/neurology/generalneurology/82537***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 04:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/04/3901007/3901007_19BB6ECE68504F508ECE867362F1AF43_191004_3901007_New_bionic_limb_use_electrodes__sensors_for_sens_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  prosthetic leg, prosthetic limb, prosthetic limb sensation, bionic limb, bionic leg sensation, nerve-stimulating leg prosthesis,  nerve-stimulating prosthetic limb,  Neuroprosthetic Leg, feeling prosthetic limb, prosthetic limb technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902721</guid>
      <title>Massive iceberg breaks from Eastern Antarctica</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists said iceberg D-28 is among the largest to calve from Antarctic ice in decades, but is not caused by climate change. USA Today reports that a huge iceberg broke off from the Amery Ice Shelf in Eastern Antarctica on September 26.The iceberg, named D-28, has an area of over 1,636 square kilometers  bigger than Greater London or Los Angeles.According to USA Today, scientists working with the Australian Arctic Division said they first discovered a rift in the early 2000s and have been observing it because they expected the ice to calve.They said the calving is part of the ice shelf's normal cycle and not due to atmospheric warming, which mostly affects Western Antarctica, and not the east where D-28 is. Since the ice shelf was already floating, the calving has no direct impact on sea levels. However, the loss of ice may influence melting under the remaining ice shelf.Maritime authorities will now be tracking the iceberg, according to CNN, for the potential hazard it poses to shipping.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Iceberg D-28 separates from Antarctica 2. Cracks open in Amery Ice Shelf, breaking the iceberg off3. The calving is not related to climate change and its future effects on Antarctica4. The iceberg is tracked by authorities for navigation safetyVOICEOVER (in English): "USA Today reports that a huge iceberg broke off from the Amery Ice Shelf in Eastern Antarctica on September 26." "The iceberg, named D-28, has an area of over 1,636 square kilometers  bigger than Greater London or Los Angeles.""According to USA Today, scientists working with the Australian Arctic Division said they first discovered a rift in the early 2000s and have been observing it because they expected the ice to calve.""They said the calving is part of the ice shelf's normal cycle and not due to atmospheric warming, which mostly affects Western Antarctica, and not the east where D-28 is. Since the ice shelf was already floating, the calving has no direct impact on sea levels. However, the loss of ice may influence melting under the remaining ice shelf.""Maritime authorities will now be tracking the iceberg, according to CNN, for the potential hazard it poses to shipping."SOURCES: USA Today, New York Times, CNNhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/10/01/iceberg-d-28-breaks-off-antartica-amery-ice-shelf/3829083002/https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/01/climate/antarctica-iceberg-d28.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/01/world/vast-iceberg-leaves-antarctic-shelf-scli-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 16:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/08/3902721/3902721_6569CD24F84B48358487042DE915B7CA_191008_3902721_Massive_iceberg_breaks_from_Eastern_Antarctica_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Iceberg, d-28, antarctica, arctic, east antarctic ice sheet, amery ice shelf, ice sheet, ice shelf, calving, los angeles, london, australian arctic division, maritime, global warming, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902473</guid>
      <title>Microplastics causes immune cells to die at a faster rate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the University Medical Center Utrecht has found that immune cells that target microplastics die three times faster than cells that aren't exposed to microplastics. The research was presented at the Plastic Health Summit on October 3 in Amsterdam.To test the microplastics and the immune cells, the scientists compared clean microplastics with contaminated microplastics. Researchers put microplastic particles of different sizes in a petri dish along with immune cells and blood plasma.The experiment found that clean microplastics were not recognized as intruders by the immune cells, and were therefore left untouched. However, the study found that larger contaminated microplastics were targeted by immune cells. According to a news release by the University Medical Center Utrecht, those immune cells died shortly after while the microplastics remained.The study also found that smaller microplastics encapsulated by the cells did not harm the immune cells.Lead author of the study Nienke Vrisekoop explained in the news release that it's unclear what will happen in the body as microplastics accumulate and are unable to be eliminated by the immune cells.She said their team plans to follow up on their research by testing microplastics that have been exposed to the wind and the weather.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Microplastics, immune cells and stopwatch2. How researchers tested the microplastics and the immune cells3. Clean microplastics weren't targeted by the immune cells 4. Larger contaminated microplastics ingested by the immune cells ended up killing them5. Smaller microplastics targeted by the immune cells were not harmedVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the University Medical Center Utrecht has found that immune cells that target microplastics die three times faster than cells that aren't exposed to microplastics." "The research was presented at the Plastic Health Summit on October 3 in Amsterdam.""To test the microplastics and the immune cells, the scientists compared clean microplastics with contaminated microplastics.""Researchers put microplastic particles of different sizes in a petri dish along with immune cells and blood plasma.""The experiment found that clean microplastics were not recognized as intruders by the immune cells, and were therefore left untouched.""However, the study found that larger contaminated microplastics were targeted by immune cells.""According to a news release by the University Medical Center Utrecht, those immune cells died shortly after while the microplastics remained.""The study also found that smaller microplastics encapsulated by the cells did not harm the immune cells."SOURCES: Inhabitat, University Medical Center Utrecht, The Ecologist, Plastic Health Coalition https://inhabitat.com/microplastics-accelerate-cell-death-at-3-times-the-normal-rate-study-says/https://www.umcutrecht.nl/nl/Nieuws/Wat-doen-microplastics-met-onze-afweerhttps://theecologist.org/2019/oct/03/microplastics-may-harm-human-healthhttps://www.plastichealthcoalition.org/press/what-health-risks-do-micro-and-nanoplastics-pose-to-the-human-body-the-plastic-health-summit-brings-scientists-influencers-and-industry-from-all-over-the-world-together-and-presents-the-preliminary/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 08:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/07/3902473/3902473_A616529CD40B49B68AEA984C209C92D7_191007_3902473_Microplastics_causes_immune_cells_to_die_at_a_fa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, microplastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, microplastics cell death, microplastics accelerates cell death, cells exposed to microplastics, immune cells microplastics, microplastics related to cell death, microplastics human health, microplastics effect on human health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902357</guid>
      <title>Ocean Cleanup's redesigned system successfully collects plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Ocean Cleanup's plastic-catching system is now collecting and retaining plastic debris from the Great Pacific Garbage Patch for the first time, the non-profit organization announced on Wednesday.The Ocean Cleanup redesigned its cleanup system earlier this year and added a parachute in order for the system to collect plastic at a more consistent speed.System 001/B uses a parachute to allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system. The system's plastic-collecting screen has been moved forward to prevent fracturing to its floating barrier.Ocean Cleanup explained on their website that the organization added bigger floats to the system's corkline in order to increase buoyancy. These are stacked on top of one another to prevent plastic waste from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier.In a news release on Wednesday, the organization explained that the system has successfully collect large pieces of plastic waste and ghost nets that are typically used for fishing. The system was also able to collect microplastics as tiny as one millimeter from the Pacific Ocean.The plastic will eventually be returned to land for recycling.Ocean Cleanup said they will start designing its next cleanup system, System 002, which will be able to collect and retain plastics for longer periods of time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New Ocean Cleanup system with the parachute 2. How the parachute works in the system3. Plastic-collecting screen in the new clean up system4. Bigger floats for the redesigned system5. Fishing nets are present in the plastic waste collected by the system6. The system has also collected microplastics7. Plastic waste being taken for recyclingVOICEOVER (in English): "The Ocean Cleanup redesigned its cleanup system earlier this year and added a parachute in order for the system to collect plastic at a more consistent speed.""System 001/B uses a parachute to allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system.""The system's plastic-collecting screen has been moved forward to prevent fracturing to its floating barrier.""Ocean Cleanup explained on their website that the organization added bigger floats to the system's corkline in order to increase buoyancy.""These are stacked on top of one another to prevent plastic waste from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier.""In a news release, the organization explained that the system has successfully collect large pieces of plastic waste and ghost nets that are typically used for fishing.""The system was also able to collect microplastics as tiny as one millimeter from the Pacific Ocean.""The plastic will eventually be returned to land for recycling."SOURCES: New Atlas, The Ocean Cleanup,The Guardian, CNNhttps://newatlas.com/environment/ocean-cleanup-starts-capturing-plastic-great-pacific-garbage-patch/https://theoceancleanup.com/updates/into-the-twilight-zone/https://theoceancleanup.com/updates/the-ocean-cleanup-successfully-catches-plastic-in-the-great-pacific-garbage-patch/https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/oct/03/ocean-cleanup-device-successfully-collects-plastic-for-first-timehttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/02/tech/ocean-cleanup-catching-plastic-scn-trnd/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 02:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/07/3902357/3902357_55AA0823EAA648038A5C920DCCB29958_191007_3902357_Ocean_Cleanup_s_redesigned_system_successfully_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ocean cleanup 2019, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup technology,  ocean cleanup project 2019, ocean cleanup, plastic pollution, polluted oceans, technology, cleaning up the oceans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902354</guid>
      <title>Ocean Cleanup's redesigned system successfully collects plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Ocean Cleanup's plastic-catching system is now collecting and retaining plastic debris from the Great Pacific Garbage Patch for the first time, the non-profit organization announced on Wednesday.The Ocean Cleanup redesigned its cleanup system earlier this year and added a parachute in order for the system to collect plastic at a more consistent speed.The company explained on their website that their previous system failed to retain plastic as the system would travel either faster or slower than the plastic.This meant that the plastic would float into the system only for it to float out of it.System 001/B uses a parachute to allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system. The system's plastic-collecting screen has been moved forward to prevent fracturing to its floating barrier.Ocean Cleanup explained on their website that the organization added bigger floats to the system's corkline in order to increase buoyancy. These are stacked on top of one another to prevent plastic waste from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier.In a news release on Wednesday, the organization explained that the system has successfully collect large pieces of plastic waste and ghost nets that are typically used for fishing. The system was also able to collect microplastics as tiny as one millimeter from the Pacific Ocean.The plastic will eventually be returned to land for recycling.Ocean Cleanup said they will start designing its next cleanup system, System 002, which will be able to collect and retain plastics for longer periods of time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New Ocean Cleanup system with the parachute 2. How the parachute works in the system3. Plastic-collecting screen in the new clean up system4. Bigger floats for the redesigned system5. Fishing nets are present in the plastic waste collected by the system6. The system has also collected microplastics7. Plastic waste being taken for recyclingVOICEOVER (in English): "The Ocean Cleanup redesigned its cleanup system earlier this year and added a parachute in order for the system to collect plastic at a more consistent speed.""System 001/B uses a parachute to allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system.""The system's plastic-collecting screen has been moved forward to prevent fracturing to its floating barrier.""Ocean Cleanup explained on their website that the organization added bigger floats to the system's corkline in order to increase buoyancy.""These are stacked on top of one another to prevent plastic waste from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier.""In a news release, the organization explained that the system has successfully collect large pieces of plastic waste and ghost nets that are typically used for fishing.""The system was also able to collect microplastics as tiny as one millimeter from the Pacific Ocean.""The plastic will eventually be returned to land for recycling."SOURCES: New Atlas, The Ocean Cleanup,The Guardian, CNNhttps://newatlas.com/environment/ocean-cleanup-starts-capturing-plastic-great-pacific-garbage-patch/https://theoceancleanup.com/updates/into-the-twilight-zone/https://theoceancleanup.com/updates/the-ocean-cleanup-successfully-catches-plastic-in-the-great-pacific-garbage-patch/https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/oct/03/ocean-cleanup-device-successfully-collects-plastic-for-first-timehttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/02/tech/ocean-cleanup-catching-plastic-scn-trnd/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 02:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/07/3902354/3902354_63DBF18FF4DD4694B192AB62B5CECE18_191007_3902354_Ocean_Cleanup_s_redesigned_system_successfully_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ocean cleanup 2019, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup technology,  ocean cleanup project 2019, ocean cleanup, plastic pollution, polluted oceans, technology, cleaning up the oceans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903296</guid>
      <title>Trump withdraws U.S. troops from Syria-Turkey border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmerica's Kurdish allies have been left to face a possible Turkish invasion alone after Trump decided to withdraw U.S. troops from Syria.According to The Guardian, the U.S. and Turkey established an arrangement in August to carry out joint patrols along a 'safe zone' on the Turkey-Syria border and keep Turkish and Kurdish troops apart. But on Monday, U.S. troops began withdrawing from the border following an order from the White House.Prior to the withdrawal, Turkey had proposed to extend the safe zone deeper in Syria to resettle non-Kurdish Syrian refugees there. The plan was opposed by the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Front, or SDF, who Turkey considers terrorists.According to Reuters, U.S. withdrawal of troops and military vehicles from key positions on the border effectively gives Turkey a green light to move into the area.On Monday, the Turkish defence ministry declared in a Twitter post that preparations for a possible military operation into Syria are completed.SDF Spokesman Mustafa Bali said the SDF will defend northeast Syria at all costs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Joint patrols on Syria-Turkey border2. Proposed Turkey safe zone to resettle refugees3. U.S. military vehicles leaving border 4. Turkey military operation into Syria5. Possibility of of ISIS regrouping6. U.S. troops redeployed to other parts of SyriaVOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Guardian, the U.S. and Turkey established an arrangement in August to carry out joint patrols along a 'safe zone' on the Turkey-Syria border and keep Turkish and Kurdish troops apart.""But on Monday, the U.S. began pulling its troops, leaving the Kurds to face a possible Turkish invasion alone.""Prior to the withdrawal, Turkey had proposed to extend the safe zone deeper in Syria to resettle non-Kurdish Syrian refugees there.""The plan was opposed by the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Front, or SDF, who Turkey considers terrorists.""According to Reuters, U.S. withdrawal of troops and military vehicles from key positions on the border effectively gives Turkey a green light to move into the area.""On Monday, the Turkish defence ministry declared in a Twitter post that preparations for a possible military operation into Syria are completed.""SDF Spokesman Mustafa Bali accused the U.S. of leaving to turn the area into a warzone, but said the SDF will defend northeast Syria at all costs.""Trump's decision has received much backlash from both Republicans and Democrats.""House Speaker Nancy Pelosi called it a threat to regional security, while Senate leader Mitch McConnell worried it might increase the risk of ISIS and other terrorist organizations regrouping.""According to The Guardian, the Trump administration insisted it wasn't supporting a Turkish offensive. A senior administration official later claimed that troops were pulled back from the border, but won't be leaving Syria.""Instead, he says the soldiers will be redeployed to more secure positions inside the country."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardian, Reutershttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-49960973https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/07/us-withdrawal-from-syria-leaves-fate-of-isis-fighters-and-families-in-detention-uncertainhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-syria-security-turkey-usa-congress-idUSKBN1WM1ZO***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 16:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/09/3903296/3903296_1026989DA074443AA0EE9098B6AA6936_191009_3903296_Trump_withdraws_U_S__troops_from_Syria_Turkey_bo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Syria withdrawal, Trump Syria withdrawal, US troops in Syria, Trump Syria, US Syria, US pulls out of Syria, Trump, Turkey]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903958</guid>
      <title>What were the mysterious fireballs that crashed in Chile?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResidents of Chiloe Island saw a mysterious fireball blazing down the sky before fragmenting on September 25.According to TVN, a local woman said that following the incident, she found burning bushes near her house.Science Alert reports that Chile's National Geology and Mining Service issued a report three days later, saying it found no evidence of a fallen meteorite.CNet reported that since the object was not identified, it was officially an unidentified flying object, or UFO."According TVN, Chilean astronomer and astrophysicist Jose Maza had said the fireball was either a meteorite or space debris that fell back to Earth.Popular Mechanics reports that since the authorities ruled out meteorite fall, the object may well have been parts of a spacecraft, satellite, or rocket booster.TVN reports that the National Geology and Mining Service is carrying out a detailed analysis of soil samples, and that it will release the results later this month.According to Science Alert, another explanation is that the falling object and the burning bush could be events that were entirely unrelated.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fireball disintegrates over Chiloe Island, Chile2. Fireball was not caused by meteorite according to official report3. Fireball possibly burning space debris4. Authorities performing analysis of samplesVOICEOVER (in English): "Residents of Chiloe Island saw a mysterious fireball streaking across the sky before fragmenting into smaller glowing orbs on September 25.""According to TVN, a local woman said that following the incident, she found burning bushes near her house.""Science Alert reports that Chile's National Geology and Mining Service issued a report three days later, saying it found no evidence of a fallen meteorite."CNet reports that since the object was not identified, it was officially an unidentified flying object, or UFO.""According TVN, Chilean astronomer and astrophysicist Jose Maza had said the fireball was either a meteorite or space debris that fell back to Earth.""Popular Mechanics reports that since the authorities ruled out meteorite fall, the object may well have been parts of a spacecraft, satellite, or rocket booster.""TVN reports that the National Geology and Mining Service is carrying out a detailed analysis of soil samples, and that it will release the results later this month.""According to Science Alert, another explanation is that the falling object and the burning bush could be events that were entirely unrelated."SOURCES: TVN, Science Alert, CNet, Popular Mechanicshttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_LXEbphHf90https://www.sciencealert.com/whatever-fell-from-the-sky-and-sparked-fires-in-chile-forget-meteoriteshttps://www.cnet.com/news/mysterious-fireball-that-crashed-and-burned-wasnt-a-meteor/https://www.popularmechanics.com/space/a29355108/chile-fireballs-meteorites/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/10/3903958/3903958_07F63CCDF679492DB5CFE5ABDC3CFCDE_191010_3903958_What_were_the_mysterious_fireballs_that_crashed__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mysterious fireballs, meteorites, unidentified flying object, ufo, space debris, chile fireballs, chilean fireballs, burning bush, aliens, chile, dalcahue, chiloe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903421</guid>
      <title>Refile - Microplastics causes immune cells to die at a faster rate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN(Refile to fix the description of microplastic particles in the second and third cut of the animation)New research from the University Medical Center Utrecht has found that immune cells that target microplastics die three times faster than cells that aren't exposed to microplastics. The research was presented at the Plastic Health Summit on October 3 in Amsterdam.To test the microplastics and the immune cells, researchers put microplastic particles of different sizes in a petri dish along with immune cells and blood plasma. The experiment found that smaller microplastics were not recognized as intruders by the immune cells, and were therefore left untouched.However, the study found that microplastic particles with a thicker coating were targeted by immune cells.  According to a news release by the University Medical Center Utrecht, those immune cells died shortly after while the microplastics remained.The study also found that smaller microplastics encapsulated by the cells did not harm the immune cells.Lead author of the study Nienke Vrisekoop explained in the news release that it's unclear what will happen in the body as microplastics accumulate and are unable to be eliminated by the immune cells.She said their team plans to follow up on their research by testing microplastics that have been exposed to the wind and the weather.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Microplastics, immune cells and stopwatch2. How researchers tested the microplastics and the immune cells3. Microplastics that weren't targeted by the immune cells 4. Larger, thicker microplastics ingested by the immune cells ended up killing them5. Smaller microplastics targeted by the immune cells were not harmedVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the University Medical Center Utrecht has found that immune cells that target microplastics die three times faster than cells that aren't exposed to microplastics." "The research was presented at the Plastic Health Summit on October 3 in Amsterdam.""To test the microplastics and the immune cells, researchers put microplastic particles of different sizes in a petri dish along with immune cells and blood plasma.""The experiment found that smaller microplastics were not recognized as intruders by the immune cells, and were therefore left untouched.""However, the study found that microplastic particles with a thicker coating were targeted by immune cells.""According to a news release by the University Medical Center Utrecht, those immune cells died shortly after while the microplastics remained.""The study also found that smaller microplastics encapsulated by the cells did not harm the immune cells."SOURCES: Inhabitat, University Medical Center Utrecht, The Ecologist, Plastic Health Coalition https://inhabitat.com/microplastics-accelerate-cell-death-at-3-times-the-normal-rate-study-says/https://www.umcutrecht.nl/nl/Nieuws/Wat-doen-microplastics-met-onze-afweerhttps://theecologist.org/2019/oct/03/microplastics-may-harm-human-healthhttps://www.plastichealthcoalition.org/press/what-health-risks-do-micro-and-nanoplastics-pose-to-the-human-body-the-plastic-health-summit-brings-scientists-influencers-and-industry-from-all-over-the-world-together-and-presents-the-preliminary/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 02:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/09/3903421/3903421_726545B6F0CF4393B4F9F3AEB7A2A19D_191009_3903421_Refile___Microplastics_causes_immune_cells_to_di_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, microplastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, microplastics cell death, microplastics accelerates cell death, cells exposed to microplastics, immune cells microplastics, microplastics related to cell death, microplastics human health, microplastics effect on human health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904095</guid>
      <title>New research finds that aspirin could protect our lungs from air pollution.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that aspirin could protect our lungs from air pollution.According to the EPA, air pollution has been known to have an adverse effect on respiratory health. Exposure to particulate matter in the air can inflame and irritate lung cells and impair lung function.A study published in the American Journal of Respiratory and Critical Care Medicine explored whether non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs or NSAIDs, such as aspirin, could protect the lungs from pollution.Researchers analyzed data from 2,280 male veterans in the greater Boston area who were given tests to determine lung function.According to a Columbia University press release, the study examined the relationship between the lung test results, self reported NSAID use, and ambient particulate matter and black carbon in the month before the test. They found that the use of NSAIDs, mainly aspirin, reduced the effect of particulate matter on lung function by half.Aspirin appeared to have a protective effect regardless of age, health status, or tobacco use. Although the mechanism remains unknown, researchers suspect NSAIDs may be mitigating the inflammation triggered by air pollution.According to study author Xu Gao, the findings suggest NSAIDs could protect people from short-term spikes of air pollution.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The institutions that conducted the research and data about participants2. The effect of air pollution on the lungs3. Aspirin reducing the harm of pollutants4. Aspirin believed effective across age, health status and smoking habitVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the EPA, air pollution has been known to have an adverse effect on respiratory health. Exposure to particulate matter in the air can inflame and irritate lung cells and impair lung function.""A study published in the American Journal of Respiratory and Critical Care Medicine explored whether non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs or NSAIDs, such as aspirin, could protect the lungs from pollution.""Researchers analyzed data from 2,280 male veterans in the greater Boston area who were given tests to determine lung function.""According to a Columbia University press release, the study examined the relationship between the lung test results, self reported NSAID use, and ambient particulate matter and black carbon in the month before the test.""They found that the use of NSAIDs, mainly aspirin, reduced the effect of particulate matter on lung function by half.""Aspirin appeared to have a protective effect regardless of age, health status, or tobacco use.""Although the mechanism remains unknown, researchers suspect NSAIDs may be mitigating the inflammation triggered by air pollution."SOURCES: American Journal of Respiratory and Critical Care Medicine, Columbia University, EPAhttps://www.mailman.columbia.edu/public-health-now/news/aspirin-may-prevent-air-pollution-harmshttps://www.atsjournals.org/doi/pdf/10.1164/rccm.201905-1003LEhttps://www.epa.gov/particle-pollution-and-your-patients-health/health-effects-pm-patients-lung-disease***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 06:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/10/3904095/3904095_7F2DD5BEDEF8464AAB8AC04BF185C199_191010_3904095_New_research_finds_that_aspirin_could_protect_ou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, air pollution effects, air pollution harm, lungs, lung health, aspirin, NSAID, air pollution, particulate matter, pollution particles, black carbon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904052</guid>
      <title>Online stores compromised by hackers stealing credit card data</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that stores on an online shopping platform have been hacked.According to ZDNet, Volusion, a software company hosting online stores, was hacked in a bid to steal credit card information from their clients.Citing research from Check Point and Trend Micro, ZDNet reports that hackers implanted malicious Javascript code onto the company's servers after gaining access to its Google Cloud infrastructure.The malicious code was then able to hijack credit card details from information that customers entered through the online stores.Cyber security company RiskIQ explained on their website that these types of hacking attacks are called "Magecarts."According to a Medium blogpost by a researcher at Check Point, more than 6,500 online stores have been impacted. This includes a Sesame Street Live online store which has since been taken down.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hackers targeting an online shopping platform2. Malicious code being implanted onto the company's servers3. The code collecting credit card data4. Stores that have been impactedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to ZDNet, Volusion, a software company hosting online stores, was hacked in a bid to steal credit card information from their clients.""Citing research from Check Point and Trend Micro, ZDNet reports that hackers implanted malicious Javascript code onto the company's servers after gaining access to its Google Cloud infrastructure." "The malicious code was then able to hijack credit card details from information that customers entered through the online stores.""Cyber security company RiskIQ explained on their website that these types of hacking attacks are called "Magecarts."""According to a Medium blogpost by a researcher at Check Point, more than 6,500 online stores have been impacted. "This includes a Sesame Street Live online store which has since been taken down." SOURCES: ZDNet, Public WWW, RiskIQ, CheckPoint Medium blog post, Volusion press releasehttps://www.zdnet.com/article/hackers-breach-volusion-and-start-collecting-card-details-from-thousands-of-sites/https://publicwww.com/websites/%22a%2Fj%2Fvnav.js%22/8https://www.riskiq.com/blog/external-threat-management/magecart-growing-threat/https://medium.com/@marcelx/sesame-street-volusion-customers-are-comprised-how-the-cookie-monster-is-stealing-cc-numbers-21eb51ec613bhttps://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/volusion-is-first-ecommerce-platform-to-migrate-to-google-cloud-300644928.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 05:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/10/3904052/3904052_102AE69D153741F5B46E91FE68154D70_191010_3904052_Online_stores_compromised_by_hackers_stealing_cr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Credit card data, hackers steal credit card data, volusion, volusion credit card data stolen, volusion hacking operation, credit card numbers hacked, credit card hacks 2019, credit card hacking operation, credit card hacking online]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904500</guid>
      <title>Hydrogen-powered flying taxi produces zero emissions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMassachusetts-based Alaka'i Technologies has developed a hydrogen-powered air vehicle called Skai that uses six rotors and performs vertical takeoffs and landings.The aircraft also sports an airframe parachute in case if several of its props fail.According to the company's website, Skai has a range of 400 miles and will be able to remain airborne for approximately four hours. It has a capacity of five passengers, including the captain.Skai will be powered by hydrogen fuel cells, which emit only pure water, according to Skai's project page.Hydrogen fuel cells consists of compressed hydrogen which reacts with an oxidizing agent such as oxygen to create energy. These cells have a greater weight-energy density than batteries and fossil fuels.The aircraft will initially be piloted. However, the company said it is looking into remote or autonomous options.Reuters reports the company is currently waiting to receive certification from Federal Aviation Administration. Steve Hanvey, the CEO of Alaka'i Technologies, told Reuters that they expect to receive certification by the end of 2020. He added that they plan to start selling the aircraft in the beginning of 2021. The company has yet to announce the price of the aircraft.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The aircraft, how it takes off and an airframe parachute2. The range of Skai and its capacity3. How the aircraft will be powered4. The aircraft has a pilot, though the company may include remote or autonomous options in the futureVOICEOVER (in English): "Massachusetts-based Alaka'i Technologies has developed a hydrogen-powered air vehicle called Skai that uses six rotors and performs vertical takeoffs and landings.""The aircraft also consists of an airframe parachute in case if several of its props fail.""According to the company's website, Skai has a range of 400 miles and will be able to remain airborne for approximately four hours.""It has a capacity of five passengers, including the captain.""Skai will be powered by hydrogen fuel cells, which only emits pure water, according to Skai's project page." "Hydrogen fuel cells consists of compressed hydrogen which reacts with an oxidizing agent such as oxygen to create energy.""According to Forbes, these cells have a greater weight-energy density than batteries and fossil fuels.""The aircraft will initially be piloted, however, the company said it is looking into remote or autonomous options."SOURCES: Inhabitat, New Atlas, Design Boom, Reuters, Uncrate, Skai, Forbeshttps://inhabitat.com/the-skai-hydrogen-powered-aircraft-produces-zero-emissions/https://newatlas.com/alakai-skai-hydrogen-vtol-air-taxi/59911/https://www.designboom.com/technology/alakai-technologies-skai-evtol-hydrogen-fuel-cell-flying-car-03-20-2019/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-hydrogen-aircraft/hydrogen-powered-flying-vehicle-touted-as-southern-california-traffic-tonic-idUSKCN1T0078https://uncrate.com/skai-zero-emission-aircraft/https://skai.co/https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2019/08/14/zeroavia-alakai-hydrogen-fuel-cell/#65a4d88f18aa***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 04:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/11/3904500/3904500_210D127C3BF94EF78986BF2322CD09DC_191011_3904500_Hydrogen_powered_flying_taxi_produces_zero_emiss_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Skai, urban air mobility vehicle, EVTOL, skai aircraft, skai hydrogen-powered aircraft, hydrogen-powered flying vehicle, skai flying vehicle zero-emissions aircraft, skai zero-emission aircraft, skai EVTOL aircraft, air taxi, hydrogen-powered air taxi, EVTOL air taxi, skai flying taxi]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906490</guid>
      <title>Electric air taxi port to be unveiled in Singapore</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGerman aviation startup company Volocopter is collaborating with British drone infrastructure and deliveries company Skyports to build the VoloPort, an electric station for flying taxis.The VoloPort will be unveiled at the Marina Bay in Singapore later this month.The VoloPort prototype in Singapore will include passenger lounges and will allow visitors to experience pre-flight check-in and boarding procedures, according to Volocopter's project website. Visitors will also have the chance to sit inside the Volocopter while it is on the ground, reports Bloomberg.A test pilot will be inside the air taxi vehicle as it takes off from the VoloPort for a three minute demo flight on October 22.Skyports Managing Director Duncan Walker told Bloomberg that visitors can provide feedback for the VoloPort so that they can tweak the final design before the air taxi service launches in 2025.He explained that the VoloPort was built in China and then taken apart to be reassembled in Singapore.Skyports' project website explains that the VoloPort will include a range of modular designs which can be adapted to fit different environments such as rooftops, parking lots and other urban locations.The air taxi flight will likely cost around US$3.75 per mile, which is roughly double the amount of money a ground-based ride would cost, according to Bloomberg. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Voloport at Marina Bay in Singapore2. What the VoloPort prototype will include3. Visitors inside the Volocopter 4. Pilot conducting test flight of the air taxi4. Different modular designs the VoloPort will includeVOICEOVER (in English): "German aviation startup company Volocopter is collaborating with British drone infrastructure and deliveries company Skyports to build the VoloPort, or vertiport, an electric station for flying taxis.""The VoloPort will be unveiled at the Marina Bay in Singapore later this month.""According to Volocopter's project website, the VoloPort prototype in Singapore will include passenger lounges and will allow visitors to experience pre-flight check-in and boarding procedures.""Bloomberg reports that visitors will also have the chance to sit inside the Volocopter while it is on the ground." "A test pilot will be inside the air taxi vehicle as it takes off from the VoloPort for a three minute demo flight on October 22.""Skyports' project website explains that the VoloPort will include a range of modular designs which can be adapted to fit different environments such as rooftops, parking lots and other urban locations."SOURCES: Bloomberg, Skyports, Volocopter, Its World Congress 2019, New Atlashttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-10-04/a-british-company-is-building-a-hub-for-flying-taxis-in-singapore?srnd=premium-europehttps://skyports.net/projects/volo-port/#https://skyports.net/https://www.volocopter.com/en/voloport/https://press.volocopter.com/index.php/volocopter-presents-air-taxi-services-at-scalehttps://itsworldcongress2019.com/programme/demonstrations/https://newatlas.com/volocopter-infrastructure-flying-taxis/54258/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 14:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/15/3906490/3906490_D2DF935887064C6AA55963A76B9941BF_191015_3906490_Electric_air_taxi_port_to_be_unveiled_in_Singapo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Volocopter, VoloPort, Air Taxi VoloPort, Vertiport, vertiport singapore, skyport, VoloPort Volocopter, VoloPort Singapore, volocopter 2019, volocopter air taxi, volocopter flying taxi, volocopter air taxi port, flying taxis, volocopter electric aircraft, volocopter system, urban air mobility vehicle, EVTOL]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906357</guid>
      <title>Taiwan president rejects China's 'one country, two systems' deal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan has rejected China's offer of reunification under the 'one country, two systems' formula.CNA reports that during China's National Day on October 1, President Xi Jinping vowed to uphold the 'one country, two systems' model in Hong Kong and Macau, and proposed a similar arrangement for Taiwan.Taiwan president Tsai Ing-wen rejected the offer, calling the arrangement a failure, as evidenced by the current state of unrest in Hong Kong and the violent suppression of its citizens' freedoms.Reuters reports that according to Tsai, Beijing's policies toward Taiwan pose a danger to regional stability.She says that regardless of party or political affiliation, the general consensus among Taiwan's 23 million people is to reject "one country, two systems."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China's "one country, two systems" model for Hong Kong, Macau, Taiwan2. Taiwan under a "one country, two systems" model3. Hong Kong unrest points to model as failure4. Taiwan rejects China's "one country, two systems"5. Chinese bomber patrols around Taiwan6. China isolating Taiwan diplomatically7. Taiwan boosting combat capabilitiesVOICEOVER (in English): "CNA reports that during China's National Day on October 1, President Xi Jinping vowed to uphold the 'one country, two systems' model in Hong Kong and Macau, and proposed a similar arrangement for Taiwan.""According to The Economist, the policy formulated by then-Chinese president Deng Xiaoping would allow Taiwan to retain a separate administration, a capitalist system, and its own armed forces so long as it recognized Beijing's Communist government as legitimate.""Taiwan president Tsai Ing-wen rejected the offer, calling the arrangement a failure, as evidenced by the current state of unrest in Hong Kong and the violent suppression of its citizens' freedoms.""Reuters reports that according to Tsai, Beijing's policies toward Taiwan pose a danger to regional stability.""She says that regardless of party or political affiliation, the general consensus among Taiwan's 23 million people is to reject 'one country, two systems.'""According to Reuters, Beijing has steadily increased pressure on Taiwan to seek reunification, sending out warnings by flying regular bomber patrols around it. ""China has also been trying to isolate Taiwan diplomatically. Since Tsai came to power, seven countries have switched allegiance to Beijing, leaving Taiwan with only 15 nations it has formal state-to-state relations with.""Despite this, Tsai claims the country is undaunted, and is working to increase combat capabilities by purchasing advanced weapons from overseas and developing home-made aircraft."SOURCES: Reuters, CNA, The Economisthttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-taiwan-anniversary-president/taiwan-leader-rejects-chinas-one-country-two-systems-offer-idUSKBN1WP0A4?utm_source=reddit.comhttp://focustaiwan.tw/news/acs/201910010019.aspxhttps://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/30/what-is-chinas-one-country-two-systems-policy***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/15/3906357/3906357_7957E90F672046818C73B3997C19EB96_191015_3906357_Taiwan_president_rejects_China_s__one_country__t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, one country two systems, taiwan sovereignty, china unification, taiwan china relations, taiwan china, taiwan president, taiwan democracy, taiwan freedom, hong kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906269</guid>
      <title>Toyota unveils autonomous bus for 2020 Olympics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANToyota says it will supply up to 20 specially designed e-Palette electric self-driving vehicles for ferrying athletes and related staff during the 2020 Tokyo Olympic and Paralympics, the company announced earlier this week.The battery-powered vehicle is equipped with large sliding doors and powered ramps to ease group boarding by Paralympians and other athletes, Toyota said in a press release published Wednesday on its website.The vehicle will feature handrails that are easy to grab regardless of height, high-contrast interior colors to assist the color-blind and a low floor.According to Toyota, the driverless vehicle will have enough room for four wheelchairs and seven standing passengers.The vehicle is designed with a focus on safety and automated low-speed driving, with cameras and sensors for light detection and ranging, and high accuracy 3D mapping.The special e-Palette will have a 360-degree field of vision and is capable of safe self-driving at speeds up to 20 km per hour with an onboard safety operator, or level-4 autonomy."According to Toyota, the circular displays at the front and rear are designed to resemble stylized eyes, enabling the vehicle to signal its status, including driving, stopping for pedestrians and recharging."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Toyota e-Palette loading paralympic 2. E-Palette interior accessibility features and capacity3. Self-driving capabilities of vehicle4. Vehicle human-machine interface VOICEOVER (in English): "Toyota says it will supply up to 20 specially-designed e-Palette electric self-driving vehicles for ferrying athletes and related staff during the 2020 Tokyo Olympic and Paralympics.""Toyota says the battery powered vehicle is equipped with large sliding doors and powered ramps to ease group boarding by Paralympians and other athletes.""The vehicle will feature handrails that are easy to grab regardless of height, high-contrast interior colors to assist the color-blind and a low floor.""According to Toyota, the driverless vehicle will have enough room for four wheelchairs and seven standing passengers.""The vehicle is designed with a focus on safety and automated low-speed driving, with cameras and sensors for light detection and ranging, and high accuracy 3D mapping.""The special e-Palette will have a 360-degree field of vision and is capable of safe self-driving at speeds up to 20 km per hour with an onboard safety operator, or level-4 autonomy.""According to Toyota, the circular displays at the front and rear are designed to resemble stylized eyes, enabling the vehicle to signal its status, including driving, stopping for pedestrians and recharging."SOURCES: Toyota Motor, New Atlashttps://global.toyota/en/newsroom/corporate/29933371.htmlhttps://newatlas.com/urban-transport/toyota-e-palette-tokyo-2020-olympics/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 06:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/15/3906269/3906269_0F0923CF5D674810A6AB66DE7AA85A5D_191015_3906269_Toyota_unveils_autonomous_bus_for_2020_Olympics_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, toyota, toyota motors, tokyo, japan, self-driving, driverless, autonomous, electric, vehicle, bus, car, pod, e-Palette, olympics, olympics 2020, paralympics, paralympics 2020]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906246</guid>
      <title>Texas police officer guns down black woman through bedroom window</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA black woman was shot dead by a police officer in Texas through the window of her own bedroom last week.Atatiana Jefferson was inside her bedroom playing video games with her 8-year-old nephew when she heard a noise outside the window and went to see what was going on. Her lawyer S. Lee Meritt told the Fort Worth Star-Telegram that she was promptly shot dead through the window by a Texan police officer.The newspaper reports that Jefferson's neighbor, James Smith, made a call to the non-emergency police hotline to check on her as the door of her house was left open.Surveillance footage from the officer's camera shows two police officers surveying the perimeters of her house using flashlights. In the footage, one of the officer spots a figure through the bedroom window and is heard saying, "Put your hands up! Show me your hands!" and proceeds to immediately fire a gunshot through the window.In the video, the man does not explicitly identify himself as a police officer.After the shooting, the officers entered the woman's residence and began providing emergency medical care. She was pronounced dead on scene.A press release by the police mentioned that there was a firearm in Jefferson's residence, though it isn't clear if she was holding the weapon during the incident.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman and her nephew playing video games2. Two police officers searching the outside of the house3. One of the officers shooting at the woman through a window4. The officers trying to rescue the womanVOICEOVER (in English): "Atatiana Jefferson was inside her bedroom playing video games with her 8-year-old nephew when she heard a noise outside the window and went to see what was going on.""Her lawyer S. Lee Meritt told the Fort Worth Star-Telegram that she was promptly shot dead through the window by a Texan police officer.""The newspaper reports that Jefferson's neighbor, James Smith, made a call to the non-emergency police hotline to check on her as the door of her house was left open.""Surveillance footage from the officer's camera shows two police officers surveying the perimeters of her house using flashlights.""In the footage, one of the officer spots a figure through the bedroom window and is heard saying, 'Put your hands up! Show me your hands!' and proceeds to immediately fire a gunshot through the window.""In the video, the man does not explicitly identify himself as a police officer.""After the shooting, the officers entered the woman's residence and began providing emergency medical care. She was pronounced dead on scene.""A press release by the police mentioned that there was a firearm in Jefferson's residence, though it isn't clear if she was holding the weapon during the incident."SOURCES: CNN, BBC News, The Dallas Morning News, Fort Worth Star-Telegram, Go Fund Me, Twitter Fort Worth Policehttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/12/us/fort-worth-police-shooting/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50032290https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/10/13/questions-and-outrage-after-fort-worth-officer-fatally-shoots-28-year-old-woman-in-her-home/https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article236067328.htmlhttps://www.gofundme.com/f/1s5tcouu9c?utm_medium=socialhttps://twitter.com/fortworthpd/status/1183069996479586306***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 06:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/15/3906246/3906246_A12CDE0ED2E8476FABC50BB431D3D9DD_191015_3906246_Texas_police_officer_guns_down_black_woman_throu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Black woman shot dead by Texas police, US police shooting, texas shooting police, fort worth texas police shooting, black woman texas shooting, woman shot dead in her own home, US shooting, Texas police, texas shooting,  woman shot and killed in texas shooting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906231</guid>
      <title>Texas police officer guns down black woman through bedroom window</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA black woman was shot dead by a police officer in Texas through the window of her own bedroom last week.Atatiana Jefferson was inside her bedroom playing video games with her 8-year-old nephew when she heard a noise outside the window and went to see what was going on. Her lawyer S. Lee Meritt told the Fort Worth Star-Telegram that she was promptly shot dead through the window by a Texan police officer.The newspaper reports that Jefferson's neighbor, James Smith, made a call to the non-emergency police hotline to check on her as the door of her house was left open.Surveillance footage from the officer's camera shows two police officers surveying the perimeters of her house using flashlights. In the footage, one of the officer spots a figure through the bedroom window and is heard saying, "Put your hands up! Show me your hands!" and proceeds to immediately fire a gunshot through the window.In the video, the man does not explicitly identify himself as a police officer.According to a press release by the Fort Worth Police, the officer drew his gun because he had perceived a threat by the person inside the residence.After the shooting, the officers entered the woman's residence and began providing emergency medical care. She was pronounced dead on scene.A press release by the police mentioned that there was a firearm in Jefferson's residence, though it isn't clear if she was holding the weapon during the incident.The Fort Worth Police said that the officer in question has been placed on administrative leave until the police incident has been thoroughly investigated.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman and her nephew playing video games2. Two police officers searching the outside of the house3. One of the officers shooting at the woman through a window4. The officers trying to rescue the womanVOICEOVER (in English): "Atatiana Jefferson was inside her bedroom playing video games with her 8-year-old nephew when she heard a noise outside the window and went to see what was going on.""Her lawyer S. Lee Meritt told the Fort Worth Star-Telegram that she was promptly shot dead through the window by a Texan police officer.""The newspaper reports that Jefferson's neighbor, James Smith, made a call to the non-emergency police hotline to check on her as the door of her house was left open.""Surveillance footage from the officer's camera shows two police officers surveying the perimeters of her house using flashlights.""In the footage, one of the officer spots a figure through the bedroom window and is heard saying, 'Put your hands up! Show me your hands!' and proceeds to immediately fire a gunshot through the window.""In the video, the man does not explicitly identify himself as a police officer.""After the shooting, the officers entered the woman's residence and began providing emergency medical care. She was pronounced dead on scene.""A press release by the police mentioned that there was a firearm in Jefferson's residence, though it isn't clear if she was holding the weapon during the incident."SOURCES: CNN, BBC News, The Dallas Morning News, Fort Worth Star-Telegram, Go Fund Me, Twitter Fort Worth Policehttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/12/us/fort-worth-police-shooting/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50032290https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/10/13/questions-and-outrage-after-fort-worth-officer-fatally-shoots-28-year-old-woman-in-her-home/https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article236067328.htmlhttps://www.gofundme.com/f/1s5tcouu9c?utm_medium=socialhttps://twitter.com/fortworthpd/status/1183069996479586306***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 05:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/15/3906231/3906231_3C7D708BA95C414CA63667DF1B6BEA22_191015_3906231_Texas_police_officer_guns_down_black_woman_throu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Black woman shot dead by Texas police, US police shooting, texas shooting police, fort worth texas police shooting, black woman texas shooting, woman shot dead in her own home, US shooting, Texas police, texas shooting,  woman shot and killed in texas shooting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906161</guid>
      <title>China lunar lander grows cotton plant on the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina successfully grew a plant on the moon in a biological first.On January 3, China's Chang'e-4 lunar probe made a milestone soft-landing on the far side of the moon. CNN reports that the spacecraft carried a self-contained biosphere called the Lunar Micro Ecosystem, or LME, that was activated upon landing.A cotton seed inside the biosphere sprouted two leaves, making it the first living thing humans have grown on the moon.According to China's state-run Science and Technology Daily, the 2.6-kilogram LME cylinder measured 20 centimeters in length and 17 centimeters in diameter.Apart from cotton, it carried potato and arabidopsis seeds, fruit fly eggs, and yeast. These were all kept in Earth-like conditions except for microgravity and lunar radiation.Xie said the LME experienced erratic temperature fluctuations, forcing scientists to terminate the experiment and shut down the power.The shutdown left the seeds and eggs unprotected in the lunar night, when temperatures dropped to a low of minus 190 degrees Celsius, according to the China Daily.IEEE Spectrum reports the cotton leaves were dead within one lunar daytime, or 14.5 Earth days.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cotton seed on Chang'e-4 sprouted two leaves2. Seeds on the Lunar Micro Ecosystem3. Cotton plant dying after LME project termination4. Tortoise originally intended for the mission, but wasn't sentVOICEOVER (in English): "On January 3, China's Chang'e-4 lunar probe landed on the moon carrying seeds and other life.""IEEE Spectrum reports that Chinese scientists, utilizing image processing and analysis, created a 3D reconstruction that showed a cotton seed sprouting two leaves." "Xie Gengxin of Chongqing University told IEEE Spectrum that Chinese scientists initially believed the seed grew only one leaf.""The seed was the first living thing humans have grown on the moon." "The spacecraft carried the biological payload in the Lunar Micro Ecosystem, or LME.""Chongqing University's Liu Han-long told China's state-ran Science and Technology Daily that the LME cylinder weighed 2.6 kilogram and was 20 centimeter in length and 17 centimeter in diameter.""According to Science and Technology Daily, Liu said the LME carried seeds of cotton, potato and thale cress, fruit fly eggs and yeast.""Xie Gengxin told CNN that Chinese scientists had hoped the LME would raise seeds and hatch flies to create a stable biosphere to inform food production on the moon." "Xie told CNN that the LME experienced erratic temperature fluctuations, forcing scientists to terminate the experiment and shut down the power.""The shutdown left the seeds and eggs unprotected in the lunar night, when temperatures dropped to a low of minus 190 degrees Celsius, according to the China Daily.""IEEE Spectrum reports that the cotton seed was dead within one lunar night, or 14.5 Earth days." "Xie told IEEE Spectrum that the team had wanted to put a small tortoise in the LME to research the effects of the moon's low gravity on animals. But the oxygen inside the craft would have been usable to tortoises for only 20 days."SOURCES: IEEE Spectrum, Science and Technology Daily, CNN, China Daily https://spectrum.ieee.org/tech-talk/aerospace/robotic-exploration/china-grew-these-leaves-on-the-moonhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/01/15/asia/china-moon-cotton-intl/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/01/17/asia/china-moon-seed-dead-intl/index.htmlhttp://www.stdaily.com/index/kejixinwen/2019-01/16/content_746973.shtmlhttp://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/201901/31/WS5c52b8eaa3106c65c34e797d.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 02:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/15/3906161/3906161_9F1CDECF0BF64B3386DD2376C3A842A5_191015_3906161_China_lunar_lander_grows_cotton_plant_on_the_moo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china cotton plant, china cotton on moon, china moon mission, china lunar mission, china lunar probe, far side of the moon, dark side of the moon, chang'e 4, chang'e 4 spacecraft, china lands on moon, lunar micro ecosystem, LME]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906146</guid>
      <title>New Orleans Hard Rock hotel collapse leaves 2 dead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least two people have been killed after a partially constructed hotel collapsed in New Orleans on Saturday.According to the Times-Picayune, 112 workers were at the construction site of the 18-story Hard Rock Hotel in New Orleans on Saturday morning.Around 9:10 a.m., the upper six to eight floors of the half-built structure collapsed, raining down debris and knocking over a construction crane in the process.According to CNN, two people were killed in the incident, and at least 30 were hospitalized. Search teams are also looking for a missing worker that may still be trapped inside the building.Officials say the site is still highly unstable, so a second collapse is still possible.According to the Times-Picayune, the threat of further collapse prompted officials to evacuate nearby buildings on Sunday night. Authorities have not said what caused the structure to fail, but promised a "relentless" investigation into the incident.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Construction workers inside half-built Hard Rock Hotel2. New Orleans Hard Rock Hotel collapsing3. Number of dead and injured in collapse aftermath4. Search teams looking for missing workerVOICEOVER (in English): At least two people have been killed after a partially constructed hotel collapsed in New Orleans on Saturday."According to the Times-Picayune, 112 workers were at the construction site of the 18-story Hard Rock Hotel in New Orleans on Saturday morning.""Around 9:10 a.m., the upper six to eight floors of the half-built structure collapsed, raining down debris and knocking over a construction crane in the process.""According to CNN, two people were killed in the incident, and at least 30 were hospitalized.""Search teams are also looking for a missing worker that may still be trapped inside the building.""Officials say the site is still highly unstable, so a second collapse is still possible."SOURCES: CNN, Nola.comhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/13/us/new-orleans-hard-rock-collapse-sunday/index.htmlhttps://www.nola.com/news/article_3c7fef1a-edfc-11e9-8552-e7b5e0a84562.htmlhttps://www.nola.com/news/article_04402c54-ed49-11e9-8228-e3441e79e10f.htmlhttps://www.nola.com/news/article_5630478a-ed15-11e9-8620-3fb22c77f304.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 02:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/15/3906146/3906146_00C4805B20244304ABFDC695FAFE25B1_191015_3906146_New_Orleans_Hard_Rock_hotel_collapse_leaves_2_de_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hard rock hotel collapse, new orleans construction collapse, hard rock collapse, new orleans collapse, deadly collapse, hard rock hotel, hard rock hotel new orleans, new orleans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906627</guid>
      <title>Official app from the Chinese Communist Party spies on its users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report from German cyber security firm Cure53 in collaboration with the U.S.-based Open Technology Fund has found that Chinese app Study the Great Nation contains code that allows authorities to access users' phone data including messages, photos, internet history and phone contacts.The app was launched in January and consists of news articles, videos and quizzes about President Xi Jinping's ideology, called "Xi Jinping Thought."The terms and conditions for the app, which was developed by Alibaba and the Chinese Communist Party, allow for it to have access to take photos and videos, collect location data, activate audio recording and even dial phone numbers. The app can also collect information from 960 different apps present on the users' phone, including apps related to shopping and traveling.Cure53 observed the Android version of the app and found that it was actively collecting data on numerous running services and then storing the data onto the phone's external storage.However, the report said it found "no evidence" that this information was being used.The security firm's report also found that the code also permits "superuser" privileges. This could allow authorities to download any software, modify files or even log users' keystrokes.When contacted by the Washington Post, China's State Council Information Office said, "We learned from those who run the Study the Great Nation app that there is no such thing as you have mentioned."Alibaba declined to comment and referred the Washington Post's questions to China's Propaganda Department.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese app, messaging icon, photos icon, internet icon and phone contacts icon2. Other information the app has access to3. App collecting data and storing it onto an external storage4. Superuser privileges that the code allows the app to accessVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report from German cyber security firm Cure53 in collaboration with the U.S.-based Open Technology Fund has found that Chinese app Study the Great Nation contains code that allows authorities to access users' phone data including messages, photos, internet history and phone contacts.""The terms and conditions for the app, which was developed by Alibaba and the Chinese Communist Party, allow for it to have access to take photos and videos, collect location data, activate audio recording and even dial phone numbers.""The app can also collect information from 960 different apps present on the users' phone, including apps related to shopping and traveling.""Cure53 observed the Android version of the app and found that it was actively collecting data on numerous running services and then storing the data onto the phone's external storage.""However, the report said it found 'no evidence' that this information was being used.""The security firm's report also found that the code also permits 'superuser' privileges.""This could allow authorities to download any software, modify files or even log users' keystrokes."SOURCES: BBC News, Cure53 report, Washington Posthttps://www.bbc.com/news/technology-50042379https://cure53.de/analysis_report_sgn.pdfhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/chinese-app-on-xis-ideology-allows-data-access-to-100-million-users-phones-report-says/2019/10/11/2d53bbae-eb4d-11e9-bafb-da248f8d5734_story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 02:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/16/3906627/3906627_54B10A56BDBB42E1BA2DF9382397F803_191016_3906627_Official_app_from_the_Chinese_Communist_Party_sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China Study the Great Nation app, Study the Great Nation, chinese app enables spying, chinese government cyber espionage, chinese tech enables spying,  chinese app on Xi Jinping, chinese spyware app]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906622</guid>
      <title>Official app from the Chinese Communist Party spies on its users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report from German cyber security firm Cure53 in collaboration with the U.S.-based Open Technology Fund has found that Chinese app Study the Great Nation contains code that allows authorities to access users' phone data including messages, photos, internet history and phone contacts.The app was launched in January and consists of news articles, videos and quizzes about President Xi Jinping's ideology, called "Xi Jinping Thought."Users earn points for reading and commenting on different articles on the app. They are also able to compete with each other as there is a scoreboard.Cure53 said the propaganda app has become the most downloaded free program in China, with more than a 100 million downloads.The terms and conditions for the app, which was developed by Alibaba and the Chinese Communist Party, allow for it to have access to take photos and videos, collect location data, activate audio recording and even dial phone numbers. The app can also collect information from 960 different apps present on the users' phone, including apps related to shopping and traveling.Cure53 observed the Android version of the app and found that it was actively collecting data on numerous running services and then storing the data onto the phone's external storage.However, the report said it found "no evidence" that this information was being used.The security firm's report also found that the code also permits "superuser" privileges. This could allow authorities to download any software, modify files or even log users' keystrokes.When contacted by the Washington Post, China's State Council Information Office said, "We learned from those who run the Study the Great Nation app that there is no such thing as you have mentioned."Alibaba declined to comment and referred the Washington Post's questions to China's Propaganda Department.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese app, messaging icon, photos icon, internet icon and phone contacts icon2. Other information the app has access to3. App collecting data and storing it onto an external storage4. Superuser privileges that the code allows the app to accessVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report from German cyber security firm Cure53 in collaboration with the U.S.-based Open Technology Fund has found that Chinese app Study the Great Nation contains code that allows authorities to access users' phone data including messages, photos, internet history and phone contacts.""The terms and conditions for the app, which was developed by Alibaba and the Chinese Communist Party, allow for it to have access to take photos and videos, collect location data, activate audio recording and even dial phone numbers.""The app can also collect information from 960 different apps present on the users' phone, including apps related to shopping and traveling.""Cure53 observed the Android version of the app and found that it was actively collecting data on numerous running services and then storing the data onto the phone's external storage.""However, the report said it found 'no evidence' that this information was being used.""The security firm's report also found that the code also permits 'superuser' privileges.""This could allow authorities to download any software, modify files or even log users' keystrokes."SOURCES: BBC News, Cure53 report, Washington Posthttps://www.bbc.com/news/technology-50042379https://cure53.de/analysis_report_sgn.pdfhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/chinese-app-on-xis-ideology-allows-data-access-to-100-million-users-phones-report-says/2019/10/11/2d53bbae-eb4d-11e9-bafb-da248f8d5734_story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 02:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/16/3906622/3906622_647B6F2CCAE64D0EB1DAA4144923695B_191016_3906622_Official_app_from_the_Chinese_Communist_Party_sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China Study the Great Nation app, Study the Great Nation, chinese app enables spying, chinese government cyber espionage, chinese tech enables spying,  chinese app on Xi Jinping, chinese spyware app]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907653</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protest leader attacked by assailants with hammers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA prominent leader in the Hong Kong protests is in stable condition following an attack by unknown assailants.  According to the Hong Kong Free Press, Civil Human Rights Front leader Jimmy Sham was en route to a meeting in Mong Kok on Tuesday night when he was attacked by four to five men wielding hammers.The South China Morning Post reports that fellow CHRF member Figo Chan said bystanders attempted to save Sham during the ambush, but one of the attackers pointed a knife at them.According to police, officers found Sham in the street bleeding from his head and arms. His assailants fled in a car, and as yet remain unidentified.He luckily suffered no damage to his brain or bones, reports the Hong Kong Free Press, and was taken to a nearby hospital. The attack on Sham is the second to occur since the anti-government protests in Hong Kong began. In August, he and a friend were attacked at a restaurant in Kowloon by two masked men with a baseball bat and steel rod. Sham was unharmed, but his friend sustained serious bruises from being hit with the bat.The CHRF strongly condemned the incident, and accused the attackers of spreading political terror to threaten people from going out onto the streets and fighting for their rights.The South China Morning Post reports that Democratic Party lawmaker Lam Cheuk-ting described the assault as clearly politically motivated, and accused police of failing to protect opposition politicians and activists. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Jimmy Sham attacked by hammer-wielding men2. Bystanders tried to help, but attackers had knife3. Jimmy Sham injured on street; assailants fleeing in car4. Hong Kong anti-government protests5. August attack on Jimmy Sham and friend VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Hong Kong Free Press, Civil Human Rights Front leader Jimmy Sham was en route to a meeting in Mong Kok on Tuesday night when he was attacked by four to five men wielding hammers.""The South China Morning Post reports that fellow CHRF member Figo Chan said bystanders attempted to save Sham during the ambush, but one of the attackers pointed a knife at them.""According to police, officers found Sham in the street bleeding from his head and arms. His assailants fled in a car, and as yet remain unidentified.""The attack on Sham is the second to occur since the anti-government protests in Hong Kong began.""In August, he and a friend were attacked at a restaurant in Kowloon by two masked men with a baseball bat and steel rod. Sham was unharmed, but his friend sustained serious bruises from being hit with the bat."SOURCES: Hong Kong Free Press, South China Morning Posthttps://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/10/16/breaking-hong-kong-protest-leader-jimmy-sham-attacked-tai-kok-tsui/https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/08/29/just-hong-kong-protest-organiser-says-masked-men-wielding-knife-baseball-bat-attacked-companion/https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/law-and-crime/article/3033256/jimmy-sham-leader-hong-kong-democracy-group-civil***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 14:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/17/3907653/3907653_8B805FD4B37B4332B7F8E9AABD83A3B9_191017_3907653_Hong_Kong_protest_leader_attacked_by_assailants__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hong kong protest, hong kong protest leader, jimmy sham, civil human rights front, CHRF, hong kong attack, hong kong assault]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907437</guid>
      <title>NASA presents new spacesuits for next lunar mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has unveiled next generation spacesuits for the space agency's 2024 Artemis III lunar mission.One of the spacesuits, called the Exploration Extravehicular Mobility Unit, or xEMU, will allow for an increased range of movement for the arms, wrists, hips and knees while astronauts are on the lunar surface as the suit uses bearings instead of zippers.The xEMU spacesuit features a backpack called the Portable Life Support System, similar to the one used during the Apollo moon landing missions in the 1960s and 1970s.According to NASA's website, the spacesuit's communication system inside the helmet has been redesigned to include multiple microphones on the inner part of the upper torso that will automatically be activated as the astronaut speaks.NASA says the new spacesuits will allow astronauts to perform longer spacewalks, withstand moon dust and the moon's extreme temperatures ranging from negative 250 degrees to 250 degrees Fahrenheit. The space agency said the increased mobility of the astronauts is to perform different scientific tasks such as analyzing moon rocks or planting scientific instruments.NASA also debuted its second spacesuit, called the Orion Crew Survival System, which will be used by astronauts during launch and reentry in the Orion spacecraft. The suit features a lighter helmet which connects to the communications system more easily, improved thermal protection and a new interface that removes carbon dioxide and supplies air to the crew members wearing the suit. NASA says each astronaut will have a customized spacesuit to ensure a better fit and a better range of motion.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Exploration Extravehicular Mobility Unit spacesuit for the lunar surface2. The spacesuit enables increased movement3. Features the spacesuit will include 4. What the spacesuit will be able to withstand5. The Orion Crew Survival System spacesuit for launch and reentryVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has unveiled next generation spacesuits, suitable for both men and women, for the space agency's 2024 Artemis III lunar mission.""One of the spacesuits, called the Exploration Extravehicular Mobility Unit, or xEMU, will allow for an increased range of movement for the arms, wrists, hips and knees while astronauts are on the lunar surface as the suit uses bearings instead of zippers.""The xEMU spacesuit features a backpack called the Portable Life Support System, similar to the one used during the Apollo moon landing missions in the 1960s and 1970s.""According to NASA's website, the spacesuit's communication system inside the helmet has been redesigned to include multiple microphones on the inner part of the upper torso that will automatically be activated as the astronaut speaks.""NASA says the new spacesuits will allow astronauts to perform longer spacewalks, withstand moon dust and the moon's extreme temperatures ranging from negative 250 degrees to 250 degrees Fahrenheit.""The space agency said the increased mobility of the astronauts is to perform different scientific tasks such as analyzing moon rocks or planting scientific instruments."SOURCES: NASA, CNN, Associated Presshttps://www.nasa.gov/suituphttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/a-next-generation-spacesuit-for-the-artemis-generation-of-astronautshttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/orion-suit-equipped-to-expect-the-unexpected-on-artemis-missionshttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/15/world/nasa-new-artemis-spacesuit-scn-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gr32VEFpSc8 ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 09:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/17/3907437/3907437_7511784ABBA44436A417B809B9F5C6A6_191017_3907437_NASA_presents_new_spacesuits_for_next_lunar_miss_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA spacesuits, moon spacesuit, nasa new moon spacesuit, future moon spacesuits, nasa new spacesuits, new nasa nasa spacesuit design, nasa spacesuit 2019, NASA Extravehicular Mobility Unit, xEMU, Orion Crew Survival System, Next Generation Spacesuit, new Artemis spacesuits]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3909198</guid>
      <title>Proposed bill prohibits drones from flying below 200 ft from houses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. Senator Mike Lee from Utah introduced a bill in Congress on October 16 to give property owners, state authorities and Native American tribes the right to regulate their airspace.The Drone Integration and Zoning Act is seeking to transfer airspace authority beneath 200 feet from the Federal Aviation Administration to local authorities, reports the Hill. Drones flying in airspace above 200 feet would still be under the authority of the FAA.The bill would essentially allow property owners and lander owners to own airspace up to 200 feet above their land in which low-flying drones would be prohibited from operating unless they have permission.Currently the FAA allows drones to operate at or below 400 feet.According to the Hill, Senator Lee had sponsored a similar bill in 2017, called the Drone Federalism Act. The bill failed to make it through its congressional committee.The FAA had previously stated in a 2015 factsheet that separate local and state jurisdiction over airspace would create a "patchwork quilt" and could severely limit the FAA in its ability in controlling the airspace and ensuring a safe and efficient traffic flow in the air.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Drone, house and a U.S. Map 2. What the new bill proposes3. A property owner owning airspace 200 feet above their land4. Current FAA regulationsVOICEOVER (in English): "U.S. Senator Mike Lee from Utah introduced a bill in Congress on October 16 to give property owners, state authorities and Native American tribes the right to regulate their airspace.""The Hill reports that the Drone Integration and Zoning Act is seeking to transfer airspace authority beneath 200 feet from the Federal Aviation Administration to local authorities.""The bill would essentially allow property owners and lander owners to own airspace up to 200 feet above their land in which low-flying drones would be prohibited from operating unless they have permission.""Currently the FAA allows drones to operate at or below 400 feet."SOURCES: The Hill, Drone Life, Congress, Federal Aviation Administrationhttps://thehill.com/policy/technology/466143-republican-lawmaker-proposes-transferring-drone-authority-to-localhttps://dronelife.com/2019/10/15/breaking-news-this-new-drone-bill-would-make-the-airspace-over-peoples-homes-private-property/https://www.congress.gov/bill/116th-congress/senate-bill/2607/actions?q=%7B%22search%22%3A%5B%22Mike+Lee%22%5D%7D&r=1&s=4https://www.faa.gov/uas/recreational_fliers/https://www.faa.gov/uas/resources/policy_library/media/UAS_Fact_Sheet_Final.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 05:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/21/3909198/3909198_E31B8EE62C2C43998011DA2E81C4C0C3_191021_3909198_Proposed_bill_prohibits_drones_from_flying_below_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Drones, drone bill, bill to regulate drones, regulating the use of drones, Drone Integration and Zoning Act, flying drones, regulating drones, unmanned aerial vehicles, airspace regulation, drones private property, FAA, Federal Aviation Administration, decentralizing drone regulation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3909143</guid>
      <title>Bell unveils new 360 Invictus attack helicopter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBell Textron presented its 360 Invictus Attack Helicopter as part of the U.S. Army's Future Reconnaissance Aircraft competition on October 1 in Arlington, Virginia.The helicopter uses a lift-sharing wing that will reduce the demand on rotor lift during forward flight, according to a news release from the company. The Invictus 360 features an articulated main rotor that is partially based on the Bell 525 Relentless. The helicopter will have a cruise speed of roughly 185 knots and a hover time of 90 minutes.The Invictus 360 will be armed with a 20-millimeter cannon and an integrated munitions launcher that is able to fire new weapons as well as current weapons.The helicopter will also be able to deploy drones from the air.Bell Textron's Invictus 360 uses a fly-by-wire flight control system equipped with sensors to improve situational awareness. This will reduce the workload of the pilot and could eventually be used for autonomous flight.The company states that its Invictus 360 represents a low risk, sustainable and affordable option compared to its competitors.This helicopter is meant to replace Bell Textron's Kiowa Warrior helicopters, which were previously used by the U.S. Army, according to Defense News. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Bell Invictus 360 and its lift-sharing wing2. The helicopter's performance metrics and rotor system3. What weapons the helicopter can carry4. The Invictus 360's avionics and potential as an unmanned aerial vehicleVOICEOVER (in English): "Bell Textron presented its 360 Invictus Attack Helicopter as part of the U.S. Army's Future Reconnaissance Aircraft competition on October 1 in Arlington, Virginia.""According to a news release from the company, the helicopter uses a lift-sharing wing that will reduce the demand on rotor lift during forward flight.""The Invictus 360 features an articulated main rotor that is partially based on the Bell 525 Relentless.""The helicopter will have a cruise speed of roughly 185 knots and a hover time of 90 minutes.""The Invictus 360 will be armed with a 20-millimeter cannon and an integrated munitions launcher that is able to fire new weapons as well as current weapons.""The helicopter will also be able to deploy drones from the air.""Bell Textron's Invictus 360 uses a fly-by-wire flight control system equipped with sensors to improve situational awareness.""This will reduce the workload of the pilot and could eventually be used for autonomous flight."SOURCES: New Atlas, Bell Textron, Military.com. Defense News https://newatlas.com/military/bell-unveils-360-invictus-attack-helicopter/https://investor.textron.com/news/news-releases/press-release-details/2019/Lethal-Sustainable-Bell-Announces-360-Invictus-For-US-Army-Future-Attack-Reconnaissance-Aircraft-Competition/default.aspxhttps://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/10/02/bell-unveils-new-360-invictus-attack-helicopter-armys-future-wars.htmlhttps://www.defensenews.com/land/2019/10/02/bell-unshrouds-invictus-its-answer-for-the-us-armys-future-attack-recon-aircraft/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/21/3909143/3909143_A21E57D1235E4134B946D8ABFE542DB4_191021_3909143_Bell_unveils_new_360_Invictus_attack_helicopter_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 360 invictus attack helicopter, Bell textron invictus helicopter, Bell 360 invictus,  360 invictus helicopter, 360 invictus bell, 360 invictus aircraft, textron, military aircraft, military helicopter, attack helicopter, single rotor aircraft, U.S.,  U.S. Army's Future Attack Reconnaissance Aircraft, US military]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3909134</guid>
      <title>Prototype for U.S. Army's future reconnaissance helicopter features side-by-side cockpit and a wing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAVX Aircraft and L3 Technologies unveiled their compound coaxial helicopter for the U.S. Army's Future Attack Reconnaissance program on April 15.The compound coaxial helicopter design, or CCH, is to feature a side-by-side cockpit to increase pilot efficiency, according to a joint press release by the two companies.The CCH will include coaxial rotors and a next generation single engine that allows the helicopter to operate for longer periods of time in highly contested airspace and in degraded environments.The companies explained the aircraft engine along with its wing used for lift will make it faster and lighter and increase its combat capabilities. The helicopter will feature twin ducted fans which can provide forward and reverse thrust.The CCH will have manually foldable rotor blades and wings that reduce the aircraft's size.After folding rotor blades and wings, the CCH could be transported via a Boeing C-17 Globemaster III or U.S. Navy guided missile destroyers.Another contender in the military program is the Sikorsky S-97 Raider, which also uses coaxial rotors but uses a push propeller instead of two ducted fans, according to New Atlas. L3 Technologies President Christopher Kubasik stated that the CCH will provide leap-ahead capability for the U.S. Army at an affordable life-cycle cost.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The AVX/L3 compound coaxial helicopter and cockpit design2. Its coaxial rotors functioning3. The CCH wing and twin ducted fans design4. Its foldable wing and rotor bladesVOICEOVER (in English): "AVX Aircraft and L3 Technologies unveiled their compound coaxial helicopter for the U.S. Army's Future Attack Reconnaissance program on April 15.""According to a joint press release by the two companies, the compound coaxial helicopter design, or CCH, is to feature a side-by-side cockpit to increase pilot efficiency.""The CCH will include coaxial rotors and a next generation single engine that allows the helicopter to operate for longer periods of time in highly contested airspace and in degraded environments.""The companies explained the aircraft engine along with its wing used for lift will make it faster and lighter and increase its combat capabilities.""The helicopter will feature twin ducted fans which can provide forward and reverse thrust.""The CCH will have manually foldable rotor blades and wings that reduce the aircraft's size.""After folding rotor blades and wings, the CCH could be transported via a Boeing C-17 Globemaster III or U.S. Navy guided missile destroyers."SOURCES: New Atlas, Business Wire, L3 Technologies YouTubehttps://newatlas.com/avx-l3-fara-competitive-prototype/59308/https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20190415005417/en/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nVdXsVGCyBQ&feature=youtu.be***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 02:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/21/3909134/3909134_6FF3A0D0FE7B49828D3AD544D51CA601_191021_3909134_Prototype_for_U_S__Army_s_future_reconnaissance__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, AVX Aircraft, L3 Technologies, AVX-L3 CCH, L3, AVX, FARA, AVX Aircraft FARA, U.S. Army's Future Attack Reconnaissance Aircraft, military aircraft, AVX compound coaxial helicopter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3909983</guid>
      <title>New gene editing tool corrects genetic mutations more precisely</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists from Harvard University and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology have developed a new method of editing DNA, called prime editing, which combines CRISPR-Cas9 with a reverse transcriptase enzyme.The CRISPR-Cas9 is used to nick one DNA strand, while the enzyme generates a new DNA strand which is inserted into the original DNA strand, according to a study published in the journal Nature. Another reverse transcriptase enzyme then guides the CRISPR-Cas9 to nick the other DNA strand. The strand is repaired as the enzyme replicates gene edits over from the new DNA strand, producing a fully editing DNA strand.According to a Harvard news release, prime editing can also be used to replace one DNA letter with another and could correct up to 89 percent of genetic mutations."In the study, researchers explained that they used prime editing to make more than 175 edits in human cells in a laboratory and successfully corrected sickle cell anemia and Tay-Sachs disease.CRISPR-Cas9 if used by itself isn't as precise as prime editing and could lead to mismatched DNA strands that either include extra DNA code or are missing a certain genetic code, according to the Harvard news release. The authors of the study concluded by saying they will investigate the effects of prime editing on human cells and will continue to test prime editing on cells.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New method of gene editing which combines CRISPR-Cas9 with a reverse transcriptase enzyme2. How prime editing works3. One DNA letter of a DNA strand being replaced and a pie chart4. Male medical body, human cells and a DNA strand being correctedVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists from Harvard University and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology have developed a new method of editing DNA, called prime editing, which combines CRISPR-Cas9 with a reverse transcriptase enzyme.""According to a study published in the journal Nature, the CRISPR-Cas9 is used to nick one DNA strand, while the enzyme generates a new DNA strand which is inserted into the original DNA strand.""Another reverse transcriptase enzyme then guides the CRISPR-Cas9 to nick the other DNA strand. The strand is repaired as the enzyme replicates gene edits over from the new DNA strand, producing a fully editing DNA strand.""According to a Harvard news release, prime editing can also be used to replace one DNA letter with another and could correct up to 89 percent of genetic mutations.""In the study, researchers explained that they used prime editing to make more than 175 edits in human cells in a laboratory and successfully corrected sickle cell anemia and Tay-Sachs disease."SOURCES: BBC News, Nature journal, The Harvard Gazette, The Guardianhttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-50125843https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1711-4https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2019/10/new-crispr-genome-editing-system-can-target-disease-causing-genetic-variations/https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/oct/21/new-gene-editing-tool-could-fix-most-harmful-dna-mutations***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 11:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/22/3909983/3909983_4631339C47D24F7498AB1F6C8EC8A092_191022_3909983_New_gene_editing_tool_corrects_genetic_mutations_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Prime editing, prime editing in human cells, prime editing genes, prime editing DNA,  gene editing, new gene editing tool, genetic modification, dna editing technology, gene editing technology, DNA editing tool]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3909724</guid>
      <title>European glass eels use internal magnetic compass to navigate waters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the University of Miami and Norway's Institute of Marine Research has found that the European eel at a certain stage of development use an internal magnetic compass to remember the magnetic direction of tidal waves as they navigate the waters.European eels are a migratory species that hatch in the Sargasso Sea and then as laevae 5,000 kilometers to Europe's continental slope. There they turn metamorphosize into a transparent larval stage called 'glass eel' and continue to Europe's coast and enter estuaries.Some of the eels continue to swim upstream to freshwater. Eels that get there then grow into the adult eel stage, which is yellow in color. These eventually become sexually mature, silver eels.Scientists gathered 222 glass eels flowing in four different directions  north, southeast, south and northwest  from separate estuaries in Austevoll, Norway and put them in a magnetic laboratory facility, according to a study published in the journal Communications Biology. When the lab's magnetic north was rotated, they observed that the eels turned towards the magnetic direction of the tidal current at their estuary.The researchers mentioned in the study that this mechanism could be helpful to eels if they lose visual reference points as they move upstream during migration. The eels' magnetic compass could also be used years later when they are silver eels as they return to the Sargasso Sea to spawn and pass away.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. European eels navigating the sea using an internal magnetic compass2. Explaining the life cycle of European eels3. How the researchers tested the glass eels4. How the eels' internal magnetic compass could help themVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the University of Miami and Norway's Institute of Marine Research has found that European eels at a certain stage of development use an internal magnetic compass to remember the magnetic direction of tidal waves as they navigate the waters.""European eels are a migratory species that hatch in the Sargasso Sea and as larvae travel 5,000 kilometers to Europe's continental slope. There they metamorphosize into a transparent larval stage called 'glass eel' and continue to Europe's coast and enter estuaries.""Some of the eels continue to swim upstream to freshwater. Eels that get there then grow into the adult eel stage, which is yellow in color. These eventually become sexually mature, silver eels.""According to a study published in the journal Communications Biology, scientists gathered 222 glass eels flowing in four different directions  north, southeast, south and northwest  from separate estuaries in Austevoll, Norway and put them in a magnetic laboratory facility.""When the lab's magnetic north was rotated, they observed that the eels turned towards the magnetic direction of the tidal current at their estuary.""The researchers mentioned in the study that this mechanism could be helpful to eels if they lose visual reference points as they move upstream during migration.""The eels' magnetic compass could also be used years later when they are silver eels as they return to the Sargasso Sea to spawn and pass away."SOURCES: Nature, Science Daily, Sci Tech Daily, University of Miami, International Union for Conservation of Nature https://www.nature.com/articles/s42003-019-0619-8https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/10/191017162216.htmhttps://news.miami.edu/rsmas/stories/2019/10/new-study-uncovers-magnetic-memory-of-european-glass-eels.htmlhttps://www.iucnredlist.org/species/60344/45833138#assessment-information***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 05:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/22/3909724/3909724_B0F5571571094475AF7794F64A97DC27_191022_3909724_European_glass_eels_use_internal_magnetic_compas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, European eel, european glass eel, glass eels, european glass eel magnetic memory, European eel magnetic memory, Anguilla anguilla, glass eel magnetic laboratory, glass eel magnetic compass]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3909717</guid>
      <title>European glass eels use internal magnetic compass to navigate waters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the University of Miami and Norway's Institute of Marine Research has found that the European eel at a certain stage of development use an internal magnetic compass to remember the magnetic direction of tidal waves as they navigate the waters.European eels are a migratory species that hatch in the Sargasso Sea and then as laevae 5,000 kilometers to Europe's continental slope. There they turn metamorphosize into a transparent larval stage called 'glass eel' and continue to Europe's coast and enter estuaries.Some of the eels continue to swim upstream to freshwater. Eels that get there then grow into the adult eel stage, which is yellow in color. These eventually become sexually mature, silver eels.Scientists gathered 222 glass eels flowing in four different directions  north, southeast, south and northwest  from separate estuaries in Austevoll, Norway and put them in a magnetic laboratory facility, according to a study published in the journal Communications Biology. When the lab's magnetic north was rotated, they observed that the eels turned towards the magnetic direction of the tidal current at their estuary.The researchers mentioned in the study that this mechanism could be helpful to eels if they lose visual reference points as they move upstream during migration. The eels' magnetic compass could also be used years later when they are silver eels as they return to the Sargasso Sea to spawn and pass away.According to a 2014 report by the International Union for Conservation of Nature, the European eel is critically endangered as its population has been steadily decreasing since the 1980s.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. European eels navigating the sea using an internal magnetic compass2. Explaining the life cycle of European eels3. How the researchers tested the glass eels4. How the eels' internal magnetic compass could help themVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the University of Miami and Norway's Institute of Marine Research has found that European eels at a certain stage of development use an internal magnetic compass to remember the magnetic direction of tidal waves as they navigate the waters.""European eels are a migratory species that hatch in the Sargasso Sea and as larvae travel 5,000 kilometers to Europe's continental slope. There they metamorphosize into a transparent larval stage called 'glass eel' and continue to Europe's coast and enter estuaries.""Some of the eels continue to swim upstream to freshwater. Eels that get there then grow into the adult eel stage, which is yellow in color. These eventually become sexually mature, silver eels.""According to a study published in the journal Communications Biology, scientists gathered 222 glass eels flowing in four different directions  north, southeast, south and northwest  from separate estuaries in Austevoll, Norway and put them in a magnetic laboratory facility.""When the lab's magnetic north was rotated, they observed that the eels turned towards the magnetic direction of the tidal current at their estuary.""The researchers mentioned in the study that this mechanism could be helpful to eels if they lose visual reference points as they move upstream during migration.""The eels' magnetic compass could also be used years later when they are silver eels as they return to the Sargasso Sea to spawn and pass away."SOURCES: Nature, Science Daily, Sci Tech Daily, University of Miami, International Union for Conservation of Nature https://www.nature.com/articles/s42003-019-0619-8https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/10/191017162216.htmhttps://news.miami.edu/rsmas/stories/2019/10/new-study-uncovers-magnetic-memory-of-european-glass-eels.htmlhttps://www.iucnredlist.org/species/60344/45833138#assessment-information***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 05:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/22/3909717/3909717_5AEDDA7F39DB47AAA6FFE12E8AAF19DD_191022_3909717_European_glass_eels_use_internal_magnetic_compas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, European eel, european glass eel, glass eels, european glass eel magnetic memory, European eel magnetic memory, Anguilla anguilla, glass eel magnetic laboratory, glass eel magnetic compass, european glass eel magnetic compass, european eel life cycle, european eel migration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3910557</guid>
      <title>China showcases Type 99 battle tank</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina featured the most current main battle tank in its arsenal, the Type 99, during its 70th National Day military parade on October 1.The Chinese army's Type 99 family of battle tanks, also known as the ZTZ99, feature a hull that resembles a lengthened T-72 hull and a turret inspired by the German Leopard II.The Type 99 has an autoloader and is armed with a Russian-style 125 millimeter smoothbore gun that fires shells and AT-11 Sniper anti-tank missiles, according to the National Interest.The article speculates the tank's 125 millimeter cannon could penetrate the frontal armor of the U.S. Abrams tank when firing tungsten rounds at close range, while a newer variant, the Type 99A2, has an even longer barrel main gun.The tank can hold three crew members: the commander, gunner and driver.The Type 99 uses a composite armor and explosive reactive armor, or ERA, explosive blocks added to the armor that resist enemy armor piercing shells and missiles, reports the National Interest. The Type 99A2 variant has multi-layered system that uses a radar to detect incoming projectiles and detonates the ERA tiles before impact, similar to the Relikt system developed by Russia.In addition, the Type 99 is protected by a laser warning receiver that warns the tank's commander if and when a hostile laser targeter is painting the tank.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Features of the Type 99's turret and hull design 2. Main gun, autoloader and offensive capabilities3. Armor package and defensive capabilities4. The tank's laser warning receiverVOICEOVER (in English): "The Chinese army's Type 99 family of battle tanks, also known as the ZTZ99, feature a hull that resembles a lengthened T-72 hull and a turret inspired by the German Leopard II.""According to the National Interest, the Type 99 has an autoloader and is armed with a Russian-style 125 millimeter smoothbore gun that fires shells and AT-11 Sniper anti-tank missiles.""The article speculates the tank's 125 millimeter cannon could penetrate the frontal armor of the U.S. Abrams tank when firing tungsten rounds at close range, while a newer variant, the Type 99A2, has an even longer barrel main gun.""The tank can hold three crew members: the commander, gunner and driver.""The National Interest reports that the Type 99 uses a composite armor and explosive reactive armor, or ERA, explosive blocks added to the armor that resist enemy armor piercing shells and missiles.""The Type 99A2 variant has multi-layered system that uses a radar to detect incoming projectiles and detonates the ERA tiles before impact, similar to the Relikt system developed by Russia.""In addition, the Type 99 is protected by a laser warning receiver that warns the tank's commander if and when a hostile laser targeter is painting the tank."SOURCES: National Interest, Global Times https://nationalinterest.org/blog/buzz/chinas-type-99-tank-serious-business-89621http://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1165934.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 12:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/23/3910557/3910557_E671DEE96BB245DEA87D30D5E0A9C0E1_191023_3910557_China_showcases_Type_99_battle_tank_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, illustration, graphic, Chinese military, China's Type 99 Tank, type 99 tank china, chinese type 99, china type 99 tank, people's liberation army tanks, chinese military tanks, people's liberation army type 99 tank]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3911065</guid>
      <title>Taiwan unveils new suicide drones at aerospace exhibition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan unveiled two military suicide drones at the Taipei Aerospace & Defense Technology Exhibition in August in a bid to counter Chinese military aggression.One of the suicide drones, called Chien Hsiang, features delta wings and two retractable side-force panels for stability. The drone is powered by a rotor engine and can travel at speeds of up to 185 kilometers per hour, according to Taiwan Sentinel. The drone is combined with an anti-radiation missile and is able to identify and attack radar emitters from an enemy's weapon system, according to Focus Taiwan.The report added that the unmanned aerial vehicle will be also able to counter China's S400 anti-aircraft missiles and has a range that covers China's coastline.   The second drone, the Fire Cardinal drone, consists of a twin propeller and includes electro-optical and infrared sensors, the National Interest reports. The drone is around four feet in length and has a wingspan of six feet and weighs roughly 15 pounds.According to Alert 5, the unmanned aerial vehicle uses an intelligence object detection system to select its target.The Taiwanese military plans to manufacture 104 Chien Hsiang drones in the next six years, as reported by Taiwan's Central News Agency. The report didn't mention how many Fire Cardinal drones the Taiwanese military plans to produce.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two new Taiwanese suicide drones: Chien Hsiang and Fire Cardinal2. Features of the Chien Hsiang drone3. The Chien Hsiang drone attacking an enemy's weapon system and the S400 anti-aircraft missile4. Features of the Fire Cardinal drone5. The Fire Cardinal drone using its intelligence object detection systemVOICEOVER (in English): "Taiwan unveiled two military suicide drones at the Taipei Aerospace & Defense Technology Exhibition in August in a bid to counter Chinese military aggression.""One of the suicide drones, called Chien Hsiang, features delta wings and two retractable side-force panels for stability.""According to Taiwan Sentinel, the drone is powered by a rotor engine and can travel at speeds of up to 185 kilometers per hour.""The drone is combined with an anti-radiation missile and is able to identify and attack radar emitters from an enemy's weapon system, according to Focus Taiwan.""The report added that the unmanned aerial vehicle will be also able to counter China's S400 anti-aircraft missiles and has a range that covers China's coastline."   "The National Interest reports that the second drone, called the Fire Cardinal drone, consists of a twin propeller and includes electro-optical and infrared sensors.""The drone is around four feet in length and has a wingspan of six feet and weighs roughly 15 pounds.""According to Alert 5, the unmanned aerial vehicle uses an intelligence object detection system to select its target."SOURCES: Jane's 360, Central News Agency, Alert 5, Focus Taiwan, National Interest, Taiwan Sentinelhttps://www.janes.com/article/90511/tadte-2019-taiwan-s-ncsist-rolls-out-indigenous-anti-radiation-loitering-munitionhttps://www.cna.com.tw/news/aipl/201908140228.aspxhttp://alert5.com/2019/08/14/taiwan-unveils-second-suicide-drone-fire-cardinal/#more-77555http://focustaiwan.tw/news/ast/201908090017.aspxhttps://nationalinterest.org/blog/buzz/taiwan-developing-%E2%80%9Csuicide-drones%E2%80%9D-73611https://nationalinterest.org/blog/buzz/chinas-nightmare-why-taiwan-building-kamikaze-drones-89596https://sentinel.tw/taiwan-tadte-2017-new/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 12:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/24/3911065/3911065_BF34F3368E5B4B1AB2F77334DD5EE4E6_191024_3911065_Taiwan_unveils_new_suicide_drones_at_aerospace_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Taiwanese military, taiwan drone, taiwan defense drone, taiwan kamikaze drone, taiwanese kamikaze drone, taiwan suicide drone, anti-radiation drones,  suicide drones, Chien Hsiang, Fire Cardinal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3910998</guid>
      <title>Russia discovers five new islands in the Arctic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Russian navy has found five new islands in the remote Arctic.Russia's defense ministry has confirmed the discovery of five new islands in the Arctic, which were revealed by accelerated glacial melting in the far north.According to the BBC, the islands were hidden under the Nansen glacier on the Novaya Zemlya archipelago, and ranged in size from 900 to 54,500 square meters.The initial discovery of the islands has been credited to Marina Migunova, who found them in 2016 while completing her final coursework as a student at the Admiral Makarov State Maritime Academy.The Guardian reports that an Arctic expedition in August and September charted the islands.The Defense Ministry also confirmed the existence of an island previously mapped as a peninsula of Hall Island and part of the Franz Josef Land archipelago.The Guardian reports that in recent years, Russia has had increased commercial and military interests in the Arctic, as retreating ice caused by rising temperatures has opened up shipping routes and previously inaccessible mineral resources.The islands have yet to be named, but Vice Admiral Alexander Moiseyev says they are "upcoming." RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Glacial melting reveals five new islands in the Arctic 2. Location of new islands3. Russian Arctic expedition charting islands4. Russian bases in ArcticVOICEOVER (in English): "Russia's defense ministry has confirmed the discovery of five new islands in the Arctic, which were revealed by accelerated glacial melting in the far north.""According to the BBC, the islands were hidden under the Nansen glacier on the Novaya Zemlya archipelago, and ranged in size from 900 to 54,500 square meters.""The Guardian reports that an Arctic expedition in August and September charted the islands.""The Defense Ministry also confirmed the existence of an island previously mapped as a peninsula of Hall Island and part of the Franz Josef Land archipelago.""The Guardian reports that in recent years, Russia has had increased commercial and military interests in the Arctic, as retreating ice caused by rising temperatures has opened up shipping routes and previously inaccessible mineral resources."SOURCES: Ministry of Defense of Russia, Moscow Times, The Guardian, BBChttps://function.mil.ru/news_page/country/more.htm?id=12249505@egNewshttps://www.themoscowtimes.com/2019/08/28/russia-discovers-5-arctic-islands-as-glaciers-melt-a67051https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/oct/22/melting-glaciers-reveal-five-new-islands-in-the-arctichttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49510721***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 10:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/24/3910998/3910998_528AA426D9F749399C7B3A76DAFB234A_191024_3910998_Russia_discovers_five_new_islands_in_the_Arctic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, New Arctic islands, Arctic islands, Arctic islands discovery, 5 new Arctic islands, glacial melt, melting glaciers, climate change, Russia in the Arctic, Russian navy, Russia Arctic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3910976</guid>
      <title>Scientific journal pulls paper questioning Syria sarin gas attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA scientific journal has pulled a controversial paper challenging the official narrative of the 2017 Syria gas attack.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sarin bomb dropped on Khan Shaykhun2. Impact crater on road3. How sarin gas works4. Sarin gas deaths5. Syria blamed for attack6. Crater inconsistent with aerial bomb7. Crater created by artillery rocket 8. Artillery rocket not a sarin delivery device9. Crater was modified10. Trump missile strike on Syria11. Discrepancies in video of sarin site12. Sarin can penetrate face masksVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the OPCW-UN Joint Investigative Mechanism, on the morning of April 4, 2017, a chemical bomb suspected to contain sarin gas was dropped from an aircraft over the rebel-held Syrian town of Khan Shaykhun.""The bomb allegedly struck the middle of a road, creating a crater 1.5 to 1.65 meters in diameter and half a meter deep, and releasing sarin gas upon impact.""Sarin is a highly toxic gas that can be inhaled, ingested, or absorbed through the skin. Once inside the body, it attacks the central nervous system.""According to an April 7 report by the Idlib Health Directorate, the gas dispersed through the town, resulting in the deaths of 89 people, 33 of them children. 541 others were injured.""UN investigators later released a report confirming evidence of sarin being dropped from a plane, and stating the Syrian government, led by Bashar al-Assad, was responsible for the April 4 attack.""But a controversial paper authored by MIT professor emeritus Theodore Postol and other experts is now challenging the mainstream narrative.""Using computational forensic analysis on the crater, Postol et. al found that its size and shape, as well as damage to a pipe thought to be the sarin vessel, is inconsistent with an aerial bomb.""Instead, detonation and impact simulations indicate that it may have been generated by a 122-milimeter artillery rocket armed with a high-explosive warhead  a weapon the Syrian government does not have a monopoly on.""This type of munition could not have been used as a delivery device for sarin, since based on the analysis, the rocket's volume would be used up by the propellant and the warhead." "The split pipe identified as a sarin container by the Joint Investigative Mechanism is likely just the casing of the rocket motor that propelled the warhead to the explosion site.""Postol et al. also analyzed photographic evidence of the crater, in particular two sets of images  one showing it with a red skeletal marker, and one without.""Advanced deterioration on the crater and the disappearance of loose debris in one set of images indicate they were taken at a later time and possibly modified. The position of the damaged pipe also changes  bending outward in one set, and inward in another.     SOURCES: Science, Theodore Postol, OPCW, Truthdig, Idlib Health Directoratehttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/10/prestigious-journal-pulls-paper-about-chemical-attack-syria-after-backlashhttps://d3ba7j4nna908t.cloudfront.net/attachments/Attachment+4+-+Computational+Forensic+Analysis+for+the+Chemical+Weapons+Attack+at+Khan+Sheikhoun+on+April+4.+2017_S.pdfhttps://reliefweb.int/sites/reliefweb.int/files/resources/N1734930.pdfhttps://www.truthdig.com/videos/a-critique-of-false-and-misleading-white-house-claims-about-syrias-use-of-lethal-gas/https://twitter.com/SyriaCivilDef/status/850323422894850048***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 09:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/24/3910976/3910976_16D3DD6173324007952823ACA8A55F66_191024_3910976_Scientific_journal_pulls_paper_questioning_Syria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Syria gas attacks, Syria chemical attack, Khan Shaykhun gas attack, OPCW, Syria cover up, alternative view Syria, Theodore Postol, Science & Global Security, journal paper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3910723</guid>
      <title>Lockheed Martin's Sikorsky unveils next generation Raider X helicopter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSikorsky, a company owned by Lockheed Martin, debuted Raider X, a light attack and reconnaissance helicopter concept on October 14 at the Association of the U.S. Army conference in Washington.The helicopter features two counter-rotating coaxial rotors and a push propeller, according to a news release from Lockheed Martin. The prototype has been submitted to partake in the Army's Future Attack Reconnaissance Aircraft Competitive Prototype program, Breaking Defense reports. Raider X will reach speeds of up to 250 knots and fly as high as 9,000 feet. It will also be able to perform high-speed maneuvers to a 60 degrees angle of bank. Lockheed Martin says the helicopter's rotors will allow it to carry out enhanced low-speed hover, off-axis hover as well as level acceleration and braking.Raider X will be part of Sikorsky's X2 line of aircraft.The company says that the helicopter will use designs and manufacturing used in other planes by Sikorsky and Lockheed Martin such as the CH-53K, CH-148 and F-35.Lockheed Martin says this will keep costs down and allow for more affordable upgrades.The helicopter is able to carry weapons, though the company did not specify which weapons will be taken onboard.Lockeed Martin says Raider X will utilize modern open systems architecture that facilitates reconfiguring or replacing sensors, other avionics and mission modules. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Features of the helicopter and the helicopter taking off2. How fast and how high the helicopter can fly3. Helicopter performing a 60 degrees angle of bank4. The helicopter performs a low-speed hover, off-axis hover, level acceleration and braking5.The helicopter will use digital designs and manufacturing used in other aircraftVOICEOVER (in English): "Sikorsky, a company owned by Lockheed Martin, debuted Raider X, a light attack and reconnaissance helicopter concept on October 14 at the Association of the U.S. Army conference in Washington.""According to a news release from Lockheed Martin, the helicopter features two counter-rotating coaxial rotors and a push propeller.""Raider X will reach speeds of up to 250 knots and fly as high as 9,000 feet." "It will also be able to perform high-speed maneuvers to a 60 degrees angle of bank.""Lockheed Martin says the helicopter's rotors will allow it to carry out enhanced low-speed hover, off-axis hover as well as level acceleration and braking.""Raider X will be part of Sikorsky's X2 line of aircraft.""The company says that the helicopter will use designs and manufacturing used in other planes by Sikorsky and Lockheed Martin such as the CH-53K, CH-148 and F-35.""Lockheed Martin says this will keep costs down and allow for more affordable upgrades."SOURCES: Lockheed Martin, New Atlas, Breaking Defense https://news.lockheedmartin.com/2019-10-14-Sikorsky-Introduces-RAIDER-X-TM-a-NextGen-Light-Attack-Reconnaissance-Helicopter-Based-on-its-Proven-X2-Technologyhttps://newatlas.com/military/sikorsky-unveils-raider-x-light-attack-helicopter/https://breakingdefense.com/2019/10/raider-x-sikorsky-supersizes-s-97-for-army-scout/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 02:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/24/3910723/3910723_802025DEAAA845D7B1E2E347981BA14B_191024_3910723_Lockheed_Martin_s_Sikorsky_unveils_next_generati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sikorsky, Lockheed Martin, Lockheed, Sikorsky, Raider X, Raider, future attack reconnaissance aircraft, FARA, light attack helicopter, attack helicopter, helicopter, prototype, coaxial rotor helicopter, coaxial rotors, coax, coax rotors, sikorsky light attack helicopter, Raider X helicopter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3911690</guid>
      <title>Google's super computer achieves 'quantum supremacy'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research by Google has shown that its Sycamore quantum processor was able to perform a target computation in 200 seconds.In a blogpost, Google explained that the same experiment would take the world's fastest supercomputer approximately 10,000 years to produce a similar result.Classical computers process data as individual bits, with each bit labelled 1 or a 0.Quantum computers use qubits. Each qubit is capable of storing 1 and 0 at the same time. This is known as superposition.Qubits are also able to bind to one another and work together in a process called entanglement. This allows the quantum computer to simultaneously calculate various solutions to one single problem at the same time.For the experiment, Google developed a 54-qubit computing chip called "Sycamore" for its quantum computer, though only 53 were used because one qubit was inoperable.Sycamore is comprised of a two-dimensional grid in which each qubit is attached to four other qubits.The quantum computer was able to sample around one million random strings of numbers in approximately three minutes, according to the study.According to Google's blog post, the company plans to make the Sycamore processor available for academic researchers, collaborators and companies interested in developing algorithms for the technology.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Google's Sycamore quantum processor in comparison to the world's fastest supercomputer2. How classical computers compute data3. How quantum computers compute data4. What Sycamore is comprised of 5. What Google's quantum computer was able to sampleVOICEOVER (in English): "New research by Google has shown that its Sycamore quantum processor was able to perform a target computation in 200 seconds.""In a blogpost, Google explained that the same experiment would take the world's fastest supercomputer approximately 10,000 years to produce a similar result.""Classical computers process data as individual bits, with each bit labelled 1 or a 0.""Quantum computers use qubits. Each qubit is capable of storing 1 and 0 at the same time. This is known as superposition.""Qubits are also able to bind to one another and work together in a process called entanglement. This allows the quantum computer to simultaneously calculate various solutions to one single problem at the same time.""For the experiment, Google developed a 54-qubit computing chip called 'Sycamore' for its quantum computer, though only 53 were used because one qubit was inoperable.""Sycamore is comprised of a two-dimensional grid in which each qubit is attached to four other qubits.""According to the study, the quantum computer was able to sample around one million random strings of numbers in approximately three minutes."SOURCES: Google AI Blog, BBC News, Nature, CNet, Gizmodohttps://ai.googleblog.com/2019/10/quantum-supremacy-using-programmable.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50154993https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1666-5https://www.cnet.com/news/google-quantum-computer-leaves-old-school-supercomputer-in-dust/https://gizmodo.com/first-look-at-sycamore-googles-quantum-computer-1839305635***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 12:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/25/3911690/3911690_DCBDD725CB4347FD8660D80CA8A5F739_191025_3911690_Google_s_super_computer_achieves__quantum_suprem_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Google, google quantum computer, 
Google sycamore, Google sycamore quantum computer, Google sycamore chip, google quantum ai, quantum computer google, quantum computing explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3911681</guid>
      <title>NASA's TESS satellite to search for alien life on exoplanets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA and Breakthrough Initiatives will collaborate to search for intelligent alien life, according to an October 23 press release from Breakthrough Initiatives.NASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, or TESS, will cooperate with Breakthrough Listen's facilities around the world.TESS, launched as a successor to the spaceprobe Kepler in 2018, carries four wide view cameras and advanced instruments capable of detecting small, rocky planets similar to Earth that could support life.Listen's primary facilities, including the Green Bank and Parkes Telescopes and MeerKAT, will take part in the collaboration that is expected to furnish meaningful data and refine analysis strategy.Advanced alien civilizations could engage in large scale engineering projects by building megastructures that interfere with stellar light, according to Breakthrough Initiatives.TESS could detect these variations in stellar light, known as lightcurves, allowing researchers to analyse abnormal or interesting changes in stellar brightness.Advanced alien civilizations could also emit signals known as technosignatures via transmitters, propulsion systems and other technological apparatus.TESS increases the probability of detecting technosignatures by only observing planets that pass their host stars as seen from Earth, or along their orbital planes where transmissions are most likely.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA announces collaboration with Breakthrough Initiatives2. TESS and radio telescopes search for small rocky planets3. Explain megastructures and lightcurves4. TESS orbit and technosignature detectionVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA and Breakthrough Initiatives will collaborate to search for intelligent alien life.""NASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, or TESS, will cooperate with Breakthrough Listen's facilities around the world, according to Breakthrough Intiative's press release from October 23."TESS, launched as a successor to the spaceprobe Kepler in 2018, carries four wide view cameras and advanced instruments capable of detecting small, rocky planets similar to Earth that could support life.""Listen's primary facilities, including the Green Bank and Parkes Telescopes and MeerKAT, will take part in the collaboration that is expected to furnish meaningful data and refine analysis strategy.""According to Breakthrough Initiatives, advanced alien civilizations could engage in large scale engineering projects by building megastructures that interfere with stellar light.""TESS could detect these variations in stellar light, known as lightcurves, allowing researchers to analyse abnormal or interesting changes in stellar brightness.""Advanced alien civilizations could also emit signals known as technosignatures via transmitters, propulsion systems and other technological apparatus.""TESS increases the probability of detecting technosignatures by only observing planets that pass their host stars as seen from Earth, or along their orbital planes where transmissions are most likely."SOURCES: Breakthrough Initiatives, Space.com, CNet https://breakthroughinitiatives.org/news/27https://www.space.com/breakthrough-listen-nasa-tess-seti-search.htmlhttps://www.cnet.com/news/alien-hunters-nasa-team-up-to-scan-planets-for-signs-of-intelligent-life/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 12:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/25/3911681/3911681_32B0F029B5934A4DB63601FFE2CFDD9F_191025_3911681_NASA_s_TESS_satellite_to_search_for_alien_life_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, Breakthrough Listen, Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, TESS, NASA exoplanets, TESS spacecraft, TESS spacecraft mission, NASA TESS satellite, NASA TESS exoplanets]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3912813</guid>
      <title>ISIS leader Al-Baghdadi dead after a U.S. raid in Syria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPresident Trump announced on Sunday that the U.S. has brought the fugitive leader of the Islamic State to justice in a "dangerous and daring" night time raid.CNN reports that according to Trump, eight helicopters carrying U.S. troops flew towards ISIS leader Abu-Bakr al-Baghdadi's compound in the Syrian village of Barisha on Saturday night.The helicopters were met with local gunfire while in transit, but returned fire and eliminated the threat.At the compound, troops avoided the booby-trapped main door and breached a wall to gain entry into the building.According to Trump, U.S. forces killed a "large number" of militants during a gun battle. At least two ISIS fighters were captured, and 11 children rescued. Two of Baghdadi's wives were also killed, but their suicide vests were unexploded.Baghdadi, who also wore a suicide vest, fled to an underground tunnel with three children while being chased by U.S. Delta Forces and K9 units. He detonated his vest after running into a dead-end, killing himself and the children.The explosion caused the tunnel to collapse, and caused serious injury to one dog, though. No U.S. personnel were killed."The BBC reports that while the blast mutilated Baghdadi's body, an on-site DNA test positively confirmed his identity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. helicopters transport Delta Force to Barisha, Syria2. Delta Force breaches wall to attack compound3. Al-Baghadi detonates sucide vest after being cornered in tunnel4. U.S. officials identifies Al-Baghdadi with field DNA testVOICEOVER (in English): "CNN reports that according to Trump, eight helicopters carrying U.S. troops flew towards ISIS leader Abu-Bakr al-Baghdadi's compound in the Syrian village of Barisha on Saturday night.""The helicopters were met with local gunfire while in transit, but returned fire and eliminated the threat.""At the compound, troops avoided the booby-trapped main door and breached a wall to gain entry into the building.""According to Trump, U.S. forces killed a 'large number' of militants during a gun battle. At least two ISIS fighters were captured, and 11 children rescued. Two of Baghdadi's wives were also killed, but their suicide vests were unexploded.""Baghdadi, who also wore a suicide vest, fled to an underground tunnel with three children while being chased by U.S. Delta Forces and K9 units.""He detonated his vest after running into a dead-end, killing himself and the children.""The explosion caused the tunnel to collapse, and caused serious injury to one dog, though. No U.S. personnel were killed.""The BBC reports that while the blast mutilated Baghdadi's body, an on-site DNA test positively confirmed his identity."SOURCES: The New York Times, CNN, BBChttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/27/us/politics/isis-leader-al-baghdadi-dead.html?action=click&module=Spotlight&pgtype=Homepagehttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2019/10/27/world/middleeast/baghdadi-isis-leader-maps.html?action=click&module=Spotlight&pgtype=Homepagehttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/27/politics/isis-abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-operation-donald-trump/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50200339***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 13:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/28/3912813/3912813_6B9C6A21847D4349AD03F371E02EFF47_191028_3912813_ISIS_leader_Al_Baghdadi_dead_after_a_U_S__raid_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Al-Baghdadi, Al-Baghdadi raid, ISIS leader, ISIS raid, Trump, Donald Trump, US raid Syria, ISIS leader raid, Islamic State, Delta Force]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3912647</guid>
      <title>Tesla begins production of its Model 3 cars in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTesla has begun a trial production of its Model 3 cars in its new Gigafactory in Shanghai this month.In a letter to shareholders, the company said it is already producing entire vehicles, from the body to paint to general assembly during the trial period. The company did not mention how long its trial production would last.The company explained on its website that its Model 3 cars will be made from a metal structure that is a mixture of aluminum and steel.The car will feature multiple cameras, a forward-facing radar as well as ultrasonic sensors to detect nearby cars.Tesla had made a deal with the Chinese government to construct a car production factory in Shanghai in 2018 and broke ground on its Chinese factory only 10 months ago, according to TechCrunch.The deal was notable as this is the first time a foreign car manufacturing company has been allowed to open up its own factory in China without a joint alliance with a local partner.Tesla explained in its letter to shareholders that the company is in its final stages of selecting a site to build its Gigafactory in Europe. The company says its European factory will manufacture Tesla's Model 3 and Model Y cars.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tesla's Model 3 in its Chinese factory2. Entire vehicles being produced in the factory3. Features of the Model 3 4. Tesla icon, Chinese flag, Tesla's Chinese factoryVOICEOVER (in English): "Tesla has begun a trial production of its Model 3 cars in its new Gigafactory in Shanghai this month.""In a letter to shareholders, the company said it is already producing entire vehicles, from the body to paint to general assembly during the trial period.""The company did not mention how long its trial production would last.""The company explained on its website that its Model 3 cars will be made from a metal structure that is a mixture of aluminum and steel.""The car will feature multiple cameras, a forward-facing radar as well as ultrasonic sensors to detect nearby cars.""According to TechCrunch, Tesla had made a deal with the Chinese government to construct a car production factory in Shanghai in 2018 and broke ground on its Chinese factory only 10 months ago."SOURCES: CNN, Tesla, TechCrunch, Reuters https://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/24/tech/tesla-gigafactory-china-europe/index.htmlhttps://ir.tesla.com/static-files/47313d21-3cac-4f69-9497-d161bce15da4https://www.tesla.com/model3https://techcrunch.com/2019/10/23/as-tesla-begins-trial-model-3-production-in-china-it-closes-in-on-a-european-factory/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-china-shanghai-plant/teslas-china-production-to-start-eyes-on-mass-production-timing-sources-idUSKBN1WH0HNhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-results/china-factory-production-key-as-tesla-reports-third-quarter-results-idUSKBN1X210B***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 08:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/28/3912647/3912647_A0D2A8E7DA8E4AE59B95132E3D9BDC07_191028_3912647_Tesla_begins_production_of_its_Model_3_cars_in_C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Tesla, Tesla factory, tesla china factory, tesla gigafactory china, tesla Model 3, tesla production,  tesla production line, tesla production 2019, tesla production China, tesla production line model 3, tesla elon musk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3913310</guid>
      <title>New Ocean Cleanup system targets plastic pollution in rivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNonprofit environmental organization the Ocean Cleanup is now tackling the problem of plastic pollution in oceans by collecting plastic waste directly from rivers before it gets to the oceans with its new system, the Interceptor, according to a news release from the organization. The Interceptor is powered by solar energy and uses lithium-ion batteries, which enables it to operate 24 hours a day, seven days a week.The Interceptor is anchored to the riverbed and uses a floating barrier that guides plastic waste from the river into the system's conveyor belt. Once plastic waste is onboard, it is automatically put into one of six dumpsters on a barge inside the system.The system alerts local operators once all six dumpsters onboard are full. Local operators then send over a vessel to pick up the plastic waste.The barge is taken back to shore with the plastic waste and emptied for recycling. The barge is then reattached to the Interceptor to collect more plastic debris.Ocean Cleanup states in their news release that the system is capable of extracting 50,000 kilograms of trash a day. The organization claims that under optimal conditions, that number could increase to 100,000 kilograms of waste per day.Ocean Cleanup has built four Interceptors till date. Two of its systems are already operating, one in Indonesia and one in Malaysia. The organization plans to roll out a third system in Vietnam and a fourth system in the Dominican Republic.Ocean Cleanup has ambitious plans of tackling 1,000 of the world's most polluting rivers, which the organization says are responsible for 80 percent of plastic waste present in oceans, before the end of 2025.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Interceptor2. Features of the Interceptor3. How the Interceptor will collect plastic waste from rivers4. Plastic waste collected by the Interceptor is taken back to land for recyclingVOICEOVER (in English): "Nonprofit environmental organization the Ocean Cleanup is now tackling the problem of plastic pollution in oceans by collecting plastic waste directly from rivers before it gets to the oceans with its new system, the Interceptor.""According to a news release from the organization, the Interceptor is powered by solar energy and uses lithium-ion batteries, which enables it to operate 24 hours a day, seven days a week.""The Interceptor is anchored to the riverbed and uses a floating barrier that guides plastic waste from the river into the system's conveyor belt.""Once plastic waste is onboard, it is automatically put into one of six dumpsters on a barge inside the system.""The system alerts local operators once all six dumpsters onboard are full. Local operators then send over a vessel to pick up the plastic waste.""The barge is taken back to shore with the plastic waste and emptied for recycling. The barge is then reattached to the Interceptor to collect more plastic debris."SOURCES: New Atlas, Ocean Cleanuphttps://newatlas.com/environment/ocean-cleanup-rivers-plastic-the-interceptor/https://theoceancleanup.com/updates/the-ocean-cleanup-unveils-plan-to-address-the-main-source-of-ocean-plastic-pollution-rivers/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MmzUVenX9lI***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/29/3913310/3913310_A3AAEEBA2FF940EBB78061D12B5C9A1C_191029_3913310_New_Ocean_Cleanup_system_targets_plastic_polluti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ocean cleanup 2019, ocean cleanup project, The Interceptor, The Interceptor Ocean Cleanup, ocean cleanup project, ocean clean up targets rivers, ocean clean up rivers, cleaning rivers, cleaning rivers in asia, ocean clean up to tackle river pollution, river pollution, river pollution solutions, ocean cleanup technology,  ocean cleanup project 2019, ocean cleanup, plastic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3913247</guid>
      <title>ISIS leader Al-Baghdadi, spokesman al-Muhajir slain after U.S. raids in Syria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Guardian reports that on Saturday, eight helicopters flew from an airbase in Iraq to ISIS leader Abu-Bakr al-Baghdadi's compound in the Syrian village of Barisha.At the compound, troops breached a wall to gain entry into the building.Baghdadi fled to an underground tunnel with three children. He detonated his suicide vest, killing himself and the children.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. helicopters transport Delta Force to Barisha, Syria2. Delta Force breaches wall to attack compound3. Al-Baghadi detonates sucide vest after being cornered in tunnel4. U.S. officials identifies Al-Baghdadi with field DNA test5. U.S. retrieves electronic records and documents from raid6. Air raid kills al-Muhajir7. SDF claims credit for giving intelligence to the U.S. VOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that around 5 p.m. on Saturday, eight helicopters, mostly CH-47s, flew from an airbase in northern Iraq to ISIS leader Abu-Bakr al-Baghdadi's compound in the Syrian village of Barisha.""The helicopters, which were carrying Delta Force commandos, were met with local gunfire while in transit, but returned fire and eliminated the threat.""At the compound, troops avoided the booby-trapped main door and breached a wall to gain entry into the building.""According to Trump, U.S. forces killed a 'large number' of militants during a gun battle. At least two ISIS fighters were captured, and 11 children rescued. Two of Baghdadi's wives were also killed, but their suicide vests were unexploded.""Baghdadi, who also wore a suicide vest, fled to an underground tunnel with three children while being chased by U.S. Delta Forces and K9 units.""He detonated his vest after running into a dead-end, killing himself and the children.""The explosion caused the tunnel to collapse, and caused serious injury to one dog. No U.S. personnel were killed.""The BBC reports that while the blast mutilated Baghdadi's body, an on-site DNA test positively confirmed his identity.""Trump said U.S. forces searched the compound for about two hours and found a trove of intelligence.""The New York Times reports that recovered electronic records and documents may contain information on the terror group's organization, finances and plans.""Fox News reports that ISIS spokesman Abu Hassan al-Muhajir, a possible successor to al-Baghadi, was killed in Northern Syria one day after the raid."According to the New York Times, Muhajir was being smuggled in the back of an oil tanker truck when a U.S. air raid destroyed the vehicle.""The Guardian reports that the Syrian Democratic Forces later claimed they played a key role in tracking Baghdadi to the Bashira compound, even taking a pair of underwear and a blood sample to confirm it was him."SOURCES: CNN, The New York Times, BBC, Guardian, Fox News https://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/27/politics/isis-abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-operation-donald-trump/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/28/us/politics/baghdadi-raid-intelligence.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/27/world/middleeast/al-baghdadi-successor-reported-killed.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50200339https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/28/visual-guide-to-the-raid-that-killed-isis-leader-abu-bakr-al-baghdadihttps://www.foxnews.com/world/isis-spokesman-abu-hassan-al-muhajir-considered-potential-al-baghdadi-successor-also-killed-in-syria-official-says***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 11:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/29/3913247/3913247_DE2C6690BF1F479A89E34A431B372FFA_191029_3913247_ISIS_leader_Al_Baghdadi__spokesman_al_Muhajir_sl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Baghdadi raid, Al Baghdadi raid, Al Baghdadi killing, Baghdadi, Al Baghdadi, ISIS leader, US raid, Syrian Democratic Forces, Al Muhajir, Trump, Donald Trump]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3912986</guid>
      <title>NASA to deploy VIPER rover to search for water ice on the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA plans to send a robotic rover to search for water ice at the moon's South Pole in 2022, according to an October 25 news release published on NASA's website.The Volatiles Investigating Polar Exploration Rover, or VIPER, will be roughly the size of a golf cart.VIPER will collect data for roughly 100 days as it uses the Neutron Spectrometer System to detect wet sections underneath the moon's surface.Once such an area is detected, VIPER will deploy a one-meter long drill to dig for soil cuttings that are up to a meter underneath its surface.These drill samples will then be analyzed by two other instruments carried by the rover: the Mass Spectrometer Observing Lunar Operations, or MSolo, and the Near InfraRed Volatiles Spectrometer System, or NIRVSS.VIPER will also gather data on how different kinds of soil environments on the moon's South Pole are affected by sunlight and different temperatures.The data will allow the space agency to map out places where water could potentially lie on the moon.NASA says that water extracted from the moon could be used for fuel in rockets or be turned into oxygen for astronauts.VIPER is part of NASA's Lunar Discovery and Exploration Program.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. VIPER rover and water from the South Pole of the moon2. How big the rover will be3. VIPER scanning the moon's surface4. VIPER drilling the moon's surface6. Samples obtained by the rover being analyzed 7. Other data VIPER will collect while on the lunar surface 8. Where water could potentially lie on the moonVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA plans to send a robotic rover to search for water ice at the moon's South Pole in 2022.""The Volatiles Investigating Polar Exploration Rover, or VIPER, will be roughly the size of a golf cart.""According to a NASA news release, VIPER will collect data for roughly 100 days as it uses the Neutron Spectrometer System to detect wet sections underneath the moon's surface.""Once such an area is detected, VIPER will deploy a one-meter long drill to dig for soil cuttings that are up to a meter underneath its surface.""These drill samples will then be analyzed by two other instruments carried by the rover: the Mass Spectrometer Observing Lunar Operations, or MSolo, and the Near InfraRed Volatiles Spectrometer System, or NIRVSS.""VIPER will also gather data on how different kinds of soil environments on the moon's South Pole are affected by sunlight and different temperatures.""The data will allow the space agency to map out places where water could potentially lie on the moon."SOURCES: New Atlas, NASAhttps://newatlas.com/space/nasas-viper-rover-water-ice-moon-2022/https://www.nasa.gov/feature/new-viper-lunar-rover-to-map-water-ice-on-the-moon***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/29/3912986/3912986_65CF4A4DB9CD43D6B8E22D99A146241D_191029_3912986_NASA_to_deploy_VIPER_rover_to_search_for_water_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, space exploration, VIPER rover, VIPER rover nasa, VIPER lunar rover, lunar exploration, Volatiles Investigating Polar Exploration Rover, NASA lunar rover, NASA moon rover, Moon's South Pole, water ice on the moon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3913679</guid>
      <title>Study triples estimates of people at risk of sea level rise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that rising sea levels will be more of a threat to the world's coastal cities than previously thought.According to a new study published in Nature Communications, previous estimates suggest 80 million people will be affected when flat, low-lying lands flood annually by 2050 as the Earth warms.The Washington Post reports that this estimate was based on coastal elevation data that detected the height of the land surface and those on it, such as trees, houses, and buildings. This resulted in errors averaging 6.5 feet globally.To gain more accuracy, a new model used laser-based coastal measurements and an algorithm to adjust the previous data set. They found that the population at risk from annual flooding is closer to 300 million.In particular, areas in Asia are especially at risk, with the model showing larger swaths of submerged land in places like Ho Chi Minh, Bangkok, and Shanghai, among others.According to the study, a scenario in which the world becomes warmer by 3.6 degrees Fahrenheit, or 2 degrees Celsius by 2100, would expose over 360 million people to annual flooding.The worst case scenario, according to scientists, would see the Antarctic ice sheet melt and as many as 640 million people threatened. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Previous estimate of population affected by sea level rise2. Error in coastal elevation data3. Adjusted data set based on laser-based coastal measurements4. New estimate of population affected by sea level riseVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in Nature Communications, previous estimates suggest 80 million people will be affected when flat, low-lying lands flood annually by 2050 as the Earth warms.""The Washington Post reports that this estimate was based on coastal elevation data that detected the height of the land surface and those on it, such as trees, houses, and buildings.""This resulted in errors averaging 6.5 feet globally.""To gain more accuracy, a new model used laser-based coastal measurements and an algorithm to adjust the previous data set.""They found that the population at risk from annual flooding is closer to 300 million.""In particular, areas in Asia are especially at risk, with the model showing larger swaths of submerged land in places like Ho Chi Minh, Bangkok, and Shanghai, among others."SOURCES: Nature Communications, Washington Post, Associated Press, New York Timeshttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-019-12808-zhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/2019/10/29/scientists-triple-their-estimates-number-people-threatened-by-rising-seas/https://apnews.com/5a5554eec18343bf874a992a7ec33a14https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2019/10/29/climate/coastal-cities-underwater.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 09:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/30/3913679/3913679_D98E56F7D51B4A658B51044566CA1BE6_191030_3913679_Study_triples_estimates_of_people_at_risk_of_sea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Rising sea levels, flood risk, sea level, sea level estimates, sea level projections, climate change, global warming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3913534</guid>
      <title>Modern human origin traced to northern Botswana</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research published in the journal Nature suggests that modern humans descended from the region south of the Zambezi River, spanning northern Botswana into parts of Namibia and Zimbabwe, in southern Africa.Scientists collected blood samples from local communities across Namibia and South Africa to compare DNA codes from different individuals, CNN reports, citing the study. Their DNA code showed that the individual's LO lineage, which is associated with the earliest known modern human populations, and its sub-branches were linked to the Makgadikgadi-Okavango palaeo-wetland.The researchers then analyzed fossils and geological records from the area itself and found that it once contained the largest lake system in Africa.The lake system began breaking apart roughly 200,000 years ago.The scientists say this would have created a vast wetland that furnished ancient humans with a sustainable ecosystem in which they could thrive. Researchers say this was the case for roughly 70,000 years before our ancestors started migrating due to changes in the climate in the area.The first wave of migrants traveled to the northeast of the wetland 130,000 years ago, while a second wave of migrants traveled southwest 110,000 years ago, CNN reports, citing the study. Those in the northeast started farming while those who traveled to the southwest became coastal foragers.Ancient humans eventually migrated outside of Africa and to different parts of the world.Some experts are skeptical of the study. Professor Chris Stringer from London's Natural History Museum told the BBC that there could have been several homelands, instead of only one.He said that the study only looked at one part of the DNA code, which is unable to provide the whole story of modern human origins.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where modern humans descended from according to study2. Blood samples to compare DNA codes from different individuals3. Fossils and geological records being analyzed4. Vast wetland that furnished ancient humansVOICEOVER (in English): "New research published in the journal Nature suggests that modern humans descended from the region south of the Zambezi River, spanning northern Botswana into parts of Namibia and Zimbabwe, in southern Africa.""Citing the study, CNN reports the scientists collected blood samples from local communities across Namibia and South Africa to compare DNA codes from different individuals.""Their DNA code showed that the individual's LO lineage, which is associated with the earliest known modern human populations, and its sub-branches were linked to the Makgadikgadi-Okavango palaeo-wetland.""The researchers then analyzed fossils and geological records from the area itself and found that it once contained the largest lake system in Africa.""The lake system began breaking apart roughly 200,000 years ago.""The scientists say this would have created a vast wetland that furnished ancient humans with a sustainable ecosystem in which they could thrive." "Researchers say this was the case for roughly 70,000 years before our ancestors started migrating due to changes in the climate in the area."SOURCES: Nature, CNN, The Guardian, BBC News https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1714-1https://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/28/world/human-origins-botswana-scn-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/oct/28/ancestral-home-of-modern-humans-is-in-botswana-study-findshttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50210701***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/30/3913534/3913534_5F661501756E406E8860F1F1C2DCC987_191030_3913534_Modern_human_origin_traced_to_northern_Botswana_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Human origins, human origins evolution, Origin of modern humans, human origins in africa, human origin botswana, Zambezi river, modern humans originated in northern Botswana, modern humans ancestral home, modern humans origin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3914393</guid>
      <title>Prominent Hong Kong pro-democracy figures assaulted in targeted attacks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMultiple pro-democracy activists in Hong Kong have been assaulted or attacked for openly standing up against China, in what critics have dubbed as "White Terror." RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Stanley Ho beaten 2. Jimmy Sham attacked 3. Isaac Cheng attacked 4. Jocelyn Chau punched in the head 5. Jannelle Leung hit in the head6. Roy Kwong punched and kicked by masked men7. Davin Wong assaulted by a masked man VOICEOVER (in English): "Multiple pro-democracy activists in Hong Kong have been assaulted or attacked for openly standing up against China, in what critics have dubbed as 'White Terror.'" "In September, Stanley Ho, a member of Hong Kong's Labor Party and a candidate in the upcoming local elections, was beaten by four unknown attackers with metal rods and sticks near a park in Sai Kung.""According to Hong Kong Free Press and AFP, his attackers fractured both of his hands and gave him a head wound.""Civil Human Rights Front leader Jimmy Sham was attacked by at least four men with hammers while he was on his way to a meeting earlier this month. Officials found Sham lying on the street and bleeding from his arms and head.""Isaac Cheng, vice president of Hong Kong's pro-democracy Demosisto party, was beaten by assailants on his way home at night in September.""In a Facebook post, the Demosisto party explained that the 19-year-old was attacked from behind by three men who punched him in the eyes. His glasses flew off his face as a result and Cheng was taken to the hospital for his injuries by party members.""Hong Kong Free Press reports Jocelyn Chau was at her booth campaigning when a middle-aged man went up to Chau and tore up her election leaflet.""The man punched Chau in the head twice when she asked him to stop littering. The 23-year-old was taken to a hospital after feeling nauseous and dizzy.""Jannelle Leung was attacked by a man who hit her in the back of her head with an unknown object as she was waiting to cross the road.""Hong Kong Democratic Party Lawmaker Roy Kwong was punched and kicked by three masked assailants as he tried to get into his car in late September.""The Hong Kong Free Press reports the masked assailants targeted Kwong's neck, the back of his head and his torso while Kwong was seen in a video lying on the ground, protecting his head and arms. Kwong called for an ambulance after the attackers ran away.""Davin Wong, former student union leader of University of Hong Kong, was assaulted by a masked man wearing a white shirt as he waited for the bus at the end of August.""Wong told DW News that the masked man used a cane to hit him on his neck and left shoulder. He said he believed the attack was planned."SOURCES: AFP, Hong Kong Free Press, Facebook, DW  https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/white-terror-hong-kongs-china-critics-beaten-targeted-attacks-doc-1ll5sh3https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/10/16/breaking-hong-kong-protest-leader-jimmy-sham-attacked-tai-kok-tsui/https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/10/14/two-young-candidates-running-hong-kong-district-council-assaulted-campaigning-streets/https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/09/26/video-shows-hong-kong-democrat-roy-kwong-repeatedly-punched-kicked-assailants-tin-shui-wai/https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/08/29/just-hong-kong-protest-organiser-says-masked-men-wielding-knife-baseball-bat-attacked-companion/https://www.facebook.com/demosisto/posts/1187890144753139https://www.dw.com/en/exiled-hong-kong-protesters-forced-to-demonstrate-from-abroad/a-50583689***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 14:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/31/3914393/3914393_6E1A091B35294B15A4281C455BA513DE_191031_3914393_Prominent_Hong_Kong_pro_democracy_figures_assaul_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Animation, Hong kong white terror, hong kong white terror, hong kong protest, hong kong protest leaders, hong kong pro-democracy leaders attacked]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3914051</guid>
      <title>Uber unveils unveils new designs for food delivery drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUber unveiled new designs for its Uber Eats food delivery drones at a Forbes Under 30 Summit in Detroit on October 28.The drone will feature six rotors and be able to carry meals for two people, Forbes reports. The drone will perform vertical takeoffs and landings and will be able to fly up to 18 miles per trip. Uber's Elevate Cloud Systems will track and guide the drone to its drop-off location.Uber says the drone will carry meals from restaurants to a specific drop-off location, where an Uber delivery driver will pick up the meal from the drone and deliver it to the customer.The company had previously mentioned it would consider landing the drones directly on top of its delivery cars in the future. These cars would use a QR code to allow drones to correctly identify which car roof to land on.In June, Uber Eats used a previous design of the delivery drone to make a few test deliveries from a McDonald's near San Diego State University.At the summit, Uber stated that it plans to start testing its updated delivery drone in San Diego next summer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Uber's newly designed delivery drone2. Uber's delivery drone taking off vertically and flying3. The drone carrying a meal to a specific drop-off location4. Uber delivery driver picking up the order from the drone and taking to the customer5. Uber drones may land directly on top of delivery cars in the futureVOICEOVER (in English): "Uber unveiled new designs for its Uber Eats food delivery drones at a Forbes Under 30 Summit in Detroit on October 28.""Forbes reports that the drone will feature six rotors and be able to carry meals for two people.""The drone will perform vertical takeoffs and landings and will be able to fly up to 18 miles per trip.""Uber's Elevate Cloud Systems will track and guide the drone to its drop-off location.""Uber says the drone will carry meals from restaurants to a specific drop-off location, where an Uber delivery driver will pick up the meal from the drone and deliver it to the customer.""The company had previously mentioned it would consider landing the drones directly on top of its delivery cars in the future. These cars would use a QR code to allow drones to correctly identify which car roof to land on."SOURCES: The Verge, TechCrunch, Forbeshttps://www.theverge.com/2019/10/28/20936410/uber-eats-food-delivery-drone-design?ICID=ref_farkhttps://techcrunch.com/2019/10/28/heres-what-the-uber-eats-delivery-drone-looks-like/https://www.forbes.com/sites/bizcarson/2019/10/28/first-look-uber-unveils-new-design-for-uber-eats-delivery-drone/#504b827278f2https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2019/06/12/uber-eats-to-test-flying-food-to-customers-by-drone-in-san-diego/#7b00777e4c31***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 05:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/10/31/3914051/3914051_2F9A628906D94DDD9E1D095B5888972C_191031_3914051_Uber_unveils_unveils_new_designs_for_food_delive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Uber eats, Uber eats food delivery drone, Uber eats delivery drone, Uber unveils new design for uber eats delivery drone, Uber eats drone delivery, uber eats drone, uber eats san diego drone, food delivery drones, self-flying vehicles, drone, drone delivery, drone technology 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
