<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 19:32:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3929615</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover extremely massive black hole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have discovered a massive black hole 15,000 light years from Earth in the Milky Way Galaxy.Professor Liu Jinfeng at the Chinese Academy of Sciences said in a press release that the stellar black hole named LB-1 is so large that, "it should not even exist in our galaxy."According to the international research team, the "monster black hole" has a mass that is 70 times greater than the mass of the sun.The discovery comes as a surprise as scientists had previously estimated the mass of most stellar black holes in our galaxy at less than 20 times the sun's mass.Scientists spotted LB-1 by looking for stars that circle a black hole. LB-1's companion has eight times the mass of the sun and circles the black hole every 79 days.The international team credits China's Large Sky Area Multi-Object Fiber Spectroscopic Telescope for making the discovery.The Gran Telescopio Canarias in Spain and the Keck I telescope in the U.S. then determined the physical parameters of LB-1 and its companion star.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.The LB-1 black hole's general position2. LB-1's mass compared to estimated mass of other Milky Way black holes3. The companion star of the black hole4. Observatories that took part in the discovery and study of LB-1VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers have discovered a massive black hole 15,000 light years from Earth in the Milky Way Galaxy.""Professor Liu Jinfeng at the Chinese Academy of Sciences said in a press release that the stellar black hole named LB-1 is so large that, 'it should not even exist in our galaxy.'""According to the international research team, the 'monster black hole' has a mass that is 70 times greater than the mass of the sun.""The discovery comes as a surprise as scientists had previously estimated the mass of most stellar black holes in our galaxy at less than 20 times the sun's mass.""Scientists spotted LB-1 by looking for stars that circle a black hole. LB-1's companion has eight times the mass of the sun and circles the black hole every 79 days.""The international team credits China's Large Sky Area Multi-Object Fiber Spectroscopic Telescope for making the discovery.""The Gran Telescopio Canarias in Spain and the Keck I telescope in the U.S. then determined the physical parameters of LB-1 and its companion star."SOURCES:  Chinese Academy of Sciences (EurekAlert)https://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-11/caos-cao112519.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/02/3929615/3929615_BCDE957F1DCF452A931FD96D6087523E_191202_3929615_Scientists_discover_extremely_massive_black_hole_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Black hole, monster black hole, stellar black hole, LB-1, LB1, milky way galaxy, galaxy, Chinese Academy of Sciences, LAMOST, China, space, astronomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929519</guid>
      <title>NASA showcases mid-size lunar lander for future missions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has unveiled designs for a medium-sized lunar lander that would be able to carry payloads that weigh up to 300 kilograms to the moon's polar regions.Payloads may include scientific instruments, a robotic rover and even a ramp for the rover.The lander will include a thermal control system, an electrical power subsystem and a navigation system with Terrain-Relative Navigation.Its metal structure will house a solid rocket motor to allow the lander to brake on arrival to the moon and a liquid propulsion system to facilitate landing on the moon's surface.The lander will take three to six days to reach the moon and will be sent via a commercial launch vehicle.As the lander makes its way to the moon, solar panels on its surface will supply power to batteries on the lander. This will help power the rover once the lander has descended to the moon's surface, and allow it to explore the lunar environment for up to six hours. The mission is part of NASA's plan to establish a permanent base on the moon.The ultimate goal is to prepare humans to make their way from the moon to the red planet in order to make human exploration of Mars a reality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Designs for medium-sized lunar lander2. Payload the lander may carry3. Features of the lander4. Structural designs of the lander5. The lander making its way to the moon6. How a rover that the lander carries as payload may operate on the moonVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has unveiled designs for a medium-sized lunar lander that would be able to carry payloads that weigh up to 300 kilograms to the moon's polar regions.""Payloads may include scientific instruments, a robotic rover and even a ramp for the rover.""The lander will include a thermal control system, an electrical power subsystem and a navigation system with Terrain-Relative Navigation.""Its metal structure will house a solid rocket motor to allow the lander to brake on arrival to the moon and a liquid propulsion system to facilitate landing on the moon's surface.""The lander will take three to six days to reach the moon and will be sent via a commercial launch vehicle.""As the lander makes its way to the moon, solar panels on its surface will supply power to batteries on the lander.""This will help power the rover once the lander has descended to the moon's surface, and allow it to explore the lunar environment for up to six hours." SOURCES: NASA, New Atlas https://www.nasa.gov/centers/marshall/news/news/releases/2019/nasa-shares-mid-sized-robotic-lunar-lander-concept-with-industry.htmlhttps://ntrs.nasa.gov/archive/nasa/casi.ntrs.nasa.gov/20190033128.pdfhttps://newatlas.com/space/nasa-unveils-mid-size-lunar-lander-rover-missions/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 12:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/02/3929519/3929519_6197C87602554D798F9B06EF9B44935C_191202_3929519_NASA_showcases_mid_size_lunar_lander_for_future__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Space exploration, nasa space exploration, nasa lunar lander concept, nasa Commercial Lunar Payload Services, robotic lunar lander, nasa lunar mission, NASA mission preparation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929443</guid>
      <title>Smoke from Amazon fires could accelerate glacial melting in Andes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe fires burning in the Amazon rainforests are accelerating the melting of Andean glaciersThe fires burning in the Amazon rainforests are accelerating the melting of Andean glaciers, according to a study Nature published on November 28.Brazilian scientists at the Rio de Janeiro State University report that smoke from the fires are carrying black carbon as far as the Zongo Glacier in Bolivia.The study focused on the Zongo Glacier between 2007 and 2010, when more fires occurred in the rainforests than normally seen.The researchers said satellite LiDAR imagery confirm black carbon particles are carried to and deposited on the Zongo, or at an altitude between three and five kilometers.Lead researcher Dr. de Magalh達es Neto talking to the BBC said that the black carbon then darkens glacial ice and snow.The research team said that tropical glaciers supply water to millions of people in South America.According to the paper, snow and ice infused with black carbon is less able to deflect sunlight, resulting in a significantly higher rate of melting.Dr. Magalh達es Neto tells the BBC that forest fires in Bolivia, Peru and Brazil may have vast social implications for the continent, as glacier loss could lead to a water crisis.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Smoke from forest fires drift to the Zongo Glacier2. LiDAR detects black carbon3. Black carbon darkens the glacier and cause it to melt4. Melting of Andean glaciers could spark water crisisVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers say the fires burning in the Amazon rainforests are accelerating the melting of Andean glaciers.""Brazilian scientists at the Rio de Janeiro State University report that smoke from the fires are carrying black carbon as far as the Zongo Glacier in Bolivia.""The researchers said satellite LiDAR imagery confirm black carbon particles are carried to and deposited on the Zongo, or at an altitude between three and five kilometers.""Lead researcher Dr. de Magalh達es Neto talking to the BBC said that the black carbon then darkens glacial ice and snow.""According to the paper, snow and ice infused with black carbon is less able to deflect sunlight, resulting in a significantly higher rate of melting.""Dr. Magalh達es Neto tells the BBC that forest fires in Bolivia, Peru and Brazil may have vast social implications for the continent, as glacier loss could lead to a water crisis."SOURCES: Scientific Reports, BBC Newshttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-019-53284-1https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50573623***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 09:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/02/3929443/3929443_45B89D5B60494E3E8BF773E9DFB3E133_191202_3929443_Smoke_from_Amazon_fires_could_accelerate_glacial_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Amazon fires, rainforest, deforestation, deforestation fires, black carbon, glaciers, tropical glaciers, andes, andean glaciers, Rio de Janeiro State University, Zongo Glacier, Brazil, Bolivia, Peru, environment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930150</guid>
      <title>Australia is getting cell phone detecting cameras</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Australian government has rolled out a smart traffic camera system to catch drivers who use cell phones on the road.Transport for New South Wales officially activated the mobile phone detection system on Monday after the testing the technology from January to June this year.According to NSW Transport, the system features high definition cameras with infrared flash. The cameras are linked to an artificial intelligence program.The optics allow the system to see into the front cabinet of road vehicles and capture clear images during day or night and in all weather conditions. The system's software then analyzes the images to spot drivers who are using mobile phones.The algorithm excludes images of legal phone use but passes the suspicious ones to authorized reviewers, who checks the images before issuing penalties and fines.NSW Transport says it expects to install 45 cameras across its jurisdiction by 2023.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. AI camera system unveiled in New South Wales2. System optics and AI3. AI distinguishes legal and illegal vehicular mobile phone use 4. Human review for images and NSW government plansVOICEOVER (in English): "The Australian government has rolled out a smart traffic camera system to catch drivers who use cell phones on the road.""Transport for New South Wales officially activated the mobile phone detection system on Monday after the testing the technology from January to June this year.""According to NSW Transport, the system features high definition cameras with infrared flash. The cameras are linked to an artificial intelligence program.""The optics allow the system to see into the front cabinet of road vehicles and capture clear images during day or night and in all weather conditions." "The system's software then analyzes the images to spot drivers who are using mobile phones.""The algorithm excludes images of legal phone use but passes the suspicious ones to authorized reviewers, who checks the images before issuing penalties and fines.""NSW Transport says it expects to install 45 cameras across its jurisdiction by 2023."SOURCES: Transport for New South Wales, BBC Newshttps://roadsafety.transport.nsw.gov.au/stayingsafe/mobilephones/technology.html https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-50630763***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 14:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/03/3930150/3930150_C14A160CC23D499D9582F9B495539EF1_191203_3930150_Australia_is_getting_cell_phone_detecting_camera_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930124</guid>
      <title>NASA &amp; ESA to conduct planetary defense tests on asteroid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA and the European Space Agency are joining hands for a planetary defense mission in order to learn how to protect Earth from a possible asteroid collision.The ESA is preparing for the Hera mission that will gather data from Didymoon, the accompanying moonlet of a binary asteroid system called Didymos, years after NASA crashes a spacecraft into it through its Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART.According to NASA, the binary asteroid system is located roughly 11 million kilometers from Earth. NASA's DART spacecraft will be guided by an onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system as it makes its way to the binary asteroid. By 2022, NASA aims to crash onto the surface of Didymoon at a speed of roughly 6 kilometers per second in order to change the speed and direction of the asteroid.Didymoon is 160 meters in width. This is roughly the width of the Great Pyramid of Giza.The Hera spacecraft will then research the crater formed by the DART experiment in 2026.According to an ESA news release, the spacecraft will collect surface samples, as well as data about the shape and dimensions of the crater.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. ESA and NASA joining hands for a planetary defense mission2. How far the binary asteroid system is3. NASA crashing a spacecraft onto the surface of asteroid Didymoon4. Dimensions of Didymoon5. ESA's Hera spacecraft researching the crater formed on the asteroid by NASA's DART experiment6. Spacecraft collecting data from the crater7. Spacecraft using thermal imaging technologyVOICEOVER (in English): "The ESA is preparing for the Hera mission that will gather data from Didymoon, the accompanying moonlet of a binary asteroid system called Didymos, years after NASA crashes a spacecraft into it through its Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART.""According to NASA, the binary asteroid system is located roughly 11 million kilometers from Earth. NASA's DART spacecraft will be guided by an onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system as it makes its way to the binary asteroid." "By 2022, NASA aims to crash onto the surface of Didymoon at a speed of roughly 6 kilometers per second in order to change the speed and direction of the asteroid.""According to the American space agency, Didymoon is 160 meters in width. This is roughly the width of the Great Pyramid of Giza.""The Hera spacecraft will then research the crater formed by the DART experiment in 2026.""According to an ESA news release, the spacecraft will collect surface samples, as well as data about the shape and dimensions of the crater.""Hera will also use thermal imaging technology to examine the asteroid's structure." SOURCES: CNET, NASA, ESA, Space.com https://www.cnet.com/news/nasa-is-going-to-shoot-an-asteroid-and-europe-will-examine-the-mess/https://www.nasa.gov/planetarydefense/darthttp://www.esa.int/Our_Activities/Space_Engineering_Technology/Hera/ESA_plans_mission_to_smallest_asteroid_ever_visitedhttps://www.esa.int/Our_Activities/Space_Engineering_Technology/Hera/Target_asteroidhttps://www.space.com/hera-asteroid-deflection-mission-european-support.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 13:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/03/3930124/3930124_9FA98818CD4B443F96204803A2332658_191203_3930124_NASA___ESA_to_conduct_planetary_defense_tests_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Double Asteroid Redirection Test,hera mission NASA, DART, planetary defense mission, asteroid, Didymos, planetary defense system, esa, asteroid, didymos, binary asteroid system, didymoon, asteroid impact]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929932</guid>
      <title>Researchers convert banana cellulose into biodegradable plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to researchers at Australia's University of South Wales, banana growing can be a highly wasteful process with 88 percent of the plant being discarded after fruit harvesting. The scientists have designed a new method that reduces this waste by reusing the pseudostem, or the banana's trunk, and turning it into biodegradable packaging.According to the university's press release, the team cut the pseudostem, then dry heated the pieces at low temperatures to remove water. The process extracts cellulose from banana plant cells in powdered form, which is then chemically treated to become the packaging material.According to the researchers, the finished product is a baking paper like polymer that may replace plastic bags and single use commercial containers for meat and fruit.They claimed that tests conducted at the university found the material to be nontoxic and can be recycled up to three times.According to one of the professors involved in the study, bananas are annual plants and could potentially provide a round the year supply of sustainable packaging material.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New polymer utilize banana plantation's agricultural waste 2. Manufacturing process of polymer3. Uses of the banana cellulose polymer4. Banana provide stable supply of materialsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to researchers at Australia's University of South Wales, banana growing can be a highly wasteful process with 88 percent of the plant being discarded after fruit harvesting.""The scientists have designed a new method that reduces this waste by reusing the pseudostem, or the banana's trunk, and turning it into biodegradable packaging.""According to the university's press release, the team cut the pseudostem, then dry heated the pieces at low temperatures to remove water." "The process extracts cellulose from banana plant cells in powdered form, which is then chemically treated to become the packaging material.""According to the researchers, the finished product is a baking paper like polymer that may replace plastic bags and single use commercial containers for meat and fruit.""They claimed that tests conducted at the university found the material to be nontoxic and can be recycled up to three times.""According to one of the professors involved in the study, bananas are annual plants and could potentially provide a round the year supply of sustainable packaging material."SOURCES: The University of New South Waleshttps://newsroom.unsw.edu.au/news/science-tech/packaging-made-banana-plants-peeling-alternative***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 08:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/03/3929932/3929932_24968A8C3FF346338DBCF64B376EDF9E_191203_3929932_Researchers_convert_banana_cellulose_into_biodeg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Banana, cellulose, plastic alternative, plastic, polymer, biodegradable, recyclable, environment, science and technology, UNSW, University University of South Wales Sydney]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929899</guid>
      <title>Underwater loudspeakers could help boost coral reef recovery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that deploying underwater loudspeakers to play the sounds of healthy coral reef could help restore damaged reefs.In a joint study by two British universities and two Australian universities, scientists recorded sounds of healthy reefs and then played these sounds via a loudspeaker for 40 days on Australia's northern Great Barrier Reef.One of the authors of the study explained that healthy coral reefs are noisy, with shrimp and fish living in the area creating noise. Once coral reefs start to degrade or are damaged, reefs turn eerily quiet. This results in fish in the reefs leaving to find a new home. At the end of the experiment, scientists found that the degraded coral reefs had a 50 percent increase in the number of juvenile fish.Lead author of the study, Tim Gordon, explained in a news release that the growth of fish population choosing to stay in the damaged reefs could help to kick-start the natural recovery process for the coral reefs.Co-author of the study, Andy Radford, from the University of Bristol, said that this technique could be combined with other coral restoration techniques to help accelerate ecosystem recovery.Though Radford added that we need to combat other threats such as climate change, water pollution and overfishing in order to better protect these ecosystems in the first place.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sounds of healthy coral being recorded by a loudspeaker2. The loudspeaker playing the sounds of the healthy coral to damaged coral3. The number of juvenile fish in the degraded reefs had increased by 50 percent after the experiment4. A growing number of fish could help naturally kick-start the recovery process for coral reefsVOICEOVER (in English): "In a joint study by two British universities and two Australian universities, scientists recorded sounds of healthy reefs and then played these sounds via a loudspeaker for 40 days on Australia's northern Great Barrier Reef.""One of the authors of the study explained that healthy coral reefs are noisy, with shrimp and fish living in the area creating noise." "Once coral reefs start to degrade or are damaged, reefs turn eerily quiet. This results in fish in the reefs leaving to find a new home.""At the end of the experiment, scientists found that the degraded coral reefs had a 50 percent increase in the number of juvenile fish.""Lead author of the study, Tim Gordon, explained in a news release that the growth of fish population choosing to stay in the damaged reefs could help to kick-start the natural recovery process for the coral reefs."SOURCES: CNet, University of Exeter, Nature Communicationshttps://www.cnet.com/news/underwater-loudspeakers-could-help-restore-damaged-coral-reefs/https://www.exeter.ac.uk/news/featurednews/title_768084_en.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-019-13186-2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 07:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/03/3929899/3929899_64799163CA454CD1BB40F672BF443A1E_191203_3929899_Underwater_loudspeakers_could_help_boost_coral_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Great barrier reef new coral, Great barrier coral, damaged coral, damaged coral underwater loudspeakers, coral reef restoration, coral reef loudspeakers, Great barrier reef loudspeakers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930538</guid>
      <title>NASA's dummies to fly around Moon to test anti-radiation vests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA will send astronaut dummies around the moon in the Orion spacecraft for the uncrewed Artemis I mission scheduled for next year, Space.com reports.  According to the outlet, NASA says the goal of the mission is to test a new piece of equipment designed to protect female astronauts from space radiation called the AstroRad. According to the European Space Agency, the pair of phantom dummies named Zohar and Helga are fitted with over 5,600 radiation sensors.Zohar will wear the AstroRad protective vest and Helgo will not, which will help researchers evaluate the effectiveness of the vest. Makers of the radiation vest, a company called StemRad, say the vest protects the breasts, bone marrow, stomach, ovaries and other vulnerable organs that contain stem cells via its variable thickness shielding.According to the Tel-Aviv based contractor, the contoured shields are solid polymer shielding elements that are arrayed in a scale like structure. According to the German Aerospace Center's Thomas Berger, though the vest is designed for women, the garment could be adjusted for males.StemRad claims its vest could allow astronauts to leave the Orioin's solar storm shelters to perform important tasks during a solar storm.According to the company, the vest significantly reduces cancer and other fatal radiation exposure risks for astronauts.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Planned Artemis I mission to send radiation dummy to space2. Radiation test dummies Helga and Zohar3. AstroRad Vest designed to protect vulnerable organs4. Vest allow astronauts to leave solar storm shelterVOICEOVER (in English): "Space.com reports that NASA will send astronaut dummies around the moon in the Orion spacecraft for the uncrewed Artemis I mission scheduled for next year.""According to the outlet, NASA says the goal of the mission is to test a new piece of equipment designed to protect female astronauts from space radiation called the AstroRad.""According to the European Space Agency, the pair of phantom dummies named Zohar and Helga are fitted with over 5,600 radiation sensors.""Zohar will wear the AstroRad protective vest and Helgo will not, which will help researchers evaluate the effectiveness of the vest.""Makers of the radiation vest, a company called StemRad, say the vest protects the breasts, bone marrow, stomach, ovaries and other vulnerable organs that contain stem cells via its variable thickness shielding.""According to the Tel-Aviv based contractor, the contoured shields are solid polymer shielding elements that are arrayed in a scale like structure.""According to the German Aerospace Center's Thomas Berger, though the vest is designed for women, the garment could be adjusted for males.""StemRad claims its vest could allow astronauts to leave the Orioin's solar storm shelters to perform important tasks during a solar storm.""According to the company, the vest significantly reduces cancer and other fatal radiation exposure risks for astronauts."SOURCES: Space.com, StemRad, European Space Agencyhttps://www.space.com/phantom-dummy-stemrad-radiation-vest-artemis-mission.htmlhttps://www.space.com/40590-anti-radiation-life-vest-deep-space.htmlhttps://www.space.com/22252-women-astronauts-radiation-risk.htmlhttps://stemrad.com/astrorad-4/https://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Human_and_Robotic_Exploration/Orion/Radiation_for_dummies***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 10:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/04/3930538/3930538_EEB759F873414D16BB135331477BE1B0_191204_3930538_NASA_s_dummies_to_fly_around_Moon_to_test_anti_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, StemRad, AstroRad, dummies, vest, vests, Lockheed-Martin, Artemis I, Orion, moon, space exploration, radiation, solar storm, astronaut]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930402</guid>
      <title>How your Smart TV could be spying on you</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe FBI warned consumers this week that their smart TVs may be collecting extensive data about them.In a message to Christmas shoppers, the agency warned that smart TVs are vulnerable to cyberattacks. This is because they are connected to the internet and include features such as microphones and cameras.The FBI said that if a device is hacked, hackers could use these features to cyberstalk someone. The bureau urged owners of smart TVs to take preventive actions against this by learning their devices' privacy settings and how to turn off its microphones and cameras.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Smart TVs could be collecting extensive data from users2. Why smart TVs are vulnerable to cyberattacks3. A hacker using microphones and camera on a smart TV to cyberstalk people4. How to prevent against such cyberattacksVOICEOVER (in English): "The FBI warned consumers this week that smart TVs may be collecting extensive data about their users." "In a message to Christmas shoppers, the agency warned that smart TVs are vulnerable to cyberattacks. This is because they are connected to the internet and include features such as microphones and cameras.""The FBI said that if a device is hacked, hackers could use these features to cyberstalk someone.""The bureau urged owners of smart TVs to take preventive actions against this by learning their devices' privacy settings and how to turn off its microphones and cameras."SOURCES: CNN, TechCrunch, FBIhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/02/politics/smart-tv-fbi-warning-cyber-monday/index.htmlhttps://techcrunch.com/2019/12/01/fbi-smart-tv-security/https://www.fbi.gov/contact-us/field-offices/portland/news/press-releases/tech-tuesdaysmart-tvs/?=portland-field-office***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 07:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/04/3930402/3930402_B29C7799E9424511A6D2262EB363BB5A_191204_3930402_How_your_Smart_TV_could_be_spying_on_you_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Smart TV, smart TV spying on you, smart TV warning, smart tv spying, smart tv cameras, smart tv cameras watching you, technology, smart technology, smart tv technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930941</guid>
      <title>NASA to attach 'robot hotel' to International Space Station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA plans to launch a storage space for robotic tools called the Robotic Tool Stowage, or RiTS, to the International Space Station.In a news release, NASA explained that the robot hotel will be launched aboard a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket, during its 19th commercial resupply mission, on December 4.Two robotic tools called Robotic External Leak Locators, or RELL, that are currently onboard the International Space Station, will be the first residents of the storage space. These robotic tools are capable of detecting gases such as ammonia and are used to find leaks in the station.NASA says the storage unit will protect the tools from space radiation, tiny meteoroids, or other high-speed objects traveling through space.The Robotic Tool Stowage's thermal system will be able to maintain a constant temperature to help the space station's robotic equipment stay functional. The location of the storage space will also make it easily accessible for the International Space Station's robotic arm called Dextre to get a hold of these tools.Once the robot hotel makes its way to the space station, astronauts will perform a spacewalk to install the storage space to the station's exterior.NASA says this type of technology could potentially be used in future space missions to the Moon, Mars, or beyond.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Storage space for robotic tools2. The storage space will be used to store Robotic External Leak Locators3. How this will protect the tools4. Astronauts installing the storage space to the exterior of the International Space StationVOICEOVER (in English): "In a news release, NASA said it plans to launch a storage space for robotic tools called the Robotic Tool Stowage, or RiTS, to the International Space Station. It will be attached to the ISS's exterior.""The robot hotel will be launched aboard a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket, during its 19th commercial resupply mission, on December 4.""Two robotic tools called Robotic External Leak Locators, or RELL, that are currently onboard the International Space Station, will be the first residents of the storage space.""These robotic tools are capable of detecting gases such as ammonia and are used to find leaks in the station.""NASA says the storage unit will protect the tools from space radiation, tiny meteoroids, or other high-speed objects traveling through space.""The Robotic Tool Stowage's thermal system will be able to maintain a constant temperature to help the space station's robotic equipment stay functional.""The location of the storage space will also make it easily accessible for the International Space Station's robotic arm called Dextre to get a hold of these tools.""Once the robot hotel makes its way to the space station, astronauts will perform a spacewalk to install the storage space to the outside of the station."SOURCES: NASA, Tech Crunch, Slash Gearhttps://www.nasa.gov/image-feature/robot-hotel-launching-to-the-international-space-stationhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2019/nasa-launching-rits-a-robot-hotel-to-the-international-space-station/https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2019/nasa-nose-importance-of-humans-robots-exploring-togetherhttps://techcrunch.com/2019/12/03/nasa-will-launch-a-robot-hotel-to-the-space-station-on-its-next-spacex-resupply-mission/https://www.slashgear.com/nasa-shows-off-the-robot-hotel-its-sending-into-space-03602094/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 07:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/05/3930941/3930941_C4060A4D757E4C8AAD85F62B532F74ED_191205_3930941_NASA_to_attach__robot_hotel__to_International_Sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Robot hotel, robot hotel NASA, International Space Station, International Space Station robot hotel, Robotic Tool Stowage, RiTS, Robotic Tool Stowage NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930856</guid>
      <title>Mandatory face-scanning may be implemented across U.S. airports</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Department of Homeland Security has proposed a new regulation that would require all travelers  including U.S. citizens and green card holders  to undergo mandatory facial scans when entering and leaving the country.Facial recognition technology typically matches an image of a person from a photo or video with a still image of them in a database. It has become increasingly used in airports throughout the world, according to CNN. The proposed regulation would be part of a broader system to track travelers as they enter and exit the United States.According to Reuters, the Trump Administration contends the face scan requirement will combat the fraudulent use of U.S. travel documents and aid the identification of criminals and suspected terrorists.The U.S. Customs and Border Protection has already conducted pilot programs that collect photographs and fingerprints from foreign travelers, but until now, U.S. citizens had been exempt, Reuters reports.   In 2017, President Trump signed an executive order to accelerate a full roll out of airport biometrics for all domestic and international travelers.According to a statement by a senior policy analyst from American Liberties Union Jay Stanley, travelers shouldn't have to submit to "invasive biometric scans" just because they want to travel.The U.S. government has been using facial recognition technology for the past 20 years, though the government has only recently started pushing for use of this technology across U.S. airports, CNN reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New regulation would require all travelers, even U.S. citizens, to undergo mandatory face scans2. How facial recognition technology works3. How the technology will be used to track travelers as they enter and exit the U.S.4. Previous pilot programs had collected photographs and fingerprints from foreign travelersVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Department of Homeland Security has proposed a new regulation that would require all travelers  including U.S. citizens and green card holders  to undergo mandatory facial scans when entering and leaving the country.""According to CNN, facial recognition technology typically matches an image of a person from a photo or video with a still image of them in a database. It has become increasingly used in airports throughout the world.""The proposed regulation would be part of a broader system to track travelers as they enter and exit the United States.""According to Reuters, the Trump Administration contends the face scan requirement will combat the fraudulent use of U.S. travel documents and aid the identification of criminals and suspected terrorists.""Reuters reports that the U.S. Customs and Border Protection has already conducted pilot programs that collect photographs and fingerprints from foreign travelers, but until now, U.S. citizens had been exempt."  "In 2017, President Trump signed an executive order to accelerate a full roll out of airport biometrics for all domestic and international travelers."SOURCES: Reuters, TechCrunch, CNN, U.S. General Services Administration   https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-privacy/u-s-homeland-security-proposes-face-scans-for-citizens-idUSKBN1Y62JOhttps://techcrunch.com/2019/12/02/homeland-security-face-recognition-airport-citizens/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/02/tech/homeland-security-facial-recognition-citizens-at-airports/index.htmlhttps://www.reginfo.gov/public/do/eAgendaViewRule?pubId=201910&RIN=1651-AB22&=biometric-collection-data-citizens***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 04:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/05/3930856/3930856_8C07ECF69014469A989F70644891BE6D_191205_3930856_Mandatory_face_scanning_may_be_implemented_acros_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Facial recognition, Face scans, US face scans, facial recognition surveillance, US facial recognition technology, US homeland security face scans, facial recognition usa, US airports face scans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931730</guid>
      <title>China turns 'Great Cannon' on Hong Kong web forum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Chinese cyberweapon dubbed the Great Cannon is launching DDoS attacks on a Hong Kong webform after years of silence, AT&T Cybersecurity reported on Wednesday.The internet security developer says analysis indicates that the Cannon begin attacking the webforum named LIHKG in August.According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Hong Kong activists have been using the forum to coordinate protests.The Citizen Lab at the University of Toronto reported previously that the Great Cannon represents a "significant escalation in state-level information control."AT&T Cybersecurity states that the Cannon inserts malicious Javascript code into browsers when users access servers within China's Great Firewall.The Great Cannon then uses the code to send numerous requests to overwhelm the targeted domain's resources and to make it unavailable.According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Great Cannon caused global disruption in 2015, when it was deployed against Github and the online freedom group GreatFire.org.The security firm says that the Chinese-language news website Mingjingnews.com was attacked from two years ago and that it expects more attacks against LIHKG.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Great Cannon makes DDoS attack on LIHKG webforum2. Forum has been used to organize protests in Hong Kong3. The Great Cannon's functioning and design4. Domains attacked by the Great CannonVOICEOVER (in English): "A Chinese cyberweapon dubbed the Great Cannon is launching DDoS attacks on a Hong Kong webform after years of silence, AT&T Cybersecurity reported on Wednesday.""The internet security developer says analysis indicates that the Cannon begin attacking the webforum named LIHKG in August.""According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Hong Kong activists have been using the forum to coordinate protests.""The Citizen Lab at the University of Toronto reported previously that the Great Cannon represents a 'significant escalation in state-level information control.'""AT&T Cybersecurity states that the Cannon inserts malicious Javascript code into browsers when users access servers within China's Great Firewall.""The Great Cannon then uses the code to send numerous requests to overwhelm the targeted domain's resources and to make it unavailable.""According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Great Cannon caused global disruption in 2015, when it was deployed against Github and the online freedom group GreatFire.org.""The security firm says that the Chinese-language news website Mingjingnews.com was attacked from two years ago and that it expects more attacks against LIHKG."SOURCES: AT&T Cybersecurity, Citizen Labhttps://cybersecurity.att.com/blogs/labs-research/the-great-cannon-has-been-deployed-againhttps://citizenlab.ca/2015/04/chinas-great-cannon/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 14:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/06/3931730/3931730_DBE66A62728B48C19F12E46BF4CFA5EC_191206_3931730_China_turns__Great_Cannon__on_Hong_Kong_web_foru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931318</guid>
      <title>Doctors 'reanimate' human heart from deceased donor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFor the first time in the U.S, doctors have successfully "reanimated" a heart from a deceased donor, prior to the heart being transplanted to an adult recipient.This procedure is known as donation after circulatory death or DCD.Donor hearts usually come from those who have been declared as brain dead but still have a beating heart. The beating heart is then transplanted into a recipient, CNN reports. Jacob Schroder, one of the doctors involved in the heart transplant procedure, told CNN that the donor heart was doused with a cold solution and removed five minutes after the person's death was announced and after heartbeat and circulation had stopped.Physicians from Duke University Medical Center then placed the heart in the TransMedics Organ Care System. The system pumps warm blood and allows the non-beating heart to be preserved and resuscitated for a transplant.Once the heart and the heart recipient is ready, the donor heart is then transplanted into the recipient via standard heart transplant procedure.Schroder explained that the procedure could increase the donor pool and the number of transplants performed by 30 percent. This would decrease wait time and the number of deaths of those waiting for a transplant.The procedure has previously been performed in medical centers in the United Kingdom and Australia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A heart from a deceased donor is brought back to life2. The donor heart being doused with cold solution and being removed from the deceased person3. How the heart is preserved and brought back to life4. The procedure could increase the donor pool and the amount of transplants performed in the U.S.VOICEOVER (in English): "For the first time in the U.S, doctors have successfully 'reanimated' a heart from a deceased donor, prior to the heart being transplanted to an adult recipient.""This procedure is known as donation after circulatory death or DCD.""Jacob Schroder, one of the doctors involved in the heart transplant procedure, told CNN that the donor heart was doused with a cold solution and removed five minutes after the person's death was announced and after heartbeat and circulation had stopped.""Physicians from Duke University Medical Center then placed the heart in the TransMedics Organ Care System. The system pumps warm blood and allows the non-beating heart to be preserved and resuscitated for a transplant.""Once the heart and the heart recipient is ready, the donor heart is then transplanted into the recipient via standard heart transplant procedure.""Schroder explained that the procedure could increase the donor pool and the number of transplants performed by 30 percent. This would decrease wait time and the number of deaths of those waiting for a transplant."SOURCES: CNN, Fox Newshttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/03/health/dcd-heart-transplant-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.foxnews.com/health/heart-from-dead-donor-revived-transplanted-us***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 03:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/06/3931318/3931318_ED76AC5148264C40BD8E618EFCD2E7C1_191206_3931318_Doctors__reanimate__human_heart_from_deceased_do_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Heart transplant, reanimating a heart, doctors reanimate heart, doctors bring heart back to life, donor heart preservation, reanimate donor heart, TransMedics Organ Care System]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931962</guid>
      <title>North American birds are getting smaller</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that tens of thousands of North American birds have become smaller in size since 1978.Scientists examined 70, 716 dead birds  52 bird species in total  that crashed into skyscrapers in Chicago.The study, published in the journal Ecology Letters, found that 49 of these bird species had a reduction in the length of their lower leg bone by 2.4 percent.Meanwhile, the average wing length of birds saw an increase of roughly 1.3 percent.The authors of the study suggested that a change in the birds' size may be a response to rising temperatures caused by climate change.They added that the birds may have evolved to have a wider wingspan to compensate for their smaller bodies and to help them migrate long distances.Scientists said that animal species tend to be smaller in warmer regions and larger in colder regions. This is to help animals carry less heat in hot areas while those in colder areas need a larger body size to conserve warmth.The researchers plan to use the data to look at the mechanics of how a birds' body changes in shape and size, according to CNN. They also plan to examine whether the change is a result of developmental plasticity  an animal's ability to change its own development as a response to the changing environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North American birds shrinking in size2. Most of these bird species had short leg bones than in the past3. What may have caused the birds to become smaller4. Bird species smaller in warmer areas than colder areasVOICEOVER (in English): "New research has found that tens of thousands of North American birds have become smaller in size since 1978.""Scientists examined 70, 716 dead birds  52 bird species in total  that crashed into skyscrapers in Chicago.""The study, published in the journal Ecology Letters, found that 49 of these bird species had a reduction in the length of their lower leg bone by 2.4 percent.""Meanwhile, the average wing length of birds saw an increase of roughly 1.3 percent.""The authors of the study suggested that a change in the birds' size may be a response to rising temperatures caused by climate change.""They added that the birds may have evolved to have a wider wingspan to compensate for their smaller bodies and to help them migrate long distances.""Scientists said that animal species tend to be smaller in warmer regions and larger in colder regions. This is to help animals carry less heat in hot areas while those in colder areas need a larger body size to conserve warmth."SOURCES: BBC News, Ecology Letters, CNN, Reutershttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50661448https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/ele.13434https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/04/world/dead-birds-body-size-climate-change-scn/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-birds/bye-bye-birdie-study-finds-north-american-birds-getting-smaller-idUSKBN1Y82NJ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 08:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/07/3931962/3931962_81A6E7A3AB8947D09357427687AB2F55_191207_3931962_North_American_birds_are_getting_smaller_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, bird population north america, north american birds shrinking, smaller north american birds, climate change birds affected, birds and climate change, global warming bird population shrinking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932755</guid>
      <title>220-pound ball of trash discovered in stomach of dead sperm whale</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA sperm whale that became stranded and died on a Scottish beach had 220 pounds of garbage in its stomach, according to the Scottish Marine Animal Strandings Scheme (SMASS).According to an SMASS Facebook post on December 1, the animal had been dead for two days by the time workers examined the carcass.  According to SMASS, the juvenile whale measured 14 meters long. Approximately 220 pounds of garbage was found in its stomach, including nets, ropes, plastic cups and bags, gloves and packaging.SMASS said that debris in the whale originated from both fishing and land sectors and that the animal had been eating litter for quite some time.The whale could have swallowed the debris between the Azores to Norway and efforts to explain why this whale ingested so much garbage is still ongoing.While the garbage did not appear to block the whale's intestines, SMASS said the debris caused indigestion and may have played a role in the stranding that resulted in the whale's demise.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Stranded whale discovered on Haris Island, Scottland2. Types and quantity of marine debris contained in the whale's stomach3.  Whale ingests the debris 4. Impact of ingested debris on whale healthVOICEOVER (in English): "A sperm whale that became stranded and died on a Scottish beach had a large mass of marine litter found in  its stomach.""According to the Scottish Marine Animal Strandings Scheme in a Facebook post on December 1, the animal had been dead for two days by the time workers examined its carcass."  "According to SMASS, the juvenile whale measured 14 meters long. Approximately 100 kilograms of garbage was found in its stomach, including nets, ropes, plastic cups and bags, gloves and packaging.""SMASS said that debris in the whale originated from both fishing and land sectors and that the animal had been eating litter for quite some time.""The whale could have swallowed the debris between the Azores to Norway and efforts to explain why this whale ingested so much garbage is still ongoing.""While the garbage did not appear to block the whale's intestines, SMASS said the debris caused indigestion and may have played a role in the stranding that resulted in the whale's demise."SOURCES: The Scottish Marine Animal Stranding Scheme, Live Sciencehttps://www.facebook.com/Strandings/posts/2547086122048826?__tn__=-Rhttps://www.livescience.com/dead-sperm-whale-trash-belly.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/09/3932755/3932755_5DFFC8A5D33E498C8751A28C11A039ED_191209_3932755_220_pound_ball_of_trash_discovered_in_stomach_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sperm whale, whale, stranding, stranded, marine debris, trash, ocean, pollution, plastic pollution, Harris Island, Isle of Harris, Scotland, environment, SMASS, Scottish Marine Animal Strandings Scheme]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932529</guid>
      <title>Plastic waste traps hermit 560,000 crabs on remote islands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study led by the University of Tasmania has found that more than 560,000 hermit crabs have died from being trapped in plastic waste on the remote Cocos Keeling and Henderson Islands.Scientists surveyed sites on both the islands for plastic debris and found open plastic containers across the islands. The study also accounted for the number of trapped crabs, both dead and alive, found inside the plastic containers.Researchers said that the piles of plastic waste present on the island beaches create physical obstacles as well as traps for the hermit crabs.The problem is exacerbated as hermit crabs don't have shells of their own, which means that they need to track down other dead crabs via their odor in order to acquire them.In one example, researchers found that this led to 526 crabs being trapped in a single plastic container.In a University of Tasmania news release scientists said that these hermit crabs are important as they help disperse seeds, fertilize the soil in tropical environments and form an integral part of the marine ecosystem.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cocos Keeling Islands, Henderson Island and a hermit crab trapped in plastic waste2. Islands filled with plastic waste and open plastic containers3. Crabs stuck in plastic containers4. The plastic creates a physical barrier and traps for the crabs5. Why the problem is exacerbated VOICEOVER (in English): "A new study led by the University of Tasmania has found that more than 560,000 hermit crabs have died from being trapped in plastic waste in the Cocos Keeling Islands and Henderson Island.""Scientists surveyed sites on both the islands for plastic debris and found open plastic containers across the islands.""The study also accounted for the number of trapped crabs, both dead and alive, found inside the plastic containers.""Researchers said that the piles of plastic waste present on the island beaches create physical obstacles as well as traps for the hermit crabs.""The problem is exacerbated as hermit crabs don't have shells of their own, which means that they need to track down other dead crabs via their odor in order to acquire them." "In one example, researchers found that this led to 526 crabs being trapped in a single plastic container."SOURCES: The Guardian, CNN,  University of Tasmania, Journal of Hazardous Materialshttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/dec/05/plastic-pollution-hermit-crabs-species-decline-henderson-cocos-islandshttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/05/world/hermit-crabs-plastic-pollution-intl-scli-scn/index.htmlhttps://www.utas.edu.au/communications/general-news/all-news/half-a-million-crabs-killed-by-plastic-debris-on-remote-islandshttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0304389419316577?via%3Dihub***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 04:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/09/3932529/3932529_6E94A989184E4F9295514E4AA868E235_191209_3932529_Plastic_waste_traps_hermit_560_000_crabs_on_remo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Plastic pollution, hermit crabs, hermit crabs trapped in plastic, hermit crabs plastic waste, plastic waste, plastic polluting the oceans, plastic debris crabs,  Cocos Island hermit crabs, Henderson Island hermit crabs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933393</guid>
      <title>White Island eruption was difficult to anticipate: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe sudden eruption of New Zealand's White Island volcano has left 5 people dead and injured dozens of others, reports CNN.According to the University of Otago, White Island straddles the Australian and Pacific tectonic plates.Magma is created beneath the island when the Pacific plate pushes against the Australian plate and sinks beneath it.The Guardian reports that White Island magma is shallow and heats groundwater to form pockets of extremely hot steam. This causes high pressure in surrounding rocks.The expansion of water into steam can be supersonic and its energy can shatter the rockbed, resulting in a steam-driven eruption, also known as hydrothermal eruption.The Guardian reports that White Island's steam-driven eruption blasted hot volcanic rocks, ash and coarse particles that can inflict impact trauma, burns and respiratory injuries.Authorities fear as many as 13 people could be dead.CNN reports that five tourists on the island have been killed, while 27 have suffered serious burns and eight are still missing as of Tuesday.The Guardian reports that steam-driven eruptions can happen quickly and without warning because their triggers are not well understood.Volcanologists at GeoNet says the White Island volcano erupted with enough force that its plumes rose to a height of three kilometers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. White Island vocation is created by subduction of the Pacific tectonic plate under the Austrlian plate 2. Trapped pockets of water is heated by magma until the steam bursts from rock, causing hydrothermal eruption3. Volcanic ejecta causes injury among island tourists4. Extent of eruptionVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the University of Otago, White Island straddles the Australian and Pacific tectonic plates." "Magma is created beneath the island when the Pacific plate pushes against the Australian plate and sinks beneath it." "The Guardian reports that White Island magma is shallow and heats groundwater to form pockets of extremely hot steam. This causes high pressure in surrounding rocks.""The expansion of water into steam can be supersonic and its energy can shatter the rockbed, resulting in a steam-driven eruption, also known as hydrothermal eruption.""The Guardian reports that White Island's steam-driven eruption blasted hot volcanic rocks, ash and coarse particles that can inflict impact trauma, burns and respiratory injuries.""Authorities fear as many as 13 people could be dead.""CNN reports that five tourists on the island have been killed, while 27 have suffered serious burns and eight are still missing as of Tuesday.""The Guardian reports that steam-driven eruptions can happen quickly and without warning because their triggers are not well understood.""Volcanologists at GeoNet says the White Island volcano erupted with enough force that its plumes rose to a height of three kilometers."SOURCES: The Guardian, The University of Otago, GeoNet, CNNhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/dec/10/what-caused-the-eruption-on-new-zealands-white-island-and-why-was-there-no-warninghttps://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2019/dec/10/new-zealand-volcano-eruption-white-island-blast-latest-updateshttps://www.otago.ac.nz/geology/research/structural-geology/alpine-fault/nz-tectonics.htmlhttps://www.geonet.org.nz/vabs/4TA6UkHTyIQchYcjnSYk80https://edition.cnn.com/australia/live-news/new-zealand-volcano-live-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/11/3933393/3933393_D42A0CB679EF4E7AB509795DB21928EC_191211_3933393_White_Island_eruption_was_difficult_to_anticipat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933200</guid>
      <title>Oceans are being depleted of oxygen due to climate change and run offs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN) warns that climate change and nutrient pollution are depleting the oceans of oxygen in a report published in December. The report states that nitrogen and phosphorus runoffs from sewage, agricultural waste and industrial pollution are the main cause of oxygen depletion, especially in coastal seas.According to the BBC, the study also found that climate change is heating the oceans and reducing the amount of oxygen they can hold. The study found the oxygen dissolved in the ocean has dropped two percent globally and as much as 40 percent in parts of the tropics.The study warns that the combined effects of warmer oceans and run offs could affect the top 1,000 meter of the water column, which is richest in biodiversity.The IUCN states that deoxygenation harms bigger fish that are oxygen sensitive, such as tuna, marlin and sharks, but favors microbes and jellyfish that are not.The report suggests that the lack of oxygen would force the fish to live closer to the surface, where they are vulnerable to overfishing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nutrient pollution from runoff2. Climate change reduces oxygenination from oceans 3. Biodiversity, fisheries in top 1,000 meters water column threatened4. Jellyfish, microbes displaces fishVOICEOVER (in English): "The International Union for Conservation of Nature warns that climate change and nutrient pollution are depleting the oceans of oxygen in a report published in December." "The report states that nitrogen and phosphorus runoffs from sewage, agricultural waste and industrial pollution are the main cause of oxygen deletion, especially in coastal seas.""According to the BBC, the study also found that climate change is heating the oceans and reducing the amount of oxygen they can hold.""The study found the oxygen dissolved in the ocean has dropped two percent globally and as much as 40 percent in parts of the tropics.""The study warns that the combined effects of warmer oceans and run offs could affect the top 1,000 meter of the water column, which is richest in biodiversity.""The IUCN states that deoxygenation harms bigger fish that are oxygen sensitive, such as tuna, marlin and sharks, but favors microbes and jellyfish that are not.""The report suggests that the lack of oxygen would force the fish to live closer to the surface, where they are vulnerable to overfishing."SOURCES: IUCN, BBC Newshttps://www.iucn.org/news/marine-and-polar/201912/marine-life-fisheries-increasingly-threatened-ocean-loses-oxygen-iucn-reporthttps://portals.iucn.org/library/node/48892https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-50690995***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 09:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/10/3933200/3933200_87788129CD74494EB6FD0714F5EAD431_191210_3933200_Oceans_are_being_depleted_of_oxygen_due_to_clima_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ocean, oceans, oxygen, deoxygenation, nutrient pollution, runoff, climate change, global warming, fisheries, IUCN, fisheries, International Union for Conservation of Nature, environment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933164</guid>
      <title>'Seahorse hotels' planned for endangered White's seahorses in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew artificial habitats could help save the endangered White's seahorse species in Australia.SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium is working with the University of Technology Sydney and the New South Wales Department of Primary Industries Fisheries on a new breeding and conservation project for Australia's White's seahorse, one of only two endangered seahorse species worldwide.The Department of Primary Industries Fisheries states on its website that the main cause for the decline of White's seahorse, also known as the Sydney seahorse, is the loss of its natural habitats.In the project's first phase, researchers collected breeding pairs of White's seahorses from Sydney Harbor. Their offspring are being kept at a custom built facility at SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium and will eventually be released into the wild.For the second phase of the project, the team will begin constructing "seahorse hotels," or artificial habitats for seahorses, in Sydney Harbor this month.Researchers say the seahorse hotels will provide a habitat for the project's seahorses when they are released into the wild. Monitoring of the seahorses will continue after their release.These artificial habitats will be transformed into natural habitats for White's seahorses as they are grown over by sponges, algae and other marine creatures.Researchers say the artificial habitats were previously trialled in Port Stephens in New South Wales, Australia in 2018 and earlier this year.Trials were found to be extremely successful as they attracted seahorses, leading to mating and breeding.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New seahorse breeding and conservation project2. First phase of the project: collecting breeding seahorses3. Second phase of the project: building "seahorse hotels" for seahorses underwater4. How these artificial habitats would transform into natural habitatsVOICEOVER (in English): "SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium is working with the University of Technology Sydney and the New South Wales Department of Primary Industries Fisheries on a new breeding and conservation project for Australia's White's seahorse, one of only two endangered seahorse species worldwide.""In the project's first phase, researchers collected breeding pairs of White's seahorses from Sydney Harbor. Their offspring are being kept at a custom built facility at SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium and will eventually be released into the wild.""For the second phase of the project, the team will begin constructing 'seahorse hotels,' or artificial habitats for seahorses, in Sydney Harbor this month.""Researchers say the seahorse hotels will provide a habitat for the project's seahorses when they are released into the wild. Monitoring of the seahorses will continue after their release.""These artificial habitats will be transformed into natural habitats for White's seahorses as they are grown over by sponges, algae and other marine creatures."SOURCES: Australian Broadcasting Corporation, University of Technology, Sydney, New South Wales Department of Primary Industrieshttps://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-07-08/seahorse-hotels-bringing-endangered-species-back/9924454https://phys.org/news/2019-12-seahorse-aims-recover-endangered-species.htmlhttps://www.dpi.nsw.gov.au/fishing/species-protection/what-current/endangered-species/whites-seahorse***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 08:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/10/3933164/3933164_352D878C6ACE46FFBB34EBD4730E8BC9_191210_3933164__Seahorse_hotels__planned_for_endangered_White_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Seahorse hotels, White's seahorses, australia White's seahorse, endangered White's seahorses, artificial habitats for seahorses]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933114</guid>
      <title>New luxury superyacht inspired by killer whales</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANItalian shipyard Rosetti Superyachts has unveiled its new luxury yacht that is designed to look like an orca.Project Orca will be 65 meters long and consist of four decks, SuperYacht Times reports. The ship will have a range of 5,000 miles and will be able to travel at a cruising speed of 12 knots.The yacht itself comes with several deck configurations. In its standard configuration, the vessel will have an open deck, a touch-and-go helipad, and snow sledges.The superyacht may also be modified to include an infinity pool, or a raised helipad with a pool and spa area in its interior.Project Orca's interior includes six cabins, which can accommodate up to 12 people along with a crew of 12. The lower deck will also be equipped with a garage to store equipment like jet skis.Fulvio Dodich, CEO and chairman of Rosetti Superyachts, said that the yacht will take approximately 36 months to be built.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New luxury superyacht2. Length of the vessel, its range and cruising speed3. Different deck configurations of the yacht4. Interior of the yachtVOICEOVER (in English): "Italian shipyard Rosetti Superyachts has unveiled its new luxury yacht that is designed to look like an orca.""SuperYacht Times reports that Project Orca will be 65 meters long and consist of four decks.""The ship will have a range of 5,000 miles and will be able to travel at a cruising speed of 12 knots.""The yacht itself comes with several deck configurations.""In its standard configuration, the vessel will have an open deck, a touch-and-go helipad, and snow sledges.""The superyacht may also be modified to include an infinity pool, or a raised helipad with a pool and spa area in its interior.""Project Orca's interior includes six cabins, which can accommodate up to 12 people along with a crew of 12.""The lower deck will also be equipped with a garage to store equipment like jet skis."SOURCES: Super Yacht Times, Yacht Harbour, Robb Report, Rosetti Superyachts https://www.superyachttimes.com/yacht-news/project-orca-concept-revealedhttps://yachtharbour.com/news/rosetti-reveals-65m-superyacht-concept-project-orca-3571?src=_pos_5https://robbreport.com/motors/marine/project-orca-rosetti-superyachts-2884412/https://www.rosettisuperyachts.it/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 07:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/10/3933114/3933114_2216C126A25D4707A24C388F717B0AC1_191210_3933114_New_luxury_superyacht_inspired_by_killer_whales_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, superyacht, Italy superyacht, Project Orca, Orca superyacht, Project Orca yacht, orca yacht, luxury superyacht, Rosetti Superyachts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933088</guid>
      <title>Pensacola shooting under investigation as presumed act of terror: FBI</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Saudi trainee at the US Navy Pensacola Air Station carried out a shooting early morning on Friday that the FBI is assuming to be a terrorist attack.The New York Times reports that federal investigators identified the shooter as Saudi air force Second Lieutenant Mohammed Alshamrani in a press event on Sunday.The commanding officer of the base told the New York Times that three sailors tried to tackle the shooter in order to save others and were killed in the attack.Deputies responding to the emergency fatally shot Alshamrani. The incident left three sailors dead and eight injured, including two deputies who were shot in the limbs.The Times reports that one Saudi national was on the scene and videoed the shooting. The FBI has detained this individual alongside with two other Saudis on base for questioning.According to the FBI, Alshamrani was carrying a 9 millimeter Glock 45 pistol with a 33 round magazine and several spare magazines when deputies shot him.FBI special agent in charge Rachel Rojas, who identified the weapon, said the shooter "purchased the weapon legally and lawfully."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The attack on Pensacola Air Station2. Casualties of the attack3. Saudi national filming the attack was detained4. Alleged shooter obtained weapons legallyVOICEOVER (in English): "A Saudi trainee at the US Navy Pensacola Air Station carried out a shooting early morning on Friday that the FBI is assuming to be a terrorist attack.""The New York Times reports that federal investigators identified the shooter as Saudi air force Second Lieutenant Mohammed Alshamrani in a press event on Sunday.""The commanding officer of the base told the New York Times that three sailors tried to tackle the shooter in order to save others and were killed in the attack.""Deputies responding to the emergency fatally shot Alshamrani. The incident left three sailors dead and eight injured, including two deputies who were shot in the limbs.""The Times reports that one Saudi national was on the scene and videoed the shooting. The FBI has detained this individual alongside with two other Saudis on base for questioning.""According to the FBI, Alshamrani was carrying a 9 millimeter Glock 45 pistol with a 33 round magazine and several spare magazines when deputies shot him.""FBI special agent in charge Rachel Rojas, who identified the weapon, said the shooter 'purchased the weapon legally and lawfully.'"SOURCES: The New York Times, BBC News, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/08/us/florida-shooting-pensacola-updates.html?action=click&module=MoreInSection&pgtype=Article&region=Footer&contentCollection=U.S.%20Newshttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/06/us/nas-pensacola-shooting.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50692597https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/06/us/pensacola-naval-station-lockdown/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 07:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/10/3933088/3933088_214B65DB65C044E0A21C5A2F347290F9_191210_3933088_Pensacola_shooting_under_investigation_as_presum_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932998</guid>
      <title>Architects propose self-sustainable vertical city of the future</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Italian firm, Luca Curci Architects have proposed 'Vertical City', a project involving a self-sustaining, zero energy building that intends to house 25,000 people. The futuristic city proposes to be settled into the sea bed close to the mainland, accessible by land, sea, and air.The cylindrical residential building would be clad in photovoltaic glazing, a technology that produces electricity from sunlight. Natural light and ventilation will be promoted through hexagonal openings in the building.The 'Vertical City' targets low poverty, no noise, no pollution, desalinization of seawater and producing 1,144,500 KWh of daily solar energy.According to Luca Curci Architects, the 750-meter-tall residential skyscraper would consist of 10 modular layers, each layer consisting of 18 floors, including a mixture of homes, offices, stores and other facilities. The building would also offer more than 200,000 square meters of green space, which includes the public garden at the top of the building.In addition to the 25,000 people housed within the central residential tower, the Vertical City as a whole, including the three adjacent towers that house offices, government departments, healthcare facilities, and educational institutions, would service over 100,000 people who would travel to the city for work, school and medical care.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Residential building targets2. Pull out of residential buildings photovoltaic glazing3. Inside the residential building4. Map of the proposed cityVOICEOVER (in English): "The Italian firm, Luca Curci Architects have proposed 'Vertical City', a project involving a self-sustaining, zero energy building that intends to house 25,000 people. The futuristic city proposes to be settled into the sea bed close to the mainland, accessible by land, sea, and air.""The cylindrical residential building would be clad in photovoltaic glazing, a technology that produces electricity from sunlight. Natural light and ventilation will be promoted through hexagonal openings in the building.The 'Vertical City' targets low poverty, no noise, no pollution, desalinization of seawater and producing 1,144,500 KWh of daily solar energy.""According to Luca Curci Architects, the 750-meter-tall residential skyscraper would consist of 10 modular layers, each layer consisting of 18 floors, including a mixture of homes, offices, stores and other facilities. The building would also offer more than 200,000 square meters of green space, which includes the public garden at the top of the building.""In addition to the 25,000 people housed within the central residential tower, the Vertical City as a whole, including the three adjacent towers that house offices, government departments, healthcare facilities, and educational institutions, would service over 100,000 people who would travel to the city for work, school and medical care."SOURCES: The Conversation, It's Liquid, Luca Curci http://theconversation.com/explainer-what-is-photovoltaic-solar-energy-12924https://www.itsliquid.com/vertical-city.htmlhttps://www.lucacurci.com/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 03:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/10/3932998/3932998_F86484248CDC415F81C73CD3169076C2_191210_3932998_Architects_propose_self_sustainable_vertical_cit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Luca Curci Architects, Vertical City, Vertical City of the future, Buildings of tomorrow, futuristic buildings, cool architecture, cool buildings, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933744</guid>
      <title>Physics of 'tiger stripes' on Saturn Moon Enceladus explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists may have finally solved the mystery of the 'tiger stripes' on Saturn's moon Enceladus, according to a study published in Nature Astronomy.The Cassini probe first detected the four strange fractures on the moon's north pole when the spacecraft orbited around Saturn 15 years ago.According to the researchers, the 'tiger stripes' are about 130 kilometers long, with fracture lines running parallel to one another, spaced at 35 kilometers apart.Lead author Doug Hemingway at the Carnegie Institute for Science says that the fissures constantly blow out water and ice, unlike any other formation known to exist on icy moons."The gravitational force is so powerful that it changes the shape of the moon, with the resulting stress creating the first tiger stripe on Enceladus.As the moon's surface ocean erupts through the fissure, the jets of water then freeze and fall back on the moon.The weight of the accumulated ice and snow puts pressure on the nearby ice sheet and breaks the crust on parallel lines. Those fractures become the moon's stripes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The location of the tiger stripes on Saturn's moon Enceladus2. The layout of the stripes and the eruption of ice and water3. Saturn's gravity field heats the ice moon and creates the first stripe 4. Eruption from the first fissure leads to the formation of the remaining stripesVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists may have finally solved the mystery of the 'tiger stripes' on Saturn's moon Enceladus." "According to a study published in Nature Astronomy, the Cassini probe first detected the four strange fractures on the moon's north pole when the spacecraft orbited around Saturn 15 years ago.""According to the researchers, the 'tiger stripes' are about 130 kilometers long, with fracture lines running parallel to one another, spaced at 35 kilometers apart.""Lead author Doug Hemingway at the Carnegie Institute for Science says that the fissures constantly blow out water and ice, unlike any other formation known to exist on icy moons.""Because Enceladus' distance to Saturn fluctuates, planetary gravity stretches and flexes the moon. This effect generates the heat that keeps Enceladus from freezing solid.""The gravitational force is so powerful that it changes the shape of the moon, with the resulting stress creating the first tiger stripe on Enceladus.""As the moon's surface ocean erupts through the fissure, the jets of water then freeze and fall back on the moon." "The weight of the accumulated ice and snow puts pressure on the nearby ice sheet and breaks the crust on parallel lines. Those fractures become the moon's stripes."SOURCES: Nature Astronomy, Carnegie Institute for Science, Space.comhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-019-0958-xhttps://carnegiescience.edu/news/how-enceladus-got-its-stripeshttps://www.space.com/saturn-moon-enceladus-tiger-stripes-physics.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 10:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/11/3933744/3933744_7FEBA227429243B995B5A6E74E28D2C3_191211_3933744_Physics_of__tiger_stripes__on_Saturn_Moon_Encela_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Enceladus, Saturn, tiger stripes, stripes, icy moon, Carnegie, Carnegie Institute for Science, Cassini, astronomy, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933590</guid>
      <title>LED fishing nets could save turtles and dolphins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at the University of Exeter and Peruvian NGO ProDelphinus have found that by putting LED lights on top of floating commercial fishing nets, the number of critically endangered species caught in them, can be reduced by 70 percent or more.The research published in the journal Biological Conservation looked at small-scale vessels departing from three Peruvian ports between 2015 and 2018. LEDs were placed every 30 feet along the float line of 864 illuminated gillnets.Each gillnet was paired with an unlit gillnet to compare the results. Eighty-six percent of the turtles caught in the unlit nets were green turtles, however, loggerhead and olive ridley turtles were also found in the nets.Among the small cetaceans captured, 47 percent were long-beaked common dolphins, 26 percent were dusky dolphins and 24 percent were Burmeister's porpoises.The findings also support previous research which suggested LED lights reduce bycatch of seabirds in gillnets by about 85 percent.Just as warning lights warn people of danger, the animals were able to see the illuminated nets, furthermore, the light modification made no change to the amount of commercial catch fisherman caught.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gillnet with attached LEDs2. Fish avoid the deployed LED net3. Comparison between unlit and lit nets4. Fish swim into the lit netVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at the University of Exeter and Peruvian NGO ProDelphinus have found that by putting LED lights on top of floating commercial fishing nets, the number of critically endangered species caught in them, can be reduced by 70 percent or more.""The research published in the journal Biological Conservation looked at small-scale vessels departing from three Peruvian ports between 2015 and 2018. LEDs were placed every 30 feet along the float line of 864 illuminated gillnets.""Each gillnet was paired with an unlit gillnet to compare the results. Eighty-six percent of the turtles caught in the unlit nets were green turtles, however, loggerhead and olive ridley turtles were also found in the nets." "Among the small cetaceans captured, 47 percent were long-beaked common dolphins, 26 percent were dusky dolphins and 24 percent were Burmeister's porpoises." "The findings also support previous research which suggested LED lights reduce bycatch of seabirds in gillnets by about 85 percent.""Just as warning lights warn of danger, the animals were able to see the illuminated nets, furthermore, the light modification made no change to the amount of commercial catch fisherman caught."SOURCES: The Times, Biological Conservationhttps://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/endangered-marine-species-see-the-light-q5t3glklrhttps://www.exeter.ac.uk/news/research/title_769892_en.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 06:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/11/3933590/3933590_3C9AAEE30BBA42A48683D2D9E1F7B869_191211_3933590_LED_fishing_nets_could_save_turtles_and_dolphins_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, LED fishing nets, fishing nets, turtles, dolphins, LED nets save turtles, gillnets, gill fishing nets]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934399</guid>
      <title>Jersey City shooting timeline</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANInvestigators are not sure why two shooters launched a deadly attack at a New Jersey kosher grocery store, federal and state officials said on Wednesday. Reuters reports that six people, including two shooters, three civilians and a police officer, died in a series of events that ended in a police shootout on Tuesday in Jersey City. According to NBC News, New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy, Attorney General Gurbir Grewal and other law enforcement leaders at the state and federal level held a press conference Wednesday to detail what took place during the incident. According to Grewal, it is believed at some point Tuesday, 47-year-old David Anderson and 50-year-old Francine Graham encountered and killed Jersey City police Det. Joseph Seals in the Bayview Cemetery in Jersey City.At roughly 12:21 p.m., a white U-Haul van driven by Anderson parked directly across the street from the JC Kosher Supermarket. Seconds later, Anderson exited the driver side door armed with a rifle as he walked toward the supermarket and immediately began shooting. Graham, who was sitting in the passenger's side of the van, then followed Anderson into the store. Inside the supermarket, the suspects encountered four civilians. Three of these civilians were killed and one survived a gunshot wound.Around 12:38 p.m., a bystander called 911 to report Seals' body in the cemetery. Grewal said that at approximately 12:43 p.m. Jersey City Police Department personnel arrived on scene and engaged the two suspects in an hours-long shootout. At approximately 3:25 p.m., an armored police vehicle broke through the front of the supermarket. Around 3:47 p.m., law enforcement discovered Anderson and Graham's bodies inside the supermarket. According to NBC News, authorities are currently in the process of identifying all available video footage from the incident.      RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Shooters encountering police officer in cemetery2. Shooters pulling up across street from supermarket3. Anderson getting out of van and walking to store4. Graham walking toward store5. Shooters entering store6. Police moving in formation down street7. Armored vehicle crashing through front of storeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to New Jersey Attorney General Gurbir Grewal, it is believed at some point Tuesday, 47-year-old David Anderson and 50-year-old Francine Graham encountered and killed Jersey City police Det. Joseph Seals in the Bayview Cemetery in Jersey City.""At roughly 12:21 p.m., a white U-Haul van driven by Anderson parked directly across the street from the JC Kosher Supermarket." "Seconds later, Anderson exited the driver side door armed with a rifle as he walked toward the supermarket and immediately began shooting." "Graham, who was sitting in the passenger's side of the van, then followed Anderson into the store." "Inside the supermarket, the suspects encountered four civilians. Three of these civilians were killed and one survived a gunshot wound." "Grewal said that at approximately 12:43 p.m. Jersey City Police Department personnel arrived on scene and engaged the two suspects in an hours-long shootout." "At approximately 3:25 p.m., an armored police vehicle broke through the front of the supermarket." SOURCES: Reuters, NBC News, CNNhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-shooting/jersey-city-gunmen-targeted-jewish-grocery-for-lethal-attack-mayor-idUSKBN1YF0WEhttps://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/jersey-city-shooting-timeline-what-we-know-so-far/2239928/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/11/us/jersey-city-new-jersey-shooting-wednesday/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/12/3934399/3934399_33621E4E93C54FFF9F0C2664476F5AF3_191212_3934399_Jersey_City_shooting_timeline_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Jersey City shooting, Jersey City attack, Jersey City shooters, David Anderson shooter, Francine Graham shooter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934376</guid>
      <title>ClearSpace wins contract for space debris collecting spacecraft: ESA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe European Space Agency has commissioned the world's first mission to capture a piece of space debris from Earth's orbit in 2025.The ESA says that the Swiss startup ClearSpace was awarded with the contract for ClearSpace-1, a spacecraft that will sport four robotic arms for grabbing debris.According to the ESA, ClearSpace-1 will recover the VESPA, a secondary payload adapter that has been left adrift since it helped deliver the Proba-V satellite to space in 2013.The VESPA is close in size to a small satellite, and its simple shape and sturdy construction makes the adaptor a prime candidate for the experiment.ClearSpace-1 will be launched into a 500-kilometer orbit to undergo testing before it moves up to VESPA's higher orbit, which sits at an altitude of 660 by 800 kilometers.Once in position, ClearSpace-1 will utilize its quartet of arms to catch Vespa under the ESA's supervision.After ClearSpace-1 captures the target, it will return to the Earth's atmosphere and burn up with the VESPA.The ESA says it will refine the chaser's capabilities with the goal of launching follow up missions in the future, including capturing multiple objects. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. ClearSpace 1 is built by Swiss-based ClearSpace and features four robotic arms2. The 2025 mission will target VESPA, a payload adaptor from the Proba-V launch3. ClearSpace will utilize its arms to capture VESPA4. The chaser spacecraft and captured debris will return to Earth and burn up VOICEOVER (in English): "The European Space Agency has commissioned the world's first mission to capture a piece of space debris from Earth's orbit in 2025.""The ESA says that the Swiss startup ClearSpace was awarded with the contract for ClearSpace-1, a spacecraft that will sport four robotic arms for grabbing debris.""According to the ESA, ClearSpace-1 will recover the VESPA, a secondary payload adapter that has been left adrift since it helped deliver the Proba-V satellite to space in 2013.""The VESPA is close in size to a small satellite, and its simple shape and sturdy construction makes the adaptor a prime candidate for the experiment.""ClearSpace-1 will be launched into a 500-kilometer orbit to undergo testing before it moves up to VESPA's higher orbit, which sits at an altitude of 660 by 800 kilometers.""Once in position, ClearSpace-1 will utilize its quartet of arms to catch Vespa under the ESA's supervision.""After ClearSpace-1 captures the target, it will return to the Earth's atmosphere and burn up with the VESPA.""The ESA says it will refine the chaser's capabilities with the goal of launching follow up missions in the future, including capturing multiple objects."SOURCES: European Space Agency, ClearSpace Onehttp://www.esa.int/Safety_Security/Clean_Space/ESA_commissions_world_s_first_space_debris_removalhttps://clearspace.today/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 12:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/12/3934376/3934376_32BE9505929F46DE8EA8A8E25BF738E1_191212_3934376_ClearSpace_wins_contract_for_space_debris_collec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ClearSpace, Clear Space, ClearSpace-1, ClearSpace 1, space debris, VESPA, space junk, satellite, European Space Agency, ESA, space, payload adaptor, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934156</guid>
      <title>How hackers could use smart home devices to access personal data</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe FBI issued a statement earlier this month warning consumers about smart home devices that could be vulnerable to hacks.This includes smart digital assistants, smart watches, smart refrigerators, home security devices, and gaming systems.FBI officials explained in the statement that these Internet of Things devices are continuously sending and receiving data, but users are typically unaware of how the data is being collected or where exactly it is being transmitted.The agency warned that hackers may be able to conduct a "virtual drive-by" of users' digital lives if they gain access via unsecured devices. This, in turn, gives them access to a user's router and everything connected to their home network.The bureau urged users to change the default password and set unique passwords for every smart home device and store sensitive and private data on a network system separate from the IoT devices.The FBI also recommended updating smart home devices regularly, and checking permissions on mobile apps linked to the smart devices.The agency further encouraged users to turn on automatic updates for software, hardware and operating systems on their smart devices for the latest updates.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Smart home devices could be vulnerable to hacks2. IoT devices sending and receiving data to a server3. A hacker accessing a user's smart home devices and their router4. Precautions to prevent smart home devices from becoming hackedVOICEOVER (in English): "The FBI issued a statement earlier this month warning consumers about smart home devices that could be vulnerable to hacks.""This includes smart digital assistants, watches, refrigerators, home security devices, and gaming systems.""FBI officials explained that these Internet of Things devices are continuously sending and receiving data, but users are typically unaware of how the data is being collected or where exactly it is being transmitted.""The agency warned that hackers may be able to conduct a 'virtual drive-by' of users' digital lives if they gain access via unsecured devices. This, in turn, gives them access to a user's router and everything connected to their home network.""The bureau urged users to set unique passwords for every smart home device, and store sensitive and private data on a network system separate from the IoT devices.""The FBI also recommended updating smart home devices regularly, and checking permissions on mobile apps linked to the smart devices."SOURCES: FBIhttps://www.fbi.gov/contact-us/field-offices/portland/news/press-releases/tech-tuesday-internet-of-things-iot***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 07:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/12/3934156/3934156_D34692B97D674F969B9BCBC5A0B2ADD6_191212_3934156_How_hackers_could_use_smart_home_devices_to_acce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Technology, smart technology, smart home devices, smart technology 2019, smart tech spying, Internet of Things, smart devices spying, smart home devices warning, smart home devices spying]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934040</guid>
      <title>Saving ozone layer reduced climate change effects</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study from the University of New South Wales has found that in addition to allowing the ozone layer to recover, the Montreal Protocol has also slowed the rate of climate change by up to 25 percent.The Montreal Protocol is an international agreement signed by countries around the world in 1987 to stop the import and production of chemicals such as chlorofluorocarbons that are harmful to the earth's ozone layer, after an "ozone hole" was found over Antarctica.Using an estimated 3 percent increase of CFC emissions per year starting from 1987, scientists estimate the Montreal Protocol has likely already helped our planet avoid 0.5 degrees Celsius to 1 degree Celsius of temperature rise over some land areas and 3 degrees Celsius to 4 degrees Celsius of temperature rise across much of the Arctic, as of 2019.The study, published in the journal Environmental Research Letters, estimates that our planet will be at least 1 degree Celsius cooler by 2050 than it would have been had the agreement not been enacted.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the Montreal Protocol has helped to reduce the effects of climate change2. How much temperatures are estimated to have risen if the Montreal Protocol was not enacted3. Earth is estimated to be at least 1属C cooler by 2050 than it would have been4. Arctic sea ice extent is higher than it would have been5. Greenland's melting ice sheet and subsequent sea level rise is also happening at a slower paceVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study from the University of New South Wales has found that in addition to allowing the ozone layer to recover, the Montreal Protocol has also slowed the rate of climate change by up to 25 percent.""The Montreal Protocol is an international agreement signed by countries around the world in 1987 to stop the import and production of chemicals such as chlorofluorocarbons that are harmful to the earth's ozone layer, after an 'ozone hole' was found over Antarctica.""The ozone layer protects our planet by deflecting harmful radiation from the sun.""Researchers tested out two different scenarios: one in which the Montreal Protocol was brought into effect and another in which the agreement wasn't.""Using an estimated 3 percent increase of CFC emissions per year starting from 1987, scientists estimate the Montreal Protocol has likely already helped our planet avoid 0.5 degrees Celsius to 1 degree Celsius of temperature rise over some land areas and 3 degrees Celsius to 4 degrees Celsius of temperature rise across much of the Arctic, as of 2019.""The study, published in the journal Environmental Research Letters, estimates that our planet will be at least 1 degree Celsius cooler by 2050 than it would have been had the agreement not been enacted.""Researchers also found that the Arctic summer sea ice extent is roughly 25 percent higher today than it would have been otherwise.""The study also suggests that Greenland's melting ice sheet and subsequent sea level rise is happening at a slower speed."SOURCES: Environmental Research Letters, ARC Center of Excellence, University of New South Wales, Australian Government Department of the Environment and Energy, National Geographichttps://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/ab4874https://climateextremes.org.au/montreal-protocol-set-to-slow-global-warming-by-at-least-1c/https://newsroom.unsw.edu.au/news/science-tech/saving-ozone-layer-1987-slowed-global-warminghttps://www.environment.gov.au/protection/ozone/montreal-protocolhttps://www.nationalgeographic.org/encyclopedia/ozone-layer/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 04:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/12/3934040/3934040_BB2B02BD90814580BBB7D9B42BEF61A8_191212_3934040_Saving_ozone_layer_reduced_climate_change_effect_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Climate change, global warming, Montreal Protocol, ozone layer, global warming slowed, ozone depletion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934951</guid>
      <title>Sinkhole causes chaos in Xiamen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA massive sinkhole swallowed up several cars and part of a busy road intersection in Xiamen, China at 9:50 pm on Thursday, Chinese officials told China News.The state-run media reports that 500 square meters of the road had collapsed near Xiamen Metro's Lucuo Station.Social media footage on China News shows at least two cars that had fallen into the pit. Chinese officials told the outlet that all personnel trapped in the sinkhole had been rescued and that no one was injured in the incident.According to China News, an underground pipe or pipes was damaged during the incident and caused flooding to the area.Citing Chinese netizens on Weibo, Taiwan's Liberty Times speculated that the water main might have been damaged prior to the incident and had caused the collapse to occur.The incident went viral on Chinese social media and netizens posted videos of brown water inundating Lucuo station up to ankle depth.Chinese officials say that the subway system will resume normal operations by 8:30pm today.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sinkhole opens on the road and cars fall into it2. Rescuers evacuate people trapped into the pit3. Underground pipe damaged sometime around the incident4. Flooding occurred at Xiamen Metro's Lucuo stationVOICEOVER (in English): "A massive sinkhole swallowed up several cars and part of a busy road intersection in Xiamen, China at 9:50 pm on Thursday.""According to state-run media China News, 500 square meters of the road had collapsed near Xiamen Metro's Lucuo Station.""A nearby dash cam captured this footage of the incident moments before the road collapsed.""Social media footage on China News shows at least two cars that had fallen into the pit.""Chinese officials told the outlet that all personnel trapped in the sinkhole had been rescued and that no one was injured in the incident.""According to China News, an underground pipe or pipes was damaged during the incident and caused flooding to the area.""Citing Chinese netizens on Weibo, Taiwan's Liberty Times speculated that the water main might have been damaged prior to the incident and had caused the collapse to occur.""The incident went viral on Chinese social media and netizens posted videos of brown water inundating Lucuo station up to ankle depth.""Chinese officials say that the subway system will resume normal operations by 8:30pm today."SOURCES: Beijing News, Liberty Times, Amoy Transit Rail (Weibo), China Newshttp://www.bjnews.com.cn/news/2019/12/13/661333.htmlhttps://news.ltn.com.tw/amp/news/world/breakingnews/3007554https://www.weibo.com/u/3108927017?is_hot=1http://www.chinanews.com/sh/2019/12-13/9032631.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 11:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/13/3934951/3934951_4E8DE9D983884B77BD3714D62D4D595A_191213_3934951_Sinkhole_causes_chaos_in_Xiamen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sinkhole, collapse, cars, subway, Xiamen, China, Xiamen metro, amtr]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934820</guid>
      <title>New recluse spider species discovered in Mexico Valley: biologists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBiologists at the National Autonomous University of Mexico said they have discovered a new species of recluse spiders named Loxosceles tenochtitlan in Mexico Valley.Quoting a researcher, El Universal reports that the spider has a distinctive dark brown coloring and a clear violin pattern on its dorsal section.According to the university's press release, the spider is set apart from other recluse spiders by its sensing appendages and sexual organs of its females.The spider also possesses a venomous bite that it utilizes as a defense mechanism.The bite causes a blue-purple ulcer on the victim that could be hard to identify clinically because it is not painful and symptoms could be confused with a common rash or infection.Biologist Valdez-Mondragon told El Universal that the spider lives in urban homes because the environment provides suitable humidity, heat and prey.The spider favors hiding in tight spots and eats cockroaches, so they could be encountered in trash cans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Loxosceles tenochtitlan spider and its violin pattern2. Spider palp, abdomen, venom fangs 3. Bite victim could develop ulcers4. Explain why the spider could live in urban domiciles VOICEOVER (in English): "Biologists at the National Autonomous University of Mexico said they have discovered a new species of recluse spiders named Loxosceles tenochtitlan in Mexico Valley.""Quoting a researcher, El Universal reports that the spider has a distinctive dark brown coloring and a clear violin pattern on its dorsal section.""According to the university's press release, the spider is set apart from other recluse spiders by its sensing appendages and sexual organs of its females.""The spider also possesses a venomous bite that it utilizes as a defense mechanism.""The bite causes a blue-purple ulcer on the victim that could be hard to identify clinically because it is not painful and symptoms could be confused with a common rash or infection.""Biologist Valdez-Mondragon told El Universal that the spider lives in urban homes because the environment provides suitable humidity, heat and prey.""The spider favors hiding in tight spots and eats cockroaches, so they could be encountered in trash cans."SOURCES: The National Autonomous University of Mexico,  El Universalhttps://www.gaceta.unam.mx/descubren-especie-de-arana-violinista-nativa/https://www.eluniversal.com.mx/english/new-recluse-spider-species-discovered-mexico***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/13/3934820/3934820_72710E2561994CEDB184A73944D36A14_191213_3934820_New_recluse_spider_species_discovered_in_Mexico__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Loxosceles tenochtitlan, spider, recluse spiders, violin spiders, venom, science, biology, Mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935271</guid>
      <title>Researchers break down plastic using sunlight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at Singapore's Nanyang Technological University this week said they have found a way to use sunlight to turn consumer plastic into a valuable chemical that could generate clean power. They reported their findings in the journal Advanced Science.Speaking in a university news release, the team said it dissolved polyethylene in a solution that contained a vanadium-based catalyst.Vanadium is a metal commonly used in steel and aluminum alloys for vehicles and aircraft.The researchers exposed the solution to artificial sunlight, which breaks the carbon bonds in polyethylene and transforms the substance into formic acid.While other conversion methods exist, the scientists said their process does not use high heat or toxic substances to produce formic acid from plastics.They explained that formic acid is utilized for power generation in hydrogen fuel cells which could be a low-emissions source of clean energy.The researchers say they are working to scale up the technology to help Singapore to turn its plastic waste into energy resources without harming the environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study claims plastics could be converted to chemicals used for energy generation2. Researchers use a vanadium-based catalyst in plastic solution3. Artificial sunlight converts the plastic solution to formic acid4. The process does not utilize toxic chemicals or high heatVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at Singapore's Nanyang Technological University this week said they have found a way to use sunlight to turn consumer plastic into a valuable chemical that could generate clean power.""They reported their findings in the journal Advanced Science.""Speaking in a university news release, the team said it dissolved polyethylene in a solution that contained a vanadium-based catalyst.""Vanadium is a metal commonly used in steel and aluminum alloys for vehicles and aircraft.""The researchers exposed the solution to artificial sunlight, which breaks the carbon bonds in polyethylene and transforms the substance into formic acid.""While other conversion methods exist, the scientists said their process does not use high heat or toxic substances to produce formic acid from plastics.""They explained that formic acid is utilized for power generation in hydrogen fuel cells which could be a low-emissions source of clean energy.""The researchers say they are working to scale up the technology to help Singapore to turn its plastic waste into energy resources without harming the environment."SOURCES: Advanced Science, Nanyang Technological Universityhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/advs.201902020 https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-12/ntu-nss121119.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 08:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/14/3935271/3935271_5DEB254E00214DA4923486477AA2DF5A_191214_3935271_Researchers_break_down_plastic_using_sunlight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935173</guid>
      <title>Researchers break down plastic using sunlight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at Singapore's Nanyang Technological University this week said they have found a way to use sunlight to turn consumer plastic into a valuable chemical that could generate clean power. They reported their findings in the journal Advanced Science.Speaking in a university news release, the team said it dissolved polyethylene in a solution that contained a vanadium-based catalyst.Vanadium is a metal commonly used in steel and aluminum alloys for vehicles and aircraft.The researchers exposed the solution to artificial sunlight, which breaks the carbon bonds in polyethylene and transforms the substance into formic acid.While other conversion methods exist, the scientists said their process does not use high heat or toxic substances to produce formic acid from plastics.They explained that formic acid is utilized for power generation in hydrogen fuel cells which could be a low-emissions source of clean energy.The researchers say they are working to scale up the technology to help Singapore to turn its plastic waste into energy resources without harming the environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study claims plastics could be converted to chemicals used for energy generation2. Researchers use a vanadium-based catalyst in plastic solution3. Artificial sunlight converts the plastic solution to formic acid4. The process does not utilize toxic chemicals or high heatVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at Singapore's Nanyang Technological University this week said they have found a way to use sunlight to turn consumer plastic into a valuable chemical that could generate clean power.""They reported their findings in the journal Advanced Science.""Speaking in a university news release, the team said it dissolved polyethylene in a solution that contained a vanadium-based catalyst.""Vanadium is a metal commonly used in steel and aluminum alloys for vehicles and aircraft.""The researchers exposed the solution to artificial sunlight, which breaks the carbon bonds in polyethylene and transforms the substance into formic acid.""While other conversion methods exist, the scientists said their process does not use high heat or toxic substances to produce formic acid from plastics.""They explained that formic acid is utilized for power generation in hydrogen fuel cells which could be a low-emissions source of clean energy.""The researchers say they are working to scale up the technology to help Singapore to turn its plastic waste into energy resources without harming the environment."SOURCES: Advanced Science, Nanyang Technological Universityhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/advs.201902020 https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-12/ntu-nss121119.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 03:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/14/3935173/3935173_A2BC29FEE0CA4539AFEE71E3EDFC10ED_191214_3935173_Researchers_break_down_plastic_using_sunlight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936202</guid>
      <title>'Impossibly big' black hole not as big as previously calculated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo new studies have called into question the size of the "impossibly big" black hole named LB-1, according to papers published independently to the arXiv database.A team led by Chinese astronomer Liu Jinfeng claimed that LB-1 is 70 times the mass of the sun, bigger than the 20-solar-mass models predicted for black holes in our galaxy.'The papers found the same basic problem with the Chinese researchers claim: it relied on evidence that the unseen black hole was wiggling very slightly as its heavy companion star wheeled around it. The new studies claim that the initial team misinterpreted what they were seeing in the light from the distant system.Movements from LB-1 create spectral light via doppler effect called H alpha line emissions.The Chinese team used China's powerful LAMOST telescope to detect H alpha line emissions, then used the black hole's movements to infer its mass.The authors of the new studies argue that the original team did not properly adjust for the emissions from LB1's star, which also emits H alpha, according to Live Science.Astrophysicists El-Badry and Quataert write in their paper that after factoring in the star, the data suggests LB1 is far more likely to be a sun-sized black hole.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  An introduction to LB-12.  The original research team's method of gauging LB-1's size 3.  China's telescope LAMOST was utilized to detect H alpha emissions4.  New studies claim original team did not take LB-1's companion star into accountVOICEOVER (in English): "Live Science reports that two independently published studies have called into question the size of the "impossibly big" black hole named LB-1.""A team led by Chinese astronomer Liu Jinfeng claimed that LB-1 is 70 times the mass of the sun, bigger than the 20-solar-mass models predicted for black holes in our galaxy.'""Two independent papers published to the arXiv database found the same basic problem with the Chinese researchers claim: it relied on evidence that the unseen black hole was wiggling very slightly as its heavy companion star wheeled around it." "The new studies claim that the initial team misinterpreted what they were seeing in the light from the distant system." "Movements from LB-1 create spectral light via doppler effect called H alpha line emissions.""The team said used China's powerful LAMOST telescope to detect H alpha line emissions, then used the black hole's movements to infer its mass.""Live Science reports that authors of the new studies argue that the original team did not properly adjust for the emissions from LB1's star, which also emits H alpha.""Astrophysicists El-Badry and Quataert write in their paper that after factoring in the star, the data suggests LB1 is far more likely to be a sun-sized black hole."SOURCES:  LiveScience, arXiv, Nature, Chinese Academy of Sciences (EurekAlert)https://www.livescience.com/impossibly-huge-black-hole-debunked.htmlhttps://arxiv.org/pdf/1912.04185.pdfhttps://arxiv.org/ftp/arxiv/papers/1912/1912.04092.pdfhttps://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-11/caos-cao112519.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/16/3936202/3936202_0E7657DCA43B4AAF8C98399457DBFC25_191216_3936202__Impossibly_big__black_hole_not_as_big_as_previo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Black hole, monster black hole, stellar black hole, LB-1, LB1, milky way galaxy, galaxy, Chinese Academy of Sciences, LAMOST, h alpha line, h alpha emission, space, astronomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935826</guid>
      <title>Stressed out plants emit sounds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from Tel Aviv University has found that plants make noise when stressed.For the study, scientists focused on tomato and tobacco plants. They placed plants into three groups. These were drought-stressed plants, plants cut at the stem and control plants. These were placed in an acoustic box for an hour.Each plant was recorded with two microphones placed 10 centimeters away.On average, drought-stressed tomato plants emitted roughly 35 ultrasonic sounds per hour, while tobacco plants produced 11 per hour. Cut tomato plants created roughly 25 sounds per hour, while tobacco plants generated 15.The study found that all control plants produced, on average, less than one sound per hour.The scientists explained in the study that these sounds could potentially be heard by other organisms up to several meters away.The tomato plants were also placed in a greenhouse setting to test whether or not sounds emitted by plants would be identified outdoors. The results matched researchers' findings from the plants in the acoustic box in that plants produce more sounds as they become dehydrated.Machine learning classifiers were able to distinguish distinct noises produced by the different plants in both the acoustic box and the greenhouse setting.Researchers suggested that in the future, farmers may be able to use this type of technology to listen out for drought-stressed crops to better assess their crops.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Stressed out tomato and tobacco plants make noise2. Plants were divided into groups and placed in an acoustic box3. How many ultrasonic sounds the different plant groups produced4. The tomato plants were also tested in a greenhouse settingVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from Tel Aviv University has found that plants make noise when stressed.""For the study, scientists focused on tomato and tobacco plants.""They placed plants into three groups. These were drought-stressed plants, plants cut at the stem and control plants. These were placed in an acoustic box for an hour.""Each plant was recorded with two microphones placed 10 centimeters away.""On average, drought-stressed tomato plants emitted roughly 35 ultrasonic sounds per hour, while tobacco plants produced 11 per hour.""Cut tomato plants created roughly 25 sounds per hour, while tobacco plants generated 15.""The study found that all control plants produced, on average, less than one sound per hour.""The tomato plants were also placed in a greenhouse setting to test whether or not sounds emitted by plants would be identified outdoors.""The results matched researchers' findings from the plants in the acoustic box in that plants produce more sounds as they become dehydrated.""Machine learning classifiers were able to distinguish distinct noises produced by the different plants in both the acoustic box and the greenhouse setting."SOURCES: BioRxiv, Live Science, New Scientisthttps://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/507590v4https://www.livescience.com/plants-squeal-when-stressed.htmlhttps://www.newscientist.com/article/2226093-recordings-reveal-that-plants-make-ultrasonic-squeals-when-stressed/?utm_source=NSDAY&utm_campaign=2f2ba57333-NSDAY_061219&utm_medium=email&utm_term=0_1254aaab7a-2f2ba57333-374016483***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 02:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/16/3935826/3935826_2C1B036378A74B9D91A13F2618E7DF2C_191216_3935826_Stressed_out_plants_emit_sounds_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Plants, plants under stress, plant stress, plant stress sounds, plant sounds, tobacco plants, airborne sounds plants, tomato plants, plants make ultrasonic noises]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936795</guid>
      <title>NASA selects asteroid target site for spacecraft to sample</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has selected a target site for the spacecraft  OSIRIS[c]-REx[d] to gather samples on the asteroid Bennu, according to the mission's principal investigator Dante Lauretta.In a statement made at the American Geophysical Union annual conference last week, Lauretta said the spacecraft has been orbiting Bennu since December 2018.Lauretta says that Nightingale lies far to the asteroid's north, with cooler temperatures than other possible sites.This means Nightingale's surface would preserve more materials dated back to Bennu's formation for the probe to collect.Citing Lauretta, Science News reports that Nightingale is a 20-meter wide crater contained in a larger crater and that parking the six-meter wide spacecraft could be a "tight fit". The New York Times reports that Bennu is one of the oldest rocks in the solar system and that the asteroid is rich in carbon and organic substances like hydrated minerals. The spacecraft will touch down on Bennu for only a split-second next year and deploy its robotic arm to gather a sample.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. OSIRIS-REx orbiting asteroid Bennu 2. NASA's reasons for selecting Nightgale as sample gathering site3. The dimension of the site and difficulties with landing the spacecraft4. The probe collect samples from the asteroid with robotic armVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has selected a target site for the spacecraft  OSIRIS[e]-REx[f] to gather samples on the asteroid Bennu.""In a statement made at the American Geophysical Union annual conference last week, the mission's principal investigator Dante Lauretta said the spacecraft has been orbiting Bennu since December 2018.""Lauretta says that Nightingale lies far to the asteroid's north, with cooler temperatures than other possible sites.""This means Nightingale's surface would preserve more materials dated back to Bennu's formation for the probe to collect.""Citing Lauretta, Science News reports that Nightingale is a 20-meter wide crater contained in a larger crater and that parking the six-meter wide spacecraft could be a 'tight fit'." "The New York Times reports that Bennu is one of the oldest rocks in the solar system and that the asteroid is rich in carbon and organic substances like hydrated minerals.""The spacecraft will touch down on Bennu for only a split-second next year and deploy its robotic arm to gather a sample."SOURCES: Science News, The New York Timeshttps://www.sciencenews.org/article/nasa-has-picked-osiris-rex-landing-site-asteroid-bennuhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/12/science/osiris-rex-nasa-asteroid-bennu.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/17/3936795/3936795_824EAB3B90014E91B6621CD0C4878EF1_191217_3936795_NASA_selects_asteroid_target_site_for_spacecraft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Osiris-rex, Osiris, spacecraft, space probe, probe, asteroid, asteroid Bennu, Bennu, nightingale,  NASA, US, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936780</guid>
      <title>NASA reveals plans for antennas on far side of moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpace researchers have proposed building a network of radio antennas on the far side of the moon, according to a NASA funded report.NASA says that the arraynamed the Farside antennaswill allow the agency to monitor the closest stellar systems more easily.The paper's lead authors professors Jack Burns and Gregg Hallinan suggest deploying 128 antennas by using a lunar rover.The antennas will be tethered to a base station that supplies central data processing, power and communications across the array's 10 kilometer span.The Farside base then will use NASA's proposed Gateway Station to transmit signals back to Earth.Habitable exoplanets closest to the solar system would possess magnetospheres that the antennas will be able to detect from the moon's far side, where there is limited sky noise.The study states that the antennas could also sound the moon's subsurface.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA plans for building antennas on moon's farside2. Lunar rover will deploy antennas tethered to moon station 3. Farside antennas will utilize Planned Gateway Station to link antenna the earth4. Farside antennas will detect habitable exoplanets, scan moon subsurfaceFarside antennas will detect habitable exoplanets, scan moon subsurfaceVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a NASA funded report, space researchers have proposed building a network of radio antennas on the far side of the moon.""NASA says that the arraynamed the Farside antennaswill allow the agency to monitor the closest stellar systems more easily.""The paper's lead authors professors Jack Burns and Gregg Hallinan suggest deploying 128 antennas by using a lunar rover.""The antennas will be tethered to a base station that supplies central data processing, power and communications across the array's 10 kilometer span.""The Farside base then will use NASA's proposed Gateway Station to transmit signals back to Earth.""Habitable exoplanets closest to the solar system would possess magnetospheres that the antennas will be able to detect from the moon's far side, where there is limited sky noise.""The study states that the antennas could also sound the moon's subsurface."SOURCES: Amazon Web Services (NASA), Space.comhttps://smd-prod.s3.amazonaws.com/science-red/s3fs-public/atoms/files/FARSIDE_FinalRpt-2019-Nov8.pdfhttps://www.space.com/farside-moon-radio-astronomy-mission-concept.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/17/3936780/3936780_80E822CD5432483696FC9845659B3902_191217_3936780_NASA_reveals_plans_for_antennas_on_far_side_of_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Farside antennas, low frequency antennas, farside project, far side of the moon, exoplanets, exoplanet, deep space, space, space exploration, Blue Origins, US, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936611</guid>
      <title>Ocean contains a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study from the Scripps Institution of Oceanography at the University of California San Diego suggests that the ocean could potentially contain a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought.Researchers say that past methods used for collecting microplastic samples, such as net tows, were inadequate as smaller plastic particles are able to escape through the holes of the net.For the study, the team developed a new technique to gather microplastics from the ocean surface.Researchers took three different cruises during three different time periods between 2009 to 2015 to gather surface seawater samples in metal buckets from the open ocean and near the shore. The samples were promptly filtered with polycarbonate filters and then frozen.Scientists also gathered 100 salp samples from the sea in 2009, 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2017 using mesh bongo nets. The study found that nearshore samples of seawater had a higher concentration of plastic than samples obtained from the open sea. Researchers then analysed the salps via epifluorescence microscopy and found that every single salp sample contained tiny microplastic pieces in their gut.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ocean filled with microplastics2. Previous methods used to collect microplastic sample3. New technique to gather seawater samples from the ocean4. Gathering salp samples from the sea5. Results of the studyVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study from the Scripps Institution of Oceanography at the University of California San Diego suggests that the ocean could potentially contain a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought.""Researchers say that past methods used for collecting microplastic samples, such as net tows, were inadequate as smaller plastic particles are able to escape through the holes of the net.""For the study, the team developed a new technique to gather microplastics from the ocean surface." "Researchers took three different cruises during three different time periods between 2009 to 2015 to gather surface seawater samples in metal buckets from the open ocean and near the shore. The samples were promptly filtered with polycarbonate filters and then frozen.""Scientists also gathered 100 salp samples from the sea in 2009, 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2017 using mesh bongo nets. Salps are gelatinous creatures that suck in seawater for food as well as to propel themselves in the ocean.""The study found that nearshore samples of seawater had a higher concentration of plastic than samples obtained from the open sea.""Researchers then analysed the salps via epifluorescence microscopy and found that every single salp sample contained tiny microplastic pieces in their gut.""Scientists estimated that the sea is contaminated by roughly 8.3 million pieces of 'mini-microplastics,' or the smallest microplastics, per cubic meter of water."SOURCES: National Science Foundation, Fox News, Limnology and Oceanography Letters, University of California San Diegohttps://phys.org/news/2019-12-microplastics-million-abundant-ocean-previously.htmlhttps://www.foxnews.com/science/oceans-a-million-times-microplastic-than-we-realizedhttps://aslopubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/lol2.10127https://scripps.ucsd.edu/news/microplastics-million-times-more-abundant-ocean-previously-thought-scripps-study-suggests***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 09:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/17/3936611/3936611_96C1E21BC555494C8806A2F47A1A08AA_191217_3936611_Ocean_contains_a_million_times_more_microplastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Microplastics, microplastic contamination, microplastics in the ocean, microplastics ocean pollution, plastic fiber, microscopic plastic, mini-microplastics, plastic pollution, plastic particles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936603</guid>
      <title>Ocean contains a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study from the Scripps Institution of Oceanography at the University of California San Diego suggests that the ocean could potentially contain a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought.Researchers say that past methods used for collecting microplastic samples, such as net tows, were inadequate as smaller plastic particles are able to escape through the holes of the net.For the study, the team developed a new technique to gather microplastics from the ocean surface.Researchers took three different cruises during three different time periods between 2009 to 2015 to gather surface seawater samples in metal buckets from the open ocean and near the shore. The samples were promptly filtered with polycarbonate filters and then frozen.Scientists also gathered 100 salp samples from the sea in 2009, 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2017 using mesh bongo nets. Salps are gelatinous creatures that suck in seawater for food as well as to propel themselves in the ocean.The study found that nearshore samples of seawater had a higher concentration of plastic than samples obtained from the open sea. Researchers then analysed the salps via epifluorescence microscopy and found that every single salp sample contained tiny microplastic pieces in their gut.Scientists estimated that the sea is contaminated by roughly 8.3 million pieces of "mini-microplastics," or the smallest microplastics, per cubic meter of water.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ocean filled with microplastics2. Previous methods used to collect microplastic sample3. New technique to gather seawater samples from the ocean4. Gathering salp samples from the sea5. Results of the studyVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study from the Scripps Institution of Oceanography at the University of California San Diego suggests that the ocean could potentially contain a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought.""Researchers say that past methods used for collecting microplastic samples, such as net tows, were inadequate as smaller plastic particles are able to escape through the holes of the net.""For the study, the team developed a new technique to gather microplastics from the ocean surface." "Researchers took three different cruises during three different time periods between 2009 to 2015 to gather surface seawater samples in metal buckets from the open ocean and near the shore. The samples were promptly filtered with polycarbonate filters and then frozen.""Scientists also gathered 100 salp samples from the sea in 2009, 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2017 using mesh bongo nets. Salps are gelatinous creatures that suck in seawater for food as well as to propel themselves in the ocean.""The study found that nearshore samples of seawater had a higher concentration of plastic than samples obtained from the open sea.""Researchers then analysed the salps via epifluorescence microscopy and found that every single salp sample contained tiny microplastic pieces in their gut.""Scientists estimated that the sea is contaminated by roughly 8.3 million pieces of 'mini-microplastics,' or the smallest microplastics, per cubic meter of water."SOURCES: National Science Foundation, Fox News, Limnology and Oceanography Letters, University of California San Diegohttps://phys.org/news/2019-12-microplastics-million-abundant-ocean-previously.htmlhttps://www.foxnews.com/science/oceans-a-million-times-microplastic-than-we-realizedhttps://aslopubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/lol2.10127https://scripps.ucsd.edu/news/microplastics-million-times-more-abundant-ocean-previously-thought-scripps-study-suggests***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 09:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/17/3936603/3936603_3F406817F4194C77A5714530104BE7A0_191217_3936603_Ocean_contains_a_million_times_more_microplastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Microplastics, microplastic contamination, microplastics in the ocean, microplastics ocean pollution, plastic fiber, microscopic plastic, mini-microplastics, plastic pollution, plastic particles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936389</guid>
      <title>Facebook shows consumers ads based on their offline shopping habits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook is able to gather data about user shopping habits, both online and offline, in order to serve targeted ads on its platform, according to a new report by Business Insider.The report says that Facebook acquires information about user purchases via its partnerships with retailers.It explains that when a consumer buys a product from a physical or online store, the retailer can retain purchase details and user information such as name, email, or phone number.This could be sent to Facebook if they want to display targeted ads to the consumer.Facebook then matches the information to a user's profile and starts displaying ads from the retail stores directly to the consumer.The company says this allows them to create a custom audience from the acquired information, allowing them to show targeted ads to Facebook users that have shopped at the store.According to Business Insider, retailers such as Macy's and Dick's Sporting Goods are using these advertising techniques to increase sales.The report mentioned that Facebook users have the option of opting out of targeted ads, by clicking the 'Not allowed' option on their Facebook ad setting page.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How Facebook gather data about online and offline shopping habits of users2. A consumer purchasing a clothing item and their information being sent to Facebook3. Facebook matches the information with a user's profile and starts showing targetted ads4. How users can opt outVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook is able to gather data about user shopping habits, both online and offline, in order to serve targeted ads on its platform.""A new report by Business Insider says that Facebook acquires information about user purchases via its partnerships with retailers.""The report explains that when a consumer buys a product from a physical or online store, the retailer can retain purchase details and user information such as name, email, or phone number."This could be sent to Facebook if they want to display targeted ads to the consumer.""Facebook then matches the information to a user's profile and starts displaying ads from the retail stores directly to the consumer.""The company says this allows them to create a custom audience from the acquired information, allowing them to show targeted ads to Facebook users that have shopped at the store.""The report mentioned that Facebook users have the option of opting out of targeted ads, by clicking the 'Not allowed' option on their Facebook ad setting page."SOURCES: Business Insiderhttps://www.businessinsider.com/facebook-learns-what-you-buy-at-physical-stores-ads-explained-2019-12***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 02:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/17/3936389/3936389_B7CE9A34F7C44AE79E5A873B4F0E4FF1_191217_3936389_Facebook_shows_consumers_ads_based_on_their_offl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Facebook, Facebook ads 2019, facebook controversies, facebook scandals, facebook hidden codes,  facebook privacy,  Facebook tracking, facebook ads privacy, facebook tracks users offline]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937361</guid>
      <title>NASA greenlights final assembly of Lockheed Martin's quiet supersonic jet prototype</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has cleared the final assembly of Lockheed Martin's quiet supersonic jet prototype, the agency said in a news release on Tuesday.Lockheed Martin says that X-59 aircraft will be a model for quiet, faster-than-sound passenger jets.Lockheed Martin states that the X-59 will be able to cruise at an altitude of 55,000 feet and achieve an airspeed of 940 miles per hour.The corporation claims technology derived from the jet will cut air travel time by half.According to NASA, the X-59's shape is specially designed to mitigate sonic boom by reducing the noise that reaches the ground.Lockheed Martin says that the airplane makes 75 Perceived Level decibels, or about as loud as a closing car door.According to NASA, the jet will feature cameras and sensors that allow safe flying without a forward-facing window.NASA says the finished jet will fly over select US communities to create instrument readings and to measure public opinion to the fly overs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The X-59 is a technology demonstrator for quiet supersonic jet airliners2. The prototype's claimed cruise altitude and airspeed 3. The jet's shape is designed to reduce sonic boom noise levels during flight4. Cockpit sensor features and noise level tests are plannedVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA says it has cleared the final assembly of Lockheed Martin's quiet supersonic jet prototype.""Lockheed Martin says that X-59 aircraft will be a model for quiet, faster-than-sound passenger jets.""Lockheed Martin states that the X-59 will be able to cruise at an altitude of 55,000 feet and achieve an airspeed of 940 miles per hour.""The corporation claims technology derived from the jet will cut air travel time by half.""According to NASA, the X-59's shape is specially designed to mitigate sonic boom by reducing the noise that reaches the ground.""Lockheed Martin says that the airplane makes 75 Perceived Level decibels, or about as loud as a closing car door.""According to NASA, the jet will feature cameras and sensors that allow safe flying without a forward-facing window.""NASA says the finished jet will fly over select US communities to create instrument readings and to measure the public's opinion."SOURCES:  NASA, Lockheed Martinhttps://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-s-x-59-quiet-supersonic-research-aircraft-cleared-for-final-assemblyhttps://www.lockheedmartin.com/en-us/products/quesst.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/18/3937361/3937361_5B895956D1A24EC49DF9B3A0F8B40DB0_191218_3937361_NASA_greenlights_final_assembly_of_Lockheed_Mart_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, X-59, X59, prototype, quiet jet, supersonic jet, jet prototype, supersonic, Lockheed Martin, Lockheed, US, NASA, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937676</guid>
      <title>Sloped toilets proposed to reduce long bathroom breaks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBritish company StandardToilet has unveiled a new design in which the toilet is tilted downwards at a 13 degree angle in a bid to reduce the amount of time spent in the bathroom.The design has been approved by the British Toilet Association, an organization that advocates for better toilet facilities across the United Kingdom.Founder of the StandardToilet, Mahabir Gill, explained to Wired that the toilet is designed to cause strain on the legs, like squat thrusts, and make you want to get up after about five minutes of use.The company says the toilet provides health benefits such as reducing haemorrhoids, musculoskeletal disorder and improving a person's posture.The company's website states that the toilet uses a water saving dual-flush system and includes specially designed slots in the toilet's rim that would allow for a quieter, more uniform flush.In a press release from the British Toilet Association, StandardToilet explains that the toilet would reduce long lines for public bathrooms in shopping malls, train stations and other public spaces.The company also says the toilet's new design would minimize the amount of time employees spend in the restroom during bathroom breaks. In the press release, StandardToilet noted that the workplace bathroom has become a space for texting and using social media.The company's founder told Wired that the toilet would mainly benefit employers not employees, with a primary focus on reducing the amount of time spent by employees on their phone while working.The toilet is currently being sold for 贈150 to 贈500, or roughly US$196 to US$655.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New toilet design which tilts downwards2. Why the toilet is designed this way3. Features of the toilet4. The design is meant to minimize the amount of time spent in bathroomsVOICEOVER (in English): "British company StandardToilet has unveiled a new design in which the toilet is tilted downwards at a 13 degree angle in a bid to reduce the amount of time spent in the bathroom.""The design has been approved by the British Toilet Association, an organization that advocates for better toilet facilities across the United Kingdom.""Founder of the StandardToilet, Mahabir Gill, explained to Wired that the toilet is designed to cause strain on the legs, like squat thrusts, and make you want to get up after about five minutes of use.""The company says the toilet provides health benefits such as reducing haemorrhoids, musculoskeletal disorder and improving a person's posture.""The company's website states that the toilet uses a water saving dual-flush system and includes specially designed slots in the toilet's rim that would allow for a quieter, more uniform flush.""In a press release from the British Toilet Association, StandardToilet explains that the toilet would reduce long lines for public bathrooms in shopping malls, train stations and other public spaces.""The company also says the toilet's new design would minimize the amount of time employees spend in the restroom during bathroom breaks. In the press release, StandardToilet noted that the workplace bathroom has become a space for texting and using social media."SOURCES: British Toilet Association, StandardToilet, Wiredhttp://www.btaloos.co.uk/?p=2134https://www.standardtoilet.net/application.htmlhttps://www.standardtoilet.net/product-specifications.htmlhttps://www.wired.co.uk/article/battle-toilet-workplace***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/19/3937676/3937676_FCC7998D22F74B1587CC3E4CA1F8C7AD_191219_3937676_Sloped_toilets_proposed_to_reduce_long_bathroom__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Toilets, downward-tilting toilets, StandardToilet, tilting toilet, tilting toilet seat, new toilet design, reinvented toilets]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3938455</guid>
      <title>President Trump impeached, set to face trial in Senate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDonald Trump has now been officially impeached, making him the third U.S. president after Andrew Johnson and Bill Clinton to face removal from office.According to CNN, the House of Representatives on Wednesday voted to impeach President Trump on two articles of impeachment: abuse of power and obstruction of Congress.The article on abuse of power accused Trump of withholding aid to pressure Ukraine into investigating his political rival Joe Biden. It passed 230 votes to 197, with only two Democrats opposing.The second article, which passed 229 to 198, charged Trump over his refusal to cooperate with the impeachment inquiry and his urging of witnesses and government agencies to do the same.CBS reports that the next steps would be for Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi to name the impeachment managers that will argue to case to senators, and transmit the impeachment articles to Senate.According to the New York Times, Pelosi has suggested that the House might delay sending the articles to the Senate, in order to negotiate the terms of the proceedings.The BBC reports that this could put off the trial for an indefinite amount of time, effectively denying Trump the acquittal he expects.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Trump impeached by House2. Vote on first impeachment article3. Vote on second impeachment article4. Impeachment managers, sending articles to Senate5. Senate trial6. Two-thirds majority needed to convict7. Republicans control Senate8. Pelosi to delay sending impeachment articlesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNN, the House of Representatives on Wednesday voted to impeach President Trump on two articles of impeachment: abuse of power and obstruction of Congress.""The article on abuse of power accused Trump of withholding aid to pressure Ukraine into investigating his political rival Joe Biden.""It passed 230 votes to 197, with only two Democrats opposing.""The second article, which passed 229 to 198, charged Trump over his refusal to cooperate with the impeachment inquiry and his urging of witnesses and government agencies to do the same.""CBS reports that the next steps would be for Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi to name the impeachment managers that will argue to case to senators, and transmit the impeachment articles to Senate.""A trial will then be held in the Senate, presided over by the Supreme Court Chief Justice, with senators acting as jury.""A two-thirds majority vote is needed to remove Trump from office.""But with the Republicans controlling the Senate with at least a 51-seat majority, and Senate leader Mitch McConnell claiming he's working with the White House, the president will likely be exonerated.""According to the New York Times, Pelosi has suggested that the House might delay sending the articles to the Senate, in order to negotiate the terms of the proceedings."SOURCES: CNN, New York Times, BBC, CBShttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/18/politics/impeachment-watch-december-18/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/18/us/politics/trump-impeached.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50840934https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-vote-house-of-representatives-articles-of-impeachment-2019-12-19/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/20/3938455/3938455_5E52302D4E53403EA4165DCEBB2A60C2_191220_3938455_President_Trump_impeached__set_to_face_trial_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump impeachment, Trump impeached, Donald Trump, impeachment, presidential impeachment, impeachment inquiry, us president, us impeachment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3938223</guid>
      <title>NASA's Mars 2020 rover successfully completes its first test drive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs part of NASA's preparation for next year's Mars mission, the Mars 2020 rover took its first driving test at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory in California on December 17.The rover was able to roll forward, backward and perform a pirouette in the laboratory over a period of 10 hours, according to NASA. The Mars 2020 rover was also able to drive over small ramps in the lab.The rover is equipped with an autonomous navigation system, which uses high-resolution navigation cameras and image processing software. Its wheels have been redesigned for added durability.NASA says the technology will allow to rover to drive roughly 200 meters per Martian day. The Mars 2020 rover will also carry a radar imager to gather data about Mars' surface.The rover will be launched in July or August of 2020. It is scheduled to land on Mars' Jerozo Crater on February of 2021.The Mars mission is part of a larger project that includes lunar missions to prepare humans to eventually explore the red planet.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mars 2020 rover's first driving test2. Different tests the rover performed3. Features of the rover4. The rover driving on Mars' surface5. The rover collecting data about Mars' surfaceVOICEOVER (in English): "As part of NASA's preparation for next year's Mars mission, the Mars 2020 rover took its first driving test at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory in California on December 17.""According to NASA, the rover was able to roll forward, backward and perform a pirouette in the laboratory over a period of 10 hours.""The Mars 2020 rover was also able to drive over small ramps in the lab.""The rover is equipped with an autonomous navigation system, which uses high-resolution navigation cameras and image processing software. Its wheels have been redesigned for added durability.""NASA says the technology will allow to rover to drive roughly 200 meters per Martian day.""The Mars 2020 rover will also carry a radar imager to gather data about Mars' surface."SOURCES: New Atlas, NASAhttps://newatlas.com/space/mars-2020-rover-first-test-drive/https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7563***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 09:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/20/3938223/3938223_579E37A8589C49CFA4CC8162A43E76F1_191220_3938223_NASA_s_Mars_2020_rover_successfully_completes_it_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mars 2020, Mars 2020 rover, mars rover, nasa mars rover 2020, nasa mars rover Mars rover, Mars mission, nasa Mars mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3938000</guid>
      <title>Volcanic climate change pre-asteroid impact may have contributed to dinosaur extinction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in Nature Communications has found evidence that another event may have contributed to the extinction of the dinosaurs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid hitting Earth2. Impact did not directly kill off dinosaurs3. Sulfur vaporized into atmosphere causes global cooling4. Global climate change killed dinosaurs5. Another contributor to dinosaur extinction6. Analysis of fossilized shells7. High mercury, warming oceans when shells formed8. Deccan Traps eruption9.Toxic mercury10. Asteroid impact accelerated climate change started by eruptionVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a timeline assembled by University of Texas at Austin researchers, the Chicxulub asteroid struck a shallow ocean some 66 million years ago, hitting it with the force of 10 billion atomic bombs.""The blast set the land ablaze, igniting trees and plants up to thousands of miles away.""Although the asteroid caused destruction at the regional level when it hit, the impact itself was not what killed off the dinosaurs.""Instead, scientists say sulfur-bearing rocks were vaporized at the site, releasing an estimated 325 million metric tons of sulfur  into the atmosphere, where it reflected sunlight away from the planet and caused global cooling.""Researchers believe the global climate change that followed was responsible for the mass extinction of the dinosaurs.""Global cooling disrupted photosynthesis, which killed the plants and caused the food chain to collapse.""Now, a new study published in Nature Communications has found evidence that another event may have contributed to the extinction.""The University of Michigan-led research collected and analyzed ancient fossilized shells from around the world, finding evidence of both ocean warming and high mercury concentrations when they were formed 66 million years ago.""These measurements are both symptoms of volcanic eruptions. They align with the onset of a series of violent eruptions that created India's Deccan Traps formations, starting before the extinction, and lasting on and off for about a million years.""Mercury is toxic to humans, fish, and wildlife. The levels researchers found in the ancient shells were found to be roughly equivalent to those in modern shells from mercury-polluted industrial sites." "Scientists believe that such a level of global mercury contamination indicates a volcanic climate change was already present before the extinction, and may have merely been accelerated by the impact event."SOURCES: University of Michigan, Nature Communicationshttps://news.umich.edu/two-in-one-fossil-shells-reveal-both-global-mercury-contamination-and-warming-when-dinosaurs-perished/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-019-13366-0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/20/3938000/3938000_9AA0CF4DB82C459290D63206B080BE22_191220_3938000_Volcanic_climate_change_pre_asteroid_impact_may__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Dinosaur extinction, dino extinction, dinosaur mass extinction, dino mass extinction, Deccan traps, volcanic climate change, volcanic eruptions, dinosaur extinction theory, dinosaur extinction cause, mercury poisoning, global mercury poisoning, global warming, fossilized shells]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937993</guid>
      <title>Greek and Turkish fighter jets spar over airspace</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTurkish and Greek fighter jets engaged in 16 mock dogfights after Greece's airspace was violated by Turkish jets on December 17 over territorial claims in the Aegean Sea. Greek air force pilots rushed to intercept the Turkish jets as they entered the country's airspace a total of 40 times on Tuesday, Stars and Stripes reports. The two nations are at odds over issues including the delimitation of territorial waters, airspace, exclusion zones and Turkey's claims over small islands in the Aegean Sea.Turkey said it could send in military forces into the eastern Mediterranean and add armed drones to northern Cyprus over the two countries' territorial disputes, Stars and Stripes reports, citing Turkish Vice President Fuat Oktay.Greek Defense Minister Nikos Panagiotopoulos had previously said that the disputed area is controlled by the Greek military.According to Greek City Times, the country plans to purchase drones from the U.S. and Israel. The technology could be used to surveil Turkey's military moves in the Mediterranean.The move comes amid growing tensions between Greece and Turkey as the U.S. has increased its military ties with Greece while the U.S. could move ahead to sanction Turkey over its military invasion in northern Syria.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Turkish and Greek fighter jet engaging in mock dogfights2. Greek fighter jet intercepting a Turkish jet3. Turkey said it could send it military forces and add armed drone to the region4. How Greece plans to surveil Turkey's military moves in the disputed regionVOICEOVER (in English): "Turkish and Greek fighter jets engaged in 16 mock dogfights after Greece's airspace was violated by Turkish jets on December 17 over territorial claims in the Aegean Sea.""Stars and Stripes reports that Greek air force pilots rushed to intercept the Turkish jets as they entered the country's airspace a total of 40 times on Tuesday.""The two nations are at odds over issues including the delimitation of territorial waters, airspace, exclusion zones and Turkey's claims over small islands in the Aegean Sea.""Citing Turkish Vice President Fuat Oktay, Stars and Stripes reports that Turkey said it could send in military forces into the eastern Mediterranean and add armed drones to northern Cyprus over the two countries' territorial disputes.""Greek Defense Minister Nikos Panagiotopoulos had previously said that the disputed area is controlled by the Greek military.""According to Greek City Times, the country plans to purchase drones from the U.S. and Israel." "The technology could be used to surveil Turkey's military moves in the Mediterranean."SOURCES: Stars and Stripes, Greek City Times, The National Herald, https://www.stripes.com/news/europe/turkey-breaches-airspace-of-greece-40-times-in-a-day-triggering-mock-dogfights-between-the-nato-allies-1.611611https://greekcitytimes.com/2019/12/19/turkish-firefighter-jets-violated-aegean-airspace-40-times-in-one-day/https://www.thenationalherald.com/274637/turkish-fighter-jets-invade-greek-airspace-16-mock-dogfights-ensue/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/20/3937993/3937993_67550DC1E2EA4357B817637711C446A2_191220_3937993_Greek_and_Turkish_fighter_jets_spar_over_airspac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Turkey fighter jets, Greek fighter jets, turkey violates Greek airspace, greek airspace, turkey greece, Aegean Sea, Turkey Greece territorial dispute, Mock Dogfights, turkey greece mock dogfights, turkish jets intercepted]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937979</guid>
      <title>Conquistador anchors discovered off Mexico Gulf Coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMexico's National Institute of Anthropology and History have announced that two 500-year-old iron ship anchors have been discovered on Mexico's Gulf Coast. These anchors could belong to the ships of Spanish conquistador, Hern叩n Cort辿s, thus potentially offering an insight into the Spanish invasion.Divers discovered the anchors 10 to 15 meters below the sea, under a thick layer of sediment. In 2018, just 1,000 feet away from the site, another anchor was found and dated back to the 15th century via its wood. The date is significant as it would fit with that of Hern叩n Cort辿s as records show he landed in Veracruz, Mexico in April 1519.All three anchors were found on the coast just north of the port city of Veracruz.Head of the Underwater Archeology Office, Dr. Roberto Junco, details the most voluminous of the three anchors as 3.68 meters long and 1.55 meters wide between its tips.Both anchors are well preserved as a result of being protected beneath the sediment of the ocean. For this reason, after documentation and measurement, they will be returned to adhere to the archaeological protocols of conservation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of anchors2. Anchor in underwater sediment3. Measurement of anchor4. Anchor is buried VOICEOVER (in English): "Mexico's National Institute of Anthropology and History have announced that two 500-year-old iron ship anchors have been discovered on Mexico's Gulf Coast. These anchors could belong to the ships of Spanish conquistador, Hern叩n Cort辿s, thus potentially offering an insight into the Spanish invasion.""Divers discovered the anchors 10 to 15 meters below the sea, under a thick layer of sediment. In 2018, just 1,000 feet away from the site, another anchor was found and dated back to the 15th century via its wood. The date is significant as it would fit with that of Hern叩n Cort辿s as records show he landed in Veracruz, Mexico in April 1519.""All three anchors were found on the coast just north of the port city of Veracruz.""Head of the Underwater Archeology Office, Dr. Roberto Junco details the most voluminous of the three anchors as 3.68 meters long and 1.55 meters wide between its tips.""Both anchors are well preserved as a result of being protected beneath the sediment of the ocean. For this reason, after documentation and measurement, they will be returned to adhere to the archaeological protocols of conservation."SOURCES: BBC, National Institute of Anthropology and Historyhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-50835844https://www.inah.gob.mx/en/boletines/8795-500-years-after-the-landing-of-cortes-researchers-discover-two-iron-anchors-in-villa-rica-veracruz***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 01:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/20/3937979/3937979_F02A553EE63848E8B178DA6B581E2709_191220_3937979_Conquistador_anchors_discovered_off_Mexico_Gulf__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 500 year old anchor found, Hern叩n Cort辿s, Aztec empire, underwater archeology, TomoNews, satire, Conquistador, Mexico Gulf Coast, anchors, anchors found]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939500</guid>
      <title>Satellite imagery spots expansion to missile launcher factory in North Korea: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNBC News reports that civilian satellite imagery by Planet Labs has revealed an expansion to the March 16 factory in North Korea's Pyongsong.Citing expert analysis given to the channel, NBC reports that these activities could mean North Korea will soon resume the testing of intercontinental ballistic missiles.Analyst Jeffrey Lewis told the channel that a temporary structure has been erected at the March 16 factory.Lewis, director of the East Asia Nonproliferation Program at the Middlebury Institute of International Studies, speculated that the structure was built to accommodate efforts to raise a missile launcher arm.Lewis told CNN the March 16 factory is involved in manufacturing civilian vehicles and missile launchers.Citing Lewis, CNN reported that the heavy-duty trucks built at the factory are powerful enough to transport large missiles.Lewis told NBC the facility's expansion occurred after North Korea's leader Kim Jong-un visited the factory in June.NBC speculates that the revelation could mean North Korea will test launch a missile designed to be capable of reaching the U.S.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Expansion of North Korea's missile launcher factory in Pyongsong sparks concerns2. New structure in March 16 factory speculated to house missile launcher arm3. March 16 factory produces missile launchers and heavy duty trucks4. Construction possibly related to new missile tests by North Korea VOICEOVER (in English): "NBC News reports that civilian satellite imagery by Planet Labs has revealed an expansion to the March 16 factory in North Korea's Pyongsong.""Citing expert analysis given to the channel, NBC reports that these activities could mean North Korea will soon resume the testing of intercontinental ballistic missiles.""Analysis Jeffrey Lewis told the channel that a temporary structure has been erected at the March 16 factory.""Lewis, director of the East Asia Nonproliferation Program at the Middlebury Institute of International Studies, speculated that the structure was built to accommodate efforts to raise a missile launcher arm.""Lewis told CNN the March 16 factory is involved in manufacturing civilian vehicles and missile launchers.""Citing Lewis, CNN reported that the heavy-duty trucks built at the factory are powerful enough to transport large missiles.""Lewis told NBC the facility's expansion occurred after North Korea's leader Kim Jong-un visited the factory in June.""NBC speculates that the revelation could mean North Korea will test launch a missile designed to be capable of reaching the U.S."SOURCES: NBC News, CNNhttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/north-korea/exclusive-satellite-photos-show-work-north-korean-site-linked-long-n1106176https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/21/politics/north-korea-satellite-images-building-expansion/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/23/3939500/3939500_49E154ACE260438D94A30F47E51E0C15_191223_3939500_Satellite_imagery_spots_expansion_to_missile_lau_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sattelite, satellites, satellite images, satellite imagery, satellite photos, factory 16, missiles, missile, ICBM, intercontinental ballistic missile, missile test, missile tests,  Pyongsong, North Korea, US, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939483</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy should seek minelaying capabilities for underwater drone program</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA retired commander has proposed using the U.S. Navy's Boeing Orca underwater drone offensively in future conflicts. According to Forbes, the Orca autonomous drone is a diesel-electric submarine with a payload baythat could carry minesand a control unit located in the forward section.In a post on the US Naval Institute blog, Commander Brian Dulla says the 'moorpedo' is a smart weapon that is both a torpedo and a moored or bottom mine.The design includes an antenna, electric power propulsion, a temporary anchor, and a shaped explosive warhead with contact and proximity triggers.The Orca drone or other platforms could lay inactive moorpedos in international waters during peacetime, which is legal under international law.The underwater offensive drone would use its anchor to lay in wait and its antenna for receiving commands.If the autonomous weapon receives the command to actuate, it would engage the propulsion system to redeploy against an enemy port.The drone would also be able to attack enemy warships entering or leaving port as a mine or strike at moored ships as a slow-moving torpedo.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. Navy's Orca underwater drone 2. Moorpedo design concept as a mine and torpedo hybrid3. Orca deploys moorpedo at international sea4. Moorpedo is activated by signal and redeploys to attack shipsVOICEOVER (in English): "A retired commander has proposed using the U.S. Navy's Boeing Orca underwater drone offensively in future conflicts."   "According to Forbes, the Orca autonomous drone is a diesel-electric submarine with a payload baythat could carry minesand a control unit located in the forward section.""In a post on the US Naval Institute blog, Commander Brian Dulla says the 'moorpedo' is a smart weapon that is both a torpedo and a moored or bottom mine.""The design includes an antenna, electric power propulsion, a temporary anchor, and a shaped explosive warhead with contact and proximity triggers.""The Orca drone or other platforms could lay inactive moorpedos in international waters during peacetime, which is legal under international law.""The underwater offensive drone would use its anchor to lay in wait and its antenna for receiving commands.""If the autonomous weapon receives the command to actuate, it would engage the propulsion system to redeploy against an enemy port.""The drone would also be able to attack enemy warships entering or leaving port as a mine or strike at moored ships as a slow-moving torpedo." SOURCES: U.S. Naval Institute, Forbeshttps://blog.usni.org/posts/2019/12/02/the-moor-pedo-a-strategic-underwater-weapon-to-re-shape-naval-conflicthttps://news.usni.org/2019/02/13/41119https://www.forbes.com/sites/hisutton/2019/12/17/the-us-navys-new-orca-drone-submarine-could-get-offensive-role/#1838652160ca***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/23/3939483/3939483_FDD54B0B09724F4791A4F37625358DB2_191223_3939483_U_S__Navy_should_seek_minelaying_capabilities_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Orca, extra large unmanned underwater vehicle, xluuv, Boeing, USN, US Navy, minelayer, naval mines, autonomous, unmanned, unmanned vehicle, drone, morpedo, mine, torpedo, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939253</guid>
      <title>Twin skyscraper designs unveiled for Brooklyn waterfront</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDanish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group and New York-based landscape architecture firm James Corner Field Operations have unveiled plans for a mixed-use development on the waterfront in Brooklyn, New York.The River Street Waterfront Master Plan would consist of two sandy beaches to improve coastal resiliency as sea levels continue to rise.The project plans to transform the area into a waterfront park with a circular walkway raised on stilts where visitors can stroll or take part in outdoor activities such as boating, Dezeen reports. To protect against heavy flooding, the seabed underneath the park will be stepped, so it can fill up with water in an emergency.The redesigned waterfront site would also include nature trails and bird watching sites for the public.The two companies also want to construct two skyscrapers beside the park. These towers would include residential units and office space as well as retail stores. The buildings would also include a YMCA gym and a swimming pool.The structures would make use of sustainable design elements such as passive solar shading.Lead designer Lisa Switkin from James Corner Field Operations explained to Dezeen that the project would provide a better wildlife environment and allow the public to live in harmony with the surrounding water.The project is currently waiting for approval from New York's City Hall, the Department of City Planning and other relevant authorities such as the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers. This process is expected to take two years. If approved, construction of the new waterfront could take up to five years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Redesigned Williamsburg waterfront2. New waterfront park3. Nature trails and bird watching sites4. Two new skyscrapers would be constructed beside the parkVOICEOVER (in English): "Danish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group and New York-based landscape architecture firm James Corner Field Operations have unveiled plans for a mixed-use development on the waterfront in Brooklyn, New York.""The River Street Waterfront Master Plan would consist of two sandy beaches to improve coastal resiliency as sea levels continue to rise.""Dezeen reports that the project plans to transform the area into a waterfront park with a circular walkway raised on stilts where visitors can stroll or take part in outdoor activities such as boating.""To protect against heavy flooding, the seabed underneath the park will be stepped, so it can fill up with water in an emergency.""The redesigned waterfront site would also include nature trails and bird watching sites for the public.""The two companies also want to construct two skyscrapers beside the park. These towers would include residential units and office space as well as retail stores.""The buildings would also include a YMCA gym and a swimming pool.""The structures would make use of sustainable design elements such as passive solar shading."SOURCES: New Atlas, Dezeen, Fast Company, The Architect's Newspaper https://newatlas.com/architecture/bjarke-ingels-group-river-street-waterfront-masterplan/https://www.dezeen.com/2019/12/12/river-street-waterfront-master-plan-big-field-operations-williamsburg-brooklyn/https://www.fastcompany.com/90440874/this-new-brooklyn-park-is-designed-to-thrive-as-sea-levels-risehttps://archpaper.com/2019/12/big-james-corner-field-operations-williamsburg-river-street/#gallery-0-slide-0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 03:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/23/3939253/3939253_02AF234F6FC1433C82DE3335899CF0FD_191223_3939253_Twin_skyscraper_designs_unveiled_for_Brooklyn_wa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Williamsburg's waterfront, River Street Waterfront Master Plan New York, new coastal brooklyn park, new brooklyn waterfront, New York city waterfront redesigned, brooklyn waterfront walkway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940004</guid>
      <title>Taipei to test self-driving buses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan's capital city of Taipei will test driverless shuttles in the second quarter next year, the Taipei Times reports.According to the shuttle's designer and operator Turing Drive Inc, the vehicle features an NVIDIA DRIVE PX2 processor, a top-mounted LIDAR and front and rear cameras.The shuttle is controlled by an A.I. that uses a deep learning algorithm to drive and has lower carbon emissions.Citing the city's transportation director Chen Hsueh-tai, the Liberty Times reports that sensors will be installed at intersections to help the shuttle recognize traffic signs.The Taipei Times reports that the pilot program will run on the part of the city's Xinyi road between the East Gate and the Keelung Road intersection at 30 kilometers per hour.Officials told the Liberty Times that a safety operator will be present on the shuttle to intervene if necessary.The shuttle line is to run during the closed hours of the city's mass transit system, or between midnight and 5:00 a.m.Chen told the paper while the technology is not yet ready for daytime, running the shuttle at night will help residents commuting at late hours.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sensors and processor of Turing Drive Inc self-driving shuttle2. Additional sensors will be installed at traffic signals to augment shuttle AI 3. The shuttle's planned route along Taipei's Xinyi road4. Vehicle will feature an onboard safety operator and run late night to early morningVOICEOVER (in English): "The Liberty Times reports that Taiwan's capital city of Taipei will test driverless shuttles in the second quarter next year.""According to the shuttle's designer and operator Turing Drive Inc, the vehicle features an NVIDIA DRIVE PX2 processor, a top-mounted LIDAR and front and rear cameras.""The shuttle is controlled by an AI that uses a deep learning algorithm to drive and has lower carbon emissions." "Citing the city's transportation director Chen Hsueh-tai, the Liberty Times reports that sensors will be installed at intersections to help the shuttle recognize traffic signs.""The Taipei Times reports that the pilot program will run on the part of the city's Xinyi road between the East Gate and the Keelung Road intersection at 30 kilometers per hour.""Officials told the Liberty Times that a safety operator will be present on the shuttle to intervene if necessary.""The shuttle line is to run during the closed hours of the city's mass transit system, or between midnight and 5:00 a.m.""Chen told the paper while the technology is not yet ready for daytime, running the shuttle at night will help residents commuting at late hours."SOURCES: Turing Inc, Taipei Times, Liberty Timeshttp://www.turing-drive.com/2019/03/29/%e5%8f%b0%e7%81%a3%e8%87%aa%e9%a7%95%e9%a4%8a%e5%85%b5%e5%8d%83%e6%97%a5-%e5%b0%b1%e5%be%85%e6%ad%a4%e6%99%82/http://www.turing-drive.com/2019/11/18/%e9%a6%96%e5%89%b5-%e8%80%97%e8%b3%87%e5%8d%83%e8%90%ac%e7%84%a1%e4%ba%ba%e6%8e%a5%e9%a7%81%e5%b7%b4%e5%a3%ab%e4%b8%8a%e8%b7%af-%e9%96%8b%e9%80%b2%e5%85%a8%e5%8f%b0%e6%9c%80%e5%a4%a7%e6%a8%82%e5%9c%92/http://www.taipeitimes.com/News/taiwan/archives/2019/12/23/2003728038https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/life/breakingnews/3016194***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/24/3940004/3940004_D426927CFC5147288EEBDEAC7292CDAC_191224_3940004_Taipei_to_test_self_driving_buses_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Driverless bus, driverless shuttle, autonomous, AI, artificial intelligence, self-driving, Turing Drive Inc, Taipei, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939849</guid>
      <title>Over 15,000 pounds of frozen beef patties recalled over possible plastic contamination</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Department of Agriculture announced that Tyson Foods subsidiary AdvancePierre Foods is recalling 15,738 pounds of its beef patty products as they may be "contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically small, green soft plastic."The USDA is classifying this as a Class II Recall. This means there is a remote probability that use of the product may result in adverse health consequences.In a statement, the company said that it is voluntarily recalling the product CN Fully Cooked Flamebroiled Beef Patties as a precaution after receiving complaints from a foodservice establishment.AdvancePierre Foods says only two of the patties were found to be contaminated.The company is recalling 1,043 cases, or roughly half a truckload of product, that were produced in September 2019.According to the USDA, the product was shipped to a warehouse in Iowa, then distributed to institutions including schools as part of a commercial sale. The product was not sold in retail stores.AdvancePierre Foods says it has not received any reports of injuries or illnesses due to consumption of the beef patties. The USDA urged institutions that have purchased the product to either discard it or return it to the place of purchase.In April of this year, AdvancePierre Foods recalled over 20,000 pounds of beef patties after consumers found pieces of soft, purple plastic in the product.AdvancePierre Foods' parent company, Tyson Foods, which has been involved in a series of food scandals, voluntarily recalled more than 5,000 cases of its crispy chicken fritters after plastic was found in the product in June 2019.The company said that the product was not sold at stores, though it was distributed to schools across the country.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A beef patty product from AdvancePierre Foods is being recalled due to possible plastic contamination2. Why the product was recalled3. How much of the product is being recalled4. Where the product was shipped and where it was distributed toVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Department of Agriculture announced that Tyson Foods subsidiary AdvancePierre Foods is recalling 15,738 pounds of its beef patty products as they may be 'contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically small, green soft plastic.'""The USDA is classifying this as a Class II Recall. This means there is a remote probability that use of the product may result in adverse health consequences.""In a statement, the company said that it is voluntarily recalling the product CN Fully Cooked Flamebroiled Beef Patties as a precaution after receiving complaints from a foodservice establishment.""AdvancePierre Foods says only two of the patties were found to be contaminated.""The company is recalling 1,043 cases, or roughly half a truckload of product, that were produced in September 2019.""According to the USDA, the product was shipped to a warehouse in Iowa, then distributed to institutions including schools as part of a commercial sale.""The product was not sold in retail stores."SOURCES: United States Department of Agriculture, AdvancePierre Foods, CNN https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-123-2019-releasehttps://www.advancepierre.com/Blog/News/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/21/us/beef-patties-recall/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 07:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/24/3939849/3939849_D5866201298743C08A1CB0133C592252_191224_3939849_Over_15_000_pounds_of_frozen_beef_patties_recall_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Frozen beef patties recall, Plastic contamination, beef patties plastic contamination, Advance Pierre Foods, contamination in beef patties]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939765</guid>
      <title>Tesla may soon unveil a new vehicle from its 'Master Plan'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTesla has yet to unveil one of its vehicles, a high passenger-density urban transport vehicle, according to the second part of the company's Master Plan. Tesla recently unveiled a new vehicle, the Tesla Semi, which was also mentioned in the plan.In the Master Plan, the automotive company stated that the new electric vehicle would include self-driving technology.The plan mentions that center aisles inside the vehicle would be eliminated in order to increase passenger area density. Seats would instead be added to the vehicle's current entryways.Tesla explains that the vehicle would be able to take passengers all the way to their destination and would improve overall traffic congestion.The plan was released in 2016, in which the automotive company explained that the vehicle is currently at its early stages of development and should soon be ready for unveiling.Tesla had previously released its first Master Plan over a decade ago, in 2006, and has since launched the Model S, Model 3 and the Roadster as part of the plan.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tesla's yet to be revealed vehicle2. The vehicle would include self-driving technology3. The vehicle's interior4. The vehicle traveling to its destinationVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the second part of Tesla's Master Plan, the company has yet to unveil one of its vehicles: a high passenger-density urban transport vehicle.""Tesla recently unveiled a new vehicle, the Tesla Semi, which was also mentioned in the plan.""In the Master Plan, the automotive company stated that the new electric vehicle would include self-driving technology.""The plan mentions that center aisles inside the vehicle would be eliminated in order to increase passenger area density.""Seats would instead be added to the vehicle's current entryways.""Tesla explains that the vehicle would be able to take passengers all the way to their destination and would improve overall traffic congestion."SOURCES: Electrek, Tesla https://electrek.co/2019/12/16/tesla-one-more-vehicle-unveil-elon-musk-master-plan-part-deux/https://www.tesla.com/blog/secret-tesla-motors-master-plan-just-between-you-and-mehttps://www.tesla.com/blog/master-plan-part-deux***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 04:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/24/3939765/3939765_8BEA77AED1FD4620B49B07453068E331_191224_3939765_Tesla_may_soon_unveil_a_new_vehicle_from_its__Ma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Tesla, new tesla vehicle, Tesla Master plan, tesla elon musk, high passenger-density urban transport, tesla news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940273</guid>
      <title>Betelgeuse being dimmer does not mean supernova likely</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers from Villanova University recently published an article noting that Betelgeuse in the constellation Orion has been significantly dimmer in recent months, leading some to speculate it could go supernova.According to CNet, one possible explanation for the dimming is that Betelgeuse is out of fuel and has begun to collapse on itself resulting in a supernova explosion. Once the star explodes, the explosion would be visible during daylight and could even be brighter than the moon at night for a few weeks or even months. However, astronomers say this is unlikely.The other likely explanation is that because Betelgeuse is a variable star that has been dimming and brightening for a millennia, the dimming could just be the most significant dip in the past 50 years or so, which is a very short amount of time in the star's lifespan.  NASA's website states that Betelgeuse is over 1,000 times larger than our sun.The star's radius is also big enough to encompass Jupiter and all four planets in our inner solar system: Mercury, Venus, Earth and Mars, CNet reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Betelgeuse becoming dimmer and dimmer2. One reason why the star could be dimming3. Another more likely reason why the star is dimming4. How big Betelgeuse is in comparison to our sun, and planets in our inner solar systemVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers from Villanova University recently published an article noting that Betelgeuse in the constellation Orion has been significantly dimmer in recent months, leading some to speculate it could go supernova.""According to CNet, one possible explanation for the dimming is that Betelgeuse is out of fuel and has begun to collapse on itself resulting in a supernova explosion." "Once the star explodes, the explosion would be visible during daylight and could even be brighter than the moon at night for a few weeks or even months.""However, astronomers say this is unlikely.""The other likely explanation is that because Betelgeuse is a variable star that has been dimming and brightening for a millennia, the dimming could just be the most significant dip in the past 50 years or so, which is a very short amount of time in the star's lifespan."  "According to CNet, many scientists have said recently over social media this is most likely what is occurring." "NASA's website states that Betelgeuse is over 1,000 times larger than our sun.""CNet reports that the star's radius is also big enough to encompass Jupiter and all four planets in our inner solar system: Mercury, Venus, Earth and Mars."SOURCES: CNet, EarthSky, The Astronomer's Telegramhttps://www.cnet.com/news/famed-star-betelgeuse-will-explode-some-day-and-its-acting-weird-right-now/https://earthsky.org/space/betelgeuse-fainting-probably-not-about-to-explodehttp://www.astronomerstelegram.org/?read=13341***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 05:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/25/3940273/3940273_2BEC8D35A3084A30989A741FA25DA032_191225_3940273_Betelgeuse_being_dimmer_does_not_mean_supernova__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Betelgeuse, red supergiant star Betelgeuse, Betelgeuse supernova, Betelgeuse explosion, Betelgeuse explained, betelgeuse dimming, betelgeuse fainting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940232</guid>
      <title>Taiwan signs US arms deal for advanced F-16 jets: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaipei has signed a U.S. arms deal for 66 F-16V fighters while upgrading older models to F-16V standard earlier in December, Taiwan's state run Central News Agency reports on Saturday.According to Lockheed Martin, the F-16V is the latest variant of the F-16, a multirole fighter that features advanced weaponry, targeting systems, electronics, and radar. Citing an unnamed military source, CNA reports that the F-16Vs have better weapons than the older generation J-11 fighters used by China's People's Liberation Army.According to the source, the F-16V may not be a match for the PLA's J-20 stealth fighter, but Taiwanese jets could utilize friendly early warning aircraft to contain the threat.The PLA deploys about 700 fighters in China's southeastern coast, which is double the size of Taiwan's tactical air arm.CNA cites the source as saying that the combination of F-16Vs and air defense systems give Taiwan's military a needed boost to combat the PLA's superior numbers.Citing associate professor Lin Ying- yu[a] at the National Chung Cheng University, the CNA reports that China's carriers are now a threat to Taiwan's eastern defensive perimeter.CNA cites Lin as saying that the F-16Vs and anti-ship missiles will serve as a deterrent to Chinese carriers and aircraft operating in the seas east of Taiwan.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. F-16V's technical features 2. F-16V believed to be superior to China's J-11 and able to contain J-203. Taiwan's fighters and air defense systems to offset China's numerical superiority 4. Advanced fighters deployed as deterrence to Chinese carriers from the eastVOICEOVER (in English): "Taiwan's state run Central News Agency reports that Taipei has signed a U.S. arms deal for 66 F-16V fighters while upgrading older models to F-16V standard.""According to Lockheed Martin, the F-16V is the latest variant of the F-16, a multirole  fighter that features advanced weaponry, targeting systems, electronics, and radar." "Citing an unnamed military source, CNA reports that the F-16Vs have better weapons than the older generation J-11 fighters used by China's People's Liberation Army.""According to the source, the F-16V may not be a match for the PLA's J-20 stealth fighter, but Taiwanese jets could utilize friendly early warning aircraft to contain the threat.""The PLA deploys about 700 fighters in China's southeastern coast, which is double the size of Taiwan's tactical air arm.""CNA cites the source as saying that the combination of F-16Vs and air defense systems give Taiwan's military a needed boost to combat the PLA's superior numbers.""Citing associate professor Lin Ying- yu[b] at the National Chung Cheng University, the CNA reports that China's carriers are now a threat to Taiwan's eastern defensive perimeter.""CNA cites Lin as saying that the F-16Vs and anti-ship missiles will serve as a deterrent to Chinese carriers and aircraft operating in the seas east of Taiwan."SOURCES: Central News Agency (Focus Taiwan), Lockheed Martin, Jane's Information Grouphttp://focustaiwan.tw/news/aipl/201912220007.aspxhttps://www.lockheedmartin.com/en-us/news/features/2016/meet-the-f-16v--the-most-technologically-advanced-4th-generation.htmlhttps://www.janes.com/article/93224/aidc-lockheed-martin-to-set-up-f-16-maintenance-facility-in-taiwan***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/25/3940232/3940232_43B720F05F96483694077117712AD874_191225_3940232_Taiwan_signs_US_arms_deal_for_advanced_F_16_jets_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, F-16V, F-16, F16V, arms sale, F-16C/D, F-16A/B, Block 70, Taiwan, U.S., China, Chinese carriers, People's Liberation Army, People's Liberation Army Navy, PLA, PLAN, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941424</guid>
      <title>China's construction of an airstrip in Cambodia is raising alarms about its military ambitions.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's construction of an airstrip in Cambodia is raising alarms about its military ambitions, according to the New York Times.Bloomberg reports that Beijing now controls 20 percent of Cambodia's coastline via the lease of Dara Sakor, where a contractor is building an airport, a deep water port, medical facilities and a resort.According to the New York Times, the Chinese claim the Dara Sakor airport  which will feature the longest runway in Cambodia  is a civilian facility.However, the newspaper reports that the construction's scale and its tight turning bays which accommodate fighter jets point to a military purpose.China-based Union Development Group holds the 99 year lease to the Dara Sakor investment zone.Citing political scientist Sophal Ear at Occidental College, the New York Times reports that China's construction of the airport is to project power in the region. According to the New York Times, the construction in Cambodia is likely a move to further Beijing's military strategy known as the "string of pearls."This strategy involves establishing infrastructure and military bases that stretch from the South China Sea to the Indian Ocean and beyond.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dara Sakor airport and investment zone 2.  Airport reportedly civilian in purpose but includes military features3.  China may use the leased zone in Cambodia to project power in the region4.  Beijing's string of pearls strategyVOICEOVER (in English): "China's construction of an airstrip in Cambodia is raising alarms about its military ambitions.""Bloomberg reports that Beijing now controls 20 percent of Cambodia's coastline via the lease of Dara Sakor, where a contractor is building an airport, a deep water port, medical facilities and a resort.""According to the New York Times, the Chinese claim the Dara Sakor airport  which will feature the longest runway in Cambodia  is a civilian facility.""However, the newspaper reports that the construction's scale and its tight turning bays which accommodate fighter jets point to a military purpose.""China-based Union Development Group holds the 99 year lease to the Dara Sakor investment zone.""Citing political scientist Sophal Ear at Occidental College, the New York Times reports that China's construction of the airport is to project power in the region.""According to the New York Times, the construction in Cambodia is likely a move to further Beijing's military strategy known as the 'string of pearls.'""This strategy involves establishing infrastructure and military bases that stretch from the South China Sea to the Indian Ocean and beyond."SOURCES: New York Times, Bloomberg, Wall Street Journalhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/22/world/asia/cambodia-china-military-bases.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2019-07-18/u-s-fears-cambodia-resort-may-become-china-naval-basehttps://www.wsj.com/articles/secret-deal-for-chinese-naval-outpost-in-cambodia-raises-u-s-fears-of-beijings-ambitions-11563732482***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 11:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/27/3941424/3941424_240469FAAE454AEBA585811F7BFDA0E1_191227_3941424_China_s_construction_of_an_airstrip_in_Cambodia__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, DaraSakor International Airport, airfield, airbase, lease, Dara Sakor investment zone, Dara Sakor, string of pearls, belt and road, Cambodia, China, US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941392</guid>
      <title>Lasers learn to accurately locate space debris</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina-based scientists have developed a way to use laser telescopes and neural network analysis to locate space debris.According to a study in the Journal of Laser Applications, the team tested the method at the Beijing Fangshen laser range telescope station.Citing the team leader Ma Tianming, the American Institute of Physics says the technology allows laser scopes to detect reflected laser light from small space debris with greater accuracy than before.It can detect space junk with a cross-section of one square meter and a distance of 1,500 kilometers from earth.According to the news release, neural networks are algorithms based on the human brain's sensory inputs, processing and outputs.Using the neural network to fine-tune telescope readings, the team says their technology is the first to have significantly augmented laser ranging accuracy.Researchers say refining the technology will enable telescopes to pinpoint orbital debris.The paper states that locating the debris would then allow spacecraft to chart a safer course to avoid space junk.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Beijing Fangshen laser range telescope station's ranging laser2. New technology allows the detection of small space debris3. Neural network modeled on human brain assists the laser telescope4. Potential uses of the technology to protect spacecraft from space junkVOICEOVER (in English): "China-based scientists have developed a way to use laser telescopes and neural network analysis to locate space debris.""According to a study in the Journal of Laser Applications, the team tested the method at the Beijing Fangshen laser range telescope station.""Citing the team leader Ma Tianming, the American Institute of Physics says the technology allows laser scopes to detect reflected laser light from small space debris with greater accuracy than before.""It can detect space junk with a cross-section of one square meter and a distance of 1,500 kilometers from earth.""According to the news release, neural networks are algorithms based on the human brain's sensory inputs, processing and outputs.""Using the neural network to fine-tune telescope readings, the team says their technology is the first to have significantly augmented laser ranging accuracy.""Researchers say refining the technology will enable telescopes to pinpoint orbital debris.""The paper states that locating the debris would then allow spacecraft to chart a safer course to avoid space junk."SOURCES: Journal of Laser Applications, American Institute of Physics (EurekAlert)https://lia.scitation.org/doi/10.2351/1.5110748https://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-12/aiop-llt122319.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/27/3941392/3941392_9591B95D2CD84FAD93DBCECC13494A99_191227_3941392_Lasers_learn_to_accurately_locate_space_debris_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Laser telescope, laser telescopes, space junk, space debris, neural network, neural networks, algorithm, algorithms, Chinese Academy of Surveying and Mapping, China, US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941367</guid>
      <title>World's largest 3D-printed building constructed in Dubai</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANApis Cor, an American construction firm that specializes in 3D printing, completed the world's largest 3D-printed building in Dubai at the end of October.The building stands at 9.5 meters and covers an area of 640 square meters, according to the company's project website. The structure was built using a mobile 3D printer onsite. It was moved around by a crane at the construction site. The 3D printer used a gypsum-based mixture developed by the company.Apis Cor said the printer was able to withstand Dubai's harsh weather conditions as the entire process took place outdoors, without temperature or humidity control.According to design magazine Dwell, the building was completed in three weeks.Traditional construction methods were used to lay the building's foundation and install the structure's roof, windows and insulation. Manual labor was used to fill the building's columns with heavy concrete and rebar.The building will provide offices for a government agency in Dubai, according to Dwell. Apis Cor said on their website that they plan to improve their 3D printing technology and develop a new version of the printer that would be twice as fast.The company plans to build affordable 3D-printed houses in the states of California and Louisiana.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The world's largest 3D-printed building2. 3D printer used to build the structure3. Printer prints the building onsite4. Traditional construction methods and manual labor also usedVOICEOVER (in English): "Apis Cor, an American construction firm that specializes in 3D printing, completed the world's largest 3D-printed building in Dubai at the end of October.""According to the company's project website, the building stands at 9.5 meters and covers an area of 640 square meters.""The structure was built using a mobile 3D printer onsite. It was moved around by a crane at the construction site.""The 3D printer used a gypsum-based mixture developed by the company.""Apis Cor said the printer was able to withstand Dubai's harsh weather conditions as the entire process took place outdoors, without temperature or humidity control.""According to design magazine Dwell, the building was completed in three weeks.""Traditional construction methods were used to lay the building's foundation and install the structure's roof, windows and insulation." "Manual labor was used to fill the building's columns with heavy concrete and rebar."SOURCES: Apis Cor, Arch Daily, Inhabitat, New Atlas, Dwell  https://www.apis-cor.com/dubai-projecthttps://www.archdaily.com/930857/dubai-municipality-to-become-the-worlds-largest-3d-printed-buildinghttps://inhabitat.com/worlds-largest-3d-printed-building-opens-in-dubai-after-2-weeks-of-construction/https://newatlas.com/architecture/apis-cor-3d-printed-building-dubai/https://www.dwell.com/article/worlds-largest-3d-printed-building-apis-cor-6a4b7f45***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/27/3941367/3941367_007CCA9CF3B24EACA3B63F94F6B2EE55_191227_3941367_World_s_largest_3D_printed_building_constructed__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 3D printing, 3D printed buildings, Dubai 3D printed building, 3D printing technology, Apis Cor, apis cor dubai, Apis Cor 3D printing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942554</guid>
      <title>New leaked documents expose questionable OPCW findings on Douma attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWikileaks has posted several documents that further exposes the coverup within the OPCW of what really happened during the alleged Douma gas attacks.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Syrian helicopter drops cylinder on Douma2. Official OPCW version of how cylinder landed on rooftop3. Official OPCW version of how cylinder landed in bedroom4. OPCW inspectors5. Only one member from Douma FFM contributed to final report6. Separate group gathered to produce final report7. Minimal damage to cylinder compared to roof unexplained8. No traces of nerve agents in alleged victims' blood9. Symptoms inconsistent with a chlorine chemical attack10. COCs present in natural environment11. COC quantifier excluded from final report12. Americans stated narrative during OPCW visitVOICEOVER (in English): "On the night of April 7, 2018, Syrian military helicopters allegedly dropped chlorine bombs on the town of Douma, killing dozens of civilians.""The Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons sent a fact-finding mission to investigate two sites where gas cylinders were found: a rooftop balcony and a bedroom. "According to the official OPCW report, the rooftop bomb first struck a corner of the balcony wall.""This initial impact decreased the cylinder's velocity and changed its trajectory, causing it to hit the concrete floor hard enough to make a hole and fracture the valve, but without sufficient energy to fall through."At the bedroom location, the official report maintains that the chlorine-filled cylinder fell parallel to the roof of a building and crashed through the concrete.""It fell through and briefly impacted the floor, then continued forward on an altered trajectory landing on the bed. The harness and valve remained intact, and its contents were not discharged."In a newly-leaked memo on Wikileaks, a scientist who was part of the Douma fact-finding mission told OPCW Director-General Fernando Arias that over 20 inspectors have expressed concern over inconsistencies in the official findings."The memo's author claims that  except for one FFM member who was a paramedic, all others on the ground in Douma were excluded in the production of the final report.""Instead, OPCW gathered a separate "core" group that operated from "Country X", believed to be Turkey, to create said report.""Wikileaks had also released the first draft of the report, in which investigators say they were unable to explain 'the relatively moderate damage to the cylinder...compared to the destruction caused to the rebar-reinforced concrete roof.'""Blood and other samples taken from alleged victims who fled to Turkey found no trace of any nerve agent  a finding left out in the final report.""No trace was detected in surrounding buildings or vegetation in Douma, either.""Another crucial finding involves the symptoms of the victims in the alleged chemical attack as being inconsistent with exposure to chlorine-containing choking or blood agents like chlorine gas, phosgene, or cyanogen chloride.""These directly contradict the final report, which states the investigation found "reasonable grounds that the use of a toxic chemical as a weapon took place."SOURCES: Wikileaks, Counterpunchhttps://wikileaks.org/opcw-douma/https://www.counterpunch.org/2019/11/15/the-opcw-and-douma-chemical-weapons-watchdog-accused-of-evidence-tampering-by-its-own-inspectors/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/30/3942554/3942554_B2B23BE672DF4625BBE563CE61841D95_191230_3942554_New_leaked_documents_expose_questionable_OPCW_fi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Douma gas attack, douma chemical attack, OPCW, OPCW report, sarin gas, chlorine gas, wikileaks, leaked OPCW documents, leaked documents, OPCW whistleblower]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942501</guid>
      <title>Russia's floating nuclear power plant starts generating electricity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe floating nuclear power plant Akademik Lomonosov has been connected to an electricity grid and successfully produced power for the first time in the Russian town of Pevek.Back in August, the vessel had set out on a three-week journey from the port of Murmansk, as reported by the Associated Press.As it is not self-propelled, the floating power unit was towed by a fleet of tugboats to the Russian town when it arrived on September 14.The vessel is 144 meters long and 30 meters wide, according to a news release from Rosatom, the company that designed the floating plant.The Akademik Lomonosov is equipped with two reactor systems, each with a 35-megawatt capacity. The reactors produce steam for a turbine that will then generate electricity.The vessel is designed to provide energy to port cities and offshore gas and oil-extracting platforms.It is capable of producing enough to power a city of 100,000 inhabitants.Rosatom claims that the floating nuclear plant is designed with a great margin of safety that exceeds all possible threats, which makes nuclear reactors "invincible" against tsunamis and other natural disasters.The Associated Press points out environmentalists have criticized the floating nuclear plant as "inherently dangerous" adding that it threatens the clean Arctic region.But Russia has dismissed these concerns, insisting that a floating nuclear power plant is completely safe.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Floating nuclear power plant connecting to the electricity grid2. The nuclear plant is not self-propelled3. Dimensions of the vessel4. It has two reactor systems5. The floating plant is designed to power port cities and offshore gas and oil-extracting platforms6. How much power it is capable of producingVOICEOVER (in English): "The floating nuclear power plant Akademik Lomonosov has been connected to the electricity grid and successfully produced power for the first time in the Russian town of Pevek.""The Associated Press reports that back in August, the vessel had set out on a three-week journey from the port of Murmansk.""As it is not self-propelled, the floating power unit was towed by a fleet of tugboats to the Russian town when it arrived on September 14.""According to a news release from Rosatom, the company that designed the floating plant, the vessel is 144 meters long and 30 meters wide.""The Akademik Lomonosov is equipped with two reactor systems, each with a 35-megawatt capacity. The reactors produce steam for a turbine that will then generate electricity.""The vessel is designed to provide energy to port cities and offshore gas and oil-extracting platforms.""It is capable of producing enough to power a city of 100,000 inhabitants."SOURCES: Business Insider, CNBC, Rosatom, Akademik Lomonosovhttps://www.businessinsider.com/russia-floating-nuclear-plant-photos-arrival-2019-9https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/20/floating-nuclear-plant-produces-electricity-in-remote-russian-region.htmlhttp://www.rosatom.ru/en/press-centre/news/rosatom-s-first-of-a-kind-floating-power-unit-connects-to-isolated-electricity-grid-in-pevek-russia-/https://www.fnpp.info/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 10:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/30/3942501/3942501_F3F8FD4ECA804601924212F127EFD4FD_191230_3942501_Russia_s_floating_nuclear_power_plant_starts_gen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Floating nuclear plant, floating nuclear power plant, russian floating nuclear plant, first floating nuclear plant, russia's first floating nuclear power plant, akademik lomonosov floating nuclear power plant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942432</guid>
      <title>Neutron star's halo could help explain antimatter near Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Fermi telescope discovered a vast halo around a neutron star that could explain why there is so much antimatter near Earth.According to NASA, there is higher than expected amount of antimatter near Earth, a phenomenon which scientists have struggled to find an explanation for. NASA published its study in Physical Review D Tuesday last week.According to NASA's news release, when a giant star dies and explodes into a supernova, its remaining core sometimes becomes a neutron star. The neutron star named Geminga is a pulsar, which constantly discharges electrons and their antimatter counterpart known as positrons into space.As charged positrons and electrons collide with photons from starlight, the added energy charge the light into gamma rays.Since the path of gamma rays are scrambled by the magnetic fields they encounter, scientists have been unable to trace the positrons back to their origins until now. Using the Fermi data, a NASA affiliated team removed background gamma radiation from the readings and determined that Geminga is in fact the source of the extra positrons.According to the study's co-author Silvia Manconi at Aachen University, the pulsar contributed about 20 percent of positrons detected near Earth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fermi telescope detects neutron star Geminga's halo 2. Geminga projects matter and antimatter into space3. Pulsar particles collide with protons to create Gamma rays 4. NASA research team separates Geminga's emissions from background radiationVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Fermi telescope discovered a vast halo around a neutron star that could explain why there is so much antimatter near Earth.""According to NASA, there is higher than expected amount of antimatter near Earth, a phenomenon which scientists have struggled to find an explanation for." "NASA published its study in Physical Review D Tuesday last week.""According to NASA's news release, when a giant star dies and explodes into a supernova, its remaining core sometimes becomes a neutron star.""The neutron star named Geminga is a pulsar, which constantly discharges electrons and their antimatter counterpart known as positrons into space.""As charged positrons and electrons collide with photons from starlight, the added energy charge the light into gamma rays.""Since the path of gamma rays are scrambled by the magnetic fields they encounter, scientists have been unable to trace the positrons back to their origins until now.""Using the Fermi data, a NASA affiliated team removed background gamma radiation from the readings and determined that Geminga is in fact the source of the extra positrons.""According to the study's co-author Silvia Manconi at Aachen University, the pulsar contributed about 20 percent of positrons detected near Earth."SOURCES: Physical Review D, NASAhttps://journals.aps.org/prd/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevD.100.123015https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2019/nasa-s-fermi-mission-links-nearby-pulsar-s-gamma-ray-halo-to-antimatter-puzzle***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 08:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/30/3942432/3942432_7C48B38636A84F12BF1E74D5C7918EF2_191230_3942432_Neutron_star_s_halo_could_help_explain_antimatte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Fermi, telescope, gamma rays, gamma radiation, halo, Geminga, positrons, positron, antimatter, anti-matter, NASA, Aachen University, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942863</guid>
      <title>'Ghost boat' with seven bodies washes up on Japanese island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapanese authorities discovered the bow of a wooden boat believed to be from North Korea on the coast of Japan's Sado Island in the Sea of Japan on December 27.Seven partially skeletonized remains were found inside the vessel, reports NHK World News. Three bodies were found with heads, two bodies were found without heads and two heads were found without bodies, the Associated Press reports, citing officials. All of the bodies were confirmed to be male, though officials said it is unclear whether or not the separate heads and the bodies came from the same people.According to NHK World News, the side of the boat bore Korean characters and numbers that were painted in red.The vessel's bow was measured to be roughly 7.6 meters long and 2 meters in height."These boats could have been involved in illegal fishing operations in the Sea of Japan, Nikkei Asian Review reports, citing authorities. Mitsuhiro Mimura, a researcher at Japan's Economic Research Institute for Northeast Asia, told the publication that this is partially due to the fact that North Korea sold fishing rights around its own coastal areas to China, forcing North Korea fishermen to go further out at sea in run down wooden boats.A number of wooden boats typically wash ashore during this time of the year after northwesterly winds blow the vessels off course, as reported by NHK World News. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bow of a wooden boat believed to be from North Korea2. Number of human remains found on the vessel3. Boat had Korean characters and numbers on it4. Boat may have been used by North Korean fishermenVOICEOVER (in English): "Japanese authorities discovered the bow of a wooden boat believed to be from North Korea on the coast of Japan's Sado Island in the Sea of Japan on December 27.""NHK World News reports that seven partially skeletonized remains were found inside the vessel.""Citing officials, the Associated Press reports that three bodies were found with heads, two bodies were found without heads, and two heads were found without bodies.""All of the bodies were confirmed to be male, though officials said it is unclear whether or not the separate heads and the bodies came from the same people.""According to NHK World News, the side of the boat bore Korean characters and numbers that were painted in red.""The vessel's bow was measured to be roughly 7.6 meters long and 2 meters in height.""Citing authorities, Nikkei Asian Review reports that these boats could have been involved in illegal fishing operations in the Sea of Japan." SOURCES: NHK News, BBC News, CNN, Associated Press, Nikkei Asian Review https://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20191228_18/amp.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/amp/world-asia-50934145https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/28/asia/bodies-japan-ghost-ship-trnd/index.htmlhttps://apnews.com/e53adbbde6ecf49d4a43f3e08e292d05https://asia.nikkei.com/Politics/Japan-Coast-Guard-launches-unit-to-handle-North-Korean-ghost-ships***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 07:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/31/3942863/3942863_44C304A15E6A420AB5D529727615531B_191231_3942863__Ghost_boat__with_seven_bodies_washes_up_on_Japa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea ghost ship, ghosts ships, north korea north korean wooden boats, north korean fishing boats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942827</guid>
      <title>Chinese global navigation system Beidou nears completion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina announced on December 27 that it is only a few months away from completing its own satellite-based position system called Beidou.China has already launched 53 satellites, including those that are longer in operation, for the navigational system since 2000, reports Nikkei Asian Review.  The final two satellites will be launched by June 2020. This will complete the network at 35 satellites. In comparison, the U.S.'s Global Positioning System, or GPS, uses approximately 30 satellites in space.China is developing a navigation system independent of the GPS in a bid to protect its own interests, Nikkei Asian Review reports. The satellite's level of location accuracy is currently within 5 meters, though Beidou Navigation Satellite System spokesperson Ran Chengqi said that the system's accuracy will improve to within centimeters by the end of next year.The company said this will help in search and rescue missions in the future.Beidou's navigation system will also be used to improve technology for self-driving vehicles and cell phones in China.According to the Nikkei Asian Review, Beidou will also include a text messaging service so that users can communicate with one another.Ran said that Beidou already has plans to export its products to roughly 120 trading partners through China's Belt and Road initiative.The country also plans to open up its navigational system to Southeast Asia, South Asia, Africa and eastern Europe.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Beidou, China's satellite-based position system, is seen in space2. How accurate the navigational system is3. How it will be used to improve technology4. Beidou will include a text messaging serviceVOICEOVER (in English): "China announced on December 27 that it is only a few months away from completing its own satellite-based position system called Beidou.""Nikkei Asian Review reports China has already launched 53 satellites, including those that are longer in operation, for the navigational system since 2000.""The final two satellites will be launched by June 2020. This will complete the network at 35 satellites.""The satellite's level of location accuracy is currently within 5 meters, though Beidou Navigation Satellite System spokesperson Ran Chengqi said that the system's accuracy will improve to within centimeters by the end of next year.""The company said this will help in search and rescue missions in the future.""Beidou's navigation system will also be used to improve technology for self-driving vehicles and cell phones in China.""According to the Nikkei Asian Review, Beidou will also include a text messaging service so that users can communicate with one another."SOURCES: Nikkei Asian Review, Tech Crunch, Engadgethttps://asia.nikkei.com/Business/China-tech/China-decouples-from-US-in-space-with-2020-GPS-completionhttps://techcrunch.com/2019/12/28/china-nears-completion-of-its-gps-competitor-increasing-the-potential-for-internet-balkanization/https://www.engadget.com/2019/12/29/china-beidou-3-gps-alternative-complete-mid-2020/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 06:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/31/3942827/3942827_D966B8E45B9D4AD2B7A178922C1F7416_191231_3942827_Chinese_global_navigation_system_Beidou_nears_co_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China beidou system, china gps system, chinese gps, china beidou, china navigation system, beidou navigation satellite system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942814</guid>
      <title>Researchers find mealworms can consume toxic additive-containing plastic safely</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists say that plastic eating mealworms maybe even more useful than previously thought.According to Stanford University, previous studies determined that mealworms' guts contain microbes that allow them to digest styrofoam. New research published in Environmental Science & Technology has found that mealworms can potentially consume toxic plastic additives in Styrofoam without any ill effects. These worms can then be used as a safe feed supplement.According to the university's news release, HBCD is a chemical added to styrofoam and other polymers as a flame retardant, but the substance is toxic.Mealworms in the experiment were able to excrete 90 percent of the HBCD they ingested 24 hours after eating the plastic and expel the remaining 10 percent within 48 hours.This means the mealworms are uncontaminated even if they substituted on styrofoam.Stanford University says that the results have significant implications, as the worms are used as feed for various livestock, including chickens.The experiment suggests worms used to consume plastic could still be used as a source of agricultural feed. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mealworms may consume styrofoam due due microbes in their guts2. HBCD is a toxic flame retardant commonly added to styrofoam3. Mealworms excrete HBCD out its system completely in three days4. Mealworms that consumed HBCD potentially usable as livestock feed supplementVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists say that plastic eating mealworms maybe even more useful than previously thought.Previous Stanford studies determined that mealworms' guts contain microbes that allow them to digest styrofoam.""New research published in Environmental Science & Technology has found that mealworms can potentially consume toxic plastic additives in Styrofoam without any ill effects. These worms can then be used as a safe feed supplement.""According to the university's news release, HBCD is a chemical added to styrofoam and other polymers as a flame retardant, but the substance is toxic.""Mealworms in the experiment were able to excrete 90 percent of the HBCD they ingested 24 hours after eating the plastic and expel the remaining 10 percent within 48 hours.""This means the mealworms are uncontaminated even if they substituted on styrofoam.""Stanford University says that the results have significant implications, as the worms are used as feed for various livestock, including chickens.""The experiment suggests worms used to consume plastic could still be used as a source of agricultural feed."SOURCES: Environmental Science & Technology, Stanford Universityhttps://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/acs.est.9b06501https://news.stanford.edu/2019/12/19/mealworms-provide-plastic-solution/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 06:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/31/3942814/3942814_1EAB21C0033A4868B62B96F0E45E63FE_191231_3942814_Researchers_find_mealworms_can_consume_toxic_add_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Plastic pollution, plastic waste, styrofoam eating worms, styrofoam, styrofoam eating mealworms, toxins, toxin, HBCD, flame retard, livestock, livestock feed, feed supplements, livestock feed supplement, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942798</guid>
      <title>Geologists claim iron snow is falling on Earth's core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIt is snowing iron at the Earth's core because molten iron crystalizes in the outer core before the substance sinks downwards, according to a study published in JGR Solid Earth.The University of Texas at Austin said in a press release that these iron particles form a 300 kilometer layer above the Earth's solid inner core.The study said that the team led by Sichuan University associate professor Zhang Youjun analyzed seismic wave signals to infer the composition of the Earth's core.The university says that scientists found seismic waves propagating slowly in the outer core's base, but quickly in the eastern hemisphere of the top inner core.The researchers believe that the varying thickness of the iron slurry layer is the cause of the speed difference.They theorize that the iron particles have the effect of slowing seismic wave travel and that the substance is thinner on the inner core's eastern hemisphere.According to the researchers, the Earth's core drives tectonic plate movement with its heat and generates the magnetic field around the planet.The researchers say that understanding the composition of the Earth's core may shed light on those larger processes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Iron snow forming in the Earth's outer core and falling on the inner core2. Study infers the composition of the Earth's core via measuring seismic wave signals3. The snowpile of iron particles on the core vary in thickness4. Composition of the Earth's core may shed light on larger geological processesVOICEOVER (in English): "A study published in JGR Solid Earth says that it is snowing iron at the Earth's core because molten iron crystalizes in the outer core before the substance sinking downwards.""The University of Texas at Austin said in a press release that these iron particles form a 300 kilometer layer above the Earth's solid inner core.""The study said that the team led by Sichuan University associate professor Zhang Youjun analyzed seismic wave signals to infer the composition of the Earth's core.""The university says that scientists found seismic waves propagating slowly in the outer core's base, but quickly in the eastern hemisphere of the top inner core.""The researchers believe that the varying thickness of the iron slurry layer is the cause of the speed difference.""They theorize that the iron particles have the effect of slowing seismic wave travel and that the substance is thinner on the inner core's eastern hemisphere.""According to the researchers, the Earth's core drives tectonic plate movement with its heat and generates the magnetic field around the planet.""The researchers say that understanding the composition of the Earth's core may shed light on those larger processes."SOURCES: JGR Solid Earth, University of Texas at Austinhttps://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1029/2019JB017792https://news.utexas.edu/2019/12/19/scientists-find-iron-snow-in-earths-core/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 05:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/31/3942798/3942798_C36CB39AB02C47B391AB188A3FAB2FDC_191231_3942798_Geologists_claim_iron_snow_is_falling_on_Earth_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Iron snow, earth's core, earth, core, inner core, outer core, seismic wave, University of Texas at Austin, Sichuan University, geology, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942737</guid>
      <title>Remote ID system proposed for drones in U.S. airspace</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Federal Aviation Administration has proposed using remote identification for unmanned aircraft systems in the U.S.The agency proposes that drones in U.S. airspace would have to meet one of three remote identification requirements: the standard remote identification; limited remote identification; or those without any remote identification.The system would allow the government to track drones across the country and could also make it possible for third parties to track the vehicles as well, CNBC reports. The agency says that the remote ID of drones is necessary "to ensure public safety and the safety and efficiency of the airspace of the United States."Drones such as amateur built vehicles and previously manufactured aerial vehicles that may not have remote identification capabilities would be required to fly within the visual line of sight and only in FAA-recognized identification areas.The FAA states in the proposal that all drones in U.S. airspace would be required to comply with the new regulations within three years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Remote identification for drones2. How standard remote identification drone would work3. How limited remote identification drone would work4. These remote identification messages would be shared to a Remote ID USS which would then have the ability to share the information with the FAA5. Where drones that don't have remote identification would be required to flyVOICEOVER (in English): "The Federal Aviation Administration has proposed using remote identification for unmanned aircraft systems, or drones, in the U.S.""The agency proposes that drones in U.S. airspace would have to meet one of three remote identification requirements: the standard remote identification; limited remote identification; or those without any remote identification.""A standard remote identification drone includes equipment that is able to connect to the internet and transmit remote identification messages to a Remote ID unmanned service supplier as well as broadcast these messages directly while in the sky.""A limited remote identification drone is an unmanned vehicle that is capable of connecting to the internet and transmitting remote identification messages to a Remote ID USS, though it is unable to broadcast these messages directly. This type of drone is restricted in operating higher than 400 feet from its control station.""According to an unpublished proposal by the FAA, the Remote ID USS would be required to have the ability to share these messages in near real-time with the FAA, and secure access to such information.""Drones such as amateur built vehicles and previously manufactured aerial vehicles that may not have remote identification capabilities would be required to fly within the visual line of sight and only in FAA-recognized identification areas."SOURCES: Federal Aviation Administration, CNBC, Tech Crunch https://www.faa.gov/uas/research_development/remote_id/https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2019/12/31/2019-28100/remote-identification-of-unmanned-aircraft-systemshttps://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2019/12/31/2019-28100/remote-identification-of-unmanned-aircraft-systemshttps://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/26/faa-remote-id-rule-for-drones-would-enable-tracking-identification.htmlhttps://techcrunch.com/2019/12/26/the-faa-proposes-remote-id-technology-for-drones/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/31/3942737/3942737_26AB8D4741234DDBB0BDF442AEAFF134_191231_3942737_Remote_ID_system_proposed_for_drones_in_U_S__air_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, FAA, remote ID drones, drone remote ID, remote ID for drones, standard remote identification UAS, limited remote identification UAS, drone regulation, remote identification of drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942717</guid>
      <title>How humpback whales hunt down tiny fish</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that the rorqual whale species, particularly humpback whales, are able to use stealth and deception to prey on tiny fish.In a Stanford University news release, scientists said they were curious as to why the small fish weren't able to escape from their predator.The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, suggests that the precise timing of the whale opening its mouth to engulf the fish allows it to avoid triggering an escape response in them.When researchers monitored anchovies' escape reaction to a virtual whale, they found that by the time the fish responded to the whale's predatory behavior, it had already expanded its jaw to capture them.The study suggests that humpback whales wait to open their jaws until they are extremely close to tiny fish in order to engulf them, a method called lunge-feeding.When whales lunge after tiny fish, their jaws expand to consume a volume of water larger than their own bodies. They then filter out the excess water before swallowing the fish they caught. This technique allows humpback whales to capture 30 to 60 percent of the school of fish at once.  Scientists did not see the whales doing the same when pursuing other prey such as krill. According to the news release, this is due to krill being less responsive to predators.David Cade, a researcher involved in the study, explained in the news release that in terms of evolution, lunge-feeding is a comparatively new eating technique for the whales.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How whales are able to prey on tiny fish2. The whale uses precise timing to engulf the small fish3. By the time the small fish responds, the whale has already expanded its jaw to capture the fish4. How the method of lunge-feeding worksVOICEOVER (in English): "New research has found that the rorqual whale species, particularly humpback whales, are able to use stealth and deception to prey on tiny fish.""In a Stanford University news release, scientists said they were curious as to why the small fish weren't able to escape from their predator.""The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, suggests that the precise timing of the whale opening its mouth to engulf the fish allows it to avoid triggering an escape response in them.""When researchers monitored anchovies' escape reaction to a virtual whale, they found that by the time the fish responded to the whale's predatory behavior, it had already expanded its jaw to capture them.""The study suggests that humpback whales wait to open their jaws until they are extremely close to tiny fish in order to engulf them, a method called lunge-feeding.""When whales lunge after tiny fish, their jaws expand to consume a volume of water larger than their own bodies. They then filter out the excess water before swallowing the fish they caught.""This technique allows humpback whales to capture 30 to 60 percent of the school of fish at once."  SOURCES: Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, Stanford University, New Atlashttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2019/12/17/1911099116https://phys.org/news/2019-12-whales-stealth-fish.htmlhttps://newatlas.com/science/giant-whales-use-stealth-hunt-tiny-fish/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 02:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/12/31/3942717/3942717_36F864A89F35444B9A77B791767BB8FC_191231_3942717_How_humpback_whales_hunt_down_tiny_fish_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Giant whales, giant whales stealth, whales use stealth, stealth whales, giant whale tiny prey, humpback whales, Rorqual whales, schooling fish, Lunge-feeding whales, whales eating fish]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
