<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3741814</guid>
      <title>Man abandons plans to swim across the Pacific Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA French-American swimming to raise awareness of plastic pollution in the oceans, has abandoned plans to swim across the Pacific Ocean after the mainsail of his support ship was damaged.The BBC reports that Ben Lecomte set off from Japan's east coast with plans to swim 9,100 kilometers across the Pacific Ocean from Choshi, Japan to San Francisco, California.Lecomte, accompanied by crew operating the support ship, started on June 5 and swam for about eight hours a day, collecting bits and pieces of plastic they spotted on the way.Lecomte had already completed 2,780 kilometers of the trip when the mainsail of his support ship was abruptly damaged by strongs winds, reports The Guardian.Lecomte and the crew had just reached the Great Pacific Garbage Patch when the mainsail was destroyed.Lecomte and his support team originally planned to swim across the Great Pacific Garbage Patch to collect water samples to test plastic pollution levels in the ocean.On his website, Lecomte claims he was the first person to swim across the Atlantic Ocean in 1998.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map showing the distance from Choshi, Japan to San Francisco2. Lecomte swimming and collecting plastic pieces3. Mainsail of the support vessel getting damaged4. Water samples from the Great Pacific Garbage PatchVOICEOVER (in English): "Ben Lecomte had set off from Japan's east coast with plans to swim 9,100 kilometers across the Pacific Ocean from Choshi, Japan to San Francisco, California.""Lecomte started on June 5 accompanied by crew operating the support ship. He swam for about eight hours a day, collecting bits and pieces of plastic they spotted on the way.""The Guardian reports Lecomte already completed 2,780 kilometers of the trip when the mainsail of his support ship was abruptly damaged by strongs winds.""He and his team originally planned to swim across the Great Pacific Garbage Patch to collect water samples to test plastic pollution levels in the ocean."SOURCES: The Guardian, The BBC, Reuters, Japan Times, Seeker, Ben Lecomte.comhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/27/great-pacific-garbage-patch-swimmer-forced-to-stop-after-nearly-3000kmhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-46357309https://www.reuters.com/article/us-swimming-pacific/swimming-trans-pacific-bid-ends-after-storm-damages-support-boat-idUSKCN1NV21Dhttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2018/11/27/national/ben-lecomte-ends-bid-swim-japan-across-pacific-support-boat-suffers-damage/#.XACkBIiFNjUhttps://www.seeker.com/conservation/ben-lecomtes-mainsail-suffers-irreparable-damageshttp://benlecomte.com/#***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/03/3741814/3741814_8084CF9189584C1CADE79ECEFBF7ECE3_181203_3741814_Man_abandons_plans_to_swim_across_the_Pacific_Oc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Pacific Ocean, great pacific garbage patch, swimming across the great pacific garbage patch, Ben Lecomte, swimming across the Pacific Ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3741720</guid>
      <title>Overworked South Koreans stay in mock prisons to escape daily life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn South Korea, people who want to escape from the demands of everyday life can do so by staying in a mock jail.According to a Reuters report, the average South Korean worked about 2,024 hours in 2017  the third longest in a survey of 36 OECD countries.To seek relief, office workers and students are paying $90 a night to stay in a mock prison facility in Hongcheon, where they spend 24 hours locked up in solitary confinement.Clients sleep on the floor of a spartan 54-square-foot cell, which has a small toilet, but no clock or mirror. They wear blue prison uniforms and given accommodation kits with a yoga mat, tea set, pen and notebook.Speaking to each other is forbidden, as is the use of mobile phones. Meals are fed through a slot in the door, and consist of steamed sweet potato and a banana shake for dinner, and rice porridge for breakfast.The 'Prison Inside Me' facility has been open for five years, and has hosted over 2,000 'inmates.' Founder Noh Ji-Hyang claims she was inspired her prosecutor husband, who worked 100-hour work weeks.She says people are wary of paying to stay in a prison cell until they actually do it and realize the real prison is the one outside.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Average hours worked by South Koreans in 20172. 24-hour solitary confinement inside mock prison facility 3. Inside mock prison cell 4. Depiction of strict prison rules, minimal mealsVOICEOVER (in English): "The average person in South Korea worked about 2,024 hours in 2017  the third longest in a survey of 36 OECD countries.""To seek relief, overworked South Koreans are paying $90 to stay in a mock prison in Hongcheon, where they spend 24 hours locked up in solitary confinement.""Clients sleep on the floor of a spartan 54-square-foot cell, which has a small toilet, but no clock or mirror. They wear blue prison uniforms and given accommodation kits with a yoga mat, tea set, pen and notebook.""Speaking to each other is forbidden, as is the use of mobile phones. Meals are fed through a slot in the door, and consist of steamed sweet potato and a banana shake for dinner, and rice porridge for breakfast."SOURCES: Reutershttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-prisonstay-idUSKCN1NS0JB?utm_source=reddit.com***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/03/3741720/3741720_D691F9BED60749918DFCC00A68B7506F_181203_3741720_Overworked_South_Koreans_stay_in_mock_prisons_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, prison break, prison stay, fake prison, overwork, south korea, prison inside me, prison, solitary confinement, south korea work culture, work life balance, weekend getaway, mock prison]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3741597</guid>
      <title>Congo witnesses second deadliest Ebola outbreak in history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to local health authorities, there are now 426 cases of Ebola in eastern Congo.Reports by the World Health Organization show there are a total of 14 health zones with confirmed and probable cases of Ebola virus disease in the North Kivu and Ituri provinces of the Democratic Republic of the Congo.The Ebola virus is transferred to humans through contact with fluids of dead wild animals that are hosts to the virus. The virus can then be transmitted among the human population through direct contact with contaminated body fluids such as sweat, saliva, blood and sexual fluids.It takes the virus up to 21 days to incubate. Muscle pain, fever, weakness and headaches are among the first symptoms. As the disease advances, symptoms can include vomiting, rash and bleeding from eyes and gums.WHO authorities stated that there is a very high chance of the outbreak spreading to areas surrounding North Kivu and Ituri, as well as to neighboring countries.Local health workers and health organizations on site are doing their best to contain the virus through vaccination, community engagement and by practicing safe burials of contagious bodies.CBC reports there are 300 WHO specialists in the area, and more than 37,000 people have received Ebola vaccinations.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Geographic location of confirmed and probable cases of Ebola virus2. Depiction of transmission of Ebola virus to humans3. Depiction of transmission of virus incubation and disease symptoms 4. Representation of spread of disease to neighboring countriesVOICEOVER (in English): "Reports by the World Health Organization show there are a total of 14 health zones with confirmed and probable cases of Ebola virus disease in the North Kivu and Ituri provinces of the Democratic Republic of the Congo.""The Ebola virus is transferred to humans through contact with fluids of dead wild animals that are hosts to the virus." "The virus can then be transmitted among the human population through direct contact with contaminated body fluids such as sweat, saliva, blood and sexual fluids.""It takes the virus up to 21 days to incubate. Muscle pain, fever, weakness and headaches are among the first symptoms." "As the disease advances, symptoms can include vomiting, rash and bleeding from eyes and gums.""WHO authorities stated that there is a very high chance of the outbreak spreading to areas surrounding North Kivu and Ituri, as well as to neighboring countries."SOURCES: World Health Organization http://www.who.int/csr/don/29-november-2018-ebola-drc/en/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 05:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/03/3741597/3741597_FBDC5E00E4EE4EB49F0D2B97ABA963A2_181203_3741597_Congo_witnesses_second_deadliest_Ebola_outbreak__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, graphic, ebola virus, virus, viral outbreak, Congo, West Africa, ebola outbreak, congo ebola outbreak, ebola outbreak in congo,ebola outbreak news, ebola outbreak congo, health, world, news, world news, conflict, humanitarian agencies, Congo, infectious diseases, disease, illness, healthcare, united nations, world health organization.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3742440</guid>
      <title>U.S. Army developing exoskeletons for soldiers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. army is developing exoskeleton technology to make soldiers deployed out in the battlefield stronger and more resilient. The exoskeleton is being developed by Lockheed Martin Corporation with a license from Canada-based B-TEMIA, which first developed the technology to help people suffering from medical related mobility issues, according to Reuters. The battery-operated exoskeleton is worn over a soldier's pants and uses sensors, artificial intelligence and other technology to aid in natural movements. Modern U.S. soldiers are now deployed into war zones carrying anywhere from 90 to 140 pounds of critical gear, including body armor, night-vision goggles and advanced radios, while the recommended limit is only 50 pounds. The goal of the exoskeleton would be to lighten the load soldiers must carry, so when they arrive at the battlefield, they aren't excessively fatigued.  According to Reuters, Lockheed Martin said last Thursday it was awarded a two-year $6.9 million contract from the U.S. Army Natick Soldier Research, Development and Engineering Center to research and develop the ONYX exoskeleton.Keith Maxwell, the exoskeleton technologies manager at Lockheed Martin Missiles and Fire Control, told Reuters that each exoskeleton is expected to cost in the tens of thousands of dollars.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Soldier wearing the ONYX exoskeleton2. Soldier running with ONYX exoskeleton on3. Soldiers carrying 90 to 140 pounds of critical gear4. Soldiers wearing and using ONYX exoskeletonsVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. army is developing exoskeleton technology to make soldiers deployed out in the battlefield stronger and more resilient." "According to Reuters, Lockheed Martin said last Thursday it was awarded a two-year $6.9 million contract from the U.S. Army Natick Soldier Research, Development and Engineering Center to research and develop the ONYX exoskeleton.""The battery-operated exoskeleton is worn over a soldier's pants and uses sensors, artificial intelligence and other technology to aid in natural movements." "Modern U.S. soldiers are now deployed into war zones carrying anywhere from 90 to 140 pounds of critical gear, including body armor, night-vision goggles and advanced radios, while the recommended limit is only 50 pounds." "The goal of the exoskeleton would be to lighten the load soldiers must carry, so when they arrive at the battlefield, they aren't excessively fatigued."  SOURCES: Reuters https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-military-exoskeleton-idUSKCN1NY2Y4?utm_campaign=trueAnthem:%20Trending%20Content&utm_content=5c00cafa04d3012a55efb7b4&utm_medium=trueAnthem&utm_source=twitter***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/04/3742440/3742440_0F6963F947CD4A64A416CBC81B5F120F_181204_3742440_U_S__Army_developing_exoskeletons_for_soldiers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US army exoskeleton, soldier exoskeleton, Lockheed Martin ONYX exoskeleton, ONYK exoskeleton, exoskeleton, Lockheed Martin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3742426</guid>
      <title>Trump administration hurries plans to drill oil in Alaska refuge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Trump administration is expediting plans to drill oil in northeast Alaska, in what is believed to be North America's largest untapped onshore reserve of oil.National Geographic reports that when Alaska's Arctic National Wildlife Refuge was created in 1980, Congress deferred a decision to manage 1.5 million acres of the coastal plain, which the USGS estimates to contain 10.4 billion barrels of oil.For decades, opposition to drilling helped keep the refuge off limits. But Trump and the Republicans are now paving the way for oil exploration.The New York Times reports that in 2017, a provision to allow for drilling in the Arctic refuge was inserted into a tax bill that was approved by the Senate and signed into law by the President. The provision authorized two lease sales of drilling rights for 400,000 acres each.Drilling plans are overseen by officials committed to oil exploration. Opponents fear the process may not be impartial, especially with speedy and less rigorous environmental impact assessments.Environmentalists are also concerned that seismic testing and eventual drilling in the refuge could threaten wildlife, including crucial habitats for caribou and polar bears.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Oil reserves in Alaska's Arctic National Wildlife Refuge2. Provisions for oil drilling passed with 2017 tax law3. Drilling overseen by Alaska-friendly officials; environmental studies fast-tracked4. Oil drilling in Alaska potentially threatening wildlife habitatsVOICEOVER (in English): "When Alaska's Arctic National Wildlife Refuge was created in 1980, Congress deferred a decision to manage 1.5 million acres of the coastal plain, which the USGS estimates to contain 10.4 billion barrels of oil.""In 2017, a provision to allow for drilling in the Arctic refuge was inserted into a tax bill that was approved by the Senate and signed into law by the President.""The provision authorized two lease sales of drilling rights for 400,000 acres each.""According to the New York Times, drilling plans are overseen by officials committed to oil exploration. Opponents fear the process may not be impartial, especially with speedy and less rigorous environmental impact assessments.""Environmentalists are also concerned that seismic testing and eventual drilling in the refuge could threaten wildlife, including crucial habitats for caribou and polar bears."SOURCES: New York Times, Nationhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/03/us/oil-drilling-arctic-national-wildlife-refuge.htmlhttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/magazine/2018/06/arctic-national-wildlife-refuge-america-oil-risk/https://naturalresources.house.gov/anwr/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/04/3742426/3742426_3776EF5EAA30426786552585520EB496_181204_3742426_Trump_administration_hurries_plans_to_drill_oil__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, alaska oil drilling, arctic oil drilling, oil drilling, arctic drilling, alaska oil, arctic national wildlife refuge, ANWR, North Slope, Area 1002, fossil fuels, oil reserves]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3742328</guid>
      <title>Residents of El Paso to drink treated sewage water</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDrought caused by climate change is forcing El Paso, Texas residents to find alternate sources of water.The city used to get most of its water from the Rio Grande which, due to rising temperatures, has been drying up, according to CNN.Scientists say the river used to receive additional water in the form of runoff and snowmelt 20 to 30 years ago.Residents have already reduced their daily water consumption by more than 35 percent since 1985, according to CNN.El Paso is now looking to become one of the first cities in the U.S. to treat sewage water and turn it into drinking water.The city is working to build a closed loop facility to treat the sewage water with multiple steps of filtration such as carbon and UV filtration to make sure there are no pathogens or microbes present.Gilbert Trejo, the chief technical officer of El Paso Water, told CNN technology helps the water be 'treated to a very high standard' making it safe to drink.El Paso also plans to use other techniques such as desalination to produce more drinkable water.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Drought in El Paso2. Rio Grande drying up3. El Paso on a map and a glass of sewage water turned into drinking water4. The process of treating sewage waterVOICEOVER (in English): "Drought caused by climate change is forcing El Paso, Texas residents to find alternate sources of water.""CNN reports the city used to get most of its water from the Rio Grande which, due to rising temperatures, has been drying up.""El Paso is now looking to become one of the first cities in the U.S. to treat sewage water and turn it into drinking water.""The city is working to build a closed loop facility to treat the sewage water with multiple steps of filtration such as carbon and UV filtration to make sure there are no pathogens or microbes present."SOURCES: CNN, Fox 13, WFTS-TVhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/30/health/water-climate-change-el-paso/index.htmlhttps://fox13now.com/2018/12/01/el-paso-to-drink-treated-sewage-water-due-to-climate-change-drought/https://www.abcactionnews.com/news/national/el-paso-texas-residents-to-drink-treated-sewage-water-due-to-climate-change-drought***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/04/3742328/3742328_769644362A4241F89B705950EE706A16_181204_3742328_Residents_of_El_Paso_to_drink_treated_sewage_wat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, USA, Texas, El Paso, sewage water, climate change, drought, treated sewage water, sewage water treatment process, sewage water to drinking water, El Paso drought]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3742169</guid>
      <title>Saudi crown prince communicated with adviser overseeing Khashoggi killing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe CIA has evidence of multiple messages between the Saudi crown prince and the adviser who oversaw the Khashoggi assassination  bolstering the agency's assessment that the prince masterminded the murder.The Washington Post reports that according to a leaked CIA report, Prince Mohammed bin Salman sent at least 11 messages to a close personal aide before and after the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi.The aide, Saud Al-Qahtani, reportedly supervised the 15-man team that killed Khashoggi on October 2, and communicated directly with the team's leader Maher Mutreb in Istanbul.According to the New York Times, Turkish intelligence recorded Mutreb on a phone call, saying 'tell your boss' that the mission had been carried out. It's believed he was talking to Qahtani.In communications intercepted by the U.S. intelligence community in August 2017, the prince told associates that if Khashoggi could not be persuaded to return to Saudi Arabia, they could lure him outside the country and make arrangements.The content and form of the prince's messages to Qahtani are unknown, and there's currently no evidence irrefutably linking him to the killing.Despite this, this, the CIA believes such an operation would not have been possible without his awareness or involvement.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Messages exchanged between Saudi crown prince and adviser during Khashoggi killing2. 15-man team sent to kill Khashoggi in Saudi consulate in Istanbul3. Khashoggi attacked inside consulate4. Maher Mutreb calling Saud Al-Qahtani after Khashoggi killing5. Prince Mohammed planning to lure Khashoggi out of Saudi ArabiaVOICEOVER (in English): "Prince Mohammed bin Salman sent at least 11 messages to a close personal aide before and after the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi, according to a leaked CIA report.""The aide, Saud Al-Qahtani, reportedly supervised the 15-man team that killed Khashoggi on October 2, and communicated directly with the team's leader Maher Mutreb in Istanbul.""According to the New York Times, Turkish intelligence recorded Mutreb on a phone call, saying 'tell your boss' that the mission had been carried out. It's believed he was talking to Qahtani.""In communications intercepted by the U.S. intelligence community in August 2017, the prince told associates that if Khashoggi could not be persuaded to return to Saudi Arabia, they could lure him outside the country and make arrangements."SOURCES: New York Times, Washington Post, Al Jazeerahttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/02/us/politics/crown-prince-mohammed-qahtani-intercepts.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/saudi-crown-prince-exchanged-messages-with-aide-alleged-to-have-overseen-khashoggi-killing/2018/12/01/faa43758-f5c3-11e8-9240-e8028a62c722_story.html?utm_term=.ceb96eb44ab5https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/mbs-communicated-adviser-khashoggi-killing-wsj-181201104013900.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/04/3742169/3742169_CB2FE29B26BB49C3AD27079B107D6AD9_181204_3742169_Saudi_crown_prince_communicated_with_adviser_ove_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, khashoggi, jamal khashoggi, khashoggi killing, journalist, mohammed bin salman, saudi crown prince, saudi consulate, saudi arabia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3742777</guid>
      <title>Denmark to send unwanted migrants to remote island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Danish government plans to banish migrant criminals to a remote island in an inlet of the Baltic Sea. According to the New York Times, up to 100 foreign criminals and rejected asylum seekers living in Denmark who cannot be deported for legal reasons will be sent to a 17-acre island called Lindholm about three kilometers away from the mainland. Ferry services would allow the foreigners to leave the island. However, they would not operate around the clock and migrants would have to be back in the island before nightfall.Lindholm Island currently hosts a research center for contagious animal diseases.  The plan was developed between Denmark's conservative coalition government and the right-wing Danish People's Party, whose support the government needs to pass legislation. The Danish People's Party celebrated the plan by posting a video on Twitter showing a brown man dressed in generic Middle Eastern clothes being dumped on the island.The Danish government will invest US$115 million in migrant housing facilities in Lindholm Island, which are projected to open in 2021.The rising number of migrants coming from the Middle East has divided Denmark. In August, hundreds took to the streets to protest after the government enacted what is known as the "burka ban."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Explanation of deportation and location of Lindholm Island 2. Representation of ferry services in Lindholm Island3. Representation of collaboration between Danish government and Danish People's Party4. Depiction of Danish government investment in infrastructure in Lindholm Island VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the New York Times, up to 100 foreign criminals and rejected asylum seekers living in Denmark who cannot be deported for legal reasons will be sent to a 17-acre island called Lindholm about three kilometers away from the mainland. ""Ferry services would allow the foreigners to leave the island. However, they would not operate around the clock and migrants would have to be back on the island before nightfall.""The plan was developed between Denmark's conservative coalition government and the right-wing Danish People's Party.""The Danish government will invest US$115 million in migrant housing facilities in Lindholm Island, which are projected to open in 2021."SOURCES: The New York Timeshttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/03/world/europe/denmark-migrants-island.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/05/3742777/3742777_DA6484F9D5AE473CBBA38EE2AEBA8698_181205_3742777_Denmark_to_send_unwanted_migrants_to_remote_isla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, denmark, immigration, right of asylum, deportation, human rights, refugees, internally displaced people, danish people's party, foreign criminals, lindholm, world, news, island, refugee, refugees, asylum seekers, middle east, danish, migrant crisis, ban, crisis, migration, migrants, danish society.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3743482</guid>
      <title>Scientists combine cancer drugs to treat melanoma</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have combined two experimental cancer drugs to treat melanoma.As part of a study published in the journal Molecular Cancer Therapeutics, researchers paired protein kinase inhibitors and ribonuclease before releasing them onto cancerous tumors.The protein kinases inhibitors work to bind and block the functions of enzymes that have been affected by cancer cells. This slows the spread of the disease. The ribonuclease then works to enter the tumor and destroy its RNA.The study found that the drug combination worked more effectively to treat melanoma than individual treatments of each drug.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Protein kinase inhibitors and ribonuclease, along with cross-section of melanoma2. The combined drugs being released onto the tumor3. The protein kinase inhibitors and ribonuclease working together to destroy cancer cells4. Protein kinase inhibitors and ribonuclease combined working to treat melanoma on the skinVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have combined protein kinase inhibitors and ribonuclease  two experimental cancer drugs   to treat melanoma.""As part of a study published in the journal Molecular Cancer Therapeutics, researchers paired both together and released them onto cancerous tumors.""The protein kinases inhibitors work to bind and block the functions of enzymes that have been affected by cancer cells. "This slows the spread of the disease.""The ribonuclease then works to enter the tumor and destroy its RNA.""The study found that the drug combination worked more effectively to treat melanoma than individual treatments of each drug."SOURCES:New Atlas,  Molecular Cancer Therapeutics, Technology Networks.com, Science Daily, Medical News Today, MIT News, https://newatlas.com/two-experimental-cancer-drugs-team-up/57504/http://mct.aacrjournals.org/content/17/12/2622https://www.technologynetworks.com/cancer-research/news/drug-combo-could-be-more-effective-against-melanoma-312795https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/12/181203131130.htmhttps://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/323884.phphttp://news.mit.edu/2018/new-drug-combination-melanoma-1203***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/06/3743482/3743482_281D1B2A8E7B4BF0B684B53D5ED1DFE3_181206_3743482_Scientists_combine_cancer_drugs_to_treat_melanom_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, melanoma, MIT, experimental cancer drugs, protein kinase inhibitors, RNA, cancer, cancer cells, melanoma cancer, melanoma treatment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3743416</guid>
      <title>2018 Nobel Prize for Medicine awarded to duo's work on cancer immunotherapy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe 2018 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine was awarded to James P. Allison and Tasuku Honjo for their work in harnessing the body's immune system to fight against cancer. Allison and Honjo established a link between immunotherapy and cancer treatment by identifying how the different cells interact with each other. According to the Conversation, Allison and Honjo were able to identify certain pathways, called "immune checkpoints," that actively stop immune cells from attacking cancerous tumors. These pathways inhibit the body's T-cellswhite blood cells that destroy infected cells and tumor cellsand prevent them from locating and attacking tumors. Allison and Honjo identified two separate proteins located on the surface of T-cells, CTLA-4 and PD-1, that interact with tumor cell proteins causing T-cells to not attack the tumor. Allison and Honjo's research led to the development of immune checkpoint inhibitors, monoclonal antibodies that block the regulatory pathways controlled by CTLA-4 and PD-1. These drugs attach to the CTLA-4 and PD-1 proteins and prevent them from turning off the T-cells. With some cancers, these new drugs have led to significant tumor regressions. The FDA has approved their use for several advanced cancers such as: metastatic melanoma, lung cancer, kidney cancer, bladder cancer head and neck cancers and other tumors.   However, there can be significant risks as well. Immune checkpoint inhibitors can cause damaging inflammation in the skin, gut, heart, lungs and other vital organs. In addition, the long-term effects of the new drugs are also currently unknown.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. T cells being inhibited from attacking tumor2. CTLA-4 and PD-1 proteins one surface of T cell3. Immune checkpoint inhibitors4. FDA has approved use of immune checkpoint inhibitors for several cancersVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Conversation, James P. Allison and Tasuku Honjo were able to identify certain pathways, called "immune checkpoints," that actively stop immune cells from attacking cancerous tumors." "These pathways inhibit the body's T-cellswhite blood cells that destroy infected cells and tumor cellsand prevent them from locating and attacking tumors." "Allison and Honjo identified two separate proteins located on the surface of T-cells, CTLA-4 and PD-1, that interact with tumor cell proteins causing T-cells to not attack the tumor." "Their research led to the development of immune checkpoint inhibitors, monoclonal antibodies that block the regulatory pathways controlled by CTLA-4 and PD-1." "These drugs attach to the CTLA-4 and PD-1 proteins and prevent them from turning off the T-cells." "The new drugs have led to significant tumor regressions. The FDA has approved their use for several advanced cancers such as: metastatic melanoma, lung cancer, kidney cancer, bladder cancer head and neck cancers and other tumors."   SOURCES: The Conversation, Lab Matehttp://theconversation.com/2018-nobel-prize-in-physiology-or-medicine-a-turning-point-in-the-war-on-cancer-104191https://www.labmate-online.com/news/laboratory-products/3/breaking-news/who-won-the-2018-nobel-prize-in-medicine/47400***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/06/3743416/3743416_84A2DC3969E64CA4A1CA6C3506A1B9E4_181206_3743416_2018_Nobel_Prize_for_Medicine_awarded_to_duo_s_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, immunotherapy, Nobel Prize Medicine, immune checkpoint, immune checkpoint inhibitors, James P. Allison, Tasuku Honjo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3743380</guid>
      <title>Drone delivery service to begin in Finland by 2019</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDrone delivery company, Wing, projects to begin services in Helsinki, Finland in spring 2019.Drones developed by the Alphabet subsidiary company provide pick-up and delivery services. The company started testing their services in Australia since 2014 and are now ready to start another trial in Finland in spring of 2019.According to the company, the drones are designed in-house. Their current model features fixed wings similar to an airplane, helicopter-like rotors and a wingspan less than 1.5 metersEach drone weighs about 5 kilograms and is able to carry packages weighing up to 1.5 kilograms. The drones are able to fly roughly 20 kilometers round trip. The company uses a special Unmanned Traffic Management platform which is an automated system that manages the drone's flight paths.During their tests in Australia the company delivered, food, bottled water and batteries to farmers in Queensland.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of drone delivery service starting in Australia and later projected to begin in Finland2. Depiction of size and model of drone3. Depiction of drone carrying then lowering package4. Representation of flight path management systemVOICEOVER (in English): "Drones developed by Alphabet's subsidiary company, Wing, provide pick-up and delivery services. The company started testing their services in Australia in 2014 and is now ready to start another trial in Finland as soon as spring of 2019.""The drones are designed in-house. Their current model features fixed wings similar to an airplane, helicopter-like rotors and a wingspan less than 1.5 meters""Each drone weighs about 5 kg and is able to carry packages weighing up to 1.5 kilograms. The drones are able to fly roughly 20 kilometers round trip. ""The company uses a special Unmanned Traffic Management platform, which is an automated system that manages the drone's flight paths."SOURCES: Winghttps://www.wing.com/finlandhttps://www.wing.com***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/06/3743380/3743380_6A32EBB4470341CB8A366466A76222F5_181206_3743380_Drone_delivery_service_to_begin_in_Finland_by_20_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Google, Googlex, Alphabet, Wing, Project Wing, self-flying vehicles, experiment, drone, drone delivery, packages, Finland, Australia, Wing, tech, technology, science, new, x, Helsinki, trial.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3743280</guid>
      <title>New eco-friendly superyacht to operate on wind turbines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrench designer Mathis Ruhl has revealed designs of a new superyacht, called the "Wind Motion 70T."According to Ruhl's website, the yacht is expected to be 70 meters long. Its rig features an updated version of the rotating twin mast concept, which results in higher aerodynamic efficiency.Hydraulic wind turbines unfold from the sails to recharge the batteries when resting at anchor, eliminating the need to return to land to refuel.The eco-friendly vessel will be able to cruise at speeds of up to 23 miles per hour, and will also feature a foredeck and alfresco areas.Ruhl has revealed details of a larger version of the yacht, but has yet to reveal how much each one costs, and when it will be available.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The superyacht with its sails down2. The yacht with its sails up in the ocean3. Hydraulic wind turbines4. Yacht cruising in the oceanVOICEOVER (in English): "French designer Mathis Ruhl has revealed designs of a new superyacht, called the 'Wind Motion 70T.'""The yacht is expected to be 70 meters long. Its rig features an updated version of the rotating twin mast concept, which results in higher aerodynamic efficiency.""Hydraulic wind turbines unfold from the sails to recharge the batteries when resting at anchor, eliminating the need to return to land to refuel.""The eco-friendly vessel will be able to cruise at speeds of up to 23 miles per hour, and will also feature a foredeck and alfresco areas."SOURCES:Super Yachts.com, Superyacht Times,  Yachtemoceans.com, Mathisruhl.comhttp://www.superyachts.com/news/meet-70-metre-concept-wind-motion-8958.htmhttp://www.superyachts.com/motor-yacht-11625/wind-motion-70t.htmhttps://www.superyachttimes.com/yacht-news/radical-new-70m-trimaran-superyacht-concepthttps://yachtemoceans.com/wind-motion-70-trimaran-mathis-ruhl/http://www.mathisruhl.com/P-WM70T.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/06/3743280/3743280_CAE77336D2DD44718E3B00EA750BD156_181206_3743280_New_eco_friendly_superyacht_to_operate_on_wind_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, France, superyacht, yacht,  french superyacht, Wind Motion 70T, eco-friendly superyacht, Rotating Twin Mast, hydraulic wind turbines, Mathis Ruhl, eco-friendly yacht]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3744216</guid>
      <title>Thales Alenia Space to build radar satellites for South Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA European satellite manufacturer has announced that it will be developing high performance satellites for South Korea.Thales Alenia Space announced in a press release that it had signed contracts with Korean Aerospace Industries and Hanwha Systems Corp. to build four high-resolution radar satellites for the Agency of Defense Development in South Korea.The company will provide the synthetic aperture radar payloads for the remote sensing satellites, which will allow all-day imaging of the Earth, even through cloud cover.The SAR satellites will be fitted with a specialized 5-meter antenna, which will be folded as 24 "petals" and open once in space.Korean authorities will reportedly be using the constellation of satellites for "surveillance, intelligence and control of specific areas of interest."The collaboration, known as the 425 project, is the latest venture between Thales Alenia Space and South Korea. The company has previously worked on a number of space programs, including KOMPSAT-5 and KASS.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Radar satellites to be developed by Thales Alenia Space 2. SAR payload will allow all-day imaging of Earth3. Satellite folded as 24 petals opening in space4. Satellite used in South Korea surveillance, intelligenceVOICEOVER (in English): "Thales Alenia Space signed contracts with Korean Aerospace Industries and Hanwha Systems Corp. to build four high-resolution radar satellites for the Agency of Defense Development in South Korea.""The company will provide the synthetic aperture radar payloads for the remote sensing satellites, which will allow all-day imaging of the Earth, even through cloud cover.""The SAR satellites will be fitted with a specialized 5-meter antenna, which will be folded as 24 'petals' and open once in space.""Korean authorities will reportedly be using the constellation of satellites for 'surveillance, intelligence and control of specific areas of interest.'"SOURCES: Thales Alenia Space, Space Newshttps://www.thalesgroup.com/en/worldwide/space/press-release/thales-alenia-space-will-support-korean-aerospace-industryhttps://spacenews.com/thales-alenia-space-to-build-four-radar-satellites-for-south-korea/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/07/3744216/3744216_9C6C98C74BA649E89EA915EFA8BA17E0_181207_3744216_Thales_Alenia_Space_to_build_radar_satellites_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, radar satellite, SAR satellite, thales alenia space, south korea satellites, satellite imaging, satellite surveillance, surveillance, 425 project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3743993</guid>
      <title>Greenland's meltwater increasing rate of sea level rise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a paper published in the journal Nature, researchers extracted ice core data in order to examine rates of surface melt and run-off in Greenland.    Ice cores are long tubes of ice and snow samples drilled from an ice-sheet or glacier. Each layer contains key climate information including changes in atmospheric carbon dioxide levels, and climate stability.The data examined goes back 339 years. The first signs of meltwater date back to the mid-1800s, coinciding with the beginning of the industrial revolution."  Data from the research revealed Greenland's ice sheets are melting more quickly than they ever have in the last 350 years.According to data from the UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, meltwater from Greenland contributes to roughly 20 percent of the world's sea-level rise.  If all the ice in Greenland melted, sea levels would rise by seven meters. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of Greenland2. Depiction of scientists extracting ice cores3. Portrayal of data found in ice cores4. Representation of Greenland ice sheets melting and sea level rising VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a paper published in the journal Nature, researchers extracted ice core data in order to examine rates of surface melt and run-off in Greenland." "Ice cores are long tubes of ice and snow samples drilled from an ice-sheet or glacier. Each layer contains key climate information including changes in atmospheric carbon dioxide levels, and climate stability.""The data examined goes back 339 years. The first signs of meltwater date back to the mid-1800s, coinciding with the beginning of the industrial revolution."  "Data from the research revealed Greenland's ice sheets are melting more quickly than they ever have in the last 350 years." "According to data from the UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, meltwater from Greenland contributes to roughly 20 percent of the world's sea-level rise."  "If all the ice in Greenland melted, sea levels would rise by seven meters." SOURCES: Nature, UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Changehttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-018-0752-4https://www.ipcc.ch/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/07/3743993/3743993_8146898F95A946DFAB2BC9374E2240F0_181207_3743993_Greenland_s_meltwater_increasing_rate_of_sea_lev_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, wildlife, ecology, climate change, greenland, icebergs, meltdown, natural disaster, global warming, rising sea levels, science, world news, news, technology, environment, ice, north pole, polar melting, greenland melting, sea level rise, extreme weather, weather, greenhouse gas, global warming, deforestation, desertification, climatic, environmental, pollution, carbon, global climate news, pole flip, abrupt climate change.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3743954</guid>
      <title>North Korea continues work on key missile bases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew images reveal North Korea has been expanding a key missile base, despite denuclearization talk during the historic summit with Trump last June.CNN reports that North Korea's recent lack of ballistic missile testing has been touted as a sign of progress by the Trump administration, but this new evidence suggests Washington and Pyongyang may not be on the same page.Satellite images obtained by CNN from the Middelbury Institute of International Studies at Monterey reveal that North Korea has continued to upgrade the Yeongjeo-dong missile base in the mountainous north and built up another facility seven miles away that hadn't been previously publicly identified.The images indicate that the large underground facility was being built in 2017, and remained under construction as of August 2018.Experts believe the site's unique location makes it a strong candidate to house the country's newest long-range missiles, including those capable of holding a nuclear warhead and striking the U.S.A Middlebury researcher told NPR that hardened drive-thru shelters are being constructed for the vehicles that would carry the missiles. Tunnel entrances are also being built.In the event of an attack, mobile missile launchers can be fueled and armed in the underground facility, and then driven to predetermined sites to fire missiles at the enemy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Yeongjeo-dong and Hoejung-ri missile bases in North Korea2. Hoejung-ri construction 3. Base as suitable host for new long-range ballistic missiles4. Construction of hardened drive-through shelters and tunnel entrancesVOICEOVER (in English): "Satellite images obtained by CNN reveal that North Korea has continued to upgrade the Yeongjeo-dong missile base and built up another facility seven miles away that hadn't been previously publicly identified.""The images indicate that the large underground facility was being built in 2017, and remained under construction as of August 2018.""Experts believe the site's unique location makes it a strong candidate to house the country's newest long-range missiles, including those capable of holding a nuclear warhead and striking the U.S.""Hardened drive-thru shelters are reportedly being constructed for the vehicles that would carry the missiles. Tunnel entrances are also being built."SOURCES: CNN, NPRhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/north-korea-satellite-images-missile-base/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/2018/12/05/673917730/north-korea-seen-expanding-missile-base***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/07/3743954/3743954_E3D578C221444C1B824977E68426A18E_181207_3743954_North_Korea_continues_work_on_key_missile_bases_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea missile base, north korea missile, denuclearization, nuclear missile, north korea, missile base, yeongjeo-dong missile base, yeongjeo-dong, hoejung-ri base, missile test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3745623</guid>
      <title>NYPD starts new drone program</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe NYPD launched its Unmanned Aircraft System program consisting of 14 drones and a group of licensed officials. According to an NYPD press release, the police department launched its Unmanned Aircraft System (UAV) program which consists of NYPD officers form the Technical Assistance Response Unit (TARU) who are licensed to operate Unmanned Aerial Vehicles or drones.The program will operate a total of 14 drones which include 11 small quadcopters for tactical operations, two large weather resistant drones and one drone for training purposes. The drones can be used for tactical operations, search and rescue operations, assistance in hostage situations, and evidence search at large and remote locations among other uses.However, the UAVs cannot be used as weapons or equipped with them nor can they be used to carry out searches without a warrant.There are currently 900 state and local police, fire and emergency units using drones in their departments in the US.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of licensed police officials and drones2. Depiction of drone models that will be used by the program 3. Portrayal of drone uses4. Representation of limitations of drone usageVOICEOVER (in English): "According to an NYPD press release, the police department launched its Unmanned Aircraft System program which consists of NYPD officers form the Technical Assistance Response Unit who are licensed to operate Unmanned Aerial Vehicles or drones.""The program will operate a total of 14 drones which include 11 small quadcopters for tactical operations, two large weather resistant drones and one drone for training purposes. ""The drones can be used for tactical operations, search and rescue operations, assistance in hostage situations, and evidence search at large and remote locations among other uses.""However, the UAVs cannot be used as weapons or equipped with them nor can they be used to carry out searches without a warrant."SOURCES: NYPDhttps://www1.nyc.gov/site/nypd/news/p1204a/nypd-new-unmanned-aircraft-system-program#/0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/10/3745623/3745623_27DB89C8FD3B47A6B688CBF30D2B7D31_181210_3745623_NYPD_starts_new_drone_program_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, News, New York City News, New york, nypd, science, technology, Government and politics, press conference, NYPD, drones, drone cameras, police.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3745353</guid>
      <title>U.S. probing Chinese tech giant Huawei</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. government is investigating Chinese tech giant Huawei for alleged bank fraud and Iranian sanctions violations, Reuters reports.The company's chief financial officer Meng Wanzhou was arrested on December 1 in Canada and could be extradited to the U.S.,  according to Reuters. Huawei has been accused of allegedly using a global banking system to bypass U.S. sanctions against Iran.The U.S. is investigating to see if Huawei has sent American products to Iran and other countries sanctioned by Washington, according to Reuters.No company, U.S. based or otherwise, is allowed to use the American financial system to channel goods and services to nations and individuals on the sanctions list.The U.S. is also looking into whether or not Huawei used HSBC to conduct the alleged transactions. If they did conduct such activities but neglected to inform HSBC, they may have committed bank fraud.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Huawei logo and a bank along with the US flag and Iran's flag2. Huawei logo, electronics and Iran flag3. Huawei and HSBC logo4. Flashing red on a bankVOICEOVER (in English): "Huawei has been accused of allegedly using a global banking system to bypass U.S. sanctions against Iran.""According to Reuters, the U.S. is investigating if Huawei has sent American products to Iran and other countries sanctioned by Washington.""The U.S. is also looking into whether or not Huawei used HSBC to conduct the alleged transactions.""If they did conduct such activities but neglected to inform HSBC, they may have committed bank fraud."SOURCES: Reuters, South China Morning Post, The Globe and Mail, CNBC,https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-tech-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-probe-of-chinas-huawei-includes-bank-fraud-accusations-sources-idUSKBN1O528Dhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/2176790/us-was-probing-huawei-alleged-global-banking-scheme-evade-us-sanctionshttps://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-canada-has-arrested-huaweis-global-chief-financial-officer-in/https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/us-probe-into-huawei-includes-accusations-of-bank-fraud-and-sanctions-violations-reuters.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 03:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/10/3745353/3745353_65D6BBD6543240088EE3AD519CDC2535_181210_3745353_U_S__probing_Chinese_tech_giant_Huawei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, US, Huawei, US sanctions, Meng Wanzhou, huawei under investigation, violating sanctions, bank fraud]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3745326</guid>
      <title>South and North Korea to conduct joint survey on railway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth and South Korea will conduct a joint survey of North Korean railway lines to eventually link the railway systems of the two countries.According to the Hankyoreh, the survey began on November 30 and will take approximately 18 days and cover over 1,200 kilometers.A South Korean train consisting of a locomotive and six passenger cars will be used in the survey.  A North Korean train with three additional North Korean passenger cars would also be linked with the South Korean train.This marks the first time a South Korean train would be travelling over a majority of North Korea's railway lines since the two Koreas were divided.Officials will survey the Seoul-Sinuiju line which goes up to the Chinese border, and the East Sea line which goes as far as Russia's border.NPR reports that the government plans to have railways running along the east and west coast of the Korean Peninsula, with a line linking them in the middle. The railway lines could also potentially connect to the rest of Asia and Europe.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North and South Korea are shown on a globe, as well as the railway track2. South Korean and North Korean trains being linked during inspection3. Seoul-Sinuiju line and the East Sea Line4.  Where the government plans to link the railwayVOICEOVER (in English): "North and South Korea are conducting a joint survey of North Korean railway lines to eventually link the railway system of the two countries, with inspectors covering about 1,200 kilometers over 18 days.""A South Korean train consisting of a locomotive and six passenger cars will be used in the survey." "A North Korean train with three additional North Korean passenger cars would also be linked with the South Korean train, according to The Hankyoreh.""Officials will survey the Seoul-Sinuju line which goes up to the Chinese border and the East Sea line which goes as far as Russia.""The government plans to have railways running along the east and west coast of the Korean Peninsula, with a line linking them in the middle."SOURCES: NPR, CNN, Korea Times, The Washington Post, The Hankyorehhttps://www.npr.org/2018/12/05/672305891/south-korea-sends-first-train-in-plan-to-reconnect-with-northhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/04/opinions/north-korea-progress-on-peace-nathan-park/index.htmlhttps://www.koreatimes.co.kr/www/nation/2018/12/356_259906.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/south-korea-sends-a-train-into-north-for-the-first-time-in-a-decade/2018/11/30/e4942e66-f459-11e8-9240-e8028a62c722_story.html?utm_term=.6f5de310aa20http://english.hani.co.kr/arti/english_edition/e_northkorea/872384.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 02:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/10/3745326/3745326_19C16305613D477FA7E7D204AEA8BB55_181210_3745326_South_and_North_Korea_to_conduct_joint_survey_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, inter korean railway, korea railway, korea rail, DMZ, north korea, south korea, train, north south korea railway, korean peninsula, InterKorean Railway project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3746213</guid>
      <title>US threatens to walk out of the INF treaty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. has threatened to withdraw from the INF nuclear weapons treaty if Russia doesn't adhere to the agreement, the Washington Post reports. The Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty, or INF, was signed between the former Soviet Union and the U.S. 30 years ago.The treaty banned the use of nuclear and non-nuclear missiles with ranges of between 500 and 5,500 kilometers.The INF Treaty helped to eliminate more than 2,600 missiles and helped to end the Cold War.The U.S. claims Russia has violated the treaty by developing and deploying a new ground-launched cruise missile.The U.S. also claims the treaty puts America at a disadvantage with China, which didn't sign the INF Treaty in 1987.The U.S. has officially given Russia 60 days, starting from Dec. 4, to abide by the treaty, or else it will withdraw from it.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. INF treaty, flag of the former U.S.S.R and the U.S.2. The treaty bans missiles with a certain range3. Nuclear missiles being eliminated4. Ground-launch cruise missileVOICEOVER (in English): "The Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty, or INF, was signed between the former Soviet Union and the U.S. 30 years ago.""The treaty banned the use of nuclear and non-nuclear missiles with ranges of between 500 and 5,500 kilometers.""The INF Treaty helped to eliminate more than 2,600 missiles and helped to end the Cold War.""The U.S. claims Russia has violated the treaty by developing and deploying a new ground-launched cruise missile."SOURCES: The Guardian, The Washington Post, https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/us-inf-russia-nuclear-treaty-deadlinehttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/trump-administration-gives-russia-60-days-to-comply-with-inf-treaty-or-the-us-will-move-to-withdraw/2018/12/04/64c5bec2-f74a-11e8-8642-c9718a256cbd_story.html?noredirect=on&utm_term=.83afcb6db0ed***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 10:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/11/3746213/3746213_CF66E3CE40B943F3833B51BFA9ACA095_181211_3746213_US_threatens_to_walk_out_of_the_INF_treaty_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, INF treaty, US, Russia, us russia inf treaty, us russia inf treaty explained, nuclear arms agreement, intermediate-range nuclear forces treaty, inf treaty explained, inf treaty withdrawal, inf treaty russia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3746205</guid>
      <title>China launches probe to explore dark side of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBeijing's mission to the unexplored dark side of the moon got underway over the weekend.China launched its Chang'e-4 lunar probe, which carries a lander and a rover, on Saturday. It is expected to be the first probe to ever make a landing on the far side of the moon. Beijing has not yet announced the official landing date of the probe. However, it is expected to land in early January 2019.The lander would include a landing camera, terrain camera, and a low-frequency spectrometer, while the rover would include a panoramic camera and a visible and a near-Infrared imaging spectrometer, according to Space.com The probe would be able to send data back via the Chinese relay satellite "Queqiao," Xinhua reports Potato, arabidopsis seeds and silkworm eggs will also be taken to the moon, according to Global Times. This will reportedly be to test if they are able to be grown in a low-gravity lunar environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chang'e-4 lunar probe2. The equipment included on the lander3. The equipment included on the rover4. The lunar probe transmitting information via a relay satelliteVOICEOVER (in English): "China launched its Chang'e-4 lunar probe, which carries a lander and a rover, on Saturday.""It is expected to be the first probe to ever make a landing on the far side of the moon.""According to Space.com, the lander would include a landing camera, terrain camera, and a low-frequency spectrometer...""...while the rover would include a panoramic camera and a visible and a near-Infrared imaging spectrometer.""Xinhua reports the probe would be able to send data back via the Chinese relay satellite 'Queqiao'."SOURCES: Space.com, The New York Times, The South China Morning Post, Global Times, Xinhua, https://www.space.com/42665-china-launches-moon-far-side-lander-rover.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/science/china-moon-change-4.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2176935/change-4-launch-chinas-bid-be-first-dark-side-moonhttps://gbtimes.com/heres-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-change-4-mission-to-the-far-side-of-the-moonhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/tech/2018-12/08/c_1123823910.htmhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-12/08/c_137659328.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 10:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/11/3746205/3746205_F81CB134BBF344C797534156FB4E5A3C_181211_3746205_China_launches_probe_to_explore_dark_side_of_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, rover, china rover, far side of the moon, dark side of the moon, china going to the dark side of the moon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3746189</guid>
      <title>US, Russia, Saudi Arabia and Kuwait water down key climate change report at COP24</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe US, Russia, Saudi Arabia, and Kuwait rejected the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change report during discussions held at the 24th Conference of the Parties to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change held in Katowice, Poland.In October, a climate change report by the U.N's IPCC warned governments of the imminent consequences of climate change, urging them to take action.According to a report IPCC report, Earth's temperature risks crossing the 1.5 Celsius threshold by 2030, which would bring about droughts, floods, and extreme heat.The report states that pollution caused by greenhouse gases needs to be cut by 45 percent by 2030 and 100 percent by 2050 in order to prevent a rise in temperature.  This report is being discussed as part of the 24th Conference of the Parties to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change held in Katowice, Poland.According to Reuters, the main goal is for world leaders to develop a rulebook detailing regulations to decelerate climate change in order to meet the Paris agreement goals.However, during discussions held at the conference, the US, Russia, Saudi Arabia, and Kuwait rejected the IPCC climate change report.US authorities claimed data from the report should be 'noted' not 'welcome.'The Kingdom of Saudi Arabia said they hoped the IPCC would address the 'gaps and challenges' in the report.According to Reuters, parties were unable to reach an agreement due to lack of consensus.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of effects of climate change on Earth2. Representation of the 24th Conference of the Parties to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change held in Katowice, Poland3. Depiction of US not supporting IPCC climate change report4. Depiction of Saudi Arabia not supporting IPCC climate change reportVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, Earth's temperature risks crossing the 1.5 Celsius threshold by 2030, which would bring about droughts, floods, and extreme heat.""The report states that pollution caused by greenhouse gases needs to be cut by 45 percent by 2030 and 100 percent by 2050 in order to prevent a rise in temperature. ""This report is being discussed as part of the 24th Conference of the Parties to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change held in Katowice, Poland.""According to Reuters, the main goal is for world leaders to develop a rulebook detailing regulations to decelerate climate change in order to meet the Paris agreement goals.""However, during discussions held at the conference, the US, Russia, Saudi Arabia, and Kuwait rejected the IPCC climate change report.""US authorities claimed data from the report should be 'noted' not 'welcome.'""The Kingdom of Saudi Arabia said they hoped the IPCC would address the 'gaps and challenges' in the report.""According to Reuters, parties were unable to reach an agreement due to lack of consensus."SOURCES: IPCC, Reutershttps://www.ipcc.ch/sr15/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-notebook/katowice-cop24-notebook-spotlight-on-u-s-coal-sideshow-idUSKBN1O9104***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 10:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/11/3746189/3746189_EE40975A1708474FB84255F70D093D84_181211_3746189_US__Russia__Saudi_Arabia_and_Kuwait_water_down_k_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, climate change, global warming, UN report, climate change UN, temperature rising, renewable energy, sea levels rising, sea level rising, UN, Russia, US, USA, America, Kuwait, Saudi Arabia, oil, temperature rise.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3746009</guid>
      <title>Transcript details Jamal Khashoggi's last words: CNN source</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA source claiming to have read the transcript of a recording of Jamal Khashoggi's death has told CNN what the journalist's final words allegedly were.CNN reports that on October 2, Jamal Khashoggi entered the Saudi consulate in Istanbul intending to pick up documents he needed to marry his Turkish fiancee.Instead, he was met inside by Saudi intelligence officer Maher Mutreb, who tells him, "You are coming back", according to a CNN source who read the transcript of the audio tape of the journalist's final moments. Members of the hit squad are then believed to have set upon Khashoggi.The gruesome recording is said to continue with Khashoggi still alive. The transcript notes the sound of screaming, gasping, and a saw presumably dismembering the journalist's body.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Khashoggi entering Saudi consulate in Istanbul2. Khashoggi met inside consulate by Maher Mutreb, attacked by Saudi operatives3. Khashoggi's final words4. Khashoggi being dismembered with a saw5. Mutreb calling Al-Qahtani6. Saudi crown prince exchanging messages with Al-Qahtani7. Saudi forensic expert advising operatives to put earphones during dismemberment8. Saudi operatives leaving consulate9. Khashoggi body doubleVOICEOVER (in English): "On October 2, Jamal Khashoggi entered the Saudi consulate in Istanbul intending to pick up documents he needed to marry his Turkish fiancee.""Instead, he was met inside by intelligence officer Maher Mutreb, who says, 'You are coming back', according to a CNN source who read the transcript of an audio tape of the journalist's final moments.'"Members of the hit squad are then believed to have set upon Khashoggi.""The head of investigations at the Turkish Sabah told Al Jazeera that Khashoggi was suffocated by a plastic bag over his head. His last words are believed to "I can't breathe."""The transcript continues with Khashoggi still alive, and notes the sound of screaming, gasping, and a saw presumably dismembering the journalist's body.""While the moment Khashoggi dies isn't specified, Mutreb reportedly made three phone calls during the scene. He is believed to be talking to Saud Al-Qahtani when he says "Tell yours, the thing is done.""Yours refers to a superior or boss, in this case Crown Prince Mohammad bin Salman, who was found to have exchanged 11 messages with Qahtani around the time Khashoggi was killed.""A voice identified in the transcript as Saudi forensics expert Salah Muhammad al-Tubaiqy is also noted as advising members of the group to put on earphones or listen to music during the dismemberment.""Turkish surveillance video captured Mutreb, Tubaiqy, and 13 other Saudi operatives departing the consulate around 4 p.m., according to earlier CNN reports.""A body double wearing a fake beard and the deceased Khashoggi's clothes was also seen leaving by the back door, reportedly as part of a cover-up."SOURCES: CNN, Al Jazeerahttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/09/middleeast/jamal-khashoggi-last-words-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/middleeast/khashoggi-saudi-hit-squad-forensics-expert-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/suffocating-khashoggi-words-turkish-reporter-181111085534099.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 06:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/11/3746009/3746009_C18622EA4A1E47368699D4E6443DD815_181211_3746009_Transcript_details_Jamal_Khashoggi_s_last_words__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Jamal Khashoggi, Khashoggi, last words, final words, Khashoggi last words, Saudi consulate Istanbul, Khashoggi audio recording, Khashoggi transcript, Saudi journalist, Saudi dissident, MBS, Saudi crown prince, Mohammed bin Salman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3746730</guid>
      <title>Asian countries expanding coal plants in other nations: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina, Japan and South Korea are expanding coal plants in developing nations despite mounting evidence that the climate continues to get worse.A new report published by coal tracking company CoalSwarm shows that these three countries continue to fund coal plant construction in other nations. They are building in places such as Indonesia, Vietnam, South Africa and Bangladesh.China, Japan and South Korea are doing this despite transitioning to renewable energy sources at home, reports CleanTechnica.  Ted Nace, Executive Director of CoalSwarm, told CleanTechnica that they build coal plants overseas to "protect their equipment manufacturers."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. South Korea, China and Japan on a map and a coal plant2. Nations funded by South Korea, China and Japan 3. Renewable energy sources4. Amount of power plants funded by South Korea, China and JapanVOICEOVER (in English): "China, Japan and South Korea are expanding coal plants in developing nations despite mounting evidence that the climate continues to get worse.""A new report published by coal tracking company CoalSwarm shows that these three countries continue to fund coal plant construction in other nations." "They are building in places such as Indonesia, Vietnam, South Africa and Bangladesh."" CleanTechnica reports that China, Japan and South Korea are doing this despite transitioning to renewable energy sources at home.""The report shows China has already funded at least 26 gigawatts of coal plants, which is equivalent to roughly 43 coal power plants.""Japan has financed around 20 gigawatts which is around 32 plants. "And, South Korea has funded at least 8 gigawatts which is around 11 coal power plants."SOURCES: Coal Swarm, Clean Technica, Phys.orghttps://endcoal.org/finance-tracker/https://endcoal.org/2018/12/new-global-coal-finance-tracker/https://cleantechnica.com/2018/12/10/china-japan-south-korea-lead-global-push-to-expand-coal-plants/https://phys.org/news/2018-12-china-unbridled-export-coal-power_1.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 08:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/12/3746730/3746730_E5D3E2876EA9450AA743F404185E9A50_181212_3746730_Asian_countries_expanding_coal_plants_in_other_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,climate change, climate change, coal plants, expanding coal plants, power plants, coal-fired power plants, coal plants expansion, overseas coal plant expansion, coal, carbon emissions, global warming, coal emissions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3746669</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover vast underground ecosystem of 'deep life' microbes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDeep life studies have revealed a rich subterranean ecosystem within the Earth almost twice the size of the world's oceans. The Guardian reports that Deep Carbon Observatory scientists made boreholes over 5 kilometers deep, and drilled 2.5 kilometers below the seabed to find an underground biosphere containing 'deep life' microbes that may have persisted for thousands or millions of years.These previously unknown lifeforms thrived despite extreme temperature and pressure. They reportedly fed on energy from rocks, and existed in a slow-motion, zombie-like state.The results suggest that 70% of the Earth's bacteria and archaea exist underground, amounting to between 15 and 23 million tonnes of carbon.Among them are barbed Altiarchaealis that live in sulphuric springs and Geogemma barossii, a single-celled organism found in hydrothermal vents on the seafloor, whose cells grow and replicate at 250 degrees Fahrenheit.Researchers have been trying to determine the boundary where life cannot exist, but the deeper they dig, the more life they find.Though there is a temperature maximum set at 251 degrees Fahrenheit, scientists think further exploration using more sophisticated instruments might break that record.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boreholes and deep sea drilling reveal deep life ecosystem2. Microbes exist despite extreme conditions3. 70% of Earth's bacteria, archaea exist underground4. Depiction of some deep life microorganismsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists made boreholes over 5 kilometers deep, and drilled 2.5 kilometers below the seabed to find an underground biosphere containing 'deep life' microbes that may have persisted for thousands or millions of years.""These previously unknown lifeforms thrived despite extreme temperature and pressure. They reportedly fed on energy from rocks, and existed in a slow-motion, zombie-like state.""The results suggest that 70% of the Earth's bacteria and archaea exist underground, amounting to between 15 and 23 million tonnes of carbon.""Among them are barbed Altiarchaealis that live in sulphuric springs and Geogemma barossii, a single-celled organism found in hydrothermal vents on the seafloor, whose cells grow and replicate at 250 degrees Fahrenheit."SOURCES: The Guardian, Agence France-Pressehttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/dec/10/tread-softly-because-you-tread-on-23bn-tonnes-of-micro-organismshttps://www.voanews.com/a/vast-zombie-like-microbial-life-lurks-beneath-seabed/4695410.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 07:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/12/3746669/3746669_C3B091C3A7894CCDA51EEBE39E9172FA_181212_3746669_Scientists_discover_vast_underground_ecosystem_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, deep life, microbes, subsea microbes, microorganisms, bacteria, subsurface bacteria, deep earth, deep sea life, deep earth life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3747438</guid>
      <title>Strasbourg gunman at large after killing three in Christmas market</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPolice are still on the hunt for a gunman who killed at least three people and injured over a dozen others in the French city of Strasbourg.The BBC reports that according to Paris public prosecutor Remy Heitz, a man with a gun was seen in Strasbourg's city center around 8 p.m. on December 11.The gunman walked through the Christmas market, open firing several times, and using a knife to wound and kill. Witnesses say he shouted 'Allahu Akbar' as he did so.Four anti-terror Operation Sentinelle soldiers patrolling the area exchanged fire with the suspect and wounded him in the arm.The gunman managed to get into a taxi, which took him to the Neudorf district near the Franco-German border, where he lived.He came across police after getting out of the taxi, resulting in another exchange of gunfire. But authorities eventually lost track of him, according to the New York Times.The suspect has since been identified as 29-year-old Cherif Chekatt, who had been convicted 27 times and was on a watchlist of potential terror threats.Among those killed by Chekatt were a Thai tourist and a local resident, while an Italian journalist was among those seriously wounded.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman shoots, stabs victims in Strasbourg Christmas market2. Gunman exchanges fire with four Operation Sentinelle soldiers3. Gunman flees in a taxi to Neudorf district4. Gunman exchanges fire with police, eventually escapesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Paris public prosecutor, the attack began around 8 p.m. on December 11.""The gunman walked through the Strasbourg Christmas market, open firing several times, and using a knife to wound and kill.""Witnesses say he shouted 'Allahu Akbar' as he did so.'""Anti-terror Operation Sentinelle soldiers patrolling the area exchanged fire with the suspect and wounded him in the arm.""The gunman managed to get into a taxi, which took him to the Neudorf district near the Franco-German border, where he lived.""He came across police after getting out of the taxi, resulting in another exchange of gunfire. "But authorities eventually lost track of him, according to the New York Times."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardian, New York Timeshttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46535862https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/12/strasbourg-france-christmas-market-shooting-gunman-was-listed-as-potential-terror-threathttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/12/world/europe/france-strasbourg-shooting.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 10:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/13/3747438/3747438_547B0323EA814B0DB128CE9C80BAEB90_181213_3747438_Strasbourg_gunman_at_large_after_killing_three_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, strasbourg shooting, strasbourg christmas market, christmas market shooting, strasbourg gunman, christmas shooting, cherif chekatt, terror attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3747375</guid>
      <title>Google releases massive development plans for Mountain View campus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoogle has announced plans for a massive development in its home city of Mountain View, California, which includes plans for office, retail, public and residential space. According to CNBC, the development is planned for the North Bayshore area of the city and includes 3.12 million square feet of offices, up to 400,000 square feet for retail stores, as many as 8,000 new homes and 35 acres of public space. "We want to see the area transformed into what the City calls 'Complete Neighborhoods,' with a focus on increasing housing options and creating great public spaces that prioritize people over cars," said Michael Tymoff, Google's Mountain View development director, in a statement.Google will team up with a developer to build up to 6,600 of those new homes on its land, with 20 percent set aside for affordable housing. The development will also have 7.5 cumulative miles of bike and pedestrian paths. All the new office buildings will be powered by 100 percent renewable energy as well.City officials are set to discuss the plans early next year. According to CNBC, Google has spent at least $2.8 billion acquiring property in Mountain View, Sunnyvale and San Jose over the last two years. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The proposed Shorebird development2. The development will include new office, retail, residential and public spaces3. Shorebird residential area with public spaces4. Shorebird will have affordable housing, bike and pedestrian paths and office buildings will be completely powered by renewable energy. VOICEOVER (in English): "Google has announced plans for a massive development in its home city of Mountain View, California, which includes plans for office, retail, public and residential space." "According to CNBC, the development is planned for the North Bayshore area of the city and includes 3.12 million square feet of offices, up to 400,000 square feet for retail stores, as many as 8,000 new homes and 35 acres of public space." "According to Google's Mountain View development director Michael Tymoff, "we want to see the area transformed into what the City calls 'Complete Neighborhoods,' with a focus on increasing housing options and creating great public spaces that prioritize people over cars."""Over 1,200 of the new residential units will be set aside for affordable housing. The development will also have 7.5 cumulative miles of bike and pedestrian paths. All the new office buildings will be powered by 100 percent renewable energy as well."  SOURCES: CNBC, Googlehttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/09/google-reveals-north-bayshore-mountain-view-development-plan.htmlhttps://www.mountainview.gov/civicax/filebank/blobdload.aspx?BlobID=28004***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 09:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/13/3747375/3747375_DFBED9573F97485FB5AC613DA1C0AD24_181213_3747375_Google_releases_massive_development_plans_for_Mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Google Mountain View development, Google home city development, Google North Bayshore development, Google complete neighborhoods]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3747282</guid>
      <title>Japanese technology project to ease traffic jams in India</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new intelligent transportation system will be installed in Bangalore, India in order control and reduce traffic jams throughout the city.The project will cost $11.3 million which will be funded by Japan's International Cooperation Agency.According to CNN, 72 sensors will be positioned over 12 traffic jam hot spots around the city. Special detectors will use ultrasonic signals to capture traffic data every 60 seconds.Six thousand and seven hundred buses across the city will have GPS devices installed in them. Additionally, 16 cameras and sensors installed in eight locations will analyze traffic volume and speed.Twenty-nine junctions will be equipped with special traffic lights that generate 'green waves'. Coordination between the traffic lights allow for uninterrupted traffic flow.The system will be installed by March 2019, and will begin operating by mid-2020.Japan's International Cooperation Agency has successfully installed an ITS in Moscow as well as similar systems in Sri Lanka and Cambodia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of Bangalore geographic location as well as area projected to be covered by new transportation system2. Portrayal of traffic jam sensors3. Depiction of GPS-equipped buses as well as traffic cameras4. Representation of 'green wave' traffic lightsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new intelligent transportation system will be installed in Bangalore, India in order control and reduce traffic jams throughout the city.""The project will cost $11.3 million which will be funded by Japan's International Cooperation Agency.""According to CNN, 72 sensors will be positioned over 12 traffic jam hot spots around the city. Special detectors will use ultrasonic signals to capture traffic data every 60 seconds.""Six thousand and seven hundred buses across the city will have GPS devices installed in them. Additionally, 16 cameras and sensors installed in eight locations will analyze traffic volume and speed.""Twenty-nine junctions will be equipped with special traffic lights that generate 'green waves'. Coordination between the traffic lights allow for uninterrupted traffic flow.""The system will be installed by March 2019, and will begin operating by mid-2020." SOURCES: CNNhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/04/asia/bangalore-india-traffic-japanese-tech/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 07:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/13/3747282/3747282_476A32D58E914D3E904F1BA8FE232009_181213_3747282_Japanese_technology_project_to_ease_traffic_jams_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Bangalore, India, Science, Japan, Tech, Science Science and Technology, Traffic, Traffic jam in India, Japanese technology, Silicon valley of India, Karnataka, JICA, foreign aid.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3747242</guid>
      <title>Molecule could determine dementia type</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have identified single tau protein molecules that could help identify what form of dementia may develop in a person's brain.The molecule has a specific structural shape, according to the study published in the journal eLife.Researchers from the University of Texas isolated single tau protein molecules from the human brain to test if it resulted in different shapes. They found that molecules with specific structures turned toxic.The scientists also plan to develop a test using either blood or spinal fluid. This test will detect these molecules and identify what they could potentially turn into. This could help identify what kind of dementia a patient has before symptoms begin to show.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Male medical body and a tau protein molecule2. A single tau protein molecule3. A human brain and single tau protein molecules on a petri dish4. A single tau protein molecule structure turning toxicVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists at UT Southwestern have identified single tau protein molecules that could help identify what form of dementia may develop in a person's brain.""According to the study published in the journal eLife, the molecule has a specific structural shape.""The researchers isolated single tau protein molecules from the human brain to test if it resulted in different shapes.""They found that molecules with specific structures turned toxic."SOURCES: New Atlas, News Medical Life Sciences, Science Daily, e Life journal, UT Southwestern Medical Center, https://newatlas.com/tau-molecule-diagnose-dementia-alzheimers/57617/https://www.news-medical.net/news/20181211/Single-tau-molecule-holds-clues-to-help-diagnose-neurodegeneration-in-its-earliest-stages.aspxhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/12/181211122433.htmhttps://elifesciences.org/articles/37813https://www.utsouthwestern.edu/newsroom/articles/year-2018/forecasting-dementia.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 06:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/13/3747242/3747242_1DC923871084494FBF3D150402FA7851_181213_3747242_Molecule_could_determine_dementia_type_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Alzheimer's disease, dementia, molecule, origins of dementia, cognitive decline, tau protein molecule,  single tau molecules, tau monomer, alzheimer's disease, dementia types]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3748104</guid>
      <title>High speed train crash in Turkey kills at least 9, dozens injured</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA high speed passenger train collided head-on with a maintenance locomotive Thursday morning in the Turkish capital of Ankara, killing at least nine people and injuring dozens others. The New York Times reported that according to Anadolu news agency, the train was carrying 206 passengers from Ankara toward Konya Province. According to Transportation Minister Mehmet Cahit Turhan, the accident occurred around 6:36 a.m. as "the train leaving Ankara station crashed into the engine turning back from" doing maintenance work on the track. According to the BBC, the crash happened at Marsandiz train station about 5 miles or 8 kilometers from Anakara's main station. According to the New York Times, the accident pushed two carriages off the track, where they ran into the support legs of an elevated walkway, causing it to collapse onto the train. Health Minister Fahrettin Koca told broadcaster NTV that 84 people were injured, including two people in critical condition, according to the New York Times.Three people have been arrested in connection with the accident, and prosecutors have been assigned to look into the crash. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Train traveling down the tracks2. Intended route for train and train passengers3. The high speed train and the maintenance locomotive on the tracks4. The accident siteVOICEOVER (in English): "A high speed passenger train collided head-on with a maintenance locomotive Thursday morning in the Turkish capital of Ankara, killing at least nine people and injuring dozens others." "The Anadolu news agency reported the train was carrying 206 passengers from Ankara toward Konya Province." "According to the BBC, the crash happened at Marsandiz station about 5 miles from Anakara's main station." "According to Transportation Minister Mehmet Cahit Turhan, the accident occurred around 6:36 a.m. as "the train leaving Ankara station crashed into the engine turning back from" doing maintenance work on the track." "According to the New York Times, the accident pushed two carriages off the track, where they ran into the support legs of an elevated walkway, causing it to collapse onto the train." SOURCES: New York Times, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/13/world/europe/turkey-train-crash.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/13/europe/turkey-train-crash-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 11:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/14/3748104/3748104_A971F1B2CDBB4E3B8097E60258641515_181214_3748104_High_speed_train_crash_in_Turkey_kills_at_least__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Turkey train crash, Ankara train crash, Turkey high speed train crash, Turkey head on train collision, train crash, train accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3748077</guid>
      <title>Strasbourg shooter killed by police after two-day manhunt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrench police have killed the man responsible for the Strasbourg Christmas market attack that left three people dead and a dozen wounded.The Guardian reports that on the morning of the attack, police tried to detain Cherif Chekatt's in connection with an armed robbery and attempted murder inquiry, but he wasn't home. Prosecutors say a grenade, a rifle, and several knives were found during a search of his apartment.Hours later, Chekatt walked through the Strasbourg Christmas market armed with a gun. He open fired several times, and also used a knife during the attack. Witnesses say he shouted 'Allahu Akbar' as he did so.Four anti-terrorism Operation Sentinelle soldiers patrolling the area exchanged fire with the 29-year-old suspect and wounded him in the arm.He managed to get into a taxi, which took him to the Neudorf district near the Franco-German border, where his apartment was located.Chekatt came across police after getting out of the taxi, resulting in another exchange of gunfire. According to the New York Times, authorities eventually lost track of him.French authorities immediately blocked main roads out of the city, and mobilized more than 700 security forces to hunt for the gunman.According to the Paris prosecutor's office, three police officers recognized Chekatt on a Neudorf street around 9 p.m. Thursday. He turned and shot at the officers when they tried to approach.Police returned fire, killing him. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Police search of gunman's home2. Gunman shoots, stabs victims in Strasbourg Christmas market3. Gunman exchanges fire with four Operation Sentinelle soldiers4. Gunman flees in a taxi to Neudorf district5. Gunman exchanges fire with police, eventually escapes6. Police manhunt for gunman7. Police recognize gunman on street, gunman shoots at police8. Police return fire, kill gunmanVOICEOVER (in English): "On the morning of the attack, police tried to detain Cherif Chekatt's in connection with an armed robbery and attempted murder inquiry, but he wasn't home. Prosecutors say a grenade, a rifle, and several knives were found during a search of his apartment.""Hours later, Chekatt walked through the Strasbourg Christmas market armed with a gun. He open fired several times, and also used a knife during the attack. Witnesses say he shouted 'Allahu Akbar' as he did so.""Four anti-terrorism Operation Sentinelle soldiers patrolling the area exchanged fire with the 29-year-old suspect and wounded him in the arm.""He managed to get into a taxi, which took him to the Neudorf district near the Franco-German border, where his apartment was located.""Chekatt came across police after getting out of the taxi, resulting in another exchange of gunfire. According to the New York Times, authorities eventually lost track of him.""French authorities immediately blocked main roads out of the city, and mobilized more than 700 security forces to hunt for the gunman.""According to the Paris prosecutor's office, three police officers recognized Chekatt on a Neudorf street around 9 p.m. Thursday. He turned and shot at the officers when they tried to approach.""Police returned fire, killing him. The weapon the suspect was using was later discovered to be an 8mm ordnance revolver."SOURCES: The Guardian, CNNhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/13/strasbourg-attack-suspect-killed-by-police-reports-sayhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/13/europe/france-strasbourg-shooting-manhunt/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 11:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/14/3748077/3748077_8F039B6B972242ED903DA87319EC4948_181214_3748077_Strasbourg_shooter_killed_by_police_after_two_da_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, strasbourg shooting, strasbourg attack, strasbourg gunman, cherif chekatt, strasbourg christmas market shooting, strasbourg shooter, christmas market shooting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3747854</guid>
      <title>China is building a nuclear test facility modeled after America's Z machine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is building a version of America's Z machine that will simulate thermonuclear explosions at a much larger scale.The South China Morning Post reports that according to a Beijing-based nuclear physicist, researchers at the nuclear weapons development base in Mianyang are building a Z machine designed to produce 60 million joules of energy.To do this, electrical pulses are fired at a target consisting of hundreds of tungsten wires. The flow of energy dissolves the tungsten into plasma and creates a strong magnetic field.Exploded particles are forced inward. They then collide with each other to produce intense radiation in the form of X-ray energy, creating conditions that reflect a nuclear explosion.The facility would allow researchers to see how weapons fare under extreme conditions. It could also help develop technology to harness clean energy in unlimited quantities.Associate professor Liu Bo from Sichuan University's Institute of Nuclear Science and Technology says the machine could be powerful enough to start fusion. This occurs when atomic nuclei merge, and results in the release of vast amounts of energyRUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese Z machine designed to produce 60 million joules of energy2. Electrical pulses fired at target of tungsten wires to create magnetic field3. Exploded particles collide to produce radiation4. Machine can be used for nuclear weapons research or for clean energyVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a Beijing-based nuclear physicist, researchers at the nuclear weapons development base in Mianyang are building a Z machine designed to produce 60 million joules of energy.""To do this, electrical pulses are fired at a target consisting of hundreds of tungsten wires. The flow of energy dissolves the tungsten into plasma and creates a strong magnetic field.""Exploded particles are forced inward. They then collide with each other to produce intense radiation in the form of X-ray energy, creating conditions that reflect a nuclear explosion.""The facility would allow researchers to see how weapons fare under extreme conditions. It could also help develop technology to harness clean energy in unlimited quantities."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, Sandia National Laboratorieshttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2177652/operation-z-machine-chinas-next-big-weapon-nuclear-arms-racehttps://www.sandia.gov/z-machine/research/science.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 07:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/14/3747854/3747854_4BA560BD2CF74DDCB112088790A249DC_181214_3747854_China_is_building_a_nuclear_test_facility_modele_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, z machine, nuclear weapon, nuclear fusion, thermonuclear explosion, weapons test, nuclear weapons test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3747809</guid>
      <title>Megalodon's extinction might have been caused by supernova explosion.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew paper proposes megalodon may have gone extinct due to supernova explosion. A new paper by researchers from the University of Kansas, Federal University of Sao Carlos and Federal University of ABC proposes that ancient large marine animals may have become extinct due to exposure to cosmic radiation from nearby supernovae.   Prehistoric seabed deposits contain high concentration of ion 60-isotopes, which come from supernovae explosions.Although the isotope is harmless, it comes with other particles called muons. These particles can interact with cells of living organisms causing mutations and cancer.Researchers believe the megalodon's large size and tendency to inhabit shallow waters made it more susceptible to exposure to the supernova cosmic rays.Its extinction coincides with the detection of one or more supernovae occurring around 2.6 million years ago.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the Megalodon's size2. Depiction of supernova explosion 3. Representation of  ion 60-isotopes and effect of muon particles on cells4. Portrayal of megalodon being hit by radioactive cosmic wavesVOICEOVER (in English): "The prehistoric shark is the largest fish ever recorded. According to the Natural History Museum of London, it could measure over 18 meters in length.""The largest megalodon tooth found measures 17.8 centimeters in length, three times the size of a great white shark tooth.""According to a research by the University of Zurich published in the journal PLOSONE, megalodons went extinct roughly 2.6 million years ago.""A new paper by researchers from the University of Kansas, Federal University of Sao Carlos and Federal University of ABC proposes that ancient large marine animals may have become extinct due to exposure to cosmic radiation from nearby supernovae." "Prehistoric seabed deposits contain high concentration of ion 60-isotopes, which come from supernovae explosions.""Although the isotope is harmless, it comes with other particles called muons. These particles can interact with cells of living organisms causing mutations and cancer.""Researchers believe the megalodon's large size and tendency to inhabit shallow waters made it more susceptible to exposure to the supernova cosmic rays.""Its extinction coincides with the detection of one or more supernovae occurring around 2.6 million years ago."SOURCES: London National History Museum, PLOSONEhttp://www.nhm.ac.uk/events/nature-live-megalodon.htmlhttps://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0111086***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 06:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/14/3747809/3747809_73213F0E898048A086037486E050F196_181214_3747809_Megalodon_s_extinction_might_have_been_caused_by_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, prehistoric, shark, megalodon, gone, extinct, body, temperature, nature, research, study, extinction, Otodus megalodon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3749393</guid>
      <title>Brexit: What is the Irish backstop?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn integral part of Brexit negotiations concerns the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.  According to the BBC, last month, E.U. leaders approved a deal with the U.K. that includes an agreement on the Irish border, with both sides looking to avoid reintroducing border posts between the two areas. According to the Washington Post, the backstop is an insurance policy that would keep Britain in the E.U. customs union if no other agreement can be found to keep an open border between Northern Ireland and Ireland.  Because the U.K. and Ireland are currently both part of the E.U. single market and customs union, goods do not need to be inspected for customs and standards, so products and services can be traded on Ireland with few restrictions.However, after Brexit, Northern Ireland and the Republic could be in different customs and regulatory systems, which could mean hold ups for goods being checked at the border. The problem now is that both the U.K. and the E.U. have different opinions on what the backstop should contain. The E.U. had originally proposed that Northern Ireland stay in the EU customs union, large parts of the single market, and the E.U. VAT system. Britain on the other hand, is against having a separate status for Northern Ireland because it feels it would damage the union as a whole. If the two sides cannot come to a deal on the backstop, it could mean a no-deal Brexit. This in turn could mean there would be some type of hard border with heavy checks in place between Northern Ireland and the Republic.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Backstop is a provision to keep an open border between Northern Ireland and Ireland2. The U.K. and E.U. disagree on the terms of the backstop3. U.K. and E.U. versions of backstop4. A hard border could appear in the event of a no-deal BrexitVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, last month, E.U. leaders approved a deal with the U.K. that includes an agreement on the Irish border, with both sides looking to avoid reintroducing border posts between the two areas." "According to the Washington Post, the backstop is an insurance policy that would keep Britain in the E.U. customs union if no other agreement can be found to keep an open border between Northern Ireland and Ireland." "The problem now is that both the U.K. and the E.U. have different opinions on what the backstop should contain." "The E.U. had originally proposed that Northern Ireland stay in the EU customs union, large parts of the single market and the E.U. VAT system." "Britain on the other hand, is against having a separate status for Northern Ireland, because it feels it would damage the union as a whole." "If the two sides cannot come to a deal on the backstop, it could mean a no-deal Brexit. This could see some type of hard border with heavy checks in place between Northern Ireland and the Republic."  SOURCES: BBC, CNNhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-politics-44615404https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/13/uk/irish-border-backstop-gbr-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 10:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/17/3749393/3749393_773D30E8F0534DBFB14C27FE0CC353CF_181217_3749393_Brexit__What_is_the_Irish_backstop__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Brexit, no deal Brexit, hard Brexit, Irish backstop, Brexit backstop]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3749296</guid>
      <title>New study finds stethoscopes are filled with bacteria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found that doctors' stethoscopes maybe filled with infectious bacteria.The researchers tested 20 traditional reusable stethoscopes and 20 single-use disposable stethoscopes used in intensive care units. These were compared with 10 unused stethoscopes.High levels of Staphylococcus aureus and other bacteria such as Pseudomonas and Acinetobacter were found to be present in the tested ICU stethoscopes.The study found that hydrogen peroxide wipes, alcohol swabs and bleach wipes reduced bacteria present but did not eliminate all of it completely.Dr. Ronald Collman, lead author of the study, said stethoscopes should regularly be cleaned using an EPA approved disinfectant. He added that future studies should focus on improving present cleaning methods.The research was published in the journal Infection Control and Hospital Epidemiology.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A doctor with a stethoscope around his neck2. A traditional reusable stethoscope, a single-use disposable stethoscopes and an unused stethoscope3. Different bacterias found on the stethoscopes 4. Hydrogen peroxide wipes, alcohol swabs and bleach wipesVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study, published in the journal Infection Control and Hospital Epidemiology, has found that doctors' stethoscopes maybe filled with infectious bacteria.""The researchers tested traditional reusable stethoscopes and single-use disposable stethoscopes used in intensive care units." "These were compared with unused stethoscopes.""High levels of Staphylococcus aureus and other bacteria such as Pseudomonas and Acinetobacter were found to be present in the tested ICU stethoscopes.""The study found that hydrogen peroxide wipes, alcohol swabs and bleach wipes reduced bacteria present but did not eliminate all of it completely."SOURCES: ABC News, Forbes, WTNH, CBS News, Infection Control and Hospital Epidemiology, https://abcnews.go.com/Health/stethoscopes-loaded-bacteria-including-staph-infection-study/story?id=59772349https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/12/13/how-dirty-is-that-stethoscope-there-is-bacteria-that-can-cause-disease/#34aeaf416ac2https://www.wtnh.com/news/health/stethoscopes-loaded-with-bacteria-including-the-one-that-causes-staph-infection-study/1657080478https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stethoscopes-loaded-with-bacteria-including-staph-study-finds/https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/infection-control-and-hospital-epidemiology/article/molecular-analysis-of-bacterial-contamination-on-stethoscopes-in-an-intensive-care-unit/E5080DEC191CA8114D4CD564258CADE3***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 07:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/17/3749296/3749296_0F194E7A9257405D8EFE98C0CAB1C6EC_181217_3749296_New_study_finds_stethoscopes_are_filled_with_bac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, stethoscopes, bacteria, Staphylococcus aureus, Pseudomonas, Acinetobacter, infection-causing bacteria, contaminated stethoscopes, stethoscopes contaminated with bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3749168</guid>
      <title>US approves use of antibiotic pesticide on citrus orchards</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to the Center for Biological Diversity, the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has approved the use of antibiotic pesticides on citrus crops.The antibiotics will be used to fight citrus canker and citrus greening disease in orchards. The plan is to use 388,000 pounds of oxytetracycline per year to treat 480,000 acres of citrus trees in Florida. According to the EPA, there is a 'high' probability that the use of the antibiotic pesticide on citrus orchards will lead to antibiotic-resistant bacteria.There is a 'medium risk' of it having a negative impact on human health. The drug is commonly used to treat pulmonary infections such as pneumonia.The World Health Organization states that antibiotic resistance is one of the biggest threats to global health.A growing number of infectious diseases are becoming harder to treat as they become more resistant to antibiotic treatment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. EPA approval of antibiotic pesticides on citrus crops2. Distribution of oxytetracycline orchards3. Probability of antibiotic-resistant bacteria development from antibiotic pesticide use4. Warning on antibiotic resistance development from WHOVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Center for Biological Diversity, the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has approved the use of antibiotic pesticides on citrus crops.""The antibiotics will be used to fight citrus canker and citrus greening disease in orchards." "The plan is to use 388,000 pounds of oxytetracycline per year to treat 480,000 acres of citrus trees in Florida." "According to the EPA, there is a 'high' probability that the use of the antibiotic pesticide on citrus orchards will lead to antibiotic-resistant bacteria.""There is a 'medium risk' of it having a negative impact on human health. The drug is commonly used to treat pulmonary infections such as pneumonia.""The World Health Organization states that antibiotic resistance is one of the biggest threats to global health.""A growing number of infectious diseases are becoming harder to treat as they become more resistant to antibiotic treatment."SOURCES: The Center for Biological Diversity, Environmental Protection Agency, World Health Organization. https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/antibiotic-resistancehttps://www.biologicaldiversity.org/news/press_releases/2018/oxytetracycline-12-10-2018.phphttps://www.regulations.gov/document?D=EPA-HQ-OPP-2015-0820-0031***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 03:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/17/3749168/3749168_B82DA99096674280B02D3749FEE67AD0_181217_3749168_US_approves_use_of_antibiotic_pesticide_on_citru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, USA, antibiotic, antibiotics, pesticide, antibiotic resistance, antibiotic resistant bacteria, bacteria, diseases, Florida, Environmental Protection Agency, The Center for Biological Diversity, World Health Organization, WHO, antibiotic treatment, agriculture, trump, trump administration, fruits.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3750036</guid>
      <title>What happens in a no-deal Brexit?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe United Kingdom is scheduled to leave the European Union at 11 p.m. GMT on March 29, 2019, and if a formal agreement cannot be reached, then there could be serious consequences for Britain. According to the Week, in a no-deal Brexit, all E.U. rules and regulations will instantly cease to apply in the U.K. In this event, there would be no remaining agreements between London and Brussels on how to handle customs, trade, travel or citizens rights. A no-deal Brexit would also mean the transition period for businesses and organizations to prepare for the changes from March 2019 to December 2020 would be off the table. According to I News, in terms of trade, the U.K. would revert back to World Trade Organization rules. Britain would then be forced to pay the E.U.'s external tariffs. Prices in the U.K. on E.U. imported goods would also go up due to tariffs.  Citizens rights for the 1.3 million Britons in the E.U. and the 3.7 million Europeans in the U.K., in terms of the right to live and work, would be unclear. Relevant E.U. laws would be transferred over, while the U.K. would no longer have to adhere to rulings from the European Court of Justice.The issue of the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland would also remain unresolved. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. In a no-deal Brexit, all EU rules will cease to apply in Britain with no agreements on customs, trade, travel or citizen rights2. No-deal effect on UK and EU trade3. Citizen rights for Britons in EU and Europeans in UK would be unclear4. UK no longer has to follow EU court rulings, Irish backstop unresolvedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Week, in a no-deal Brexit, all E.U. rules and regulations will instantly cease to apply in the U.K." "In this event, there would be no remaining agreements between London and Brussels on how to handle customs, trade, travel or citizens rights." "According to I News, in terms of trade, the U.K. would revert back to World Trade Organization rules. Britain would then be forced to pay the E.U.'s external tariffs. Prices in the U.K. on E.U. imported goods would also go up due to tariffs."  "Citizens rights for the 1.3 million Britons in the E.U. and the 3.7 million Europeans in the U.K., in terms of the right to live and work would be unclear." "Relevant E.U. laws would be transferred over, while the U.K. would no longer have to adhere to rulings from the European Court of Justice.""The issue of the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland would also remain unresolved." SOURCES: The Week, I News, Washington Posthttps://www.theweek.co.uk/fact-check/95547/fact-check-what-a-no-deal-brexit-really-meanshttps://inews.co.uk/news/brexit/no-deal-brexit-what-meaning-uk-leave-uk-consequences/https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2018/12/13/heres-what-eu-has-lose-event-no-deal-brexit/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.1eb67ac417ff***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 10:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/18/3750036/3750036_7202E1EA9D064CE5945380F81CD2AE9F_181218_3750036_What_happens_in_a_no_deal_Brexit__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Brexit, no-deal Brexit, hard Brexit, soft Brexit, Brexit negotiations]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3749886</guid>
      <title>China and Russia researching atmosphere altering technology</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina and Russia are testing technology that can manipulate areas of the atmosphere for potential military applications, reports the South China Morning Post.The newspaper, citing a Chinese scientist familiar with the research, reports China and Russia are conducting heating experiments in the Earth's ionosphere. The ionosphere is a layer of the Earth's atmosphere that consists of ionized layers and free electrons. It can bounce radio waves across long distances.In one experiment, a Russian ionospheric heating facility called Sura injected electrons into the sky. They covered roughly 500 kilometers of the Russian city of Vasilsursk. The experiment made radio waves in the area peak at 260 megawatts.Controlling the ionosphere would allow for manipulation of communication signals around the world.A Chinese electromagnetic surveillance satellite called Zhangheng - 1 used special sensors to collect data from the experiments.China and Russia performed five experiments in June. During one of the experiments, the city reached an electric spike with 10 times more negatively charged subatomic particles than surrounding regions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of China and Russia collaboration2. Representation of location of experiments and its effect on communication3. Depiction of Zhangheng - 1 satellite gathering information from experiment site4. Representation of effect of experiments in Vasilsursk. VOICEOVER (in English): "According to South China Morning Post, China and Russia are conducting heating experiments in the Earth's ionosphere." "The ionosphere is a layer of the Earth's atmosphere that consists of ionized layers and free electrons. "It can bounce radio waves across long distances.""In one experiment, a Russian ionospheric heating facility called Sura injected electrons into the sky.""They covered roughly 500 kilometers of the Russian city of Vasilsursk. The experiment made radio waves in the area peak at 260 megawatts.""Controlling the ionosphere would allow for manipulation of communication signals around the world.""A Chinese electromagnetic surveillance satellite called Zhangheng - 1 used special sensors to collect data from the experiments.""China and Russia performed five experiments in June.""During one of the experiments, the city reached an electric spike with 10 times more negatively charged subatomic particles than surrounding regions."SOURCES: South China Morning Posthttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2178214/china-and-russia-band-together-controversial-heating-experiments***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 07:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/18/3749886/3749886_FC50CAC263324A2DB0008059DB086283_181218_3749886_China_and_Russia_researching_atmosphere_altering_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, News, China, Science, China science, Russia, China military, Climate change, Extreme weather, atmosphere, Sura, Zhangheng-1, satellite, heating experiment.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3749776</guid>
      <title>Artificial islands restore nature to lake in the Netherlands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn ambitious project led by a Dutch non-governmental organization has built five artificial islands from silt to restore nature to one of Europe's largest freshwater lakes.The Markermeer lake northeast of Amsterdam used to teem with an abundance of wildlife. It was created as part of a land reclamation plan that was scrapped over concerns it would dry out land around it and destroy an important site for migratory birds.However, silt from a dam used to create the Markermeer clouded the lake's waters, suffocating the algae that formed the base of its aquatic food chain.Dutch ngo Natuurmonumenten aimed to change that by silt to create five artificial islands. The five islands were built over a period of two-and-a-half years.Boskalis, the company that built the islands, dug a 1,200 meter trench on the main artificial island to allow silt to be drained by ocean currents to form marshy areas with fertile soil.According to a report by AFP and articles on Natuurmonumenten and Boskalis's websites, these areas are now home to birds such as sparrows, the greylag goose, the common tern and the night heron.An abundance of plankton in the water provides a guaranteed source of food for the birds.Experts have also counted 127 differents kinds of plants on the islands, most of them brought by windborne seeds.The main artificial island contains three wooden bird observatories, footbridges and unpaved roads and is open to the public. The other four islands are reserved only for wildlife and plants.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Five artificial islands appearing on Markermeer lake2. The main artificial island is shown, with ocean currents impacting the silt and forming green areas3. Birds coming to the artificials isles and plankton in the water4. Differents plants on the island VOICEOVER (in English): "An ambitious project by Dutch ngo Natuurmonumenten has used silt that clouded the Markermeer lake to create five artificial islands.""The five islands were built over a period of two-and-a-half years.""Boskalis, the company that built the islands, dug a 1,200 meter trench on the main artificial island to allow silt to be drained by ocean currents to form marshy areas with fertile soil.""These areas are now home to birds such as sparrows, the greylag goose, the common tern and the night heron.""An abundance of plankton in the water provides a guaranteed source of food for the birds.""Experts have also counted 127 differents kinds of plants on the islands, most of them brought by windborne seeds."SOURCES: AFP, Natuurmonumenten, Boskalis, Wageningen University & Research, Rewilding Europe, https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/dutch-build-artificial-islands-bring-wildlife-back-doc-1be2ad1https://dialogue.wur.eu/spotlight/nature-restores-marker-wadden/https://www.wur.nl/en/article/IJsselmeer-region-water-management-nature-and-economic-development.htmhttps://rewildingeurope.com/rew-project/marker-wadden-restoration-project/https://www.natuurmonumenten.nl/projecten/marker-wadden/english/tackling-the-silt-problemhttps://boskalis.com/csr/cases/marker-wadden.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 05:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/18/3749776/3749776_84CF033611944430911F73CB8633BEFA_181218_3749776_Artificial_islands_restore_nature_to_lake_in_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, lelystad, artificial islands, wildlife, netherlands artificial islands, netherlands wildlife, lelystad, dutch artificial islands, silt, lelystad port, markermeer lake, markermeer lake wildlife, marine life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3749730</guid>
      <title>552-carat yellow diamond is largest ever found in North America</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA yellow diamond discovered in a Canadian mine in October is said to be the largest in North America.Dominion Diamond Mines announced in a December 13 press release that it had unearthed a 552-carat yellow diamond at the Diavik Diamond Mines in Canada's Northwest Territories.According to Bloomberg, the gem is the size of a chicken egg. It's also three times the size of the previous record holder  the 187.7-carat Diavik Foxfire which was recovered at the same mine in 2015.Though the Diavik mine produces high-quality diamonds, the largest ones are normally found in mines in southern Africa. Bloomberg calculations rank the yellow diamond as seventh among the 21st century's biggest diamonds.Dominion says the diamond is gem-quality, or suitable for jewelry, though its worth is undetermined. It will not be sold in its rough form, as the company is expected to select a partner to cut and polish the stone.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 552-carat yellow diamond unearthed in Canada mine2. Yellow diamond three times the size of previous record holder3. Larger diamonds normally found in southern Africa mines4. Yellow diamond suitable for jewelry, to be cut and polished before saleVOICEOVER (in English): "Dominion Diamond Mines announced in a press release that it had unearthed a 552-carat yellow diamond at the Diavik Diamond Mines in Canada's Northwest Territories.""According to Bloomberg, the gem is the size of a chicken egg. It's also three times the size of the previous record holder  the 187.7-carat Diavik Foxfire which was recovered at the same mine in 2015.""Though the Diavik mine produces high-quality diamonds, the largest ones are normally found in mines in southern Africa. Bloomberg calculations rank the yellow diamond as seventh among the 21st century's biggest diamonds.""Dominion says the diamond is gem-quality, or suitable for jewelry, though its worth is undetermined. It will not be sold in its rough form, as the company is expected to select a partner to cut and polish the stone."SOURCES: Dominion Diamond Mines, Bloomberghttps://www.ddmines.com/dominion-diamond-mines-announces-the-recovery-of-the-largest-diamond-ever-found-in-north-america-at-diavik/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-14/miners-find-chicken-egg-sized-diamond-in-canada-s-frozen-north***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 03:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/18/3749730/3749730_3D6F6CDA233D4AFB80368533871737AB_181218_3749730_552_carat_yellow_diamond_is_largest_ever_found_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, yellow diamond, diamond, largest diamond, largest diamond in north america, diavik mines, chicken egg sized diamond, 552 carat diamond, dominion diamond mines, diamond mines, africa diamond, canada diamond, canadamark]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3749685</guid>
      <title>Apple plans to expand operations across the US including $1 billion Texas campus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANApple announced on a press release that it will open new facilities in Austin, Texas.The company said it will invest $1 billion on its new campus, which will spread across 133 acres and generate 5,000 new jobs. Apple also plans to expand its operations to San Diego, Seattle and Culver City, California, creating a total of more than 1,000 jobs.Additionally, it intends to hire hundreds of new employees in offices in New York, Pittsburgh and Boulder, Colorado within three years. The plan also includes a $10 billion investment in U.S. data centers in the next five years.Apple in August became the first U.S. publicly traded company to reach a $1 trillion market capitalization.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of size and employment opportunities to be created by Apple in Austin2. Depiction of employment opportunities to be created by Apple in San Diego, Seattle and Culver City, California.3. Depiction of location of Apple expansion to New York, Pittsburgh and Boulder, Colorado4. Representation of Apple's investment in U.S. data centersVOICEOVER (in English): "Apple announced on a press release that it will open new facilities in Austin, Texas. The company said it will invest $1 billion on its new campus, which will spread across 133 acres and generate 5,000 new jobs." "Apple also plans to expand its operations to San Diego, Seattle and Culver City, California, creating a total of more than 1,000 jobs.""Additionally, it intends to hire hundreds of new employees in offices in New York, Pittsburgh and Boulder, Colorado within three years." "The plan also includes a $10 billion investment in U.S. data centers in the next five years"SOURCES: Applehttps://www.apple.com/newsroom/2018/12/apple-to-build-new-campus-in-austin-and-add-jobs-across-the-us/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/18/3749685/3749685_F3E7C401F6FF4BD69D401D7DB3CAFC9E_181218_3749685_Apple_plans_to_expand_operations_across_the_US_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Apple, Austin, Texas, tech, company, investment, campus, Apple new campus, apple expansion.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3750697</guid>
      <title>The Ocean Cleanup system isn't capturing plastic as planned</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA system designed to reduce the amount of plastic pollution in the Pacific Ocean has not been collecting plastic. According to Forbes, the Ocean Cleanup System 001 created by The Ocean Cleanup left San Francisco in September with an overall goal of cleaning up half of the Great Pacific Garbage Patch in five years and a 90 percent reduction by 2040. System 001 is a 2,000 feet long floater, with a 10-foot deep skirt connected below. The floater is designed to stop plastics from flowing over the system, while the skirt traps particles from escaping underneath. It's made from HDPE plastic and is flexible enough to bend with the waves, but rigid enough to form a U-shaped barrier to trap floating plastics pollution, according to Fast Company. The design takes advantage of natural oceanic forces to retrieve and concentrate the plastic.According to project leaders, aside from 2 metric tons of discarded fishing nets, no significant amount of plastic has yet been removed.The problem appears to be the system is moving too slow. Plastic enters the system, but is only concentrated for a few days, which is not long enough for it to be harvested. The organization said another problem is the system creates waves, preventing some plastic from entering the device. According to the organizers, increasing the span of System 001 should increase the surface that will effectively catch wind and waves, adding force, and increasing the floater's speed. They plan to make the system 25 percent bigger by opening the floater around 197 to 230 feet.According to Forbes, the team will continue to work to find a solution and hope to launch a System 002 in early 2020.     RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. System 001 leaving San Francisco2. System 001 floating at sea3. System 001 has removed fishing nets, but not a significant amount of plastic4. System 001 creates waves, preventing plastic from entering device5. Organizers want to increase span of system to increase floater speed6. The team plans to make the system 25 percent bigger and 60 to 70 meters widerVOICEOVER (in English): "The Ocean Cleanup System 001 created by The Ocean Cleanup left San Francisco in September with an overall goal of cleaning up half of the Great Pacific Garbage Patch in five years and a 90 percent reduction by 2040." "System 001 is a 2,000 feet long floater, with a 10-foot deep skirt connected below. The floater is designed to stop plastics from flowing over the system, while the skirt traps particles from escaping underneath." "According to project leaders, aside from 2 metric tons of discarded fishing nets, no significant amount of plastic has yet been removed.""The problem appears to be the system is moving too slow, so plastic enters the system, but is only concentrated for a few days, which is not long enough for it to be harvested." "The organization said another problem is the system creates waves, preventing some plastic from entering the device." "According to the organizers, increasing the span of System 001 should add surface that will effectively catch wind and waves, adding force, and increasing the floater's speed." "They plan to make the system 25 percent bigger by opening the floater around 197 to 230 feet."SOURCES: Forbes, CNN, Fast Companyhttps://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffkart/2018/12/05/the-ocean-cleanup-isnt-capturing-plastic-but-organizers-are-testing-a-solution/#5b16da6a1749https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/18/us/ocean-cleanup-system-pacific-garbage-patch-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.fastcompany.com/40560810/the-revolutionary-giant-ocean-cleanup-machine-is-about-to-set-sail***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 11:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/19/3750697/3750697_DA435A262FA844BFBF8E6EE4A96F5E8B_181219_3750697_The_Ocean_Cleanup_system_isn_t_capturing_plastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, The Ocean Cleanup, The Ocean Cleanup System 001, Great Pacific Garbage Patch, plastic pollution, ocean plastic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3750455</guid>
      <title>US Air Force launches first next-generation GPS satellite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe new satellite model, called GPS III, is the first of 32 planned GPS III satellites that will replace older ones currently in orbit. GPS III satellites have an improved accuracy of one to three meters under good conditions, three times more accurate than current GPS systems.The satellite is also proven to be compatible with existing GPS constellations as well as other international global navigation satellite systems. This allows for improved connectivity and accuracy among civilian users around the world.The new satellite models will also have stronger military signals less prone to jamming and will last 25 percent longer than any of the GPS satellites currently in orbit. Officials from the Government Accountability Office said the price of production of a GPSIII satellite is $577 million.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Falcon9 launch2. Representation of new GPS upgrade3. Representation of GPS III improved accuracy4. Portrayal of GPSIII improvements for military useVOICEOVER (in English): "The new first-generation GPS satellite will be launched into orbit on a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket.""The new satellite model, called GPS III, is the first of 32 planned GPS III satellites that will replace older ones currently in orbit." "GPS III satellites have an improved accuracy of one to three meters under good conditions, three times more accurate than current GPS systems.""The satellite is also proven to be compatible with existing GPS constellations as well as other international global navigation satellite systems. This allows for improved connectivity and accuracy among civilian users around the world.""The new satellite models will also have stronger military signals less prone to jamming and will last 25 percent longer than any of the GPS satellites currently on-orbit."SOURCES: APhttps://www.apnews.com/b05b1b6d22ec4058bf7419744205104b***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 06:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/19/3750455/3750455_DBF3282A7A254AB492202B1BF6C6B953_181219_3750455_US_Air_Force_launches_first_next_generation_GPS__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, Air Force, GPS satellite, US Air Force, USAF, next generation GPS satellite, SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket, GPS III satellites, Lockheed Martin, Schriever Air Force Base, SpaceX, Cape Canaveral.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3750335</guid>
      <title>NASA study says Saturn is losing its rings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew NASA research confirms that Saturn is losing its rings at a rate which researchers describe as a "worst-case-scenario." Phys.org reports that using observations made by Voyager 1 and 2 decades ago, scientists say the rings are being pulled into Saturn by gravity as a dusty rain of ice particles under the influence of the planet's magnetic field. According to James O'Donoghue of NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Maryland, this 'ring rain' drains enough water every 30 minutes to fill an Olympic-sized swimming pool. According to scientists' estimates, the rings could be completely gone in 100 million years. Saturn's rings are mainly composed of chunks of water ice ranging in size from microscopic dust to boulders several yards in width.  Ring particles have several forces acting upon them. Saturn's gravity want to draw the particles towards the planet, while their orbital velocity wants to shoot them out towards space.  The tiny particles can also get electrically charged from the Sun or from plasma clouds.These charged particles can also feel the pull of Saturn's magnetic field, which curves inward toward the planet at Saturn's rings. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Saturn's rings being pulled in by gravity and Saturn's magnetosphere2. Ring rain drains enough water to fill pool, rings gone in 100 million years3. Forces acting on ring particles4. Charged particles interacting with magnetic fieldVOICEOVER (in English): "Using observations made by Voyager 1 and 2 decades ago, scientists say the rings are being pulled into Saturn by gravity as a dusty rain of ice particles under the influence of the planet's magnetic field." "According to James O'Donoghue of NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Maryland, this 'ring rain' drains enough water every 30 minutes to fill an Olympic-sized swimming pool." "According to scientists' estimates, the rings could be completely gone in 100 million years." "Ring particles have several forces acting upon them. Saturn's gravity want to draw the particles towards the planet, while their orbital velocity wants to shoot them out towards space.  "The tiny particles can also get electrically charged from the Sun or from plasma clouds.These charged particles can also feel the pull of Saturn's magnetic field, which curves inward toward the planet at Saturn's rings." SOURCES: Phys.orghttps://phys.org/news/2018-12-nasa-reveals-saturn-worst-case-scenario.html ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 03:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/19/3750335/3750335_0448C403E33849BFAE6E4C28D1615BB8_181219_3750335_NASA_study_says_Saturn_is_losing_its_rings_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Saturn, Saturn's rings, Saturn losing its rings, Saturn losing rings, ring rain, Saturn rings, planetary rings]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3750311</guid>
      <title>Chinese city uses cockroaches to process food waste</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs Chinese cities expand and create more food waste, cockroaches could be used as an effective tool in waste disposal.Jinan, a city in northern China has been feeding a billion cockroaches with 50 tonnes of kitchen waste a day, reports Reuters.The food scraps arrive at the Shandong Qiaobin Agricultural Technology Company and are run through pipes and fed to cockroaches in their cells.When the cockroaches eventually die, the company says they can be used to feed livestock such as pigs as cockroaches are a good source of protein.The company plans to set up three more waste disposal plants, aiming to process a third of the city's food waste.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A Chinese flag, food waste in bins and cockroaches are shown2. A pile of food waste and a bunch of cockroaches 3. Machinery processing the food waste and cockroaches eating the processed food waste4. Dead cockroaches and a pigVOICEOVER (in English): "As Chinese cities expand and create more food waste, cockroaches could be used as an effective tool in waste disposal.""Reuters reports a city in northern China has been feeding a billion cockroaches with 50 tonnes of kitchen waste a day.""The food scraps arrive at the Shandong Qiaobin Agricultural Technology Company and are run through pipes and fed to cockroaches in their cells.""When the cockroaches eventually die, the company says they can be used to feed livestock such as pigs as cockroaches are a good source of protein."SOURCES: Reuters, NOQ report https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-cockroaches-idUSKBN1O90PXhttps://noqreport.com/2018/12/16/china-farming-cockroaches-billions/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 02:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/19/3750311/3750311_50FAF47828084F9ABE12516D1414E788_181219_3750311_Chinese_city_uses_cockroaches_to_process_food_wa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, china cockroach farm, processing food waste, cockroaches processing food waste, cockroaches food waste]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3751407</guid>
      <title>Trump begins troop withdrawal from Syria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPresident Trump has ordered full withdrawal of U.S. troops from Syria, after claiming on Wednesday the Islamic State group had been "defeated.""We have defeated ISIS in Syria, my only reason for being there during the Trump Presidency," the president said in a Twitter post Wednesday morning. According to White House Press Secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders in a statement, "we have started returning United States troops home as we transition to the next phase of this campaign." According to Reuters, the decision for a total pull out coincides with the approximately 2,000 U.S. troops finishing up a campaign to retake territory held by Islamic State militants. One U.S. official told Reuters the administration is looking to withdraw troops within 60 to 100 days and the U.S. State Department was evacuating all personnel in Syria within 24 hours. According the BBC, U.S. troops have largely been stationed in the Kurdish region in northern Syria. A partnership with an alliance of Syrian Kurdish and Arab fighters, known as the Syrian Democratic Forces, or SDF, is said to have played a major role in the elimination of IS forces throughout the territory.Many of the remaining U.S. soldiers in Syria are special operations forces working closely with the SDF. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. US troops being withdrawn from Syria2. US troops during campaign 3. US troop and personnel removal timeline4. US troops have been mainly stationed in Kurdish controlled northern SyriaVOICEOVER (in English): "President Trump has ordered full withdrawal of U.S. troops from Syria, after claiming on Wednesday the Islamic State group had been "defeated."""According to Reuters, the decision for a total pull out coincides with the approximately 2,000 U.S. troops finishing up a campaign to retake territory held by Islamic State militants." "One U.S. official told Reuters the administration is looking to withdraw troops within 60 to 100 days and the U.S. State Department was evacuating all personnel in Syria within 24 hours." "According the BBC, U.S. troops have largely been stationed in the Kurdish region in northern Syria." "A partnership with an alliance of Syrian Kurdish and Arab fighters, known as the Syrian Democratic Forces, or SDF, is said to have played a major role in the elimination of IS forces throughout the territory."SOURCES: New York Times, Reuters, BBChttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/19/us/politics/trump-syria-turkey-troop-withdrawal.html?action=click&module=Top%20Stories&pgtype=Homepagehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-syria/trump-starts-withdrawal-of-us-forces-from-syria-claims-victory-idUSKBN1OI1JChttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46623617***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 12:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/20/3751407/3751407_8789C04929254CE796198D51F15AB78B_181220_3751407_Trump_begins_troop_withdrawal_from_Syria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump, Syria, Trump Syria withdrawal, US troop withdrawal, Syria civil war]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3751313</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy has had 18 unsafe encounters with China since 2016</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. military statistics indicate that American naval forces have had more than a dozen unsafe encounters with Chinese forces over the last two years.Commander Nate Christensen, spokesman of the U.S. Pacific fleet, told CNN there have been 18 unsafe or unprofessional interactions with China and one with Russia since 2016.Most incidents reportedly happened during 2017. At least three that took place in February, May, and July involved Chinese fighter jets unsafely intercepting Navy surveillance planes.The U.S. frequently conducts freedom of navigation operations in the South China Sea to challenge China's maritime claims in the area. This has resulted in several incidents throughout the years.The most recent encounter occurred on September 30 while the USS Decatur was sailing near Gavin Reef in the South China Sea's Spratly Islands.PRC destroyer Luyang reportedly came within 135 feet of the American vessel's bow, forcing it to maneuver to avoid a collision.The U.S. Air Force has had at least one encounter with China during the same period. In May 2017, Chinese SU-30 fighter jets came within 150 feet of a radiation detection plane over the East China Sea. One SU-30 was reportedly flying upside down directly above the American plane.Incidents are typically addressed through diplomatic and military channels, but the frequency of such encounters raises the possibility of a collision or clash that could spark major conflict between Washington and Beijing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. Navy unsafely intercepted 18 times by China, once by Russia since 20162. Chinese fighter jet intercepting Navy surveillance plane on three incidents in 20173. U.S. freedom of navigation in South China Sea resulting in altercations with China4. USS Decatur sailing near Spratlys in South China Sea5. Chinese destroyer came within 135 feet of USS Decatur6. 7.VOICEOVER (in English): "Commander Nate Christensen, spokesman of the U.S. Pacific fleet, told CNN there have been 18 unsafe or unprofessional interactions with China and one with Russia since 2016.""Most incidents reportedly happened in 2017. At least three that took place in February, May, and July involved Chinese fighter jets unsafely intercepting Navy surveillance planes.""The U.S. frequently conducts freedom of navigation operations in the South China Sea to challenge China's maritime claims in the area. This has resulted in several incidents throughout the years.""The most recent encounter occurred on September 30 while the USS Decatur was sailing near Gavin Reef in the South China Sea's Spratly Islands.""PRC destroyer Luyang reportedly came within 135 feet of the American vessel's bow, forcing it to maneuver to avoid a collision.""The U.S. Air Force has had at least one encounter with China during the same period. In May 2017, Chinese SU-30 fighter jets came within 150 feet of a radiation detection plane over the East China Sea.""One SU-30 was reportedly flying upside down directly above the American plane.""Incidents are typically addressed through diplomatic and military channels, but the frequency of such encounters raises the possibility of a collision or clash that could spark major conflict between Washington and Beijing."SOURCES: CNNhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/03/politics/navy-unsafe-encounters-china/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2017/05/18/politics/china-us-jets-intercept/index.html?no-st=1545275598***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 10:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/20/3751313/3751313_1F61C3DD0A3B4209B1A8BE8F3349ED11_181220_3751313_U_S__Navy_has_had_18_unsafe_encounters_with_Chin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US China, US navy intercept, South China Sea, US China tension, US navy, Chinese navy, unsafe intercept, unsafe encounter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3751299</guid>
      <title>Polar vortex could bring harsh winter to U.S. east coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANClimate scientists are warning that a polar vortex could sweep across the U.S. east coast and unleash one of the harshest winters in years.According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, the polar vortex is an area of low pressure, cold air surrounding the north and south poles. The 'vortex' or counterclockwise flow of air keeps frigid air closer to the poles.But during winter in the Northern Hemisphere, the vortex can often become less stable and expand. As a result, cold Arctic air is sent southward with the jet stream, causing severe winter weather.The Washington Post reports that vortex disruption has been associated with a phenomenon known as a sudden stratospheric warming event. During such an event, the prevailing winds decrease or change direction, and the layer warms. When this occurs, the vortex is displaced and sometimes splits apart.Based on American modeling systems, the disruption is projected to occur this month. The European system, however, delays it until early January.While it's difficult to predict which region will be struck first, University of Oklahoma meteorology professor Jason Furtado claims Eurasia will be hit first, based on model forecasts. This means the Lower 48 states are likely weeks away from feeling any effect.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of a polar vortex2. Depiction of arctic air sent southward3. Depiction of severe winter weather4. Vortex disruption associated with sudden stratospheric warming event5. Vortex becomes displaced, splits apart6. Vortex disruption felt in Eurasia first, Lower 48 states weeks from feeling any effectVOICEOVER (in English): "The polar vortex is an area of low pressure, cold air surrounding the north and south poles. The 'vortex' or counterclockwise flow of air keeps frigid air closer to the poles.""But during winter in the Northern Hemisphere, the vortex can often become less stable and expand.""As a result, cold Arctic air is sent southward with the jet stream, causing severe winter weather.""Vortex disruption has been associated with a phenomenon known as a sudden stratospheric warming event. During such an event, the prevailing winds decrease or change direction, and the layer warms.""When this occurs, the vortex is displaced and sometimes splits apart.""While it's difficult to predict which region will be struck first, University of Oklahoma meteorology professor Jason Furtado claims Eurasia will be hit first, based on model forecasts.""This means the Lower 48 states are likely weeks away from feeling any effect."SOURCES: Washington Post, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, Fox 5 DChttps://www.washingtonpost.com/weather/2018/12/17/polar-vortex-could-unleash-winter-wallop-by-january/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.c9086212a433https://www.noaa.gov/infographic/science-behind-polar-vortexhttp://www.fox5dc.com/weather/potential-for-polar-vortex-on-the-horizon-heres-what-you-need-to-know***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 10:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/20/3751299/3751299_1D4FCFA1C8D24CE587F88554127FD83D_181220_3751299_Polar_vortex_could_bring_harsh_winter_to_U_S__ea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, polar vortex, polar vortex 2018, jet stream, sudden stratospheric warming, sudden stratospheric warming event, vortex disruption, winter, harsh winter, severe winter, arctic air]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3750929</guid>
      <title>Japan upping military spending</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan is set to increase military spending over the next five years to deter threats from China and Russia.Tokyo plans to purchase 45 F-35B advanced stealth fighter jets, Reuters reports.This aircraft can perform short take-offs and vertical landings.These Japanese navy has two helicopter carriers called Izumo and Kaga.These are set to be modified with reinforced decks and may also be fitted with ramps for the new stealth fighter.The country also plans to purchase Aegis Ashore air defense radars, Boeing KC-46 Pegasus refueling planes as well as the Northrop Grumman E-2 Hawkeye early-warning planes and other equipment.Additionally, Japan also plans to buy longer-range Raytheon SM-3 interceptor missiles to defend against North Korea if necessary.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The F-35B fighter jets are shown taking off and landing vertically2. The Izumo and Kaga helicopter carriers3. The Aegis Ashore air defense radars and the Boeing Co KC-46 Pegasus 4. The Northrop Grumman E-2 Hawkeye plane5. Raytheon SM-3 interceptor missiles and North Korea on a mapVOICEOVER (in English): "Reuters reports Japan plans to purchase 45 F-35B advanced stealth fighter jets. "This aircraft can perform short take-offs and vertical landings.""Japan's navy has two helicopter carriers called Izumo and Kaga.""These are set to be modified with reinforced decks and may also be fitted with ramps for the new stealth fighter.""The country also plans to purchase Aegis Ashore air defense radars, Boeing KC-46 Pegasus refueling planes...""...as well as the Northrop Grumman E-2 Hawkeye early-warning planes and other equipment.""Additionally, Japan also plans to buy longer-range Raytheon SM-3 interceptor missiles to defend against North Korea if necessary."SOURCES: Reuters, South China Morning Post, Japan Today, Japan Times, https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-defence/japan-bolsters-military-to-counter-china-russia-in-east-asia-idUSKBN1OH05Zhttps://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/2178442/japans-new-defence-guidelines-plans-first-aircraft-carrier-andhttps://japantoday.com/category/politics/japan-draft-defense-plan-seeks-aircraft-carrier-for-us-jetshttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2018/12/13/national/politics-diplomacy/japans-new-defense-guidelines-will-outline-plans-integrated-flexible-multidimensional-force/#.XBiQroiFNjU***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 02:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/20/3750929/3750929_9053D3A6A0F84FA78ECD300ACB619C2B_181220_3750929_Japan_upping_military_spending_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan, japanese military, japanese military equipment,  china, russia, north korea, military, defense, japan f-35b, Izumo, Kaga, advanced stealth fighter jets, longer-range Raytheon sm-3 interceptor missiles, Northrop Grumman e-2 Hawkeye, Aegis Ashore air defense radars, Boeing Co KC-46 Pegasus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3751936</guid>
      <title>Company develops 3D-printed vegan meat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Italian bioengineer at a Spanish startup claims to have invented the world's first vegan steak made using 3D printing technology.Giuseppe Scionti from Spanish startup Novameat created a mixture that includes rice, peas and seaweed to create a 3D-printed patty that mimics the fleshy texture of texture of beef.Scionti said the the machine is able to create the meat-like texture without using high temperatures and keep the nutritional content of the steak.The ingredients are turned into a paste and mixed with a paella colourant and inserted into syringes.The syringes are inserted into a 3D printer and then printed into a steak-like product. After being printed, the steak can go on to be cooked.In addition to the steak, the company has also developed a vegan chicken breast made from ingredients including lipids, fibers, minerals and vitamins that mimics the texture animal meat.Scionti, who founded Nova Meat, told architecture and design magazine Dezeen that it takes around 30 minutes to print a 100 gram of steak.In addition to creating an ethical meat alternative, Scionti hopes the vegan steaks will help reduce greenhouse gas emissions from livestock to make our planet more sustainable.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rice, peas and seaweed along with the 3D printed vegan meat2. The ingredient turned into a paste, mixed with a colorant and put into syringes 3. The 3D printer printing the steak4. A vegan chick breast with made with lipids, fibers, minerals and vitaminsVOICEOVER (in English): "Giuseppe Scionti from Spanish startup Novameat concocted a mixture that includes rice, peas and seaweed to create a 3D-printed patty that mimics the fleshy texture of texture of beef.""The ingredients are turned into a paste and mixed with a paella colourant and inserted into syringes.""The syringes are inserted into a 3D printer and then printed into a steak-like product.""After being printed, the steak can go on to be cooked.""In addition to the steak, the company has also developed a vegan chicken breast made from ingredients including lipids, fibers, minerals and vitamins that mimics the texture animal meat."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Nova Meat, Food Navigator, Dezeen, 3D printing Industry, https://inhabitat.com/3d-printed-vegan-steak-could-aid-world-hunger-relief-efforts/https://www.novameat.com/https://www.foodnavigator.com/Article/2018/10/18/Italian-researcher-on-3D-printing-tech-for-plant-based-meat-We-re-bio-hacking-plant-protein-structure-at-micro-and-nano-scalehttps://www.dezeen.com/2018/11/30/novameat-3d-printed-meat-free-steak/https://3dprintingindustry.com/news/novameat-3d-prints-vegetarian-steak-from-plant-based-proteins-144722/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 10:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/21/3751936/3751936_1080377830794D9BA6C66C5DC73B35F2_181221_3751936_Company_develops_3D_printed_vegan_meat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, spain, 3D printing, nova meat, nova meat 3D, plant based meat, 3D printed meat,  nova meat giuseppe scionti, nova meat 3d, 3d printed food, meat substitute, giuseppe scionti]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3751883</guid>
      <title>U.S. charges Chinese hackers in global scheme to target companies and military</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Justice Department charged two Chinese nationals on Thursday in a worldwide hacking scheme to acquire business and military secrets in a campaign allegedly directed by the Chinese Communist Party. Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein said hackers from a group referred to as Advanced Persistent Threat 10, or APT 10, stole information from more than 45 businesses in the U.S. in coordination with China's state security service, CNN Business reported. According to the indictment, the hackers also targeted U.S. military service members, stealing "sensitive data belonging to the Navy, including the names, Social Security numbers, dates of birth, salary information, personal phone numbers and email addresses of more than 100,000 Navy personnel."According to Rosenstein, the U.S. coordinated with 11 other countries: Brazil, Canada, Finland, France, Germany, India, Japan, Sweden, Switzerland, the United Arab Emirates and the United Kingdom. According to the indictment, the hackers worked for a company with ties to the Chinese government. The two are accused of attacks from 2006 to 2018. The charges include aggravated identity theft, conspiracy to commit computer intrusions and conspiracy to commit wire fraud. The charges come amid rising trade tensions between the U.S. and China. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. DOJ has charged two Chinese hackers2. Chinese hackers stealing information from U.S. businesses3. Chinese hackers stealing information from U.S. Navy4. US coordinated efforts with 11 other countriesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Justice Department charged two Chinese nationals on Thursday in a worldwide hacking scheme to acquire business and military secrets in a campaign allegedly directed by the Chinese Communist Party." "According to CNN, Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein said the hackers were from a group referred to as Advanced Persistent Threat 10, or APT 10. They stole information from more than 45 businesses in the U.S. in coordination with China's state security service."  "According to the indictment, the hackers also targeted U.S. military service members. 'Sensitive data belonging to the Navy, including the names, Social Security numbers, dates of birth, salary information, personal phone numbers, and email addresses of more than 100,000 Navy personnel' were reportedly stolen.""According to Rosenstein, the U.S. coordinated with 11 other countries: Brazil, Canada, Finland, France, Germany, India, Japan, Sweden, Switzerland, the United Arab Emirates and the United Kingdom." SOURCES: CNNhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/20/tech/chinese-hacker-charges/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 09:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/21/3751883/3751883_769C283079184993ACCFA6A88E68C39A_181221_3751883_U_S__charges_Chinese_hackers_in_global_scheme_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China hacking, DOJ charges Chinese hackers, APT 10, Advanced Persistent Threat 10, China hackers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3751626</guid>
      <title>Japan's new sightseeing train designed like a wooden Kyoto house</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan's Hankyu Railway has announced plans to operate the second-generation of the "Kyo-train" from March of next year.The train's interior is themed "Japanese Modern, "Kyomachiya," which refers to the wooden townhouses traditionally found in Kyoto in the 1950's.The carriages will include circular windows and a mini Japanese garden. Each of the six carriages will depict Kyoto's changes across the seasons with one depicting autumn and maple leaves while another depicts winter and bambooThe train will travel between Osaka Umeda Station and Kyoto Kawaramachi Station.Passengers will not need to pay extra or book a reservation to experience the luxurious interior of the new "Kyo-train." Tickets will only cost about 400 yen or around US$4.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Kyotrain on a train track2. Interior of the Kyotrain3. What the Kyotrain carriages will depict4. Where the train will travel betweenVOICEOVER (in English): "Japan's Hankyu Railway has announced plans to operate the second-generation of the 'Kyotrain' from March of next year.""The train's interior is themed 'Japanese Modern, 'Kyomachiya,' which refers to the wooden townhouses traditionally found in Kyoto.""The carriages will include circular windows and a mini Japanese garden.""Each of the six carriages will depict Kyoto's changes across the seasons with one depicting autumn and maple leaves while another depicts winter and bamboo""The train will travel between Osaka Umeda Station and Kyoto Kawaramachi Station."SOURCES: Hankyu Railway, Sora News 24, Grapee, http://www.hankyu.co.jp/global/en/characteristic/special_specification_train/index.htmlhttps://soranews24.com/2018/12/11/the-all-new-kyotrain-maybe-japans-most-japanese-train-ever-will-take-you-to-kyoto-this-spring/https://grapee.jp/en/107462***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 03:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/21/3751626/3751626_51BE8480CB994FA88C8B1C8EA8DDBC3D_181221_3751626_Japan_s_new_sightseeing_train_designed_like_a_wo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan, sightseeing train, kyoto, wooden kyoto house, japanese sightseeing train, japanese train, kyotrain, hankyu railway, Kyomachiya, kyotrain interior, traditional kyoto design]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3752667</guid>
      <title>Ford develops prototype for high-tech noise-canceling dog kennel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFord has designed a prototype for a noise-canceling dog kennel employing the same noise-control technology installed in some Ford vehicles. The design is part of an innovation series called Interventions, which explores the use of automotive technologies to solve everyday problems. According to a press release published in the company's blog, the kennel is isolated with high-density cork, noise cancellation panels, anti-vibration block risers, and soundproof ventilation.Special microphones installed within the kennel detect loud noises. A built-in audio system then generates opposing frequencies, significantly reducing noise within the kennel.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of design of Ford's dog kennel prototype versus regular dog house2. Representation of comparison of technology in Ford cars and new kennel prototype3. Depiction of materials used to build  noise-cancellation dog kennel4. Representation of noise-cancellation dog kennel in use. VOICEOVER (in English): "Ford has designed a prototype for a noise-canceling dog kennel employing the same noise-control technology installed in some Ford vehicles." "The design is part of an innovation series called Interventions, which explores the use of automotive technologies to solve everyday problems." "According to a press release published in the company's blog, the kennel is isolated with high-density cork, noise cancellation panels, anti-vibration block risers, and soundproof ventilation.""Special microphones installed within the kennel detect loud noises. A built-in audio system then generates opposing frequencies, significantly reducing noise within the kennel."SOURCES:Ford Europehttps://fordeurope.blogspot.com/2018/12/ford-quiet-kennel-safe-place-for-mans.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 23:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/23/3752667/3752667_8BB0F2AF9C1B426CB1998C80FFC6E558_181223_3752667_Ford_develops_prototype_for_high_tech_noise_canc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ford, Ford Europe, noise cancellation, noise cancellation technology, noise canceling dog kennel, innovation, high tech, new tech, new technology, prototype.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3752616</guid>
      <title>Drone activity shuts down Gatwick airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTens of thousands of passengers have had their travel plans disrupted after one of London's busiest airports shut down due to drone activity on the runway.According to the BBC, the runway at Gatwick Airport was closed after two drones were seen flying over a perimeter fence around 9 p.m. on Wednesday.It reopened around 3 a.m. Thursday, before closing again after 45 minutes amid further sightings. Sussex police say there have been 50 reported sightings in 24 hours.The New York Times reports that at least 800 flights were canceled, affecting over 100,000 passengers. Incoming flights were diverted to other airports, with some landing as far as Paris and Amsterdam.Twenty police units searched the airfield perimeter on Thursday, but could not locate the drones' operators.Sussex police had earlier ruled out shooting down the drones, citing concerns over stray bullets. But they are now considering it as a tactical option.According to a spokesman for the Ministry of Defense, the British army has also been called in to assist, and are deploying specialist equipment.According to USA Today, authorities described the drones as "industrial specification." This indicates they are larger than hobby aircraft, and "could be more dangerous if they crash into a plane's windshield or get absorbed by its engines."Officials have called the repeated drone incursions a "deliberate act", but say there's no indication to suggest that it is terror-related.With the drone still at large, officials say Gatwick Airport could remain closed for all of Friday.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Runway closure after drones seen flying over Gatwick Airport perimeter fence2. Passengers stranded in airport, canceled and diverted flights3. Police searching for drone operator; possibility of shooting down drone4. Industrial drone larger than hobby crafts, more dangerous if it hits plane windshield, engineVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, the runway at Gatwick Airport was closed after two drones were seen flying over a perimeter fence around 9 p.m. on Wednesday.""It reopened around 3 a.m. Thursday, before closing again after 45 minutes amid further sightings. Sussex police say there have been 50 reported sightings in 24 hours.""The New York Times reports that at least 800 flights were canceled, affecting over 100,000 passengers. Incoming flights were diverted to other airports, with some landing as far as Paris and Amsterdam.""Twenty police units searched the airfield perimeter on Thursday, but could not locate the drones' operators.""Sussex police had earlier ruled out shooting down the drones, citing concerns over stray bullets. But they are now considering it as a tactical option.""According to USA Today, authorities described the drones as 'industrial specification.' This indicates they are larger than hobby aircraft, and 'could be more dangerous if they crash into a plane's windshield or get absorbed by its engines.'"SOURCES: New York Times, BBC, USA Today, The Independenthttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/20/world/europe/gatwick-airport-drones.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-sussex-46640033https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-sussex-46623754https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2018/12/20/londons-gatwick-airport-shutdown-drones-cause-flight-delays-chaos/2373311002/https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/gatwick-airport-live-updates-flight-delays-latest-drones-airlines-cancellations-christmas-travel-a8691976.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/23/3752616/3752616_296E3A9B0B23463497975C8ECF25DB43_181223_3752616_Drone_activity_shuts_down_Gatwick_airport_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, gatwick airport shutdown, gatwick airport drone, gatwick airport, gatwick flights, gatwick cancelled flights, drone, rogue drone, drone in airport, drone collision, cancelled flights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3753120</guid>
      <title>Japan to withdraw from whaling commision to resume whaling</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Japanese government reportedly has plans to resume commercial whaling for the first time in 30 years.According to Kyodo News, Japan plans to withdraw from the International Whaling Commission in 2019 amid plans to resume commercial whaling.Japan has to present its official withdrawal to the commission by the end of the year. If accepted, the decision would be effective the following June.The decision comes after the IWC rejected Japan's proposal to resume commercial whaling at an annual meeting in Brazil in September. Although Japan has not technically practiced commercial whaling for 30 years, it has been hunting whales in the Antarctic Ocean for "scientific research" under the exception of an IWC rule.According to the BBC, Japanese whalers have caught between about 200 and 1,200 whales each year. They claim they are investigating stock levels to see whether the whales are endangered or not.If Japan leaves the IWC, the country can no longer continue to conduct "scientific" whaling expeditions in the Antarctic. However, the Japanese government plans to limit its whaling to its exclusive economic zone, which covers an area of over four million square kilometers, according to geography website World Atlas.Iceland and Norway are the only other countries in the world that authorize whaling. Both are members of the IWC.IWC members Denmark, Russia, St. Vincent and the Grenadines, and the US allow indigenous or aboriginal subsistence whaling for a few native populations who hunt whales as part of their culture.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of members of IWC and withdrawal of Japan2. Representation of the location of Japan's Antarctic whaling activities3. Representation of Japanese whale hunting4. Representation of Japan's Exclusive Economic ZoneVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Kyodo News, Japan plans to withdraw from the International Whaling Commission in 2019 amid plans to resume commercial whaling.""Japan has to present its official withdrawal to the commission by the end of the year. If accepted, the decision would be effective the following June.""Although Japan has not technically practiced commercial whaling for 30 years, it has been hunting whales in the Antarctic Ocean for 'scientific research' under the exception of an IWC rule.""According to the BBC, Japanese whalers have caught between about 200 and 1,200 whales each year. They claim they are investigating stock levels to see whether the whales are endangered or not.""If Japan leaves the IWC, Japan can no longer continue to conduct 'scientific' whaling expeditions in the Antarctic." "However, the Japanese government plans to limit its whaling to its exclusive economic zone, which covers an area of over four million square kilometers, according to geography website World Atlas."SOURCES: Kyodo News, BBC, International Whaling Commission, World Atlashttps://english.kyodonews.net/news/2018/12/05bd54236e5a-urgent-japan-to-withdraw-from-iwc-to-resume-commercial-whaling-sources.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-46629341https://iwc.int/aboriginalhttps://iwc.int/commercialhttps://www.worldatlas.com/articles/countries-with-the-largest-exclusive-economic-zones.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/24/3753120/3753120_73C5C89DA0FB4852AEC959E4E7F488E6_181224_3753120_Japan_to_withdraw_from_whaling_commision_to_resu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, whaling, conservation, Japan, whales, whale, laws, illegal, poaching, caught, regulations, commercial, species, populations, environment, ecosystem, whaling in Japan, whaling regulation.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3754501</guid>
      <title>Mexican governor, senator husband killed in helicopter crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe first female governor of Mexico's second largest city, and her senator husband lost their lives in a tragic Christmas Eve helicopter crash.According to the BBC, the Mexico city bound helicopter carrying Puebla governor Martha Erika Alonso and Senator Rafael Moreno Valle took off from a Puebla city helipad on Monday afternoon.The Augusta 109 helicopter reportedly lost contact with air traffic control and crashed 10 minutes after takeoff. It came down around 2:50 p.m. local time in a cornfield in the municipality of Santa Maria Coronango.Alonso and Moreno Valle died in the crash along with the two pilots and another unidentified passenger.Federal and state officials say they have opened investigations into the cause of the accident, but some are calling for an independent probe as the case is potentially sensitive.Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador's leftist Morena party had challenged the validity of Alonso's election in July. There were allegations that Moreno Valle, who governed Puebla from 2011 to 2017, manipulated the election to pass power to his wife.Alonso was sworn in just ten days ago after an electoral tribune validated the results.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Helicopter carrying Mexican governor, senator leave Puebla for Mexico City2. Helicopter lost contact with air traffic control, crashes 10 minutes after takeoff3. Helicopter crashes in Santa Maria Coronango4. Helicopter crash victimsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, the Mexico city bound helicopter carrying Puebla governor Martha Erika Alonso and Senator Rafael Moreno Valle took off from a Puebla city helipad on Monday afternoon.""The Augusta 109 helicopter reportedly lost contact with air traffic control and crashed 10 minutes after takeoff.""It came down around 2:50 p.m. local time in a cornfield in the municipality of Santa Maria Coronango.""Alonso and Moreno Valle died in the crash along with the two pilots and another unidentified passenger."SOURCES: BBC, Washington Posthttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-46677061https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/the_americas/mexico-aviation-crash-claims-puebla-governor-ex-governor/2018/12/24/74b696e0-07d9-11e9-8942-0ef442e59094_story.html?utm_term=.640847ece4ab***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/26/3754501/3754501_38B16C6156EE4907B6F4E8713EC5BC3A_181226_3754501_Mexican_governor__senator_husband_killed_in_heli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mexico helicopter crash, mexico helicopter accident, helicopter crash, helicopter accident, puebla governor, puebla helicopter crash, martha erika alonso, rafael moreno valle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3754310</guid>
      <title>Archaeologists uncover an ancient horse in Pompeii</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe remains of a horse wearing a harness have been discovered at the Villa of the Mysteries in Pompeii, according to the BBC.The villa is believed to have belonged to a high-ranking military official. The horse was found intact along with the skeletons of two other horses.Five bronze items and four conifer-wood finds coated in lamina bronze were also discovered, according to an Archaeological Park of Pompeii press release.The excavation is ongoing. Previously items such as kitchen utensils and a wooden bed had been discovered at the villa.The villa was originally dug up in the early 20th Century but had been a target of robbers.Massimo Osanna, director of Pompeii's archaeological park, told Italian news agency ANSA the whole area would be excavated before being opened up to the public.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pompeii on a globe and the remains of a horse wearing a harness2. The skeleton of two other horses3. Bronze items and conifer-wood finds4. Items previously uncovered in the ongoing excavationVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, the remains of a horse wearing a harness have been discovered at the Villa of the Mysteries in Pompeii.""The horse was found intact along with the skeletons of two other horses.""According to an Archaeological Park of Pompeii press release, five bronze items and four conifer-wood finds were also discovered.""The excavation is ongoing. Previously items such as kitchen utensils and a wooden bed had been discovered at the villa."SOURCES: ANSA, The BBC, The Washington Post,  Archaeological Park of Pompeii press releasehttp://www.ansa.it/sito/notizie/cultura/arte/2018/12/23/eccezionale-a-pompei-ritrovato-il-sauro-bardato-del-generale_7864c314-368f-448a-8b7d-899888e3b586.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46671050https://www.washingtonpost.com/history/2018/12/24/archaeologists-release-stunning-photos-new-pompeii-find-horses-remarkably-preserved-lava/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.31434f8ee757http://pompeiisites.org/en/comunicati/a-third-thoroughbred-with-an-elaborate-military-harness-has-been-discovered-in-the-stable-of-civita-giuliana/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 06:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/26/3754310/3754310_D3C368B1AD654A16ABA4B3A29724B140_181226_3754310_Archaeologists_uncover_an_ancient_horse_in_Pompe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pompei, archaeology, excavation, mount vesuvius, pompeii remains found, pompeii horse remains, Villa of the Mysteries, wine press, pompeii excavation, pompeii excavation site]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3755167</guid>
      <title>Israeli startup creates world's first lab-grown steak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIsraeli startup Aleph Farms has reached an important milestone in cellular meat production by creating the world's first lab-grown steak.According to the company, the steak has a similar texture to conventional meat, and has the same smell, however the taste and thickness still need to be refined. According to Business Insider, the prototype took 2-3 weeks to grow, with a small strip costing $50. According to Digital Trends, to grow the meat, Aleph Farms first isolates four types of animal cells from a living cow. These cells are then nourished in a growth medium to develop into a complex matrix that replicates muscle tissue.   According to co-founder and CEO Didier Toubia talking to Digital Trends, "this improved meat production method saves significant amounts of water and land, avoids animal welfare issues and antibiotics use." According to Toubia, they still need at least two more years of development before the meat is commercially available.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lab-grown steak characteristics2. Lab-growth time and steak cost3. Lab-growing process4. Benefits of lab-grown meat productionVOICEOVER (in English): "Israeli startup Aleph Farms has reached an important milestone in cellular meat production by creating the world's first lab-grown steak.""According to the company, the steak has a similar texture to conventional meat, and has the same smell, however the taste and thickness still need to be refined." "According to Business Insider, the prototype took 2-3 weeks to grow, with a small strip costing $50." "According to Digital Trends, to grow the meat, Aleph Farms first isolates four types of animal cells from a living cow. These cells are then nourished in a growth medium to develop into a complex matrix that replicates muscle tissue."   "Speaking to Digital Trends, co-founder and CEO Didier Toubia said, 'this improved meat production method saves significant amounts of water and land, avoids animal welfare issues and antibiotics use.'" SOURCES: Business Insider, Digital Trendshttps://www.businessinsider.com/aleph-farms-israeli-startup-makes-first-lab-grown-clean-steak-meat-photos-video-2018-12https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/aleph-farms-lab-grown-meat/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 13:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/27/3755167/3755167_57D20BE6335146ADA2880C06F9CF71FB_181227_3755167_Israeli_startup_creates_world_s_first_lab_grown__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, lab-grown steak, lab grown meat, lab grown beef, Aleph Farms, Aleph Farms Minute Steak]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3755016</guid>
      <title>US weapons and advisors used in Saudi Arabia-Yemeni conflict</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a report by the Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, Saudi Arabia is America's number one weapons buyer.The country accounts for 18 percent of total U.S. arms sales, which is equivalent to roughly $9 billion.According to CNN, the US signed a $29.4 billion deal in 2011 for 84 new F-15SA fighter jets, and the modernization of 70 current F-15s, including munitions, spare parts, training, maintenance, and logistics.In 2017, the U.S. military sold the Kingdom a $750 million program focused on how to carry out airstrikes. They also authorized the sale of over $510 million in precision-guided munitions, according to The New York Times.In the same year, the U.S. brokered a $110 billion arms deal that should be fulfilled over the next ten years.According to an official statement released by the U.S. State Department, Saudi Arabia is expected to purchase tanks, fighter jets, combat ships, and Air and Missile Defense systems.Currently, there are around 100 American military personnel providing intelligence support for the coalition. However, fewer than 35 are reportedly based in Saudi Arabia. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of percentage of US arms purchased by Saudi Arabia 2. Representation of US F-15s and services sold to Saudi Arabia 3. Representation of US authorities advising Saudi Arabia airstrikes4. Representation of weapons and arms expected to be purchased by Saudi Arabia in the $110 billion arms dealVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report by the Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, Saudi Arabia is America's number one weapons buyer. The country accounts for 18 percent of total U.S. arms sales, which is equivalent to roughly $9 billion.""According to CNN, the US signed a $29.4 billion deal in 2011 for 84 new F-15SA fighter jets, and the modernization of 70 current F-15s, including munitions, spare parts, training, maintenance, and logistics.""In 2017, the U.S. military sold the Kingdom a $750 million program focused on how to carry out airstrikes. They also authorized the sale of over $510 million in precision-guided munitions, according to The New York Times.""In the same year, the U.S. brokered a $110 billion arms deal that should be fulfilled over the next ten years.""According to an official statement released by the U.S. State Department, Saudi Arabia is expected to purchase tanks, fighter jets, combat ships, and Air and Missile Defense systems.""Currently, there are around 100 American military personnel providing intelligence support for the coalition. However, fewer than 35 are reportedly based in Saudi Arabia." SOURCES: Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, CNN, The New York Times, U.S. State Departmenthttps://www.sipri.org/sites/default/files/2018-03/fssipri_at2017_0.pdfhttps://edition.cnn.com/2011/12/29/world/meast/u-s--saudi-fighter-sale/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/25/world/middleeast/yemen-us-saudi-civilian-war.htmlhttps://www.state.gov/r/pa/prs/ps/2017/05/270999.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 09:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/27/3755016/3755016_79B2839F514F4F9E82B2739025C5C5B5_181227_3755016_US_weapons_and_advisors_used_in_Saudi_Arabia_Yem_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, saudi arabia, us, usa, weapons, made in usa, explainer, atlas, map, us arms trade, us arm sales, us military, saudi, monarchy, kingdom of saudi arabia, geopolitics, history, military, us saudi arms deals, yemen, yemen war, yemen crisis, arab, middle east, saudi bombs, Khashoggi, jamal khashoggi, yemen humanitarian crisis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3754894</guid>
      <title>Home-sharing company to install facial recognition door locks in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese home-sharing company Xiaozhu, plans to install door locks equipped with facial recognition in Chengdu, China.According to the South China Morning Post, the company said it will install the smart locks in 80 percent of its listings within the city. The smart locks will scan the face of tenants to verify their identity. Xiaozhu also plans to add devices such as smoke detectors, gas alarms and burglar alarms to more apartments.This comes as the Chinese government is looking to tighten controls and enhance security in home sharing platforms. The country's home sharing industry is worth 14.5 billion yuan or US$ 2.1 billion, according to China's State Information Center.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A door is shown being installed with a smart lock 2. 80 percent of houses being installed with smart locks3. The smart lock scanning the face of a person4. Smoke detectors, gas alarms and burglar alarmsVOICEOVER (in English): "The South China Morning Post reports Chinese home-sharing company Xiaozhu, plans to install door locks equipped with facial recognition in Chengdu, China.""The company said it will install the smart locks in 80 percent of its listings within the city.""The smart locks will scan the face of tenants to verify their identity.""According to the South China Morning Post, Xiaozhu also plans to add devices such as smoke detectors, gas alarms and burglar alarms to more apartments."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, China News, https://www.scmp.com/tech/start-ups/article/2179495/chinese-home-sharing-site-xiaozhu-roll-out-facial-recognition-enabledhttps://www.scmp.com/tech/start-ups/article/2122812/chinas-airbnb-introduce-check-ins-using-facial-recognitionhttp://www.chinanews.com/business/2018/12-25/8712134.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 06:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/27/3754894/3754894_985404DA90694194B41F36B5BD092286_181227_3754894_Home_sharing_company_to_install_facial_recogniti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, facial recognition, xiaozhu, chinese airbnb, smart locks, smart door locks, facial recognition-enabled door locks,  facial scan technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3754841</guid>
      <title>Playing video games linked to enhanced brain connectivity and increased gray matter, research shows.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the Chinese University of Electronic Science and Technology and Australia's Macquarie University have found correlations between playing action video games and increased gray matter volume and brain connectivity.According to the study published in the journal Nature, the researchers used MRI scans to study the brains of 27 regular video game players described as 'action video game experts' and 30 amateur participants.The team focused on studying the insular cortex, a brain region located within the folds of the brain's cortex.According to a paper published in the journal Cell, the insular cortex receives input from different areas of the brain, acting as a hub that links brain regions.The insular cortex also manages sensory, emotional, motivational and cognitive functions such as decision making, empathy and self-awareness.Results from the study showed that the 'action video game experts' had superior functional brain connectivity as well as increased gray matter volume in insular subregions.This could be due to the coordination between attention and sensorimotor functions used during an average action video game where players complete roughly 150 sensorimotor responses per minute using the keyboard and mouse.The expert gamers studied in the research had at least six years of professional gaming experience and were recognized champions in regional and national championships of multiplayer online battle video games.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of young man gaming with a projection of his brain.2. Representation of the young man getting an MRI scan and location of insular cortex3. Representation of brain and nervous system4. Depicition of coordination between attention and sensorimotor functionsVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the Chinese University of Electronic Science and Technology and Australia's Macquarie University have found correlations between playing action video games and increased gray matter volume and brain connectivity.""According to the study published in the journal Nature, the researchers used MRI scans to study the brains of 27 regular video game players described as 'action video game experts' and 30 amateur participants.""The team focused on studying the insular cortex, a brain region located within the folds of the brain's cortex.""According to a paper published in the journal Cell, the insular cortex receives input from different areas of the brain, acting as a hub that links brain regions.""The insular cortex also manages sensory, emotional, motivational and cognitive functions such as decision making, empathy and self-awareness." "Results from the study showed that the 'action video game experts' had superior functional brain connectivity as well as increased gray matter volume in insular subregions.""This could be due to the coordination between attention and sensorimotor functions used during an average action video game where players complete roughly 150 sensorimotor responses per minute using the keyboard and mouse."SOURCES: Nature, Cellhttps://www.nature.com/articles/srep09763#discussionhttps://www.cell.com/action/showPdf?pii=S0960-9822%2817%2930546-8***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 05:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/27/3754841/3754841_D9D547642574425992F35345C8D2E37E_181227_3754841_Playing_video_games_linked_to_enhanced_brain_con_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, video games, gaming, video games health, neuroscience, China, Australia, MRI, Cell, Nature.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3754825</guid>
      <title>Indonesia to build new tsunami warning system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIndonesia says it plans to build a new warning system that is capable of detecting tsunamis caused by undersea landslides, days after waves triggered by a volcano killed at least 429 people. According to the BBC, a government agency said a new system of buoys would be installed next year.   According to the spokesman for the Agency for the Assessment and Application of Technology, Iyan Turyana, the new system will work by detecting the size of waves.Indonesia has had no operational tsunami warning buoys since 2012, due to lack of funding, vandalism to the buoys, and mechanical failure. It is believed that activity from the Anak Krakatau volcano caused undersea landslides which triggered Saturday's tsunami. According to officials, around 150 people are still unaccounted for and 16,000 have been displaced.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Early warning system detecting tsunami caused by undersea landslides2. Tsunami detection buoys3. Tsunami buoys have been not been functioning since 20124. Volcanic eruption causing a tsunamiVOICEOVER (in English): "Indonesia says it plans to build a new warning system that is capable of detecting tsunamis caused by undersea landslides, days after waves triggered by a volcano killed at least 429 people." "According to the BBC, a government agency said a new system of buoys would be installed next year."   "According to spokesman for the Agency for the Assessment and Application of Technology Iyan Turyana, the new system will work by detecting the size of waves.""Indonesia has had no operational tsunami warning buoys since 2012, due to lack of funding, vandalism to the buoys and mechanical failure." "It is thought activity from the Anak Krakatau volcano caused undersea landslides which triggered Saturday's tsunami." SOURCES: BBChttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-46680434***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 04:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/27/3754825/3754825_0BFC0ACAC63C429297718F4A8EE22FFF_181227_3754825_Indonesia_to_build_new_tsunami_warning_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Indonesia, Indonesia tsunami, tsunami warning system, tsunami detection system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3754790</guid>
      <title>Indonesia to build new tsunami warning system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIndonesia says it plans to build a new warning system that is capable of detecting tsunamis caused by undersea landslides, days after waves triggered by a volcano killed at least 429 people. According to the BBC, a government agency said a new system of buoys would be installed next year.   According to the spokesman for the Agency for the Assessment and Application of Technology, Iyan Turyana, the new system will work by detecting the size of waves.Indonesia has had no operational tsunami warning buoys since 2012, due to lack of funding, vandalism to the buoys, and mechanical failure. It is believed that activity from the Anak Krakatau volcano caused undersea landslides which triggered Saturday's tsunami. According to officials, around 150 people are still unaccounted for and 16,000 have been displaced.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Early warning system detecting tsunami caused by undersea landslides2. Tsunami detection buoys3. Tsunami buoys have been not been functioning since 20124. Volcanic eruption causing a tsunamiVOICEOVER (in English): "Indonesia says it plans to build a new warning system that is capable of detecting tsunamis caused by undersea landslides, days after waves triggered by a volcano killed at least 429 people." "According to the BBC, a government agency said a new system of buoys would be installed next year."   "According to spokesman for the Agency for the Assessment and Application of Technology Iyan Turyana, the new system will work by detecting the size of waves.""Indonesia has had no operational tsunami warning buoys since 2012, due to lack of funding, vandalism to the buoys and mechanical failure." "It is thought activity from the Anak Krakatau volcano caused undersea landslides which triggered Saturday's tsunami." SOURCES: BBChttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-46680434***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 03:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/27/3754790/3754790_A8D1074B5D0A4459831E2477470B40C9_181227_3754790_Indonesia_to_build_new_tsunami_warning_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Indonesia, Indonesia tsunami, tsunami warning system, tsunami detection system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3755787</guid>
      <title>Super Blood Wolf Moon to occur on January 20-21</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA rare lunar phenomenon called a Super Blood Wolf Moon eclipse will occur on the night of January 20-21. According to WCPO, a super blood wolf moon eclipse is actually three separate phenomena happening at the same time: a lunar eclipse, a super moon and a wolf moon. A lunar eclipse happens when the Earth is positioned between the sun and the moon, casting the moon completely in the Earth's shadow and giving it a reddish, "bloody" glow. A supermoon occurs when the moon is within 90 percent of its closest possible distance to the Earth, which makes it look bigger in the sky.   The "wolf moon" refers to the first full moon of the year. This year's full moon will also occur at the same time as the lunar eclipse and a supermoon. According to EarthSky.org, the umbral lunar eclipse will last just over three-and-a-half hours with totality occurring for about an hour. This is when the moon sits in the shadow of our planet, causing the moon to have a reddish glow as a result of light scattering. The lunar event will be visible for all of North America, and parts of Europe and Africa. The Middle East and other parts of Africa will be able to see a partial eclipse. The eclipse will not be visible for East Asia or Australia. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Super blood wolf moon eclipse2. Lunar eclipse3. Supermoon and wolf moon4. Umbral lunar eclipseVOICEOVER (in English): "A rare lunar phenomenon called a Super Blood Wolf Moon eclipse will occur on the night of January 20-21." "According to WCPO, a super blood wolf moon eclipse is actually three separate phenomena happening at the same time: a lunar eclipse, a super moon and a wolf moon." "A lunar eclipse happens when the Earth is positioned between the sun and the moon, casting the moon completely in the Earth's shadow and giving it a reddish, "bloody" glow." "A supermoon occurs when the moon is within 90 percent of its closest possible distance to the Earth, which makes it look bigger in the sky."   "The "wolf moon" refers to the first full moon of the year. This year's full moon will also occur at the same time as the lunar eclipse and a supermoon." "According to EarthSky, the umbral lunar eclipse will last just over three-and-a-half hours with totality occurring for about an hour. This is when the moon sits in the shadow of our planet, causing the moon to have a reddish glow as a result of light scattering." SOURCES: EarthSky.org, WCPOhttps://earthsky.org/?p=295245https://www.wcpo.com/lifestyle/super-blood-wolf-moon-eclipse-will-take-place-on-jan-20***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 12:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/28/3755787/3755787_ABFB0D4A0B8B4D8393BF3A7600AA26CE_181228_3755787_Super_Blood_Wolf_Moon_to_occur_on_January_20_21_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, lunar eclipse, super blood wolf moon eclipse, supermoon, blood moon, wolf moon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3755725</guid>
      <title>Japan and South Korea in row over radar incident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan has accused South Korea of aiming a warship targeting radar at a Japanese military plane.South Korean Navy's KDX-I destroyer allegedly locked its targeting radar onto a Japanese Kawasaki P-1 patrol aircraft last week, according to Defense News.The South Korean ship was said to be near the Dokdo islets searching for North Korean fishing boats. The Japanese plane was reportedly in the airspace of the Noto Peninsula. South Korea says the destroyers used a three-dimensional radar instead of a target radar and did not "intend to trace any Japanese patrol aircraft."Japanese Defense Minister Takeshi Iwaya called it "an extremely dangerous act", according to The South China Morning Post.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Japanese flag and South Korean flag along with the Kawasaki P-1 patrol aircraft and KDX-I destroyer2. The KDX-I destroyer locking its targeting radar with a Japanese Kawasaki P-1 patrol aircraft3. Where the South Korean ship and the Japanese aircraft were at the time of the encounter 4. Flashing red on the three-dimensional radarVOICEOVER (in English): "Japan has accused South Korea of aiming a warship targeting radar at a Japanese military plane.""According to Defense News, South Korean Navy's KDX-I destroyer allegedly locked its targeting radar onto a Japanese Kawasaki P-1 patrol aircraft last week.""The South Korean ship was said to be near the Dokdo islets searching for North Korean fishing boats. The Japanese plane was reportedly in the airspace of the Noto Peninsula. ""South Korea says the destroyers used a three-dimensional radar instead of a target radar and did not 'intend to trace any Japanese patrol aircraft."SOURCES: Defense News, The Diplomat, Asian Nikkei, South China Morning Post, Korea Times,https://www.defensenews.com/global/asia-pacific/2018/12/26/is-radar-feud-sign-of-future-military-confrontation-between-south-korea-and-japan/https://thediplomat.com/2018/12/japan-south-korea-in-row-over-alleged-radar-lock-incident/https://asia.nikkei.com/Politics/International-Relations/Japan-urges-South-Korea-to-prevent-repeat-of-radar-lock-onhttps://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/2179173/japan-rebukes-south-korea-extremely-dangerous-weapons-radar-lockhttp://m.koreatimes.co.kr/pages/article.asp?newsIdx=260806***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 11:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/28/3755725/3755725_B15E1897B0214AF4AF6A5A3B8C5A91BD_181228_3755725_Japan_and_South_Korea_in_row_over_radar_incident_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, military, south korea, japan, military confrontation, radar operations, target radar, three-dimensional radar, dokdo islets, radar face-off, japan south korea relations,Kawasaki P-1 aircraft, KDX-I destroyer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3755500</guid>
      <title>New high-tech band-aids could heal wounds faster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEngineers at the University of Wisconsin-Madison have developed a high-tech band-aid that uses electrical stimulation to heal wounds.The band-aid is made using sheets of polytetrafluoroethylene, copper foil and polyethylene terephthalate, according to a study published in the journal ACS Nano.In a University of Wisconsin-Madison news release, Professor Xudong Wang explained the band-aid consists of tiny electrodes that send out electric pulses generated from the body movements of the wearer once it is applied on the wound.These band-aids were tested on rodents and results showed that the electrical band-aid reduced healing time to three days, compared to 12 days for the rodents that were given a normal band-aid.The technology could be used to heal chronic skin wounds such as diabetic foot ulcers, venous ulcers and non-healing surgical wounds, according to the study.Wang explained in the news release that the device is as convenient as "a bandage you put on your skin."Wang added that she believes the device would be just a bit more expensive than a regular band-aid.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the electric band-aid2. What the electric band-aid is made out of3. The electric bandage being put on the skin and electric pulses being sent out 4. Electric and conventional band-aids tested on rodentsVOICEOVER (in English): "Engineers at the University of Wisconsin-Madison have developed a high-tech band-aid that uses electrical stimulation to heal wounds.""According to a study published in the journal ACS Nano, the band-aid is made using sheets of polytetrafluoroethylene, copper foil and polyethylene terephthalate.""In a University of Wisconsin-Madison news release, Professor Xudong Wang explained the band-aid consists of tiny electrodes that send out electric pulses generated from the body movements of the wearer once it is applied on the wound.""These band-aids were tested on rodents and results showed that the electrical band-aid reduced healing time to three days, compared to 12 days for the rodents that were given a normal band-aid."SOURCES: Science Daily, University of Wisconsin-Madison News, ACS Nano journal, https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/12/181219115519.htmhttps://news.wisc.edu/its-not-a-shock-better-bandage-promotes-powerful-healing/https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsnano.8b07038***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 06:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/28/3755500/3755500_16604080FA5240FC83B54BD2932710EA_181228_3755500_New_high_tech_band_aids_could_heal_wounds_faster_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, smart band-aids, high-tech band-aids, bandages, electric band-aids, self-powered band-aid, e-bandages, electric bandages, wearable nanogenerator]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3755323</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk unveils Starship prototype</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe SpaceX Starship is designed for satellite delivery, space missions and interplanetary transport.According to a statement by SpaceX founder Elon Musk, the Starship is made of stainless steel that, when polished, creates a mirror-like surface that reflects thermal energy.Stainless steel performs better at higher temperatures than other lighter materials like carbon fiber. This resistance to high temperatures is especially useful during the rocket's re-entry to Earth.Elon Musk stated the new rocket would be ready for test flights by 2019. The company hopes to launch an unmanned flight to Mars in 2022, and a manned mission to the Red Planet as soon as 2024.SpaceX also plans to use the ship for other types of missions as well. According to data revealed by SpaceX, it would take the rocket under 40 minutes to travel from London to Hong Kong, a distance that takes a commercial flight almost 12 hours.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of Starship spacecraft and its uses2. Depiction of thermal energy bouncing off the spacecraft's stainless steel finish3. Depiction of stainless steel high resistance to heat4. Representation of Starship flying to MarsVOICEOVER (in English): "The SpaceX Starship is designed for satellite delivery, space missions and interplanetary transport.""According to a statement by SpaceX founder Elon Musk, the Starship is made of stainless steel that, when polished, creates a mirror-like surface that reflects thermal energy.""Stainless steel performs better at higher temperatures than other lighter materials like carbon fiber. This resistance to high temperatures is especially useful during the rocket's re-entry to Earth.""Elon Musk stated the new rocket would be ready for test flights by 2019." "The company hopes to launch an unmanned flight to Mars in 2022, and a manned mission to the Red Planet as soon as 2024."SOURCES: SpaceX, CNEThttps://www.cnet.com/news/elon-musk-shows-off-mars-starship-prototype-rocket-under-construction/https://www.spacex.com/mars***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 01:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/28/3755323/3755323_DFCBCF386CCF44178F4C4F09BC77321D_181228_3755323_Elon_Musk_unveils_Starship_prototype_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Elon Musk, SpaceX, interplanetary travel, mars, missions to mars, spacex mars, spacecraft, space race.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3756195</guid>
      <title>Seaweed eating microbes used to manufacture bioplastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from Tel Aviv University studied the potential use of Ulva lactuca algae as a sustainable alternative for large-scale production of biopolymers.According to the paper published in the journal Science Direct, the research team cultivated the Ulva lactuca algae, also known as sea lettuce, and fed it to a single-cell organism called Haloferax mediterranei.The single cell organism then discharged a bioplastic polymer called polyhydroxyalkanoate, or PHA.PHA is a completely biosynthetic and biodegradable bioplastic polymer. Products made of PHA generate zero toxic waste and are completely recyclable into organic waste.According to New Atlas, current biodegradable products aren't entirely environmentally friendly as making them requires large amounts of natural resources like fertile soil and fresh water.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of lab technicians studying Ulva Lactuca algae2. Representation of Haloferax mediterraneis consuming Ulva Lactuca algae3. Depiction of Haloferax mediterranei excreting PHA4. Representation of biodegradable plastics made of PHAVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from Tel Aviv University studied the potential use of Ulva lactuca algae as a sustainable alternative for large-scale production of biopolymers.""According to the paper published in the journal Science Direct, the research team cultivated the Ulva lactuca algae, also known as sea lettuce,  and fed it to a single-cell organism called Haloferax mediterranei.""The single cell organism then discharged a bioplastic polymer called polyhydroxyalkanoate, or PHA.""PHA is a completely biosynthetic and biodegradable bioplastic polymer. Products made of PHA generate zero toxic waste and are completely recyclable into organic waste."SOURCES: Science Direct, New Atlashttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960852418313610?via%3Dihubhttps://newatlas.com/seaweed-biodegradable-plastic/57812/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 10:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/29/3756195/3756195_914DD2CE88A94F75948CE0FF104DEB6A_181229_3756195_Seaweed_eating_microbes_used_to_manufacture_biop_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, eco friendly, eco friendly products, biodegradable plastic, biodegradable products, sustainable living, bioplastic manufacturing, bioplastic, microbes, biotechnology.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3756986</guid>
      <title>China's Type 001A aircraft carrier performs fourth sea trial</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's Type 001A aircraft carrier is all set to conduct its fourth sea trial.The aircraft carrier's latest trial involved 32 J-15 fighter jets and took place on December 27, according to the South China Morning Post.The Type 001A aircraft carrier can carry up to 40 aircrafts. The carrier is powered by a steam turbine and also has a ski-jump deck for take-offs.The Liaoning Maritime Safety Administration said the sea trial took place near the Bohai Strait in the northern Yellow Sea.The ship was expected to test its aviation system, radar, and communication systems.The carrier is expected to be delivered to the PLA Navy by April, according to the Global Times.The aircraft carrier was previously tested during sea trials in May, August and October of 2018.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Type 001A aircraft carrier and a J-15 fighter jet2. The aircraft carrier is shown carrying other aircrafts3. Features of the aircraft carrier4. Where the sea trial will take place5. What the carrier is expected to test during the trialVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the South China Morning Post, China's Type 001 aircraft carrier latest trial involving 32 J-15 fighter on December 27.""China's Type 001A aircraft carrier can carry up to 40 aircraft.""The carrier is powered by a steam turbine and has a ski-jump deck for take-offs.""The Liaoning Maritime Safety Administration said the sea trial would take place near the Bohai Strait in the northern Yellow Sea.""The ship is also expected to test its aviation system, radar, and communication systems.""According to the Global Times, the carrier is expected to be delivered to the PLA Navy by April." SOURCES: South China Morning Post, Global Times, Sputnik News, https://www.scmp.com/news/asia/article/2179704/chinas-type-001a-carrier-sets-out-fourth-sea-trial-analysts-say-callhttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1133810.shtmlhttps://sputniknews.com/military/201812271071047774-Chinas-Newest-Carrier-Begins-Flight-Tests/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/31/3756986/3756986_06645BE383C24F0E855977F59698D4E7_181231_3756986_China_s_Type_001A_aircraft_carrier_performs_four_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, aircraft carrier, chinese aircraft carrier, China navy, PLA, aircraft carrier, Type 001A aircraft carrier, Type 001A sea trial, Type 001A carrier, china Type 001A aircraft carrier]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3756867</guid>
      <title>New high-tech band-aids could heal wounds faster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEngineers at the University of Wisconsin-Madison have developed a high-tech band-aid that uses electrical stimulation to heal wounds.The band-aid is made using sheets of polytetrafluoroethylene, copper foil and polyethylene terephthalate, according to a study published in the journal ACS Nano.In a University of Wisconsin-Madison news release, Professor Xudong Wang explained the band-aid consists of tiny electrodes that send out electric pulses generated from the body movements of the wearer once it is applied on the wound.These band-aids were tested on rodents and results showed that the electrical band-aid reduced healing time to three days, compared to 12 days for the rodents that were given a normal band-aid.The technology could be used to heal chronic skin wounds such as diabetic foot ulcers, venous ulcers and non-healing surgical wounds, according to the study.Wang explained in the news release that the device is as convenient as "a bandage you put on your skin."Wang added that she believes the device would be just a bit more expensive than a regular band-aid.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the electric band-aid2. What the electric band-aid is made out of3. The electric bandage being put on the skin and electric pulses being sent out 4. Electric and conventional band-aids tested on rodentsVOICEOVER (in English): "Engineers at the University of Wisconsin-Madison have developed a high-tech band-aid that uses electrical stimulation to heal wounds.""According to a study published in the journal ACS Nano, the band-aid is made using sheets of polytetrafluoroethylene, copper foil and polyethylene terephthalate.""In a University of Wisconsin-Madison news release, Professor Xudong Wang explained the band-aid consists of tiny electrodes that send out electric pulses generated from the body movements of the wearer once it is applied on the wound.""These band-aids were tested on rodents and results showed that the electrical band-aid reduced healing time to three days, compared to 12 days for the rodents that were given a normal band-aid."SOURCES: Science Daily, University of Wisconsin-Madison News, ACS Nano journal, https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/12/181219115519.htmhttps://news.wisc.edu/its-not-a-shock-better-bandage-promotes-powerful-healing/https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsnano.8b07038***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 04:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/31/3756867/3756867_3DE3A60473B04EDABC5885B1DCDEE36B_181231_3756867_New_high_tech_band_aids_could_heal_wounds_faster_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, smart band-aids, high-tech band-aids, bandages, electric band-aids, self-powered band-aid, e-bandages, electric bandages, wearable nanogenerator]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3756826</guid>
      <title>Frenchman attempts to cross the Atlantic in a barrel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrenchman Jean-Jacques Savin, 71, is travelling across the Atlantic Ocean in a large, orange barrel.The barrel is 3 meters in length and 2.10 meters in width, according to Savin's website.The interior of the barrel consists of a six-square-meter living space, which includes a tiny kitchen and a sleeping bunk along with a pothole for Savin to enjoy the view.Savin explains on his website that he brought along satellite technology and equipment to gather data about the ocean. He also took an amphora of white wine and a block of foie gras.Savin set sail from El Hierro in the Canary Islands and is attempting to reach the Caribbean using only ocean currents and winds to propel his barrel, the New York Times reports.Savin is sharing his progress on social media by sharing pictures and tracking GPS coordinates. He plans to celebrate New Years' and his 72nd birthday at sea. Savin raised money for the journey through crowdfunding and receiving partial funding from two barrel makers.On his website, atlantique-tonneau.com, Savin states that he has already crossed the Atlantic four times using only a sailboat.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Jean-Jacques Savin, a dotted line across the Atlantic Ocean on a globe and the dimensions of the barrel are shown2. The interior of the barrel3. Items Savin brought along 4. Where Savin will set sail from along with the barrel in the oceanVOICEOVER (in English): "71-year-old Frenchman Jean-Jacques Savin is travelling across the Atlantic Ocean in a large, orange barrel. According to Savin's website, the barrel is 3 meters in length and 2.10 meters in width.""The interior of the barrel consists of a six-square-meter living space which includes a tiny kitchen and a sleeping bunk along with a pothole for Savin to enjoy the view.""Savin explained that he brought along satellite technology and equipment to gather data about the ocean. He also took an amphora of white wine and a block of foie gras.""The New York Times reports Savin set sail from El Hierro in the Canary Islands and is attempting to reach the Caribbean using only ocean currents and winds to propel his barrel."SOURCES: The New York Times, Jean-Jacques Savin's facebook, Jean-Jacques Savin's website, CNN, https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/27/world/europe/france-barrel-atlantic-jean-jacques-savin.htmlhttps://www.facebook.com/BOUTESA/http://www.atlantique-tonneau.comhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/27/europe/barrel-atlantic-crossing-scli-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/12/31/3756826/3756826_FBF39751676F4285A79AC3E5A96E1C37_181231_3756826_Frenchman_attempts_to_cross_the_Atlantic_in_a_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, frenchman, atlantic ocean, giant barrel, Jean-Jacques Savin, Jean-Jacques Savin atlantic ocean, crossing the atlantic ocean, crossing the atlantic in a barrel,atlantic ocean, frenchman barrel, frenchman barrel crossing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3757553</guid>
      <title>Japan finds huge deposit of rare-earth minerals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA deposit of rare-earth minerals has been discovered off the coast of Japan. These minerals were found 6,000 meters beneath sea level near Japan's Minamitorishima Island in April 2018, according to a study published in the journal Nature.An estimated 16 million ton of rare minerals including yttrium, dysprosium, europium and terbium have been found in the deposit.These rare earth minerals are used in smartphones and electric cars as well as rechargeable batteries.It is rare for large amounts of minerals to be found in huge deposits, according to the U.S. Geological Survey.Japan started looking for rare-earth minerals after a dispute with China, which is currently the largest exporter of rare earths minerals, according to a Reuters report.In 2014, China held back shipments of rare-earth minerals to Japan during a row over disputed islands between the two nations.At the same time, China cut back its export of rare-earth minerals and increased the price of the minerals to preserve its resources.After China, the largest amount of rare earth reserves are found in Vietnam, Brazil, Russia, South Africa and India, according to Statista 2018.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of Japan and an inset of a mix of rare-earth minerals2. Cross section of the ocean3. Rare minerals found in the deposit4. How these rare minerals are usedVOICEOVER (in English): "A deposit of rare-earth minerals has been discovered off the coast of Japan, according to a study published in the journal Nature.""These minerals were found 6,000 meters beneath sea level near Japan's Minamitorishima Island in April 2018.""An estimated 16 million ton of rare minerals including yttrium, dysprosium, europium and terbium have been found in the deposit.""These rare earth minerals are used in smartphones and electric cars as well as rechargeable batteries."SOURCES: Science Alert, Financial Post, Nature journal, CNBC, The Asahi Shimbun, USGS, Reutershttps://www.sciencealert.com/japan-discovered-a-rare-earth-mineral-deposit-that-can-supply-the-world-for-centurieshttps://interestingengineering.com/rare-earth-mineral-deposit-that-can-supply-the-world-found-in-japanhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-23948-5https://www.cnbc.com/2018/04/12/japan-rare-earths-huge-deposit-of-metals-found-in-pacific.htmlhttp://www.asahi.com/ajw/articles/AJ201804170045.htmlhttps://pubs.usgs.gov/fs/2002/fs087-02/fs087-02.pdfhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-rareearths-idUSKBN0H001T20140905***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 07:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/01/3757553/3757553_A366A81236D541B78D22C621348DFC7E_190101_3757553_Japan_finds_huge_deposit_of_rare_earth_minerals_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan, rare-earth minerals, mineral deposit, semi-finite mineral deposit, japan finds rare mineral deposit, minamitorishima island, rare minerals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
