<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 19:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3885070</guid>
      <title>Futuristic public toilets planned for San Francisco</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmerican architectural company SmithGroup has won a design competition for San Francisco's public toilets.The structure is called AmeniTREES [b]and consists of a toilet and a green roof with vegetation, According to SmithGroup's website.An irrigation system underneath the green roof will collect rainwater. The collected water will be filtered and stored in a storage tank. It can be used to wash the units or flush down the toilet.The architectural firm's website explains that by harvesting rainwater, the city will minimize its reliance on potable water.The structure will consist of a silver exterior with metal panels and a digital screen that companies can use for advertising.The AmeniTREES will have four variations: a single unit, a double unit, a double unit with a bench and a double unit with a rooftop tree.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The new high-tech public toilets2. The structure with a green roof on top3. Cross section of how the structure will collect and utilize rainwater4. The structure's exterior being used for digital advertisingVOICEOVER (in English): "American architectural company SmithGroup has won a design competition for San Francisco's public toilets.""According to SmithGroup's website, the structure is called AmeniTREES [c]and consists of a toilet and a green roof with vegetation.""An irrigation system underneath the green roof will collect rainwater.""The collected water will be filtered and stored in a storage tank. It can be used to wash the units or flush down the toilet.""The structure will consist of a silver exterior with metal panels and a digital screen that companies can use for advertising."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Smith Group, https://inhabitat.com/high-tech-public-toilets-proposed-for-san-francisco-can-recycle-rainwater-for-reuse/https://www.smithgroup.com/https://www.smithgroup.com/projects/san-francisco-amenitrees***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 12:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/02/3885070/3885070_6685CEB1E1B244AF99945A5713873F5D_190902_3885070_Futuristic_public_toilets_planned_for_San_Franci_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, toilets, high-tech toilets, san franciso high-tech toilets, SmithGroup, SmithGroup high-tech toilets, amenitrees, amenitrees high-tech toilets, eco-friendly public toilets, sustainable public toilets, sustainable public toilet design]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3884799</guid>
      <title>China rotates troops into Hong Kong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has sent a fresh batch of troops into Hong Kong in what Beijing is calling a "routine rotation."The People's Liberation Army's Hong Kong Garrison conducted a rotation of its soldiers in the semi-autonomous city of Hong Kong on Thursday morning at 4:00 a.m.This is the 22nd rotation since the Chinese army began garrisoning the city after the handover in 1997, according to Chinese state news agency Xinhua.Military vehicles of the People's Liberation Army were seen passing Huanggang Port, a port of entry between mainland China and Hong Kong. The Chinese military is prepared to "maintain stability and prosperity" in the city amid ongoing protests, reports Xinhua.Images shared by Xinhua show the Hong Kong Garrison had changed its armored vehicles from a Type 092 military version to the WJ-03B. According to the South China Morning Post, this model is typically used by armed police officers for the purpose of controlling riots.The Chinese air force also sent in armed helicopters later on Thursday morning.As Hong Kong has been rocked by months of anti-government and pro-democracy protests, many are wary of China's next step. Beijing is keen on putting an end to the protests before October 1, which marks the 70th anniversary of the founding of the People's Republic of China, Reuters reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese military vehicles entering Hong Kong2. Map of China and Hong Kong border3. The armored vehicle the Chinese army had previously used and the one they deployed this time4. Chinese helicopters entering Hong KongVOICEOVER (in English): "The People's Liberation Army's Hong Kong Garrison conducted a rotation of its soldiers in the semi-autonomous city of Hong Kong on Thursday morning at 4:00 a.m.""According to Chinese state news agency Xinhua, this is the 22nd rotation since the Chinese army began garrisoning the city after the handover in 1997.""Military vehicles of the People's Liberation Army were seen passing Huanggang Port, a port of entry between mainland China and Hong Kong.""Xinhua reports the Chinese military is prepared to 'maintain stability and prosperity' in the city amid ongoing protests.""Images shared by Xinhua show the Hong Kong Garrison had changed its armored vehicles from a Type 092 military version to the WJ-03B.""According to the South China Morning Post, this model is typically used by armed police officers for the purpose of controlling riots.""The Chinese air force also sent in armed helicopters later on Thursday morning."SOURCES: The Guardian, CNN, Reuters, Hong Kong Free Press, Xinhua, South China Morning Post https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/29/chinese-troop-movement-into-hong-kong-prompts-uneasehttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/29/asia/hong-kong-pla-china-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests/china-says-troops-will-defend-hong-kongs-prosperity-ahead-of-planned-pro-democracy-march-idUSKCN1VJ06Bhttps://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/08/30/china-conducts-routine-hong-kong-troop-rotation-ahead-banned-rally/http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-08/29/c_138346117.htmhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-08/29/c_138346677_3.htmhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/gangao/2019-08/30/c_1124939087.htmhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3024820/chinese-militarys-move-hong-kong-sunrise-was-routine-annual***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 02:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/02/3884799/3884799_CBE04F3119114E63BD4DD10F4D58B084_190902_3884799_China_rotates_troops_into_Hong_Kong_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china troops hong kong, china troops hong kong border, china troops enter hong kong, people's liberation army, people's liberation army hong kong, people's liberation army hong kong garrison, hong kong garrison]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3885708</guid>
      <title>At least eight dead, 26 missing in California boat fire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least eight people are dead and dozens more missing after a boat caught fire off the California coast.According to CBS LA, the 75-foot long charter dive boat 'Conception' was anchored near California's Santa Cruz Island on Monday, carrying 6 crew members and 33 passengers.At around 3:15 a.m., a mayday call went out alerting authorities to a fire onboard.The LA Times reports that many of the passengers were sleeping below deck when the blaze broke out. Five crew members who were awake and on the deck escaped by jumping into the water, and were later rescued by a good Samaritan vessel.The Ventura County Fire Department tried to extinguish the flames that had completely engulfed the Conception. The boat eventually sank in 64 feet of water, some 20 yards offshore.CNN reports that according to U.S. Coast Guard officials, the Conception is currently inverted on the ocean floor.So far, four bodies have been recovered and four more seen on the ocean floor near the sunken vessel. 26 people are still unaccounted for.The cause of the blaze is also as yet unknown. Authorities are still mounting search and rescue operations, and will do so until dawn tomorrow.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Conception dive boat anchored near Santa Cruz Island catches fire2. Passengers sleeping below deck; crew members on deck escape3. Boat sinks as firefighters extinguish blaze4. Number of dead and missingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CBS LA, the 75-foot long charter dive boat 'Conception' was anchored near California's Santa Cruz Island on Monday, carrying 6 crew members and 33 passengers.""At around 3:15 a.m., a mayday call went out alerting authorities to a fire onboard.""The LA Times reports that many of the passengers were sleeping below deck when the blaze broke out. Five crew members who were awake and on the deck escaped by jumping into the water, and were later rescued by a good Samaritan vessel.""The Ventura County Fire Department tried to extinguish the flames that had completely engulfed the Conception. The boat eventually sank in 64 feet of water, some 20 yards offshore.""CNN reports that according to U.S. Coast Guard officials, the Conception is currently inverted on the ocean floor.""So far, four bodies have been recovered and four more seen on the ocean floor near the sunken vessel. 26 people are still unaccounted for."SOURCES: CNN, Los Angeles Times, CBS LA, BBChttps://edition.cnn.com/us/live-news/california-boat-fire/index.htmlhttps://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-09-02/california-boat-fire-family-friends-await-answers-on-loved-oneshttps://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/09/02/dozens-missing-charter-boat-fire-off-ventura-county-coastline-santa-cruz-island/https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-49556638***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 15:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/03/3885708/3885708_8B4650FD1A7845A59D9FF1C52C73E936_190903_3885708_At_least_eight_dead__26_missing_in_California_bo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, california boat fire, dive boat fire, conception fire, boat fire, santa cruz island, conception dive boat, charter dive boat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3885431</guid>
      <title>iPhones are being hacked by malicious websites: Google</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoogle's Project Zero has uncovered a hacking operation in which websites carry malware that steal sensitive data from iPhones if users simply visit the site.The research, which was made public in a Project Zero blog post, had uncovered a total of 14 different vulnerabilities across different iPhone operating systems from iOS10 to iOS12. The malicious websites would exploit the server and attack the users' device to install a monitoring implant, according to a blogpost by Project Zero. Once the implant was successfully installed, users had their passwords exposed as well as their chat histories on apps such as WhatsApp, Telegram and iMessage.Hackers were also able to access a person's contacts, Gmail database and their location.Google had informed Apple about security issues on its phones, reports the Guardian.  Apple then released a new operating system update in which once users updated their iPhones, the malware was removed.Project Zero did not name the infected websites or the number of victims of the attack.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Iphone, website and a malware icon2. A monitoring implant is installed in the phone3. What the hackers were able to access4. Apple's new system update that removed the malwareVOICEOVER (in English): "Google's Project Zero has uncovered a hacking operation in which websites carry malware that steal sensitive data from iPhones if users simply visit the site.""According to a blogpost by Project Zero, the malicious websites would exploit the server and attack the users' device to install a monitoring implant.""Once the implant was successfully installed, users had their passwords exposed as well as their chat histories on apps such as WhatsApp, Telegram and iMessage.""Hackers were also able to access a person's contacts, Gmail database and their location.""The Guardian reports that Google had informed Apple about security issues on its phones." "Apple then released a new operating system update in which once users updated their iPhones, the malware was removed."SOURCES: Technology Review, The Guardian, Google Project Zero, CNN https://www.technologyreview.com/s/614243/websites-have-been-quietly-hacking-iphones-for-years-says-google/https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/aug/30/hackers-monitoring-implants-iphones-google-sayshttps://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2019/08/a-very-deep-dive-into-ios-exploit.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/30/tech/google-iphone-hack-vulnerability/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 07:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/03/3885431/3885431_063F267EF2DB4EA3A03273C0BBCF2FB6_190903_3885431_iPhones_are_being_hacked_by_malicious_websites___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, google, iphone, iphone hack, iphone hack 2019, project zero, project zero google, project zero iphone, website hack iphones, websites hack your iphone, iOS malware, iphone malware, apple's operating system hacked, iphone hacking operation, iphone hacked websites]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3885348</guid>
      <title>U.S. could soon open Alaska's Tongass National Forest for business</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. President Donald Trump's administration is pushing for the commercialization of America's largest national forest for potential mining and logging opportunities.President Trump is looking to exempt the Tongass National Forest from logging restrictions that were put into place by the Clinton administration, the Washington Post reports, citing three unnamed people that were briefed on the issue.According to the U.S. Department of Agriculture, under the policy, road construction and timber harvesting is not allowed on roadless areas in designated national forests. Congress had designated more than 5.7 million acres of the Alaskan forest land as wilderness that cannot be developed any circumstances, reports the Washington Post. If President Trump's administration succeeds, around 9.5 millions acres of Alaskan forest land could be affected.According to the Washington Post, the move would open up the Alaskan rainforest to potential logging, mining and energy projects.Ecologists pointed out that the forest is home to animals such as the brown bears, Sitka black-tailed deer and the Northern Goshawk, among other species. Chris Wood, president of Trout Unlimited, an environmental group, said that the region's salmon fishing industry could also be impacted as many wild salmon are spawn in Tongass National park.Previously, only specific projects approved by the U.S. Forest Service were allowed to take place in the Alaskan forest.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. President Trump on a podium, the Tongass National Forest, mining inset and inset of logs2. What previously wasn't allowed in the forest, and how much of the forest could be developed3. The forest being opened up for logging, mining and energy projects4. Wildlife that could be threatened if the rainforest is opened up for businessVOICEOVER (in English): "President Trump is looking to exempt the Tongass National Forest from logging restrictions that were put into place by the Clinton administration, the Washington Post reports, citing three unnamed people that were briefed on the issue.""According to the U.S. Department of Agriculture, under the policy, road construction and timber harvesting is not allowed on roadless areas in designated national forests.""The Washington Post reports that Congress had designated more than 5.7 million acres of the Alaskan forest land as wilderness that cannot be developed any circumstances." "If President Trump's administration succeeds, around 9.5 millions acres of Alaskan forest land could be affected.""According to the Washington Post, the move would open up the Alaskan rainforest to potential logging, mining and energy projects.""Ecologists pointed out that the forest is home to animals such as the brown bears, Sitka black-tailed deer and the Northern Goshawk, among other species.""Chris Wood, president of Trout Unlimited, an environmental group, said that the region's salmon fishing industry could also be impacted as many wild salmon are spawn in Tongass National park."SOURCES: The Washington Post, Inhabitat, EcoWatch, CNN, U.S. Department of Agriculture Forest Service,  https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/trump-pushes-to-allow-new-logging-in-alaskas-tongass-national-forest/2019/08/27/b4ca78d6-c832-11e9-be05-f76ac4ec618c_story.htmlhttps://inhabitat.com/millions-of-acres-of-alaskan-rainforest-may-be-opened-for-business/https://www.ecowatch.com/amazon-wildfires-trump-alaska-exploitation-2640082295.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/28/politics/tongass-national-forest-donald-trump-alaska/index.htmlhttps://www.fs.usda.gov/roadmain/roadless/2001roadlessrulehttps://www.fs.usda.gov/detail/tongass/specialplaces/?cid=stelprdb5393510***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 05:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/03/3885348/3885348_2802592CDC2D49B1BF36C431DB0A9849_190903_3885348_U_S__could_soon_open_Alaska_s_Tongass_National_F_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, alaskan rainforest, opening up alaska's rainforest, tongass national forest, tongass national forest alaska, tongass national forest logging, trump alaska, trump alaskan rainforest, trump tongass national forest, trump tongass national forest logging, trump alaska mining, trump alaska logging]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3885276</guid>
      <title>China's lunar rover discovers gel-like substance on far side of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's Chang'e 4 mission has found an unusually colored gel-like substance on the far side of the moon.Space.com reports that on July 28, the Yutu-2 lunar rover had been exploring the far side of the moon. While reviewing the rover's images, a Chang'e 4 team member noticed that one crater seemed to contain a material distinct from the rest of the lunar surface.The Yutu-2 was directed to approach the crater and examine its inside with its Visible and Near-Infrared Spectrometer.Mission scientists have not revealed what the substance is, describing it only as gel-like and with an unusual color.Outside researchers have suggested that one possible explanation is that the substance is melted glass created from meteorites striking the surface of the moon.China's Chang'e 4 spacecraft successfully made the first-ever soft landing on the far side of the moon on January 3. The Yutu-2 rover is now on its ninth lunar day, with each day equivalent to two Earth weeks.In May, Chinese scientists also announced that they'd found evidence of material from the lunar mantle in the regolith of the moon's Von Karman crater.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Crater filled with substance spotted in photos taken by Yutu 2 lunar rover2. Yutu 2 finds gel-like material inside crater3. Gel-like material possibly melt glass from meteorite strike4. Material from lunar mantle found in Von Karman craterVOICEOVER (in English): "Space.com reports that on July 28, the Yutu-2 lunar rover had been exploring the far side of the moon. While reviewing the rover's images, a Chang'e 4 team member noticed that one crater seemed to contain a material distinct from the rest of the lunar surface.""The Yutu-2 was directed to approach the crater and examine its inside with its Visible and Near-Infrared Spectrometer.""Mission scientists have not revealed what the substance is, describing it only as gel-like and with an unusual color.""Outside researchers have suggested that one possible explanation is that the substance is melted glass created from meteorites striking the surface of the moon.""In May, Chinese scientists also announced that they'd found evidence of material from the lunar mantle in the regolith of the moon's Von Karman crater."SOURCES: Space.com, Cnethttps://www.space.com/china-far-side-moon-rover-strange-substance.htmlhttps://www.cnet.com/news/chinas-lunar-rover-discovers-strange-substance-on-far-side-of-the-moon/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 02:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/03/3885276/3885276_610B84177A6745EF92702EC995B71DBE_190903_3885276_China_s_lunar_rover_discovers_gel_like_substance_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, moon gel, lunar gel, gel like substance, moon finds, moon discovery, China lunar rover, Yutu 2, Chang'e 4, lunar rover, strange substance, weird substance, far side of the moon, dark side of the moon, meteorite strike, meteorite melt glass]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3886156</guid>
      <title>Microplastic particles found in Lake Tahoe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has uncovered microplastic particles from the depths of Lake Tahoe.Scientists from the Desert Research Institute collected water samples from Lake Tahoe and found microplastic particles in them for the first time. Synthetic fiber and bits of red and blue plastic were found in the lake's waters, according to the Los Angeles Times.Researchers used pumps, funnels, tubing and filters to collect water samples from six different locations across Lake Tahoe.Once the plastic particles were gathered in the water filters, the scientists oxidized organic matters such as insects, twigs and algae. They then used a high-density liquid separation method to separate the sediments from the microplastics.According to the Reno Gazette Journal, the team is now in the process of examining the microplastics and identifying the different types of plastics and where they came from.The research team will present its findings to the American Geophysical Union in December.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Water sample from Lake Tahoe containing microplastics2. How the researchers collected the water samples3. Microplastics being separated from the sediments4. Microplastics being examinedVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists from the Desert Research Institute collected water samples from Lake Tahoe and found microplastic particles in them for the first time.""According to the Los Angeles Times, synthetic fiber and bits of red and blue plastic were found in the lake's waters.""Researchers used pumps, funnels, tubing and filters to collect water samples from six different locations across Lake Tahoe.""Once the plastic particles were gathered in the water filters, the scientists oxidized organic matters such as insects, twigs and algae.""They then used a high-density liquid separation method to separate the sediments from the microplastics.""According to the Reno Gazette Journal, the team is now in the process of examining the microplastics and identifying the different types of plastics and where they came from."SOURCES: LA Times, Reno Gazette Journal, https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2019-08-26/lake-tahoe-microplastic-pollution-detectedhttps://www.rgj.com/story/news/2019/08/22/microplastics-found-scientists-desert-research-institute-nevada/2080122001/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/04/3886156/3886156_C01CEE80208048F9B1BBE8EAB8B450CB_190904_3886156_Microplastic_particles_found_in_Lake_Tahoe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, plastic pollution, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, plastic litter, Lake tahoe, microplastics Lake tahoe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3886096</guid>
      <title>Why Hurricane Dorian's path is so hard to predict</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Tampa Bay Times reports that Hurricane Dorian had initially been forecast to directly hit Florida's east coast. But the next day, forecasts showed the storm's center drifting east of the state, and then later edging a bit back to the west.Experts have said Dorian's path has been especially unpredictable, and here's why.National Weather Service meteorologist Lance Wood told Live Science that the Atlantic high pressure system steering Hurricane Dorian started to weaken on the west side.Weakened winds have led to the storm moving very slowly at just 7 miles per hour. This puts its approach further into the future and makes forecasting its track more difficult.According to the Weather Channel, Dorian is expected to turn north as a gap opens up between the high-pressure Bermuda High system in the Atlantic and a low pressure system from the Great Lakes region.The timing and angle of the turn will depend on its interactions with the Bermuda High system, which forecasters have limited knowledge of and thus cannot accurately project.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Changing forecasts for Hurricane Dorian's track2. Atlantic high pressure system steering Dorian weakens, storm slows3. Timing and angle of Dorian's turn north unpredictable 4. Where Hurricane Dorian could make landfallVOICEOVER (in English): "The Tampa Bay Times reports that Hurricane Dorian had initially been forecast to directly hit Florida's east coast. But the next day, forecasts showed the storm's center drifting east of the state, and then later edging a bit back to the west.""Experts have said Dorian's path has been especially unpredictable, and here's why.""National Weather Service meteorologist Lance Wood told Live Science that the Atlantic high pressure system steering Hurricane Dorian started to weaken on the west side.""Weakened winds have led to the storm moving very slowly at just 7 miles per hour. This puts its approach further into the future and makes forecasting its track more difficult.""According to the Weather Channel, Dorian is expected to turn north as a gap opens up between the high-pressure Bermuda High system in the Atlantic and a low pressure system from the Great Lakes region.""The timing and angle of the turn will depend on its interactions with the Bermuda High system, which forecasters have limited knowledge of and thus cannot accurately project.""According to NWS meteorologist Joel Cline, the most likely scenario is that Dorian will miss Florida's east coast and move northward toward Georgia. It is then expected to either pass close to or make landfall in South Carolina or North Carolina.""The Los Angeles Times reports that if the storm does push toward the U.S. East coast, there is a potential for heavy rain and with it, damage from storm surges and flooding."SOURCES: Tampa Bay Times, Live Science, Weather Channel, National Geographic, LA Timeshttps://www.tampabay.com/hurricane/2019/09/01/3-reasons-hurricane-dorian-has-been-so-hard-to-forecast/https://www.livescience.com/hurricane-dorian-path-tricky.htmlhttps://www.livescience.com/where-will-hurricane-dorian-make-landfall.htmlhttps://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2019-09-02-hurricane-dorian-labor-day-bahamas-florida-georgia-carolinashttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2019/08/hurricane-dorian-science-behind-the-storm/https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-08-31/what-forces-are-pulling-hurricane-dorian-to-the-north***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 10:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/09/04/3886096/3886096_552519E09E8049B1B29B0CAC2E6D08BB_190904_3886096_Why_Hurricane_Dorian_s_path_is_so_hard_to_predic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hurricane dorian, hurricane dorian path, hurricane dorian unpredictable, storm path, hurricane path, hurricane dorian track, hurricane track]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3885923</guid>
      <title>Microplastics found in human stool samples: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found small pieces of plastic, ranging from 50 to 500 micrometers in size, present in human stool samples.Researchers from the Medical University of Vienna tested fecal samples from eight different participants aged 33 to 65. The participants came from Japan, Russia, the Netherlands, the United Kingdom, Italy, Poland, Finland and Austria. The scientists found that all eight stool samples tested positive for microplastics.They identified nine different plastic types in the samples, with polypropylene and polyethylene terephthalate being the most common type of plastic. On average, the