<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3623030</guid>
      <title>Researchers discover 300-year-old shipwreck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe shipwreck of a 300-year-old Spanish ship discovered off the coast of Colombia was found to have treasures that may be worth up to $17 billion.The ship was found with the help of an underwater robot submarine. The Remus 6000 went 2,000 feet below the surface and was equipped with a long-range sonar that scanned the sea floor. The drone also took pictures of anything that seemed unusual, CBS reports.When researchers revisited the site recently, they found cannons engraved with dolphins. The researchers claim that this is a sign the ship was the San Jose, without a doubt.The exact location the shipwreck is still kept a secret, but it was found off the coast of Cartagena, Colombia in 2015. It supposedly has a cargo full of gold, silver and emeralds that could be worth nearly $17 billion, CBS reports.Since the treasure has been discovered, both Spain and Colombia are claiming that they are the rightful owner of the ship.The researchers have mentioned that since they "are explorers, not treasure hunters," they would not be involved in the dispute between Spain and Colombia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show the submarine drone locating the shipwreck and its process of doing so.2. Scientists discovered cannons engraved with dolphins and other artifacts at the shipwreck.3. Show the approximate location of the shipwreck where there might be treasures worth up to $17 billion.4. Show the treasure scattered on the seafloor as two nations claim the shipwreck as their own.VOICEOVER (in English): "CBS reports that the Remus 6000, a robot submarine, went 2000 feet below the surface to find the 300-year-old ship and was equipped with a long-range sonar which scanned the sea floor. The drone also took pictures of anything that seemed unusual.""When researchers revisited the site recently, they found cannons engraved with dolphins. The researchers pointed out that this is a sign that the ship was the San Jose, without a doubt. ""CBS reports that the exact location the shipwreck is still kept a secret, but it was found off the coast of Cartagena, Colombia in 2015. It supposedly has a cargo full of gold, silver and emeralds that could be worth nearly $17 billion.""Since the treasure has been discovered, both Spain and Colombia are claiming that they are the rightful owner of the ship."SOURCES: Business Insider, CBS Newshttp://www.businessinsider.com/shipwreck-may-have-up-to-17-billion-in-treasure-2018-5?utm_content=buffer0ea57&utm_medium=social&utm_source=facebook.com&utm_campaign=buffer-tihttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/robot-submarine-finds-shipwreck-san-jose-carrying-17-billion-treasure/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 06:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/01/3623030/3623030_1466EEF97B064751AC822576B7A2177E_180601_3623030_Researchers_discover_300_year_old_shipwreck_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2B3/D22/2B3D22F4E75B48CBACEDF928666618BC_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Colombia, Spain, Shipwreck, treasure, Caribbean Sea, Remus 6000, Spanish galleon San Jose]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624980</guid>
      <title>Beijing developing 'China Space Station'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina Is working on a newly planned station dated for a 2019 launch.Beijing expects the "China Space Station" to be operational by 2022. The space station will be able to host up to six astronauts over 180-day periods.This is around the same time span that astronauts will spend on the International Space Station.China says their planned space station will orbit Earth at altitudes of between 340 kilometers and 450 kilometers. The ISS orbits at around 400 kilometers.China's space station may outlast the ISS, as that craft's future is unclear after 2025. Reportedly, the U.S. government is considering pulling its funding or privatizing it. According to Yahoo News, the U.S. has banned China from using the ISS since 2011.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China Space Station over Earth2. Astronaut outside China Space Station3. China Space Station orbiting Earth4. China  Space Station and International Space Station over EarthVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: United Nations Office for Outer Space Affairs, Yahoo newshttp://www.unoosa.org/documents/doc/psa/hsti/CSS_1stAO/CSS_1stAO_Handbook_2018.pdfhttps://www.yahoo.com/news/space-race-china-releases-plans-135409411.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 11:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/04/3624980/3624980_EC90063AB5E44D25A7708C73193B77E9_180604_3624980_Beijing_developing__China_Space_Station__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A75/AF4/A75AF449C00E4D97B048FDDA7F9408A9_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  china space station, css space station, iss, iss css, nasa, china space, china in space, astronauts, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624756</guid>
      <title>The Fujiwhara effect and typhoons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA European weather forecast model predicts Taiwan may get hit by two typhoons at the same time this month.According to Taiwan News, a model from European Centre for Medium-Range Weather Forecasts predicts twin cyclones could interact with each other and bring storms to the island-nation. This kind of weather event is rare. Though the European model predicts this will occur, others do not.Taiwanese meteorologist Wu Der-rong[a] told Taiwan News that weather simulations from Taiwan, Europe and the U.S. differ. He also said it in it's too early to draw conclusions on whether it will happen.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 2. 3. 4. VOICEOVER (in English): "As two cyclones move near each other, they begin to orbit one another." "This is known as the Fujiwhara effect.""They move either in a clockwise movement, if the storm in the southern hemisphere, and counterclockwise if it is in the northern hemisphere.""The effect is said to begin when they are around 900 miles apart.""How this happens depends on the size of both cyclones."If one is large and the other smaller, the bigger one will hold more power in the interaction.""Eventually both cyclones will merge, with one typically absorbing the other."SOURCES: Taiwan News, Central Weather Bureau (Taiwan), USA Todayhttps://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3444683https://www.cwb.gov.tw/V7e/knowledge/encyclopedia/ty013.htmhttps://usatoday30.usatoday.com/weather/wfujiwha.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 06:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/04/3624756/3624756_6257BFF206124953BE1397110C97E1F8_180604_3624756_The_Fujiwhara_effect_and_typhoons_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/541/4A3/5414A3FFE2C34BDCB0D5E3F5A96C5C87_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, fujiwhara, fujiwhara effect explained, taipei, weather, storms, cyclones, typhoons, hurricanes, tropical storms, fujiwhara explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3625559</guid>
      <title>Dozens killed as Guatemala's Mount Fuego erupts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least 62 people have been killed with dozens more missing after Mount Fuego erupted on Sunday in Guatemala, according to officials.Villages located along the mountainside were buried in volcanic ash, mud and rocks during the 16-hour eruption, the BBC reported.Mt. Fuego is a stratovolcano, which are classic-cone shaped peaks built up from layers of ash and lava rocks, according to Smithsonian Magazine. Stratovolcanoes have violent eruptions that launch columns of ash and scorching rock miles into the air. When these clouds collapse, they form deadly pyroclastic flows  avalanches of hot rocks, gas and volcanic ash.    According to the BBC, around 1.7 million people have been affected by the eruption in four regions. According to the head of the National Disaster Management Agency Sergio Cabañas, the town of El Rodeo was completely "buried."The towns of Alotenango and San Miguel Los Lotes were also affected. Temporary shelters have been set up for around 3,000 evacuated residents. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of Mt. Fuego 2. Stratovolcano cross section3. Depiction of pyroclastic flowsVOICEOVER (in English): "At least 62 people have been killed with dozens more missing after Mount Fuego erupted on Sunday in Guatemala. According to the BBC, villages located along the mountainside were buried in volcanic ash, mud and rocks during the 16-hour eruption.""According to Smithsonian Magazine, Mt. Fuego is a stratovolcano, which are classic-cone shaped peaks built up from layers of ash and lava rocks." "Stratovolcanoes have violent eruptions that launch columns of ash and scorching rock miles into the air. When these clouds collapse, they form deadly pyroclastic flows  avalanches of hot rocks, gas and volcanic ash."SOURCES: BBC, Smithsonian Magazine, UPIhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-44350974https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/five-things-know-about-eruption-guatemala-180969233/https://www.upi.com/At-least-25-dead-17-million-affected-by-Guatemala-volcano-eruption/6591528113470/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 08:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/05/3625559/3625559_FBECBBEA474C43D4B5F3CAAC4F0B0114_180605_3625559_Dozens_killed_as_Guatemala_s_Mount_Fuego_erupts_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E7F/035/E7F0357394B8449A950EC5F04916185E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, volcano, volcanic eruptions, Guatemala Mt Fuego eruption, Mt Fuego eruption, Guatemala volcano, Mt Fuego volcano]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3625512</guid>
      <title>LINE partnering with ICON to create blockchain ecosystem</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan's largest messaging app LINE announced around mid-May a partnership with the South Korean blockchain project ICON.According to Bitcoinist, the joint venture is called "UNCHAIN" and will see the LINE development team create a wide range of decentralized applications, dApps, and deploy its blockchain central net on the ICON blockchain protocol. As of May 31st, the ICON blockchain network had a market cap of around $1.4 billion. According to an ICON blogpost, "Unchain will create a blockchain ecosystem fueled by a token economy, where the users are rewarded for their contributions to the network."LINE is a popular messaging app in many countries throughout Asia, with over 200 million active monthly users. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of people using LINE and ICON2. LINE will be developing decentralized apps with ICON3. Depiction of ICON blockchain system4. ICON market cap and LINE monthly usageVOICEOVER (in English): "Japan's largest messaging app LINE announced around mid-May a partnership with the South Korean blockchain project ICON.""According to Bitcoinist, the joint venture is called "UNCHAIN" and will see the LINE development team create a wide range of decentralized applications, dApps, and deploy its blockchain central net on the ICON blockchain protocol." "According to an ICON blogpost, "Unchain will create a blockchain ecosystem fueled by a token economy, where the users are rewarded for their contributions to the network.""As of May 31st, the ICON blockchain network had a market cap of around $1.4 billion. LINE is a popular messaging app in many countries throughout Asia, with over 200 million active monthly users." SOURCES: Bitcoinist, CCN, Medium, Coin Market Caphttp://bitcoinist.com/blockchain-apps-take-over-south-korea/http://bitcoinist.com/icon-icx-announces-massive-partnership-with-line-to-create-unchain/https://www.ccn.com/messaging-giant-line-partnership-icon/https://medium.com/helloiconworld/joint-venture-between-icon-and-line-unchain-b802fa0fa071https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/icon/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 07:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/05/3625512/3625512_330DE67DBA044B598BEC359860493264_180605_3625512_LINE_partnering_with_ICON_to_create_blockchain_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1DB/A4E/1DBA4E3D98C345779263E92D30B11D42_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, LINE, ICON ICX, LINE ICON partnership, LINE blockchain, Unchain, blockchain technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626377</guid>
      <title>Patient remains awake during 90 minutes of CPR</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new Danish study is raising awareness of the rare but disturbing phenomenon of patients being awake during CPR.At the Euroanaesthesia congress in Copenhagen, anaesthesiologist Dr. Rune Sarauw Lundsgaard presented the case of a 69-year-old man who went to the hospital after three days of indigestion symptoms, but suffered cardiac arrest while being admitted, CNN reports.A medical team immediately began chest compressions. CPR was administered over the next 90 minutes, with the patient reportedly showing signs of conscious awareness.A high level of awareness during CPR is extremely rare, according to experts, since blood flow to the brain is often insufficient.Strangely, the man's heart remained non functioning and without electrical activity, which caused him to lose consciousness each time doctors held off on CPR.Despite being given several shots of epinephrine, his heart failed to restart on its own. The man eventually died after compressions were stopped for good.An autopsy later revealed that the patient had suffered a complete aortic dissection, a lethal condition in which blood is forced between the inner and outer aorta layers.Since the decision to terminate CPR happened while the man was still conscious, it raised serious ethical questions, including the use of sedation when resuscitating patients.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of man going into cardiac arrest2. Patient shows signs of conscious awareness during 90-minute CPR3. Patient becoming unconscious every time CPR is stopped4. Heart fails to restart on its own; patient dies after paramedics stop compressionsVOICEOVER (in English): "A doctor at the Euroanaesthesia congress in Copenhagen presented the case of a 69-year-old man, who went to the hospital after three days of indigestion, but suffered cardiac arrest while being admitted.""A medical team immediately began chest compressions. CPR was administered over the next 90 minutes, with the patient reportedly showing signs of conscious awareness.""Strangely, the man's heart remained non functioning and without electrical activity, which caused him to lose consciousness each time doctors held off on CPR.""Despite being given several shots of epinephrine, his heart failed to restart on its own. The man eventually died after compressions were stopped for good."SOURCES: CNN, CTV Newshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/06/04/health/cpr-awareness-resuscitation-study/index.htmlhttps://www.ctvnews.ca/health/doctors-report-strange-case-of-man-who-stayed-awake-during-cardiac-arrest-1.3959006***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 11:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/06/3626377/3626377_EF7D0C29D20A499F83D986A38336D775_180606_3626377_Patient_remains_awake_during_90_minutes_of_CPR_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/24A/96D/24A96D02D2254EF681750847FE961113_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, CPR, cardiac arrest, CPR awareness, emergency response, rare medical case, strange medical case, heart problems, indigestion, nausea, aortic dissection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626178</guid>
      <title>Samsung Pass to incorporate CHAIN ID blockchain identification</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSamsung is partnering up with theloop to develop CHAIN ID in order to incorporate the blockchain identification technology into its Samsung Pass service.Samsung Pass is an identity management service that utilizes biometric authentication, similar to Apple's Touch ID and Face ID. CHAIN ID is a blockchain identification system that lets people use the same certificate at any bank or securities company that belongs to the Korea Financial Investment Blockchain Consortium, according to Medium. According to Medium, CHAIN ID is the first blockchain based joint authentication system designed from theloop's 'loopchain' blockchain engine. The system is currently being used by 11 securities companies in South Korea. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Samsung Pass integrating CHAIN ID2. Iris scan and facial recognition depictions3. CHAIN ID system being used at banks and securities companies4. CHAIN ID designed with loopchain blockchain engineVOICEOVER (in English): "Samsung is partnering up with theLOOP to develop CHAIN ID in order to incorporate the blockchain identification technology into its Samsung Pass service.""Samsung Pass is an identity management service that utilizes biometric authentication, similar to Apple's Touch ID and Face ID." "CHAIN ID is a blockchain identification system that lets people use the same certificate at any bank or securities company that belongs to the Korea Financial Investment Blockchain Consortium.""According to Medium, CHAIN ID is the first blockchain based joint authentication system designed from theloop's 'loopchain' blockchain engine." SOURCES: Medium, Decyrpto.nethttps://medium.com/helloiconworld/chan-id-developed-using-loopchain-to-be-used-in-samsung-pass-service-69669928369dhttps://medium.com/helloiconworld/icon-koreas-online-banking-security-gets-first-upgrade-in-almost-20-years-4d36f5ac31f1https://decrypto.net/2018/05/samsung-pass-to-use-theloops-chain-id/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 06:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/06/3626178/3626178_FCB89ABD34CF4FF0BF60FAD105AFBDBB_180606_3626178_Samsung_Pass_to_incorporate_CHAIN_ID_blockchain__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DA4/DC9/DA4DC97D7F7746D58F49BA87D9D68DA7_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, blockchain, blockchain technology, Samsung, Samsung Pass, loopchain, Samsung CHAIN ID, CHAIN ID]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627344</guid>
      <title>Guatemala volcano search and rescue resumes with at least 99 dead and almost 200 missing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEmergency crews have resumed search and rescue operations in the surrounding areas affected by Sunday's Mt. Fuego eruption, which has killed at least 99 people, with around 200 people still missing.  Rescue work was stopped temporarily on Tuesday when a second eruption sent plumes of gas and molten rock down Fuego's south side, reported the BBC. Some places are still so hot that when rescuers poked metal rods into the ground, clouds of smoke came pouring out, reported The Guardian.Firefighters said the temperatures reached between 750 to 1,300 Fahrenheit under the surface at some locations.   Reuters reports the volcano had its most violent eruption in more than 40 years on Sunday when it sent ash 33,000 feet up into the atmosphere. No evacuation alert was given before the massive eruption on Sunday, said Guatemala's Disaster Relief Agency Chief Sergio Cabañas. More than 1.7 million people were affected by the eruption, with 3,319 people currently in shelters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of rescue workers2. Rescue workers poking ground with metal rod3. Fuego's eruption sent up ash 33,000 feet up high4. Depiction of Fuego eruption aftermathVOICEOVER (in English): "Emergency crews have resumed search and rescue operations in Guatemala after Sunday's Mt. Fuego eruption, which has killed at least 99, with around 200 people still missing."  "According to the Guardian, some places are still so hot that when rescuers poked metal rods into the ground, clouds of smoke came pouring out. Firefighters said the temperatures reached between 750 to 1,300 degrees Fahrenheit under the surface at some locations." "According to Reuters, the volcano had its most violent eruption in more than 40 years on Sunday when it sent ash 33,000 feet up into the atmosphere." "More than 1.7 million people were affected by the eruption, with over 3,000 people currently in shelters."  SOURCES: Reuters, BBC, Guardianhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-guatemala-volcano/evacuations-ordered-after-new-explosion-at-guatemala-volcano-idUSKCN1J12XRhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-44378775https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/06/guatemala-volcano-latest-los-lotes-200-missing?CMP=share_btn_tw***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 13:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/07/3627344/3627344_E2F4C2D77BC94F56A0B56C8B59FAAC0E_180607_3627344_Guatemala_volcano_search_and_rescue_resumes_with_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/680/487/6804876B1E45407AB993A3AD77709611_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Guatemala volcano, Guatemala volcano eruption, Mt Fuego eruption, Mt Fuego search and rescue, volcano search and rescue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627278</guid>
      <title>Woman's advanced stage breast cancer eradicated with immunotherapy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA woman's advanced stage breast cancer that had spread to other parts of her body was cured using her own immune cells. Doctors say the treatment marks the first time a T-cell immunotherapy application for late-stage breast cancer was successful. The results were published in the journal Nature Medicine. Judy Perkins, a 49-year-old engineer, from Florida was selected for the new therapy after chemotherapy failed to stop the tumor in her right breast from spreading to her liver and other areas, according to the Guardian. She was told she only had three years to live. Doctors from the National Cancer Institute in Maryland first took biopsies from Perkins' tumors, looked at the DNA mutations specific to her cancer. Physicians then extracted immune cells called tumor infiltrating lymphocytes, TILs, from the biopsies. Billions of these immune cells were then grown in the lab. The researchers then injected 80 billion of the TILs into Perkins' body. The treatment was given in tandem with pembrolizumab, a standard cancer drug that helps the immune system. After 42 weeks, tests showed Perkins was completely free of cancer. According to the Guardian, researchers are now planning full scale clinical trials.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman's advanced stage breast cancer was treated with t-cell immunotherapy 2. Doctors performing biopsy 3. Patient's lab grown t cells were injected into her body along with standard cancer drug4. After 42 weeks, the patient was cancer freeVOICEOVER (in English): "A woman's advanced stage breast cancer that had spread to other parts of her body was cured using her own immune cells. It marks the first time a T-cell immunotherapy application for late-stage breast cancer was successful.""Doctors from the National Cancer Institute in Maryland first took biopsies from the woman's tumors and looked at the DNA mutations specific to her cancer. Physicians then extracted immune cells called tumor infiltrating lymphocytes, TILs, from the biopsies."  "Billions of these immune cells were then grown in the lab. The researchers then injected 80 billion of the TILs into Perkins' body. The treatment was given in tandem with pembrolizumab, a standard cancer drug that helps the immune system." "After 42 weeks, tests showed Perkins was completely free of cancer." SOURCES: Guardian, The Independenthttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jun/04/doctors-hail-world-first-as-womans-advanced-breast-cancer-is-eradicatedhttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/breast-cancer-cure-tcell-immunotherapy-tumour-treatment-disease-world-first-a8382806.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 11:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/07/3627278/3627278_AD911A6A83534BECB5128C79F8DC6976_180607_3627278_Woman_s_advanced_stage_breast_cancer_eradicated__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/24B/B20/24BB204DCBA846609D26113BC75646C6_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, breast cancer, breast cancer cured, late-stage breast cancer cured, t cell immunotherapy, immunotherapy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627986</guid>
      <title>NASA Curiosity rover finds ancient organic molecules on Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAfter decades of searching for organic compounds on the Red Planet, scientists have finally been successful.NASA announced on Thursday that rock and soil samples taken by the Curiosity rover from Mars' Gale crater has yielded organic molecules believed to be 3 billion years old.Organic molecules refer to chemical compounds that contain carbon. They can come from both living and nonliving sources, and are the chemical building blocks for all life on Earth.Curiosity's Sample Analysis at Mars instrument, or SAM, heated the samples to over a thousand degrees Fahrenheit, releasing small hydrocarbons that may be fragments of bigger, more complex molecules.While the organics could have resulted from biological activity, NASA says they are just as likely to have emerged from geological processes, or from a meteor crashing into the planet.Still, the discovery of the molecules sheds light on the planet's history  painting a picture of an ancient Mars that had favorable conditions for life.It likewise spurs on future explorations, with both NASA and the European Space Agency developing new technologies to search for signs of life.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Curiosity rover samples containing organic matter2. Depiction of organic molecules3. Depiction of heated samples releasing hydrocarbons4. Depiction of possible sources for the organic moleculesVOICEOVER (in English): "Rock and soil samples taken by the NASA's Curiosity rover from an ancient Martian lake bed has yielded organic molecules believed to be 3 billion years old.""Organic molecules are chemical compounds that contain carbon. They can come from both living and nonliving sources, and are the building blocks for all life on Earth.""Curiosity's Sample Analysis at Mars instrument heated the samples to over a thousand degrees Fahrenheit, releasing small hydrocarbons that may be fragments of bigger, more complex molecules.""While the organics could have had biological sources, NASA says they are just as likely to have emerged from geological processes, or from a meteor crashing into the planet."SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-finds-ancient-organic-material-mysterious-methane-on-mars***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 11:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/08/3627986/3627986_9941CC7F5F5D48D6905FC31A86C4E92F_180608_3627986_NASA_Curiosity_rover_finds_ancient_organic_molec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DF4/509/DF4509C0901A465E9351FF82E2EBB98F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Mars, NASA, curiosity rover, organic molecule, organic matter, life on mars, hydrocarbons, ancient mars, building blocks of life, red planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627933</guid>
      <title>'Sonic Attacks' in China could just be ultrasonic surveillance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAlleged cases of "sonic attacks" in China and Cuba has raised the question of how sound can used as a weapon.U.S. diplomats in Guangzhou, and previously Havana, have been diagnosed with unexplained brain injuries following abnormal sensations of sound and pressure, prompting fears of a sonic weapon, The New York Times reports.Ultrasound is a possibility, but an unusual weapon choice: it loses power with distance more quickly than audible sounds, and requires precise alignment with a subject.University of Maryland researchers theorized that the illness may have resulted from surveillance gear being positioned too closely together.Ultrasonic devices can interfere with each other in a phenomenon known as intermodulation distortion, producing audible sound similar to what patients claimed to hear.When placed at too close range or combined with other ultrasonic emitters, these devices can cause cavitation damage, causing bubbles to form in body fluids, tissues, or cells.It's hard to say for certain what exactly triggered the diplomats' mystery ailments, but more than one expert has chimed in to say bad engineering or a bad spy job is more plausible an explanation than a sonic attack.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of U.S. diplomats' symptoms2. Depiction of surveillance devices as possible cause of illness3. Depiction of intermodulation distortion4. Depiction of cavitation damageVOICEOVER (in English): "U.S. diplomats in Guangzhou have been diagnosed with unexplained brain injuries following abnormal sensations of sound and pressure, prompting fears of a sonic weapon.""University of Maryland researchers theorized that the illness may have resulted from surveillance gear being positioned too closely together.""Ultrasonic devices can interfere with each other in a phenomenon known as intermodulation distortion, producing audible sound similar to what patients claimed to hear.""When placed at too close range or combined with other ultrasonic emitters, these devices can cause cavitation damage by causing bubbles to form in body fluids, tissues, or cells."SOURCES: The Conversation, University of Michigan, New York Timeshttps://theconversation.com/sonic-attacks-in-china-and-cuba-how-sound-can-be-a-weapon-97380https://news.umich.edu/cuba-sonic-attacks-a-covert-accident/https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/06/world/asia/china-guangzhou-consulate-sonic-attack.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 10:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/08/3627933/3627933_BC9370B6F9EF4DD387A3D14A88F409DB_180608_3627933__Sonic_Attacks__in_China_could_just_be_ultrasoni_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/217/50F/21750FB66D6042E0A46B8D88BE9363F8_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sonic attack, mysterious illness, mystery disease, brain injury, brain trauma, surveillance, ultrasonic, ultrasound, weaponized sound, sound as weapon, cavitation, us diplomats, china, cuba]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627569</guid>
      <title>American Airlines plans to debut smaller seats and bathrooms on Boeing 737-Max planes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmerican Airlines is shrinking bathrooms for its North American flights, reports Miami News.Smaller bathrooms will be installed on the new Boeing 737-Max airplanes, which reportedly will be just 24 inches wide.American airlines also plans to decrease its front-to-back space between economy class by another two inches, reports KHON.American Airlines commented that the new airplanes will have 172 seats, compared to previously having 160 seats.The airline had previously been in the news for shrinking its overhead bins. American Airlines has also reportedly been receiving a lot of negative feedback from travel bloggers, frequent fliers and even flight attendants.For now, the new single-aisle aircraft will be in use starting later this year and will be flown mainly in North America.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the smaller bathroom of the new aircraft2. Showing how the aisle seat in the aircraft has become smaller3. Show the aircraft seats becoming smaller while increasing in number4. Showing how the overhead compartment of the aircraft has shrunkVOICEOVER (in English): "Smaller bathrooms will be installed on the new Boeing 737-Max airplanes, with each bathroom being just 24 inches wide.""KHON reports American Airlines also plans to decrease its front-to-back space between economy class by another 2 inches.""American Airlines commented that the new airplanes will have 172 seats, compared to previously having 160 seats.""The airline had previously been in the news for shrinking its overhead bins."SOURCES: WSVN 7 NEWS, KHONhttps://wsvn.com/news/us-world/american-airlines-to-debut-smaller-bathrooms-for-north-american-flights/http://www.khon2.com/news/local-news/american-airlines-debuts-tiny-bathrooms/1211914967***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 03:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/08/3627569/3627569_CB9DFB39340746089043506209BD7DDB_180608_3627569_American_Airlines_plans_to_debut_smaller_seats_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/8B0/C67/8B0C67760E7142D78D069D0F15DE03F4_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,American Airlines, Airlines, AA, airplane, plane, flight bathrooms, shrinking airplane bathrooms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3628441</guid>
      <title>Earth days getting longer as moon moves away</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research shows that days on Earth are getting longer as the moon slowly spirals away from us.Due to gravitational forces between Earth and its satellite, the moon moves away at a rate of 3.82 centimeters per year, causing our planet's rotation to slow, according to the study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.Earth currently completes a full rotation on its axis every 23 hours, 56 minutes, 4 seconds, according to NASA.But researchers using astrochronology on geological rock layers found that when the moon was closer to Earth 1.4 billion years ago, a day was just over 18 hours.The length of a day has grown one seventy-five thousandth of a second on average per year, and is expected to continue at this rate for the next millions or billions of years.The Guardian reports that the moon will eventually stop moving when it reaches a stable distance from Earth. When this happens, the two will be tidally locked- rotating at the same pace, with the moon visible from only one side of Earth.Of course, that's assuming either of them survive the Sun's destructive red giant phase.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of moon moving away from the Earth2. Depiction of one full Earth rotation in present time3. Depiction of one full Earth rotation 1.4 billion years ago4. Depiction of Earth tidally locked to the moonVOICEOVER (in English): "Due to gravitational forces between Earth and its satellite, the moon moves away at a rate of 3.82 centimeters per year, causing our planet's rotation to slow.""Earth currently completes a full rotation on its axis every 23 hours, 56 minutes, 4 seconds, according to NASA.""But researchers using astrochronology on geological rock layers found that when the moon was closer to Earth 1.4 billion years ago, a day was just over 18 hours.""The moon will eventually stop moving when it reaches a stable distance from Earth. When this happens, the two will be tidally locked- rotating at the same pace, with the moon visible from only one side of Earth."SOURCES: Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, University of Wisconsin-Madison, The Guardian, NASAhttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/05/30/1717689115https://news.wisc.edu/thank-the-moon-for-earths-lengthening-day/https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jun/04/the-days-are-getting-longer-but-very-very-slowlyhttps://www.grc.nasa.gov/www/k-12/Numbers/Math/Mathematical_Thinking/telling_time_by_the_stars.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 06:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/09/3628441/3628441_9EAF6341AD724055ADC5EA18BB62F8DC_180609_3628441_Earth_days_getting_longer_as_moon_moves_away_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/831/C70/831C709653D549C2B8257F4ACAA50086_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, moon, earth, longer days, astrochronology, 24 hour days, 18 hour days, day length, day hours, timeopt, astronomical theory, Milankovitch cycles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629991</guid>
      <title>What happens during the June 21 summer solstice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe 2018 summer solstice will soon be upon us, marking the beginning of different seasons depending on where you live. The earth rotates on a tilted axis while orbiting the sun, which means different parts of the planet are pointed at or away from the sun depending on the time of year.During the solstice on June 21, the North Pole is tilted toward the sun, allowing it to shine at a 90-degree angle on the Tropic of Cancer, which sits at 23.5 degrees north of the equator.Anyone standing right on the Tropic of Cancer at noon on solstice day will see the sun directly overhead, and find themselves casting a very minimal shadow.Since the northern hemisphere faces the sun, it will experience the longest day and the start of summer. For the southern hemisphere, which tilts away from the sun, it is the shortest day and the start of winter.The opposite happens during the December's winter solstice. The northern hemisphere, now tilted away, is experiencing winter, while the sun-facing south ushers in summer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Earth's tilted axis, rotation, and orbit around the sun2. Depiction of sun shining directly on the Tropic of Cancer 3. Depiction of solstice as seen from the Tropic of Cancer4. Depiction of differences between days in the northern and southern hemispheresVOICEOVER (in English): "The Earth rotates on a tilted axis while orbiting the Sun, which means different parts of the planet are pointed at or away from the Sun depending on the time of year.""During the solstice on June 21, the North Pole is tilted toward the Sun, allowing it to shine at a 90-degree angle on the Tropic of Cancer.""Anyone standing right on the Tropic of Cancer at noon on solstice day will see the Sun directly overhead, and find themselves casting a very minimal shadow.""Since the northern hemisphere faces the sun, it will experience the longest day and the start of summer. For the southern hemisphere, which tilts away from the sun, it is the shortest day and the start of winter."SOURCES: Business Insider, USA Todayhttp://www.businessinsider.com/when-is-summer-solstice-longest-day-of-year-june-2018-6https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2014/06/20/summer-solstice-explained-sun-earth/10887737/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/12/3629991/3629991_E6CEE1EB9A5E487F97D052A0D1A8B9D7_180612_3629991_What_happens_during_the_June_21_summer_solstice_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/950/6D7/9506D716BADB4A73874480D77AF73D09_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, summer solstice, june solstice, 2018 solstice, summer solstice explained, summer solstice explainer, solstice explainer, earth, sun, tilted axis, summer, winter, why we have seasons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629801</guid>
      <title>How Easter Islanders put 13-ton hats on statues</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers say they have figured out how Easter Islanders transported 13-ton stone hats across the island and placed them on top of 33-feet tall moai statues.The study, published in the Journal of Archaeological Science, examined how ancient islanders were able to move the additional red stone cylinders, pukao, onto the tops of the statues, according to NPR. Easter Island has almost 1,000 moai statues spread across the island, with around 100 of them wearing the pukao hats. Researchers say the pukao were added later, but are unsure of the exact dates.  After constructing 3D models of the stone cylinders, scientists closely analyzed the details and features of each pukao.They developed a hypothesis that the hats were rolled up to the top of the statues using long ramps with a technique known as parbuckling.  Archaeologist Carl Lipo, co-author of the study, described the technique being similar to the way barrels used to be loaded onto cargo ships, saying "people would wrap ropes around the center of the barrel and then, from the top of the ramp, pull the barrel up the ramp. … All the attributes we saw match that model." Using the 3D models, the team was able to calculate how long the ramp would have to be, in addition to how many workers would be required to pull the pukao into place. With a ramp 75 to 328 feet long, with an incline of 5 to 20 degrees, a team of 15 people could maneuver a pukao into position, according to ArsTechnica. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Moai statue with pukao2. Moai statue with parbuckling ramp3. Pukao being pulled up ramp4. Pukao being put in placeVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers say they have figured out how Easter Islanders transported 13-ton stone hats across the island and placed them on top of 33-feet tall moai statues.""After constructing 3D models of the stone cylinders, scientists closely analyzed the details and features of each pukao. They developed a hypothesis that the hats were rolled up to the top of the statues using long ramps with a technique known as parbuckling."  "Using the 3D models, the team was able to calculate how long the ramp would have to be, in addition to how many workers would be required to pull the pukao into place." "With a ramp 75 to 328 feet long, with an incline of 5 to 20 degrees, a team of 15 people could maneuver a pukao into position." SOURCES: NPR, ArsTechnicahttps://www.npr.org/2018/06/07/618087324/how-did-easter-islanders-lift-statues-13-ton-hats-researchers-may-have-the-answehttps://arstechnica.com/science/2018/06/how-easter-islands-famous-statues-got-their-giant-stone-hats/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 11:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/11/3629801/3629801_634C16C8D59C46B283D79DA2684C2826_180611_3629801_How_Easter_Islanders_put_13_ton_hats_on_statues_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/6BA/5D3/6BA5D351F8894D3485C2372B2DB0F73F_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Easter Island, Easter Island pukao moai statues, pukao, moai statues, parbuckling]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629794</guid>
      <title>Singapore security on high alert for Trump-Kim summit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSingapore has been busy preparing the city for the historic Trump-Kim summit to be held on June 12. Singapore Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong told the press on Sunday that hosting the meeting was costing the city-state US$15 million, mainly on enhanced security. According to the South China Morning Post, Interior minister K. Shanmugam said around 5,000 police officers and first responders will be on hand for the meeting. Singapore in total has 13,000 police officers and 2,500 first responders, the South China Morning Post reported. An unspecified number of military personnel have also been deployed, and with at least two warships on patrol off Sentosa island where the meeting will be held. The Singaporean government has also designated areas around the three hotels  the Shangri-La, St. Regis and Capella   to be used in the summit as "special event areas."Police in these "special event areas" have enhanced powers to stop and search vehicles.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Singapore spending $15 million in security for summit meeting2. Singapore is deploying around 5,000 police officers and 2,500 first responders3. Three hotels have been designated special event areas with heightened security4. Singapore also has military soldiers deployed as well as at least two warshipsVOICEOVER (in English): "Singapore has been busy preparing the city for the historic Trump-Kim summit to be held on June 12. Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong told the press on Sunday that hosting the meeting was costing the city-state US$15 million, mainly on enhanced security." "According to the South China Morning Post, Interior minister K. Shanmugam said around 5,000 police officers and first responders will be on hand. For comparison, Singapore has 13,000 police officers and 2,500 first responders in total.""The Singaporean government has also designated areas around the three hotels  the Shangri-La, St. Regis and Capella   to be used in the summit as "special event areas."Police in these "special event areas" have enhanced powers to stop and search vehicles." "An unspecified number of military personnel have also been deployed, and with at least two warships on patrol off Sentosa island where the meeting will be held." SOURCES: Channel News Asia, SCMPhttps://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/singapore/shanmugam-confident-security-in-place-for-trump-kim-summit-10415630http://www.scmp.com/news/asia/diplomacy/article/2150120/singapores-security-high-alert-historic-trump-kim-summit-after***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 11:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/11/3629794/3629794_E8017EE8AE89468AB0C23E9D6F79A5CD_180611_3629794_Singapore_security_on_high_alert_for_Trump_Kim_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FFF/A75/FFFA7551FF084435BAE5A94035D9C681_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Trump Kim summit, Trump Kim meeting, Trump Kim Singapore, Trump Kim Summit security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629746</guid>
      <title>Emirates planning to replace windows on planes with virtual ones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEmirates says it is planning to replace all of their windows in airplanes with virtual windows instead.Emirates Airlines President Sir Tim Clark told the BBC the "ultimate aim was to have no windows at all."Clark claims that the aircrafts will be lighter this way and could fly faster and fly higher while burning less fuel.Clark also claims that the projected images are "so good, it's better than with the natural eye."For now, the virtual windows are being used in Emirates' Boeing 777-300ER aircraft in the first class cabin. The virtual windows are supposed to look 'just like the real thing," reports ABC Net.Aviation expert Douglas Drury claims there aren't really any safety concerns. Though Drury says that there should be windows in critical places, such as the emergency exits, to have a clear view of the aircraft wings. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the Emirates aircraft becoming a windowless airplane2. After the plane becomes windowless, it becomes slimmer and flies faster and higher3. We see how the virtual windows look like from inside the aircraft4. Showing that there should be at least some windows inside an aircraft, in case of an emergency.VOICEOVER (in English): "Emirates Airlines president Sir Tim Clark told the BBC the 'ultimate aim was to have no windows at all.""Clark claims that the aircrafts will be lighter this way and could fly faster and fly higher while burning less fuel.""For now, the virtual windows are being used in Emirates' Boeing 777-300ER aircraft in the first class cabin. ""Aviation expert Douglas Drury claims there aren't really any safety concerns. ""Though Drury says that there should be windows in critical places, such as the emergency exits, to have a clear view of the aircraft wings."SOURCES: The BBC, The Sun, ABC Net, Arabian Businesshttps://www.bbc.com/news/business-44383220?ns_mchannel=social&ns_campaign=bbcnews&ocid=socialflow_facebook&ns_source=facebookhttps://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/6464460/emirates-windowless-planes/http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-06-07/would-you-travel-on-a-windowless-plane/9843722http://www.arabianbusiness.com/transport/397915-aircraft-of-the-future-may-have-no-windows-says-emirates-tim-clark***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 10:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/11/3629746/3629746_E57A319A7D66436994C405399800521E_180611_3629746_Emirates_planning_to_replace_windows_on_planes_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/364/96F/36496F87C8D645889234FC8463F8109A_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Emirates, windowless airplanes, virtual windows, flying without windows, planes, airplanes without windows]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630490</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered planet is more than 600 light years away from Earth.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of scientists in India have discovered a sub-Saturn sized exoplanet, reports the Financial Times.The planet, called EPIC 211945201b or K2-236b, is reportedly 600 light years away from Earth.The planet has a mass of around 27 Earths while its radius is six times that of Earth. Scientists used the PRL Advance Radial-velocity Abu-sky Search spectrograph, or PARAS, to measure the mass of a planet travelling around a star.The surface temperature of the planet is approximately 600 degrees Celsius, which makes it virtually uninhabitable. Distance-wise, it is seven times closer to its sun-like star in comparison to Earth and its sun.It takes around 19.5 days to complete one rotation around its Sun-like star.The scientists believe elements such as ice, silicates, and iron content make up around 60-70 percent of the total mass of the planet, based on the calculations of the mass and the radius, reports The Economic Times.This type of a discovery is crucial in our understanding of how these types of planets are formed, the Financial Express reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the new planet and how far away it is from Earth2. Showing how big the new planet is compared to Earth.3. Showing the surface of K2-236b and we also see how close the planet is to its Sun-like Star4. Showing how  K2-236b rotates around its Sun-like Star and we also see the elements that may makeup K2-236b. VOICEOVER (in English): "The planet's sun-like star is reportedly 600 light years away from Earth.""The planet has a mass of around 27 Earths while its radius is six times that of Earth. ""The surface temperature of the planet is approximately 600 degrees Celsius, which makes it virtually uninhabitable. Distance-wise, it is seven times closer to its sun-like star in comparison to Earth and its sun.""It takes around 19.5 days to complete one rotation around its Sun-like star.""The Economic Times reports that the scientists believe elements such as ice, silicates, and iron content make up around 60-70 percent of the total mass of the planet, based on the calculations of the mass and the radius."SOURCES: The Economic Times, Financial Express, The Times of India,https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/science/indian-scientists-discover-planet-600-light-years-away/light-years-away-from-earth/slideshow/64509281.cmshttps://www.financialexpress.com/lifestyle/science/india-discovers-its-own-planet-where-a-year-ends-in-19-5-days-amazing-things-to-know/1200647/https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/home/science/india-discovers-new-planet-joins-elite-club/articleshow/64515199.cms***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 09:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/12/3630490/3630490_3F8F63E5307F45689CE8B17160E4AB67_180612_3630490_Newly_discovered_planet_is_more_than_600_light_y_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F96/87F/F9687FAC1A944339B307192831248D0B_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Space, Space Discovery, Planet discovery, Exoplanet, K2-236b, K2-236, EPIC 211945201b, Sun-like star, Spectrograph, Observatory]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631071</guid>
      <title>Venezuela reports first case of polio since 1989</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA young child is reportedly afflicted with polio in Venezuela  the first reported case of the crippling disease since it's eradication in the country in 1989.The Telegraph reports that according to the Pan-American Health Organization, the child lived in an impoverished indigenous community in the Delta Amacuro state.According to the CDC, poliomyelitis, or polio, is caused by the poliovirus, which enters through the mouth via contact with contaminated feces, or through droplets from a cough or sneeze.The virus multiplies in small intestine, before being carried through the bloodstream to the central nervous system, where it destroys motor neuron cells.The majority of infected don't get sick, while one in four develop non-paralytic polio with flu-like symptoms. Paralytic polio, though rare, can lead to muscle pain, paralysis, and even death.In some cases, those who contracted and fully recovered from the disease as kids can develop symptoms years later as adults.Young children, especially those who are malnourished an unvaccinated, are especially susceptible to polio. The disease has no cure, but is preventable through immunization.Venezuela has been plagued with economic and political crises in recent years. Local health authorities who were supposed to report cases of polio within 24 hours, took more than a month to do so.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of how poliovirus is contracted2. Depiction of poliovirus multiplying and attacking nervous system3. Depiction of types of polio4. Depiction of polio immunizationVOICEOVER (in English): "Poliomyelitis is caused by the poliovirus, which enters through the mouth via contact with contaminated feces, or through droplets from a cough or sneeze.""The virus multiplies in small intestine, before being carried through the bloodstream to the central nervous system, where it destroys motor neuron cells.""According to the CDC, the majority of infected don't get sick, while 1 in 4 develop non-paralytic polio with flu-like symptoms. Paralytic polio, though rare, can lead to muscle pain, paralysis, and even death.""Young children, especially those who are malnourished and unvaccinated, are especially susceptible to polio. The disease has no cure, but is preventable through immunization."SOURCES: Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Mayo Clinic, Smithsonian National Museum of American Historyhttps://www.cdc.gov/polio/about/https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/polio/symptoms-causes/syc-20376512https://amhistory.si.edu/polio/virusvaccine/how.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 07:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/13/3631071/3631071_161071D0E2914691966292778DB777DB_180613_3631071_Venezuela_reports_first_case_of_polio_since_1989_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/B10/94E/B1094E5DBFE440F088993907D1DC4E35_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, polio, poliomyelitis, polio vaccine, what is polio, polio explainer, contagious diseases, polio virus, polio comeback, polio venezuela]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630904</guid>
      <title>US debuts world's fastest supercomputer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. has unveiled its latest supercomputer which is twice as powerful as the world's current leader. The Summit supercomputer can process 200,000 trillion calculations per second  or 200 petaflops, the BBC reports. China's Sunway TaihuLight supercomputer had been the most powerful machine with 93 petaflops of processing power. Summit will be used first in the areas of astrophysics, cancer research and systems biology, according to the BBC. The computer was developed in tandem by IBM and NVidia, and is located at the Oak Ridge National Laboratory, ORNL, in Tennessee.The supercomputer has 4,608 compute servers and has more than 10 petabytes of memory. According to the BBC, the U.S. now has 143 of the world's top 500 supercomputers, while China has 202.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Summit supercomputer2. Depiction of CPU chips and GPU chips inside Summit 3. Summit will first be used in areas of astrophysics, cancer research and systems biology4. Summit supercomputer is roughly the size of 2 tennis courts and weighs as much as a commercial jetlinerVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. has unveiled its latest supercomputer which is twice as powerful as the world's current leader. According to BBC, the Summit supercomputer can process 200,000 trillion calculations per second  or 200 petaflops." "Supercomputers are usually large, expensive systems that house tens of thousands of processors tasked with carrying out specialized calculation-intensive problems." "According to the BBC, Summit will be used first in the areas of astrophysics, cancer research and systems biology." "Summit has 4,608 compute servers and has more than 10 petabytes of memory. According to Techspot, the supercomputer is housed in a 5,600 square foot space, roughly the size of two tennis courts and weighs nearly as much as a commercial airplane." SOURCES: BBC, Quartzhttps://www.bbc.com/news/technology-44439515https://qz.com/1301510/the-us-has-the-worlds-fastest-supercomputer-again-the-200-petaflop-summit/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 03:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/13/3630904/3630904_395288D9B4A545E69EA3F627FFB8EAB6_180613_3630904_US_debuts_world_s_fastest_supercomputer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/05A/CE9/05ACE93B83294C63AA90B0789B643960_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Summit supercomputer, US Summit supercomputer, US fastest supercomputer, supercomputer, IBM Summit, NVidia Summit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636311</guid>
      <title>U.S. expecting North Korea to return troop remains</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe United States is expecting North Korea to return up to 200 sets of remains believed to be troops who died during the Korean War.According to CNN, administration officials said arrangements are being made to accept the remains, although no set date or location have yet been determined. The Defense Department says there are up to 5,300 sets of U.S. service member remains still in North Korea, with a total of 7,697 personnel still missing in action. Some of the remains were from downed pilots, others from ground troops, while others may be those who died as prisoners of war. When the transfer does occur, it is expected North Korean officials will give the remains to United Nations officials at the DMZ. The UN will then hand them over to U.S. military personnel. The remains will then be sent to a military laboratory in Hawaii for DNA identification and matching. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NK returning 200 troop remains to US2. 5,300 sets of remains still in NK, with 7,697 missing in action3. Remains from downed pilots, ground troops and POWs4. Remains being tested for DNA identification and matchingVOICEOVER (in English): "The United States is expecting North Korea to return up to 200 sets of remains believed to be troops who died during the Korean War. According to CNN, administration officials said arrangements are being made to accept the remains, although no set date or location have yet been determined." "The Defense Department says there are up to 5,300 sets of U.S. service member remains still in North Korea, with a total of 7,697 personnel still missing in action." "Some of the remains were from downed pilots, others from ground troops, while others may be those who died as prisoners of war." "The remains will then be sent to a military laboratory in Hawaii for DNA identification and matching." SOURCES: CNN https://edition.cnn.com/2018/06/19/politics/north-korea-kia-remains-return/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/20/3636311/3636311_9A677AAC67FE4359AB0F6310CAD490C6_180620_3636311_U_S__expecting_North_Korea_to_return_troop_remai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9F5/AB9/9F5AB920B3B449B29AA427009F5CB523_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Korean War, US troop remains, North Korea, North Korea US troop remains, US servicemember remains]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636834</guid>
      <title>U.S. toddlers and babies eating more sugar than maximum amount recommended for adults</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention finds that U.S. infants are consuming excessive amounts of sugar that even exceed maximum levels recommended for some adults. The results were presented at the American Society for Nutrition's annual meeting on June 10, Quartz reports.Researchers focused on the sugar added during food preparation or processing such as cane sugar, high-fructose corn syrup and honey, not natural sugars found in fruit or milk.  The study looked at more than 800 children between six months and 23 months who had taken part in the 2011 to 2014 National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey. Parents were told to keep track of every item their child ate or drank during a 24-hour period. Scientists then calculated an average sugar intake from the sample.The results showed toddlers 12 to 18 months consumed 5.5 teaspoons of sugar per day, while toddlers 19 to 23 months ate 7.1 teaspoons a day.For comparison, the daily recommended limits for added sugar for children 2 to 19 years old and adult women is 6 teaspoons or less a day, and 9 teaspoons or less a day for adult men.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Infants consuming sugary foods, exceeding maximum levels recommended for adults2. Sample size was more than 800 infants3. Study looked at processed sugars intake4. Average sugar consumption for toddlersVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention finds that U.S. infants are consuming excessive amounts of sugar that even exceed maximum levels recommended for some adults." "The study looked at more than 800 children between six months and 23 months who had taken part in the 2011 to 2014 National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey, where parents were told to record every item their child ate or drank during a 24-hour period." "Researchers focused on the sugar added during food preparation or processing  such as cane sugar, high-fructose corn syrup and honey  not natural sugars found in fruit or milk.""The results showed toddlers 12 to 18 months consumed 5.5 teaspoons of sugar per day, while toddlers 19 to 23 months ate 7.1 teaspoons a day." SOURCES: CBS News, Quartzhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/us-babies-toddlers-eat-way-too-much-added-sugar-study-finds/https://qz.com/1302201/american-toddlers-are-eating-more-sugar-than-the-amount-recommended-for-adults/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 08:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/21/3636834/3636834_B78BA795EBBC4D6CA2E6907523D2F8D1_180621_3636834_U_S__toddlers_and_babies_eating_more_sugar_than__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/782/AFB/782AFB71B9AB40CF9EB450E3E93CCADE_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sugar, sugar consumption, toddler sugar consumption, baby sugar consumption, CDC study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636584</guid>
      <title>Quebec ups energy rate for crypto miners</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccess to Quebec's power grid is going to cost new cryptocurrency miners triple.This week Quebec increased energy prices for new blockchain companies by 300 percent to 15 cents per kilowatt hour, reports Bloomberg. The province is powered entirely by renewable energy sources, and most of this comes from hydropower. Bloomberg reports new blockchain energy requests would go beyond what Quebec can provide power for in the short and medium-term.  State-owned provincial power administrator Hydro-Quebec will keep the rate in place for several weeks until a new power limit and pricing model is calculated.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Quebec and hydro power 2. Depiction of blockchain industry coming to Quebec3. Depiction of more blockchain companies coming to Quebec4. Depiction of new power rate and blockchain companiesVOICEOVER (in English): "Quebec is powered entirely by renewable energy sources, with most of it sourced from hydropower.""Bloomberg reports the province offers the lowest energy rates in North America.""Because of this, cryptocurrency blockchain firms with their high-energy demands moved to Quebec after the government incentivised with them low rates.""According to Bloomberg, this was a bid to absorb excess energy from hydro-dams.""This week Quebec increased energy prices for new blockchain companies by 300 percent to 15 cents per kilowatt hour.""Bloomberg reports new blockchain energy requests would go beyond what Quebec can provide power for in the short and medium-term.""State-owned provincial power administrator Hydro-Quebec will keep the rate in place for several weeks until a new power limit and pricing model is calculated."SOURCES: Bloomberg, Hydro-Quebec, Blokt, Reutershttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-19/Quebec-hikes-power-prices-for-crypto-miners-to-halt-new-requestshttp://www.hydroQuebec.com/about/our-energy.htmlhttps://blokt.com/news/Quebec-freezes-crypto-mining-power-requests-amid-excessive-demandhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-bitcoin-Quebec/canadas-Quebec-halts-crypto-mining-projects-may-raise-fees-idUSKCN1J31Q5***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 02:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/21/3636584/3636584_B31A52EFFD264FA5B414D78F7A8FD1C0_180621_3636584_Quebec_ups_energy_rate_for_crypto_miners_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/4C1/C46/4C1C461CA4AA41FEA9B445327B723A7F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Quebec, Quebec energy, Quebec cryptocurrency, bitcoin mining, cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency power, blockchain, blockchain power needs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636579</guid>
      <title>Oldest ever plague genome found in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have unearthed findings that changes current thinking on how old the plague is. Research published in the journal Nature Communication describes how scientists found the bacterium Yersinia Pestis on the teeth of 3,800-year-old human remains in Samara, Russia.Researchers looked at the remains of nine people, two of them had the bacteria.Yersinia Pestis gave rise to the bubonic plague. The scientist used sequencing to analyze the samples and found that they pre-date current thinking on the plague's lineage  3,000 years  by around 1,000 years. Researchers suggest that there was at least two strains of plague lineage floating around at the time. Previously it was suggested to be one.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of location and findings2. Depiction of Y pestis and flea3. Depiction of Y Pestis analysis and bronze age area 4. Depiction of second strain of Y Pestis in bronze age areaVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in the journal Nature Communication describes how scientists found the bacterium Yersinia Pestis on the teeth of 3,800-year-old human remains in Samara, Russia.""Researchers looked at the remains of nine people, two of them had the bacteria.Yersinia Pestis gave rise to the bubonic plague.""The scientists used sequencing to analyze the samples and found that they pre-date current thinking on the plague's lineage  3,000 years  by around 1,000 years.""That puts it somewhere in the Bronze Age.""Researchers suggest that there was at least two strains of plague lineage floating around at the time.""Previously it was suggested to be one."SOURCES: Nature Communications, Max Planck Institute, https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-018-04550-9http://www.shh.mpg.de/979007/oldest-bubonic-plaque***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 02:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/21/3636579/3636579_42D48E2A2CF74E24A3D990E14C6306B7_180621_3636579_Oldest_ever_plague_genome_found_in_Russia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C37/B45/C37B45FDF6514ABFBDD629EBD3BCFEF0_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  ancient civilizations, Russia, Samara, Yersinia Pestis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637614</guid>
      <title>Drinking too much alcohol can increase cancer risk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study finds that light drinkers have the lowest combined risk of developing cancer and dying prematurely, even when compared to people who did not drink at all. According to NPR, scientists looked at 100,000 adults in their mid-50s to early 70s, and had each complete a survey about their alcohol consumption. Researchers then tracked these people for nine years and found that the more alcohol consumed, the higher the risk of developing cancer and dying. The findings were published in the journal PLOS Medicine. Heavy drinkers were the most at risk. Scientists found that men who drank three or more drinks per day were three to four times more likely to develop esophagus or liver cancer. Other alcohol-related cancers were colorectal and breast cancer in women.According to NPR, a drink is a single shot of liquor, 5 ounces of wine or 12 ounces of beer.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study found that light drinkers have lowest combined risk of developing cancer and dying prematurely2. Study followed 100,000 older adults for nine years 3. Heavy drinkers had higher incidences of cancer4. How much alcohol is in a drinkVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study finds that light drinkers have the lowest combined risk of developing cancer and dying prematurely, even when compared to people who did not drink at all. "According to NPR, scientists looked at 100,000 adults in their mid-50s to early 70s, and had each complete a survey about their alcohol consumption. Researchers then tracked these people for nine years and found that the more alcohol consumed, the higher the risk of developing cancer and dying." "Heavy drinkers were the most at risk. Scientists found that men who drank three or more drinks per day were three to four times more likely to develop esophagus or liver cancer. Other alcohol-related cancers were colorectal and breast cancer in women.""According to NPR, a drink is a single shot of liquor, 5 ounces of wine or 12 ounces of beer."  SOURCES: NPRhttps://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/06/19/621547571/drinking-alcohol-can-raise-cancer-risk-how-much-is-too-much***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 08:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/22/3637614/3637614_A48BD736D27048A58896A821A01963BD_180622_3637614_Drinking_too_much_alcohol_can_increase_cancer_ri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/475/299/47529929B7634DB6AFAAA92B972C56F5_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, drinking, drinking excessive alcohol, drinking causes cancer, light drinker, heavy drinker]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637556</guid>
      <title>NASA outlines plan to prepare Earth for an asteroid strike</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has come up with a plan to protect the Earth from asteroids, in the unlikely event that one were to hit the planet.Titled "National Near-Earth Object Preparedness and Strategy Action Plan", the document details the steps NASA and Federal Emergency Management Agency will take to prevent asteroids from hitting Earth, and to prepare the planet should such a catastrophic event take place.Large asteroids can obliterate life on Earth, but smaller ones may also cause serious damage. The 130 to 200-foot wide asteroid that hit Tunguska, Russia in 1908, for example, levelled over 700 square miles of forest, and would have been able to destroy the entire metropolitan New York area.The outlined plan involves five main goals. The first involves enhancing detection of near-Earth objects, or asteroids that pass within 28 million miles of Earth's orbit. The second goal is to improve modelling and prediction, to help determine when and where a potential asteroid strike will occur.The third objective is to come up with new ways to deflect an asteroid, such as the Double Asteroid Redirection Test that's set to be launched in 2021.Goal four aims to increase international cooperation, while the fifth and final goal calls for the U.S. to come up with an emergency plan should an asteroid ever crash with little to no warning.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of a large asteroid obliterating life on Earth, and a small asteroid causing damage2. Depiction of asteroid classified as near Earth objects3. Depiction of predicting when and where an asteroid will strike4. Depiction of the Double Asteroid Redirection Test5. Depiction of increased international cooperation, emergency planVOICEOVER (in English): "Large asteroids can obliterate life on Earth, but smaller ones may also cause serious damage, like the rock that hit Tunguska, Russia in 1908, which levelled over 700 square miles of forest.""As a result, NASA has outlined a plan with five goals. The first involves enhancing detection of near-Earth objects, or asteroids that pass within 28 million miles of Earth's orbit.""The second goal is to improve modelling and prediction, to help determine when and where a potential asteroid strike will occur.""The third objective is to come up with new ways to deflect an asteroid, such as the Double Asteroid Redirection Test that's set to be launched in 2021.""Goal four aims to increase international cooperation, while the fifth and final goal calls for the U.S. to come up with an emergency plan should an asteroid ever crash with little to no warning."SOURCES: White House, CBShttps://www.whitehouse.gov/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/National-Near-Earth-Object-Preparedness-Strategy-and-Action-Plan-23-pages-1MB.pdfhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/nasa-asteroid-protection-plan-near-earth-objects-white-house-fema/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/22/3637556/3637556_84BA1EDABFAC46C09089CE26DBDE0458_180622_3637556_NASA_outlines_plan_to_prepare_Earth_for_an_aster_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1D6/1FF/1D61FF20534B41639D4E9DCCA0369551_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, asteroid, asteroid strike, asteroid protection, emergency plan, NASA, armageddon, asteroid apocalypse, near Earth objects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3638182</guid>
      <title>Orlando airport implements facial recognition for international travelers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOrlando's main airport hub is implementing facial recognition technology for international travelers. The Orlando Sentinel reports that Florida's Orlando International Airport is set to be the first U.S. airport to use facial scanners to process passengers on all inbound and outbound international flights.The scans will be checked against passenger passport photos and travel information on a Department of Homeland Security database, to verify a travelers identity.Biometric screening is expected to speed up passenger processing, but concerns have been voiced over privacy and potential information theft.In response, the U.S. Customs and Border Protection says scans in the database are deleted after 14 days, but could be removed almost immediately in the future. Photos of foreign nationals, however, are also kept in the Automated Biometric Identification System for up to 75 years.The system currently claims to have a 99% accuracy rate, though officials can manually screen passports and fingerprints if a photo doesn't match or a U.S. citizen decides to opt out.Once fully implemented, facial scanners will be stationed inside the airport's 30 international departure gates and two CBP checkpoints. The technology is also being used in other U.S. airports, though to a lesser degree.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of facial scanners being used at Orlando airport2. Depiction of face scans checked against stored biometric information3. Depiction of scans being deleted from the database after 14 days4. Depiction of traditional screening if photo doesn't match, or citizen opts outVOICEOVER (in English): "Orlando International Airport is set to be the first airport in the U.S. to use facial recognition to process passengers on all inbound and outbound international flights.""The scans will be checked against passenger passport photos and travel information on a Department of Homeland Security database, to verify a traveler's identity.""U.S. Customs and Border Protection claims scans in the database are deleted after 14 days, but could be removed almost immediately in the future.""The system currently has a 99% accuracy rate, though officials can manually screen passports and fingerprints if a photo doesn't match or a U.S. citizen decides to opt out."SOURCES: WKMG, Orlando Sentinel, News13https://www.clickorlando.com/news/what-to-know-about-the-new-facial-recognition-technology-at-orlando-international-airporthttp://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/transportation/os-orlando-airport-facial-recognition-20180621-story.htmlhttp://www.mynews13.com/fl/orlando/news/2018/06/21/oia-to-use-facial-recognition-tech-at-airport***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 05:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/23/3638182/3638182_4699F902683E40AF9238638053321DC7_180623_3638182_Orlando_airport_implements_facial_recognition_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A41/E0E/A41E0EC0F6A44DB49BA2760FEE142702_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, facial recognition, facial scanner, face scan, face scanner, airport, biometrics, biometric screening, facial recognition tech, privacy, orlando airport, customs border Protection, homeland security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639354</guid>
      <title>Gene-edited pigs resistant to deadly PRRS virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have successfully made pigs resistant to a deadly virus by editing their genes.According to the study, published in the Journal of Virology, Porcine Reproductive and Respiratory Syndrome  or PRRS  causes breathing problems and death in young pigs, and stillborns in infected sows.To address this, researchers from the University of Edinburgh's Roslin Institute used gene editing to remove a small section of the pigs' CD163 receptor, which the PRRS virus attaches to. They then exposed the gene-edited pigs to the virus and found that the animals did not become infected.Scientists say the genetic edit is permanent, meaning the pigs' resistance to the disease will be passed down through natural breeding.The Edinburgh team stressed that unlike genetic modification, which is highly controversial, no foreign genes are added in during the editing process. But with no regulations in place, it may take years before the technology can be applied to commercially raised swines.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Porcine Reproductive and Respiratory Syndrome in pigs2. Depiction of small region of pig DNA deleted using gene editing3. Depiction of gene edited pigs immune to Porcine Reproductive and Respiratory Syndrome4. Depiction of PRRS resistance being passed down via natural breedingVOICEOVER (in English): "Porcine Reproductive and Respiratory Syndrome, or PRRS, causes breathing problems and death in young pigs, and stillborns in infected sows.""To address this, University of Edinburgh researchers used gene editing to remove a small section of the pigs' CD163 receptor, which the PRRS virus attaches to.""They then exposed the gene-edited pigs to the virus and found that the animals did not become infected.""Scientists say the genetic edit is permanent, meaning the pigs' resistance to the disease will be passed down through natural breeding."SOURCES: Journal of Virology, BBChttp://jvi.asm.org/content/early/2018/05/31/JVI.00415-18.full.pdf+htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-44388038#***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 06:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/25/3639354/3639354_3C02C1392076447BB7263FF500629C0C_180625_3639354_Gene_edited_pigs_resistant_to_deadly_PRRS_virus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1E0/934/1E0934207C124F64A4364D57CF1CF209_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, gene editing, gene edited pigs, porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, PRRS, gene modification, GM, farm animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639298</guid>
      <title>Norway's electric plane takes flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorwegian fliers may be travelling on electric powered aircraft within the next decade.According to Norwegian government information, the Alpha Electro G2 aircraft has a range of 170 km and can fly for up to 1 hour.Manufacturer Pipistrel says the aircraft's motor has power of around 50 kilowatts, with a 21 kilowatt per hour battery.This is small compared to batteries used by electric cars. Pipistrel says the aircraft can be recharged quickly at customized charging stations. The plane was tested this month at Oslo airport. Carrying two passengers, it weighed 570 kg and was airborne for several minutes. Reuters reports that the passengers described the experience as cramped, but quieter than normal aircraft.The country plans to operate domestic flights electric by 2025, with a view to having all electrically powered come 2040.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of electric plane flying2. Depiction of electric plane and electric car3. Depiction of electric plane being charged4. Depiction of passengers inside electrical planeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Norwegian government information, the Alpha Electro G2 aircraft has a range of 170 km and can fly for up to 1 hour.""Manufacturer Pipistrel says the aircraft's motor has power of around 50 kilowatts, with a 21 kilowatt per hour battery.""This is small compared to batteries used by electric cars. "Variants of the Tesla Model S electric car use the 75 and 100 kilowatt per hour batteries.""Pipistrel says the aircraft can be recharged quickly at customized charging stations. "The plane was tested this month at Oslo airport.""Carrying two passengers, it weighed 570 kg and was airborne for several minutes.""Reuters reports that the passengers described the experience as cramped, but quieter than a normal aircraft."SOURCES: Avinor, Pipistrel, Tesla, Reutershttps://avinor.no/en/aviation/news/first-electric-aircraft/http://www.pipistrel.si/news/the-first-flight-of-electric-aircraft-in-norwayhttps://www.tesla.com/modelshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-norway-electric-flight/norway-tests-tiny-electric-plane-sees-passenger-flights-by-2025-idUSKBN1JE27D***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 05:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/25/3639298/3639298_E6CD771994A94345A17025AAEA8B0464_180625_3639298_Norway_s_electric_plane_takes_flight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/535/913/53591342A6864DEC949B4BF901DC3B79_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, electrical airplane, norway, electrical airplane flight, electrical aircraft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639283</guid>
      <title>'Digital Key' may replace car keys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew technology may soon see traditional car keys being replaced by smartphones.The 'Digital Key', developed by the Car Connectivity Consortium, CCC, can lock and unlock cars, as well as start the vehicle's engine, according to Mashable. CCC members include several car and smartphone manufacturers, according to information on the consortium website.Mashable reports the technology would enable shared access to vehicles across different smartphones. It uses technology such as GSMA, Bluetooth, Near Field Communication and GlobalPlatform, according to information on the CCC website.Their aim is to standardize the digital key as a car key solution across the automotive industry.Mashable reports that the digital key currently requires manufacturer installation.The next version of the technology, called Digital Key 2.0, should enable users to set it up themselves. That's expected for release in 2019.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of technology being used2. Depiction of technologies used by Digital Key3. Depiction of different people using Digital Key at their vehicles4. Depiction of different versions of technologyVOICEOVER (in English): "The digital key can reportedly lock and unlock cars, as well as start the vehicle's engine.  "Mashable reports the technology would enable shared access to vehicles across different smartphones.""It uses technology such as GSMA, Bluetooth, Near Field Communication and GlobalPlatform."The digital key was developed by the Car Connectivity Consortium. Their members include a number of car and smartphone manufacturers.""Their aim is to standardize the digital key as a car key solution across the automotive industry.""Mashable reports that the digital key currently requires manufacturer installation.""The next version of the technology, called Digital Key 2.0, should enable users to set it up themselves."SOURCES: Car Connectivity Consortium, Mashablehttps://carconnectivity.org/press-release/car-connectivity-consortium-announces-publication-digital-key-release-1-0-specification-delivering-industry-standardized-smart-phone-car-key-solution/https://carconnectivity.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Digital_Key_Brochure_Final.pdfhttps://mashable.com/2018/06/21/digital-car-key-ccc/#NvsYSGP8lsqL***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 05:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/25/3639283/3639283_570A40A233C647E5A80DFFE3B384AE07_180625_3639283__Digital_Key__may_replace_car_keys_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F56/4CC/F564CCA2244B43D8AB38E5B2A9530E79_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, digital key, car connectivity consortium, CCC car key, keyless car, keyless car security, keyless car technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640200</guid>
      <title>July lunar eclipse will reportedly be longest this century</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe longest lunar eclipse of this century will appear over Earth at the end of July, according astronomer Bruce McClure. Writing on EarthSky.org, astronomer Bruce McClure says the lunar eclipse on July 27 will also be an apogean moon   when the Earth is at its furthest point from the moon. McClure notes this will be the lengthiest lunar eclipse of the current century (2001 to 2100).According to data from NASA, the eclipse will last 1 hour 42 minutes and 57 seconds.The celestial event will be viewable from most of Africa, the Middle East as well as central, east and southeast Asia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the a lunar eclipse2. Depiction of the Earth, sun and moon in alignment3. Depiction of lunar eclipse in night sky4. Depiction of where lunar eclipse will be visibleVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA, Earth creates several shadows during an eclipse. The primary ones are called the penumbra and the umbra.""During a lunar eclipse, the moon enters the umbra, with its color changing to dark red.""These occur when the sun, moon and Earth are in perfect alignment with each other.""Writing on EarthSky.org, astronomer Bruce McClure says the lunar eclipse on July 27 will also be an apogean moon  when the earth is at its farthest point from the moon.""According to data from NASA, the eclipse will last 1 hour 42 minutes and 57 seconds."McClure writes this will be the century's longest lunar eclipse.""The celestial event will be viewable from most of Africa, the Middle East as well as central, east and southeast Asia."SOURCES: EarthSky.org, NASA, Daily Expresshttp://earthsky.org/?p=282841https://eclipse.gsfc.nasa.gov/LEplot/LEplot2001/LE2018Jul27T.pdfhttps://www.express.co.uk/news/science/978904/blood-moon-2018-july-total-lunar-eclipse-date-full-moon-why-longest-century***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 08:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/26/3640200/3640200_5B76A0FE83B241D0B49B321734EF7099_180626_3640200_July_lunar_eclipse_will_reportedly_be_longest_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/834/FEA/834FEA34BC4C4D3DBB5316BEF0BA8F07_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  longest lunar eclipse, lunar eclipse, moon, blood moon, moon eclipse, astronomy, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640188</guid>
      <title>China wants to track all citizens' cars with RFID chips</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Chinese Communist Party is planning to track all new cars using RFID chips in a voluntary program that begins on July 1, that will become mandatory by 2019.   China's Ministry of Public Security and the ministry's Traffic Management Research Institute is working on the new tracking system, Wall Street Journal reports.Chinese officials claim that windshield RFID chips will help the government study and improve congestion, thereby reducing pollution. Officials claim another goal is to help combat the rise of vehicular terrorist attacks. The system will not be able to locate a car like GPS, and it is unclear how much citizen information will be stored on the chips beyond car color and license plate. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. All news cars by 2019 will need RFID chips installed2. Depiction of an car tag RFID system 3. Car RFID tag system being used to study congestion4. System will collect color and license plate information at the leastVOICEOVER (in English): "The Chinese Communist Party is planning to track all new cars using RFID chips in a voluntary program that begins on July 1, that will become mandatory by 2019."   "According to the Wall Street Journal, China's Ministry of Public Security and the ministry's Traffic Management Research Institute is working on the new tracking system.""Chinese officials claim that windshield RFID chips will help the government study and improve congestion, thereby reducing pollution. Officials claim another goal is to help combat the rise of vehicular terrorist attacks.""The system will not be able to locate a car like GPS, and it is unclear how much citizen information will be stored on the chips beyond car color and license plate." SOURCES: The Vergehttps://www.theverge.com/2018/6/13/17458432/china-surveillance-car-tracking-mandatory-rfid-chips ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 07:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/26/3640188/3640188_0A94E01B81024DA9BA60F10F18475816_180626_3640188_China_wants_to_track_all_citizens__cars_with_RFI_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/84F/330/84F330C732F64D0EA75218ABB5112D90_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China cars RFID, China tracking new cars, China surveillance programs, China car RFID chips, China tracking cars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640925</guid>
      <title>South Korea plans railway linking Korean Peninsula to Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFollowing the successful inter Korean summit, South Korea is now planning to build an extensive network that will connect the Korean Peninsula to Russia via rail.AFP reports that North and South Korea have begun talks about connecting their railways, using existing lines that run from Seoul to Pyongyang, and on to the Chinese border city of Sinuiju.The project also plans to build a separate high-speed railway that would allow trains to go from Seoul to Sinuiju at speeds of up to 350 kilometers per hour, reports Donga.Current North Korea rail infrastructure only allows slow moving trains at less than 50 kph, and will need to be upgraded to handle increased speeds and heavier loads.The completed lines will later connect to Moscow and the rest of the Trans-Siberian railway, ultimately establishing a land route between Europe and the two Koreas.The railway plan is one of the trilateral infrastructure projects between South Korea and Russia, the other two being energy and electricity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of inter Korean railway2. Depiction of planned high-speed rail between Seoul and Sinuiju3. Depiction of North Korean rail infrastructure being upgraded4. Depiction of inter Korean railway connecting to Trans Siberian railwayVOICEOVER (in English): "North and South Korea have begun talks about connecting their railways, using existing lines that run from Seoul to Pyongyang, and on to the Chinese border city of Sinuiju.""The project also plans to build a separate high-speed railway that would allow trains to go from Seoul to Sinuiju at speeds of up to 350 kilometers per hour.""Current North Korea rail infrastructure only allows slow moving trains at less than 50 kph, and will need to be upgraded to handle increased speeds and heavier loads.""The completed lines will later connect to Moscow and the rest of the Trans-Siberian railway, ultimately establishing a land route between Europe and the two Koreas."SOURCES: Telegraph, Donga, AFP (Straits Times)https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/25/south-korea-plans-26bn-rail-link-russia-wake-north-korea-summit/http://news.donga.com/3/all/20180430/89859669/1https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/north-and-south-korea-hold-talks-on-connecting-railways***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 08:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/27/3640925/3640925_E262101B20F04B348BEE0123996BE7B9_180627_3640925_South_Korea_plans_railway_linking_Korean_Peninsu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/5D5/850/5D58505CE5054F85B2D4DF925FD58B3C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, korean rail, inter korean rail, high speed rail, railway, rail link, north korea, south korea, russia, korean peninsula, trans siberian railway, eurasia rail]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640881</guid>
      <title>NSA used AT&amp;T buildings for mass surveillance: Intercept</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. National Security Agency used 8 AT&T facilities across the country as part of a mass surveillance program, according to the Intercept.According to the Intercept, the National Security Agency may be using AT&T buildings across the U.S. as part of a mass surveillance program called FAIRVIEW.The Intercept identified AT&T facilities in Seattle, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Dallas, Atlanta, Chicago, Washington and New York city. The website reports that these locations process AT&T customer data, as well as large amounts of information from other internet providers inside the U.S. and abroad.The FAIRVIEW program, in which AT&T is the sole member, reportedly gives the NSA access to international communications cables, routers and switches.  According to the New York Times, this provided the agency access to billions of metadata records, as well as texts, emails and phone calls.An AT&T spokesperson told the Intercept the company was "required by law to provide information to government and law enforcement".The NSA told the website they couldn't confirm or deny their reporting, but said they are "bound by both policy and law to protect U.S. persons' privacy and civil liberties."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of building locations reported by the Intercept2. Depiction of data cable3. Depiction of NSA surveillance and the world4. Depiction of mass surveillance on a high streetVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Intercept, the National Security Agency may be using AT&T buildings across the U.S. as part of a mass surveillance program called FAIRVIEW.""The Intercept identified AT&T facilities in Seattle, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Dallas, Atlanta, Chicago, Washington and New York city.""The FAIRVIEW program, in which AT&T is the sole member, reportedly gives the NSA access to international communications cables, routers and switches. "This has been reported to provide the agency access to billions of metadata records, as well as texts, emails and phone calls."SOURCES: The Intercept, The Washington Times, CNET, The New York Timeshttps://theintercept.com/2018/06/25/att-internet-nsa-spy-hubs/https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/25/potential-nsa-spying-hub-revealed-dc-t-building/https://www.cnet.com/news/at-t-lets-nsa-hide-and-surveil-in-plain-sight-the-intercept-reports/https://www.nytimes.com/2015/08/16/us/politics/att-helped-nsa-spy-on-an-array-of-internet-traffic.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 07:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/27/3640881/3640881_454966158C33490ABC1474A89458A6A2_180627_3640881_NSA_used_AT_T_buildings_for_mass_surveillance__I_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/523/D31/523D31908A754C11AD92439CAA17DA89_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nsa, mass surveillance, government surveillance, spying, at&t, telecoms, privacy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641786</guid>
      <title>Images show continuing construction at North Korean nuclear facility</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCommercial satellite photos from June 21 show construction continuing at North Korea's Yongbyon Nuclear Scientific Research Center.According to 38 North, images show modifications to the 5 MWe reactor's secondary cooling loop appear to be finished from the outside. However, determining the reactor's operational status was difficult. The status of the Radiochemical Laboratory where the plutonium is separated from spent fuel rods remains uncertain, while the sites Thermal Plant coal bins show usage, suggesting operations there have continued.    Building of support facilities around the Experimental Light Water Reactor, ELWR, also look to be complete externally.Work at the site however, should not be seen as having any relationship with the country's pledge to denuclearize.    According to 38 North, North Korea is expected to proceed with nuclearization until they are given specific orders from Pyongyang. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Yongbyon site 2. The radiochemical laboratory3. The thermal plant4. Support facilities around the ELWRVOICEOVER (in English): "According to 38 North, images show modifications to North Korea's 5 MWe reactor secondary cooling loop appear to be finished from the outside, however determining the reactor's operational status was difficult." "The status of the Radiochemical Laboratory where the plutonium is separated from spent fuel rods remains uncertain, while the sites Thermal Plant coal bins appear to be somewhat depleted, suggesting operations there have continued."    "Construction of support facilities around the Experimental Light Water Reactor also look to be complete externally."SOURCES: 38 North https://www.38north.org/2018/06/yongbyon062618/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 11:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/28/3641786/3641786_D9F4D1A70CEE4EF9A907D94ED93222A9_180628_3641786_Images_show_continuing_construction_at_North_Kor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/4F9/6FA/4F96FAD5F8B54943906D293B7627AD6E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, North Korea, Yongbyon Nuclear Research Facility, North Korea nuclear infrastructure, North Korea nuclear improvements]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641746</guid>
      <title>Search continues for Thai soccer team, coach lost inside cave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHeavy rains and flooding are hampering search and rescue efforts for a young soccer team and their coach, who went missing in northern Thailand.The Bangkok Post reports that a dozen boys aged 11 to 16 and their 25-year-old soccer coach have been missing since going into Chiang Rai's Tham Luang cave on Saturday, June 22.The long cave complex has several chambers which have flooded due to rain. Rescue divers found handprints in one area, but have yet to reach a section of dry ground where the boys are believed to be trapped.High-pressure pumps have been installed inside the cave to drain flooded passages, but persistent rainfall has kept water levels rising.Workers searching for alternative entryways found a vertical shaft that likely lead into the cave, and dropped food and water in case the team was nearby.Authorities are also planning to drill new passageways to speed up the hunt for missing soccer players. They remain hopeful that the team will survive since tourists trapped in the cave during past floods were rescued once the waters receded.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of teen soccer players and coach go missing inside Thai cave2. Depiction of flooded chambers and rescue efforts inside cave system 3. Depiction of water being drained out of flooded chambers4. Depiction of food and water dropped down a vertical shaftVOICEOVER (in English): "A dozen boys aged 11 to 16 and their 25-year-old soccer coach have been missing since going into Chiang Rai's Tham Luang cave on Saturday.""The long cave complex has several chambers which have flooded due to rain. Rescue divers found handprints in one area, but have yet to reach a section of dry ground where the boys are believed to be trapped.""High-pressure pumps have been installed inside the cave to drain flooded passages, but persistent rainfall has kept water levels rising.""Workers searching for alternative entryways found a vertical shaft that likely lead into the cave, and dropped food and water in case the team was nearby."SOURCES: Chiang Rai Times, Bangkok Post, New York Timeshttps://www.chiangraitimes.com/heavy-rains-continue-to-hamper-rescue-operations-for-the-13-missing-footballers-in-tham-luang-cave.htmlhttps://www.bangkokpost.com/news/general/1493358/rescuers-aim-for-safe-haven-in-flooded-cavehttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/27/world/asia/thailand-cave-soccer-search.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 10:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/28/3641746/3641746_A044349200FD476C8BDF92F409991EBC_180628_3641746_Search_continues_for_Thai_soccer_team__coach_los_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/6DF/833/6DF833CBAC474760B3C5D805D745FB73_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Thai cave, missing boys, soccer, football, missing soccer team, missing football team, soccer players, Tham Luang cave, Thailand cave, cave divers, Chiang Rai]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641667</guid>
      <title>Mars to look bigger and brighter from Earth next month</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMars will appear bigger and brighter from Earth in the next few weeks, reports Newsweek.Next month, Mars will be closest it has been to Earth in the past 15 years.The planet will be 35.8 million miles from Earth.It reportedly takes twice the amount of time for Mars, around 687 days, to orbit the sun than it does for Earth. NASA reports that Mars will be in "opposition" at the same time. This means Mars and the Sun will appear on opposite sides of Earth.Mars will be visible to the naked eye, looking like a bright, orange star.Mars will reportedly appear "five times brighter than usual" and spectators will be able to view the planet in the evening sky, which will appear dimmer and dimmer as Earth moves away from Mars.Astronomer Dean Regas, told Newsweek that most of the world, except Alaska, northern Canada, Greenland and Iceland would be able to view the phenomenon next month after sunset.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show Mars getting closer to Earth2. Show Mars and Earth revolving around the Sun3. Show Mars and the Sun on opposite sides 4. Show Mars in the night skyVOICEOVER (in English): "Next month, Mars will be the closest it has been to Earth in the past 15 years. The planet will be 35.8 million miles from Earth.""It takes twice the amount of time for Mars, around 687 days, to orbit the sun than it does for Earth. ""NASA reports that Mars will be in 'opposition' at the same time. This means Mars and the sun will appear on opposite sides of Earth.""Mars will reportedly appear 'five times brighter than usual' and spectators will be able to view the planet in the evening sky, which will appear increasingly dimmer as Earth moves away from Mars."SOURCES: NASA,Newsweek, Space.comhttps://mars.nasa.gov/allaboutmars/nightsky/opposition/http://www.newsweek.com/mars-appear-larger-brighter-it-has-15-years-next-month-981824https://www.space.com/40724-summer-of-mars-2018.htmlhttps://www.space.com/40588-mars-at-opposition.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 08:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/28/3641667/3641667_3A52ECD53BCF402AB012EC1DA2DA2D01_180628_3641667_Mars_to_look_bigger_and_brighter_from_Earth_next_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/691/8BA/6918BAF589E04D3BB48AB3EB252016E2_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Mars, Earth, Mars and Earth in opposition, Brighter and larger Mars, Astronomy, Space, Space exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642784</guid>
      <title>JAXA space probe arrives near asteroid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Japanese space probe has reached its destination after travelling through space for three years.The Hayabusa 2 spacecraft blasted off in December 2014, Reuters reports. This week it arrived at its destination, Asteroid Ryugu, some 3 billion kilometers from Earth.Reuters reports Hayabusa 2 will orbit the asteroid for a few months in order to map its surface before it attempts a landing. The probe will use explosives and a cannon to craft a hole the surface, then collect from samples from the area.After the Hayabusa 2 has finished its work on the asteroid, the probe will begin a year-and-a-half journey back to Earth. It's expected to return in 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Hayabusa-2 flight path2. Depiction of Hayabusa-2 near asteroid and mapping it3. Depiction of Hayabusa-2 collecting samples4. Depiction of Hayabusa-2 coming back to Earth VOICEOVER (in English): "Reuters reports the Hayabusa 2 spacecraft blasted off in December 2014.""This week it arrived at its destination, Asteroid Ryugu, some 3 billion kilometers from Earth.""Reuters reports Hayabusa 2 will orbit the asteroid for a few months in order to map its surface before it attempts a landing.""The probe will use explosives and a cannon to craft a hole the surface, then collect from samples from the area.""After the Hayabusa 2 has finished its work on the asteroid, the probe will begin a year-and-a-half journey back to Earth. It's expected to return in 2020."SOURCES: JAXA, Reuters, Space http://global.jaxa.jphttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-japan-probe/japan-probe-arrives-at-asteroid-after-nearly-four-year-space-odyssey-idUSKBN1JN0F1https://www.space.com/41014-japanese-hayabusa2-probe-arrives-asteroid-ryugu.htmlhttps://www.space.com/23320-japan-test-fires-space-cannon-hayabusa2.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 14:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/29/3642784/3642784_9295CCAD4B904DD7B75FDC7833C9CF18_180629_3642784_JAXA_space_probe_arrives_near_asteroid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/815/892/815892C57232475A8243B0C1D753818D_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, jaxa, space probe, hayabusa-2, hayabusa, space mission, science, ryugu asteroid, asteroids, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642572</guid>
      <title>Gunman kills five in Maryland newsroom shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFive people are dead and many others injured after a man with targeted a newspaper office in Maryland.The Baltimore Sun reports that a suspect wielding a shotgun and smoke grenades shot through the glass doors of the Capital Gazette office around 2:40 p.m. on Thursday.According to one witness, he opened fire on several people, killing two women and three men, and injuring at least three others.Employees reportedly hid under their desks during the deadly incident and pleaded for help on social media.Police arrived within a minute of the shooting, surrounding the gunman and taking him into custody. Civilians were escorted out of the building soon after.The shooter was later identified as 38-year-old Jarrod Ramos, a local with a long-standing grudge against the Capital Gazette. He previously sued the paper for defamation, but lost after failing to prove that what the paper published about him was RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of gunman shooting glass office doors2. Depiction of shooter gunning down newspaper employees3. Depiction of employees hiding under desks4. Depiction of police apprehending suspectVOICEOVER (in English): "A suspect wielding a shotgun and smoke grenades shot through the glass doors of the Capital Gazette office around 2:40 p.m. on Thursday.""According to one witness, he opened fire on several people, killing two women and three men, and injuring at least three others.""Employees reportedly hid under their desks during the deadly incident and asked for help over social media.""Police arrived within a minute of the shooting, surrounding the gunman and taking him into custody. Civilians were escorted out of the building soon after."SOURCES: Baltimore Sun, NBChttp://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/crime/bs-md-gazette-shooting-20180628-story.htmlhttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/suspect-maryland-newspaper-shooting-had-sued-capital-gazette-defamation-n887626***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 10:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/29/3642572/3642572_555E119C5E764D59831F454E20C8AB34_180629_3642572_Gunman_kills_five_in_Maryland_newsroom_shooting_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A2C/4F7/A2C4F79A83DE4AB492342617474319AF_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, shooting, gunman, capital gazette, capital gazette shooting, newsroom shooting, newspaper office, vendetta, grudge, defamation suit, jarrod ramos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642556</guid>
      <title>Animals becoming nocturnal to avoid humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLike the dinosaurs millions of years ago, humans are now the planet's super predator, and it's driving all other wildlife to take the night shift.In a new study published in the journal Science, researchers from the University of California, Berkeley analyzed previous studies that captured the 24-hour movements of over 62 medium to large-bodied mammal species across six continents.They found that human disruption made animals 1.36 times more nocturnal on average, meaning those that typically split activities evenly between day and night became 68% more active at night.Human disturbance in this case wasn't just limited to destructive behavior. Even activities like hiking, farming, or wildlife-viewing evoked the same behavioral pattern.The consequences are potentially negative. Animals that lack the traits to thrive nocturnally become vulnerable to non-human predators, affecting their chances at survival and reproduction.Scientists have already noticed some of these changes. Coyotes in California's Santa Cruz Mountains have begun hunting at night to avoid hikers, forgoing their usual daytime prey of squirrels and birds for nocturnal rats and rabbits.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study encompasses 62 mammal species across 6 continents2. Depiction of animals being more nocturnal3. Depiction of all types of human disturbance making wildlife nocturnal4. Depiction of potentially negative consequencesVOICEOVER (in English): "UC Berkeley researchers analyzed previous studies that captured the 24-hour movements of over 62 medium to large-bodied mammal species in six continents.""They found that human disruption made animals 1.36 times more nocturnal on average, meaning those that typically split activities evenly between day and night became 68% more active at night.""Human disturbance in this case wasn't just limited to destructive behavior. Even activities like hiking, farming, or wildlife-viewing evoked the same behavioral pattern.""The consequences are potentially negative. Animals that lack the traits to thrive nocturnally become vulnerable to non-human predators, affecting their chances at survival and reproduction."SOURCES: University of California Berkeley, Scientific American, The New York Timeshttps://nature.berkeley.edu/human-disturbance-creates-more-nocturnal-natural-worldhttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/humans-are-driving-other-mammals-to-become-more-nocturnal/https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/15/science/animals-human-nocturnal-study.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 10:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/06/29/3642556/3642556_22A1C48844904E3BA79ECFD9B4B75415_180629_3642556_Animals_becoming_nocturnal_to_avoid_humans_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A41/77D/A4177D17D3B44BDF98769E08DDA092C7_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nocturnal animals, fear of humans, animals going nocturnal, nocturnal wildlife, nocturnal, diurnal, animals avoiding humans, human disturbance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
