<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 11:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>4004253</guid>
      <title>Seemingly recovered COVID-19 patients still have viral RNA in fecal matter: new study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHealth authorities might be able to detect COVID-19's spread by testing the sewers of a community for the coronavirus's RNA.Citing a new study in Gastroenterology, British Columbia Centre of Disease Control told the CBC that wastewater testing could be an early warning system for community transmission.According to a research team from China's Guangdong Province, traces of SARS-CoV-2's RNA have been found in the stool samples of hospitalized patients. The study involved 73 patients of both genders whose ages ranged from 10 months to 78 years old. Stool samples of 39 patients, or 53 percent, tested positive for the coronavirus RNA.Additionally, some patients started testing negative for the virus in respiratory samples, even as their stool samples continued to show positive results. Endoscopy indicated that the 17 patients, or 23 percent of the total, were still infected and that they may have been able to infect others via fecal-oral transmission.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Wastewater tests may help detect COVID-19 communal transmission 2. Novel coronavirus RNA found in patients' stool sample3. Virus RNA found in more than 50 percent of 73 hospitalized patients 4. Patients can show negative results in respiratory tests but positive in stool testsVOICEOVER (in English): "Health authorities might be able to detect COVID-19's spread by testing the sewers of a community for the coronavirus's RNA.""Citing a new study in Gastroenterology, British Columbia Centre of Disease Control told the CBC that wastewater testing could be an early warning system for community transmission.""According to a research team from China's Guangdong Province, traces of SARS-CoV-2's RNA have been found in the stool samples of hospitalized patients.""The study involved 73 patients of both genders whose ages ranged from 10 months to 78 years old.""Stool samples of 39 patients, or 53 percent, tested positive for the coronavirus RNA.""Additionally, some patients started testing negative for the virus in respiratory samples, even as their stool samples continued to show positive results." "Endoscopy indicated that the 17 patients, or 23 percent of the total, were still infected and that they may have been able to infect others via fecal-oral transmission."SOURCES: Gastroenterology, CBC Newshttps://www.gastrojournal.org/article/S0016-5085(20)30282-1/pdfhttps://www.cbc.ca/news/health/covid-19-wastewater-1.5590882***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 09:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/01/4004253/4004253_57E79848AD2644F1BB9CFF373D50D6B9_200601_4004253_Seemingly_recovered_COVID_19_patients_still_have_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, COVID-19, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, stool test, stool tests, viral RNA, oral-fecal transmission, wastewater testing, wastewater tests, sewage testing, sewage tests, Sun Yat-sen University, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004211</guid>
      <title>Mysterious weak spot in the Earth's magnetic field is spreading: ESA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA mysterious anomaly in the Earth's magnetic field that stretches from South America to Africa is spreading and scientists do not understand why.New data from the European Space Agency's SWARM constellation of satellites show that a weak spot in the Earth's magnetic field known as the South Atlantic Anomaly has been growing in size since 1970 and may possibly be developing a second cell centered above the coast of southwest Africa.The Earth's magnetic field, which is generated by the dynamo action of its molten metal core, protects the planet from the full impact of solar and cosmic radiation. According to the ESA, over the last two centuries, the global magnetic field has lost 9 percent of its strength on a global average.For now, the most significant effect of the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly is interference with satellites and spacecraft that pass over the region. However, the Earth's magnetic field destabilizes and reconstitutes itself over geological time, with sometimes even the north and south magnetic poles trading places.According to the ESA, it is not clear what is causing the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly, but it could be related to the African Large Low Shear Velocity Province, one of two giant underground masses of rock that float like hidden continents where the Earth's mantle meets the outer core.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. South Atlantic Anomaly and emergence of a possible second cell on a map2. Earth's magnetic field is generated by the dynamo action of its molten metal core3. Earth's magnetic field protects the planet from solar and cosmic radiation4. Satellite in orbit over Earth5. African Large Low Shear Velocity Province and Pacific Large Low Shear Velocity ProvinceVOICEOVER (in English): "New data from the European Space Agency's SWARM constellation of satellites show that a weak spot in the Earth's magnetic field known as the South Atlantic Anomaly has been growing in size since 1970 and may possibly be developing a second cell centered above the coast of southwest Africa.""The Earth's magnetic field, which is generated by the dynamo action of its molten metal core, protects the planet from the full impact of solar and cosmic radiation. According to the ESA, over the last two centuries, the global magnetic field has lost 9 percent of its strength on a global average.""For now, the most significant effect of the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly is interference with satellites and spacecraft that pass over the region. However, the Earth's magnetic field destabilizes and reconstitutes itself over geological time, with sometimes even the north and south magnetic poles trading places.""According to the ESA, it is not clear what is causing the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly, but it could be related to the African Large Low Shear Velocity Province, one of two giant underground masses of rock that float like hidden continents where the Earth's mantle meets the outer core."SOURCES: European Space Agency, Geophysical Journal Internationalhttps://www.esa.int/Applications/Observing_the_Earth/Swarm/Swarm_probes_weakening_of_Earth_s_magnetic_fieldhttps://academic.oup.com/gji/article/207/2/1122/2583772***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/01/4004211/4004211_AA8DC149AD67476D8901530EDFE36B09_200601_4004211_Mysterious_weak_spot_in_the_Earth_s_magnetic_fie_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, South Atlantic Anomaly, magnetic field, electromagnetic field, solar wind, radiation, European Space Agency, ESA, SWARM, satellite, African Large Low Shear Velocity Province, magnetic pole]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004452</guid>
      <title>Gum inflammation triggered by vaping may lead to gum diseases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of researchers has found unhealthy bacteria and inflammation in the gums of e-cigarette smokers that could lead to more severe gum diseases. Research published in the journal Science Advances found that the gums of healthy individuals who used e-cigarettes contained damaging bacteria and showed signs of gum disease.The team of specialists studied the gums of 123 individuals. 25 of them were smokers, another 25 were non-smokers, 20 used e-cigarettes, 25 were former smokers who used e-cigarettes and 28 were both cigarette and e-cigarette smokers.Results showed that e-cigarette use causes a change in the microbial landscape of the gums, making its healthy bacteria unrecognizable to our immune system. This then triggers an inflammatory response in the gums and coats healthy bacteria with a layer of slime.This phenomenon was observed even in those using non-nicotine e-cigarettes. This  caused the team of researchers to believe that the liquid in electronic cigarettes could be triggering this phenomenon.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. E-cigarette smoke causing gum disease 2. Study participants3. Healthy bacteria in the mouth become coated with slime due to e-cigarette smoke4. Non-nicotine e-cigarettes also affect gum tissueVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in the journal Science Advances found that the gums of healthy individuals who used e-cigarettes contained damaging bacteria and showed signs of gum disease.""The team of specialists studied the gums of 123 individuals. 25 of them were smokers, another 25 were non-smokers, 20 used e-cigarettes, 25 were former smokers who used e-cigarettes and 28 were both cigarette and e-cigarette smokers.""Results showed that e-cigarette use causes a change in the microbial landscape of the gums, making its healthy bacteria unrecognizable to our immune system. This then triggers an inflammatory response in the gums and coats healthy bacteria with a layer of slime.""This phenomenon was observed even in those using non-nicotine e-cigarettes. This  caused the team of researchers to believe that the liquid in electronic cigarettes could be triggering this phenomenon."SOURCES: Science Advances, Ohio State Newshttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/22/eaaz0108https://news.osu.edu/a-few-months-of-vaping-puts-healthy-people-on-the-brink-of-oral-disease/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 03:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/02/4004452/4004452_FC7D5D443A39409BA140670600A1356B_200602_4004452_Gum_inflammation_triggered_by_vaping_may_lead_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  E-cigarettes, vaping, vape, vaping illness, gum disease, electronic cigarettes, oral microbiome, oral disease, gum disease, inflammatory response]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005044</guid>
      <title>Novel coronavirus could be a hybrid of bat and pangolin viruses: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, could be a hybrid that descended from different clades of bat and pangolin viruses, according to new research in Science Advances.Writing in a news release, the team says the bat virus RaTG13 is the closest genetic relative to SARS-CoV-2, with a 96.3 percent RNA similarity. However, the bat virus does not have the spike protein parts used by SARS-CoV-2 for infecting humans.Yet another close relative, a clade of SARS-like pangolin virus from China, has receptor-binding domains that closely match the corresponding parts of the novel coronavirus.The bat and pangolin viruses likely recombined to form SARS-CoV-2. Recombining may occur when two similar viruses infect the same cell. When this happens, molecules that made up the distinct viruses are reshuffled into a new pathogen.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SARS-CoV-2 could be a hybrid of bat and pangolin viruses2. Bat virus RaTG13 is the closest genetic relative to SARS-CoV-23. Pangolin SARS-like virus possesses similar spike proteins to SARS-CoV-24. Recombination of bat and pangolin viruses in a cell produces SARS-CoV-2VOICEOVER (in English): "SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, could be a hybrid that descended from different clades of bat and pangolin viruses, according to new research in Science Advances.""Writing in a news release, the team says the bat virus RaTG13 is the closest genetic relative to SARS-CoV-2, with a 96.3 percent RNA similarity. However, the bat virus does not have the spike protein parts used by SARS-CoV-2 for infecting humans.""Yet another close relative, a clade of SARS-like pangolin virus from China, has receptor-binding domains that closely match the corresponding parts of the novel coronavirus.""The bat and pangolin viruses likely recombined to form SARS-CoV-2. Recombining may occur when two similar viruses infect the same cell. When this happens, molecules that made up the distinct viruses are reshuffled into a new pathogen."SOURCES: Science Advances, Duke Universityhttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/early/2020/05/28/sciadv.abb9153https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/05/200529161221.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/03/4005044/4005044_0B232EF2403F4BF4848DD447589A50BF_200603_4005044_Novel_coronavirus_could_be_a_hybrid_of_bat_and_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004884</guid>
      <title>Proxima Centauri B is officially the exoplanet closest to our solar system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of specialists from the University of Geneva has confirmed the existence of an exoplanet orbiting in the habitable zone of a neighboring sun. Researchers have confirmed the presence of Proxima Centauri B, an exoplanet that orbits in the habitable zone of the star closest to our sun, Proxima Centauri, according to a report published in the journal Astronomy and Astrophysics.Researchers from the University of Geneva were able to confirm its existence by using a new generation spectrograph located in Chile called ESPRESSO.Their observations showed that Proxima B is 1.17 times the mass of Earth and orbits its sun in 11.2 days.Proxima B receives similar energy from its sun and could, therefore, harbor life. However, this exoplanet's sun is an active red dwarf and it hits the exoplanet with roughly 400 times the amount of X-rays that Earth receives.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of Proxima Centauri2. Visualization of the ESPRESSO spectrometer3. Comparison to Earth with Proxima Centauri B4. X-rays from Proxima Centauri sun hitting Proxima B planetVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers have confirmed the presence of Proxima Centauri B, an exoplanet that orbits in the habitable zone of the star closest to our sun, Proxima Centauri, according to a report published in the journal Astronomy and Astrophysics.""Researchers from the University of Geneva were able to confirm its existence by using a new generation spectrograph located in Chile called ESPRESSO.""Their observations showed that Proxima B is 1.17 times the mass of Earth and orbits its sun in 11.2 days.""Proxima B receives similar energy from its sun and could, therefore, harbor life. However, this exoplanet's sun is an active red dwarf and it hits the exoplanet with roughly 400 times the amount of X-rays that Earth receives."SOURCES: Journal of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Phys.orghttps://arxiv.org/pdf/2005.12114v1.pdfhttps://phys.org/news/2020-05-espresso-presence-earth-nearest-star.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 05:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/03/4004884/4004884_DA84B70581B941888476AC38B0A60126_200603_4004884_Proxima_Centauri_B_is_officially_the_exoplanet_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Proxima b, proxima centauri, space, Earth-like planet proxima b, TomoNews, ESPRESSO, earth sized planet, exo planet, new planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005327</guid>
      <title>New Ebola Outbreak Detected in the Democratic Republic of the Congo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo has confirmed the deaths of five individuals who were infected with Ebola.Citing authorities in the Democratic Republic of Congo, the United Nations Children's Fund reports that a new Ebola outbreak has occurred in the country's city of Mbandaka. This is the eleventh outbreak in the country since the virus's discovery in 1976.Nine individuals are reported to have been infected. Five of them have died. The individuals died between the 18th and 30th of May but were confirmed to be Ebola-related yesterday.The virus's incubation period lasts from 2 to 21 days. Symptoms of the Ebola virus include fever, headache, muscle pain and fatigue. These symptoms are followed up by vomiting and diarrhea.Ebola is passed on by human-to-human transmission. Individuals can be infected if they come in contact with sweat, mucous, saliva, blood, or other body fluids of infected people.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of new Ebola outbreak2. Number of infected and deaths3. Ebola virus symptoms4. Ebola virus transmissionVOICEOVER (in English): "Citing authorities in the Democratic Republic of Congo, the United Nations Children's Fund reports that a new Ebola outbreak has occurred in the country's city of Mbandaka. This is the eleventh outbreak in the country since the virus's discovery in 1976.""Nine individuals are reported to have been infected. Five of them have died. The individuals died between the 18th and 30th of May but were confirmed to be Ebola-related yesterday.""The virus's incubation period lasts from 2 to 21 days. Symptoms of the Ebola virus include fever, headache, muscle pain and fatigue. These symptoms are followed up by vomiting and diarrhea.""Ebola is passed on by human-to-human transmission. Individuals can be infected if they come in contact with sweat, mucous, saliva, blood, or other body fluids of infected people."SOURCES: UNICEF, WHOhttps://www.unicef.org/press-releases/ebola-resurfaces-%C3%A9quateur-province-north-western-democratic-republic-congohttps://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/ebola-virus-disease***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 06:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/04/4005327/4005327_16B723C06B8E442EA87C581903CADAC1_200604_4005327_New_Ebola_Outbreak_Detected_in_the_Democratic_Re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media,, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ebola virus, virus, viral outbreak, Congo, West Africa, ebola outbreak, congo ebola outbreak, ebola outbreak in congo,ebola outbreak news, ebola outbreak congo, health, world, news, world news, conflict, humanitarian agencies, Congo, infectious diseases, disease, illness, healthcare, united nations, world health organization.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005779</guid>
      <title>Scientists create human cells with squid-like transparency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have engineered color-shifting abilities into human cells. Researchers say their project is inspired by female opalescent inshore squids that evade predators by changing their colors from translucent to opaque white.According to the study in Nature Communications, squids and octopuses can cloak because their skin contains leucophore cells, which includes protein molecules called reflectins. This substance scatters light and creates an iridescent camouflage.In a news release, the scientists say they took human embryonic kidney cells and introduced genes that express reflectin. These cells are then cultured and examined under a microscope.The study's co-author was cited as saying the cells grew ball-shaped nanostructures throughout the cell bodies, and the spheres contain reflectin molecules. This means the reflectin behaved optically as if they were in squids.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Opalescent inshore squids use light scattering abilities to evade predators 2. Optical camouflage properties come from reflectins in squid cells3. Research team add reflectin expressing genes to human cells4. Cultured human cells grew reflectins packaged in nanospheresVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have engineered color-shifting abilities into human cells. Researchers say their project is inspired by female opalescent inshore squids that evade predators by changing their colors from translucent to opaque white.""According to the study in Nature Communications, squids and octopuses can cloak because their skin contains leucophore cells, which includes protein molecules called reflectins. This substance scatters light and creates an iridescent camouflage.""In a news release, the scientists say they took human embryonic kidney cells and introduced genes that express reflectin. These cells are then cultured and examined under a microscope." "The study's co-author was cited as saying the cells grew ball-shaped nanostructures throughout the cell bodies, and the spheres contain reflectin molecules. This means the reflectins behaved optically as if they were in squids."SOURCES:  Nature Communications, Phys.orghttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-020-16151-6https://phys.org/news/2020-06-scientists-human-cells-squid-like-transparency.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 07:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/05/4005779/4005779_C8DC3A4DAE044301BAA7B31A00575054_200605_4005779_Scientists_create_human_cells_with_squid_like_tr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, squid-inspired, squid-like transparency, translucent squid, translucent squids, offshore squid, offshore squids, optical camouflage, light scattering, biotechnology, genetic engineering, reflectin, reflectins, nanostructure, human cells, human cells, University of California Irvine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005729</guid>
      <title>A Fossil of a Rare Dinosaur has Been Identified in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFive years after the discovery of a pterosaur fossil, a PhD student in Australia noticed that it had been mislabeled and that it actually belonged to a rare dinosaur called Elaphrosaurus. Paleontologists at Australia's Swinburne University of Technology discovered they had mistakenly identified a fossil as the bone of an ancient flying reptile called pterosaur, but it actually belonged to a rare dinosaur called elaphrosaur. This is the first elaphrosaur found in Australia.Citing Stephen Poropat, the lead author of the study, The Guardian reports that only three other elaphrosaurs species have been found in Tanzania, China and Argentina.The elaphrosaur was part of the theropod family, which includes predators like the Tyrannosaurus Rex and velociraptors. It was roughly as tall as a small Emu and measures 2 meters from its head to the end of its tail."According to the research published in the journal Gondwana Research, the elaphrosaur the team discovered lived during the cretaceous period. At this time, Australia's land was located in the Arctic Circle.Researchers believe that the elaphrosaurs may have lived in a habitat containing a diverse variety of plants and trees such as conifers, gingkos, ferns, horsetails, conifers, and flowering plants.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of the excavation site2. Length and height of the elaphrosaur3. Habitat of elaphrosaur during the cretaceous period 4. Close-up of the elaphrosaur's habitatVOICEOVER (in English): "Paleontologists at Australia's Swinburne University of Technology discovered they had mistakenly identified a fossil as the bone of an ancient flying reptile called pterosaur, but it actually belonged to a rare dinosaur called elaphrosaur. This is the first elaphrosaur found in Australia.""The elaphrosaur was part of the theropod family, which includes predators like the Tyrannosaurus Rex and velociraptors. It was roughly as tall as a small Emu and measures 2 meters from its head to the end of its tail.""According to the research published in the journal Gondwana Research, the elaphrosaur the team discovered lived during the cretaceous period. At this time, Australia's land was located in the Arctic Circle.""Researchers believe that the elaphrosaurs may have lived in a habitat containing a diverse variety of plants and trees such as conifers, gingkos, ferns, horsetails, conifers, and flowering plants."SOURCES: Gondwana Research, The Guardian, Phys.orghttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1342937X20301234?via%3Dihubhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/may/18/rare-long-necked-dinosaur-that-roamed-the-polar-world-unearthed-in-australiahttps://phys.org/news/2020-05-australia-elaphrosaur-victoria.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 05:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/06/05/4005729/4005729_D4100CB8B29E420BB7E965B74C9AAB1F_200605_4005729_A_Fossil_of_a_Rare_Dinosaur_has_Been_Identified__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, elaphrosaur, Swinburne University of Technology, dinosaurs, dinos, fossil, dinosaur fossil]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
