<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3869461</guid>
      <title>Japan approves human-animal embryo experiments</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan has become the first country to greenlight a controversial experiment involving hybrid human-animal embryos.According to Nature magazine, experts at Japan's Science Ministry have approved a University of Tokyo proposal to grow human stem cells in mouse, rat, and pig embryos, and transplant them into surrogate animals.Lead researcher Hiromitsu Nakauchi says the goal is to create animals with human organs than can then be used for transplants.The proposal is the first one approved since Japan lifted a ban in March on developing animal embryos with human cells beyond 14 days, and bringing them to term.Nakauchi told Nature that they will be creating animal embryos that lack a gene to produce certain organs. Once injected with human induced pluripotent stem cells or IPS cells, the embryo will use the IPS cells to make the organ.He says he plans to grow mouse embryos for 14.5 days until they are almost to term. Rats will be grown to near term for 15.5 days, and pigs for up to 70 days.Nakauchi's 2017 experiment saw him and his team successfully cure a diabetic mouse by growing a healthy new mouse pancreas using a rat embryo.Science Alert reports that while the treatment is meant to target only the organ being grown, the experiment will be suspended if the team detects more than 30% of the animal's brain to be human.This is one of the Japanese government's conditions, in order to prevent humanized animals from coming into existence.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Stem cells grown in mouse, rat, pig embryos to produce human organs for transplants2. Human IPS cells injected into genetically modified animal embryo3. Mouse pancreas grown in rat embryo during 2017 experiment 4. Experiment to be suspended if over 30% of brain detected to be humanVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Nature magazine, experts at Japan's Science Ministry have approved a University of Tokyo proposal to grow human stem cells in mouse, rat, and pig embryos, and transplant them into surrogate animals.""Lead researcher Hiromitsu Nakauchi says the goal is to create animals with human organs than can then be used for transplants.""Nakauchi told Nature that they will be creating animal embryos that lack a gene to produce certain organs. Once injected with human induced pluripotent stem cells or IPS cells, the embryo will use the IPS cells to make the organ.""He says he plans to grow mouse embryos for 14.5 days until they are almost to term. Rats will be grown to near term for 15.5 days, and pigs for up to 70 days.""Nakauchi's 2017 experiment saw him and his team successfully cure a diabetic mouse by growing a healthy new mouse pancreas using a rat embryo.""Science Alert reports that while the treatment is meant to target only the organ being grown, the experiment will be suspended if the team detects more than 30% of the animal's brain to be human."SOURCES: Nature, Science Alerthttps://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-02275-3https://www.sciencealert.com/japan-just-gave-approval-for-scientists-to-work-on-human-animal-embryo-experiments***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 10:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/02/3869461/3869461_279299EC142C4C3DB96AE74EB6825440_190802_3869461_Japan_approves_human_animal_embryo_experiments_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, human animal hybrid, mutant embryos, hybrid embryos, mutant experiments, hybrid experiments, human animal experiments, human animal hybrid experiments, stem cell research, stem cell experiment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3869353</guid>
      <title>Plastic consumption turning seabirds smaller, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the University of Tasmania has found that seabirds are becoming smaller in size due to their consumption of plastic.Researchers analyzed the flesh-footed shearwaters on Lord Howe Island, Australia and found that their wings and bills had become shorter.The study was published in the journal Environmental Science & Technology. It found that plastic had caused the birds to have a lower body mass and decreased kidney function.Jennifer Lavers, lead author of the study, explained in a university news release that they took blood samples from the seabirds and found that the birds had a higher cholesterol, a higher concentration of uric acid as well as reduced blood calcium levels.According to the researchers, the consumption of plastic is resulting in a decline of the flesh-footed shearwaters as they are feeding their offspring tiny pieces of plastic, instead of fish.In the news release, Lavers said their research suggested that any amount of plastic ingestion is enough to have an impact on the health of an individual.The number of seabirds who die every year from eating plastic waste is estimated to be around 1 million, according to a United Nations Ocean conference factsheet from 2017.Seabirds mistakenly consume plastic as it looks and smells like food and floats on the surface of the water, according to the World Wild Fund for Nature Australia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flesh-footed shearwaters consuming plastic2. The effects of plastic on flesh-footed shearwaters bodies3. What researchers found in blood samples taken from the seabirds4. Why researchers believe the population of flesh-footed shearwaters are in declineVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the University of Tasmania has found that seabirds are becoming smaller in size due to their consumption of plastic.""Researchers analyzed the flesh-footed shearwaters on Lord Howe Island, Australia and found that their wings and bills had become shorter.""The study was published in the journal Environmental Science & Technology. It found that plastic had caused the birds to have a lower body mass and decreased kidney function.""Jennifer Lavers, lead author of the study, explained in a university news release that they took blood samples from the seabirds and found that the birds had a higher cholesterol, a higher concentration of uric acid as well as reduced blood calcium levels.""According to the researchers, the consumption of plastic is resulting in a decline of the flesh-footed shearwaters as they are feeding their offspring tiny pieces of plastic, instead of fish."SOURCES:  CNN, University of Tasmania, Environmental Science & Technology, Science Daily, World Wild Fund for Nature Australia, United Nations https://edition.cnn.com/2019/07/30/health/seabirds-plastic-pollution-health-problems-scli-intl/index.htmlhttp://www.imas.utas.edu.au/__data/assets/pdf_file/0003/1253847/Seabird-plastic-ingestion-Jennifer-Lavers-MR.pdfhttps://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.est.9b02098https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/07/190730092638.htmhttps://www.wwf.org.au/news/blogs/how-many-birds-die-from-plastic-pollutionhttps://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/content/documents/Ocean_Factsheet_Pollution.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 08:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/02/3869353/3869353_2C6DC0F789DB4ABF9774D2FBAAE0F55C_190802_3869353_Plastic_consumption_turning_seabirds_smaller__st_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic pollution, seabirds, plastic pollution seabirds, plastic pollution animation, plastic pollution animals, animals suffering from plastic pollution, seabirds getting smaller]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3869327</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy jet crashes in Death Valley National Park</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn F/A-18E Super Hornet fighter jet has crashed in Death Valley National Park.The aircraft was flying over Death Valley National Park during a routine training exercise on July 31 at approximately 10:00 a.m. local time when it crashed near the Naval Air Weapons Station China Lake, according to a tweet from the U.S. Naval Air Forces. Death Valley National Park spokesman Patrick Taylor told CNN that the crash caused seven visitors to suffer minor injuries. Taylor explained that this particular area of the park is known as Stars Wars Canyon and is a popular site for visitors to observe military training flights.In a statement to the United States Naval Institute News, the Navy said search and rescue units were sent to the scene. The pilot's status is currently unknown and the cause of the accident is under investigation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The fighter jet in the sky2. The aircraft crashing3. Victims of the jet crash4. Spectators watching training military jetsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a tweet from the U.S. Naval Air Forces, an F/A-18E Super Hornet fighter jet was flying over Death Valley National Park on July 31 at approximately 10:00 a.m. local time.""The jet was undergoing a routine training exercise when it crashed near the Naval Air Weapons Station China Lake.""Death Valley National Park spokesman Patrick Taylor told CNN that the crash caused seven visitors to suffer minor injuries.""Taylor explained that this particular area of the park is known as Stars Wars Canyon and is a popular site for visitors to observe military training flights."SOURCES: CNN, NPR, U.S. Naval Air Forces, CBS News, United States Naval Institute, ABC 10 News  https://edition.cnn.com/2019/07/31/politics/navy-jet-crash-california/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/2019/07/31/747093070/u-s-military-jet-crashes-in-death-valley-national-park-injuring-7-on-the-groundhttps://twitter.com/flynavy/status/1156634093322268674https://www.cbsnews.com/news/navy-fighter-jet-crashes-california-death-valley-national-park-live-updates-today-2019-07-31/https://news.usni.org/2019/07/31/california-super-hornet-crashes-near-china-lake-condition-of-pilot-unknownhttps://www.10news.com/news/navy-fighter-jet-crashes-in-central-california-search-underway-for-pilot***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 08:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/02/3869327/3869327_6C819AD2664047F895C5776EF59FD86B_190802_3869327_U_S__Navy_jet_crashes_in_Death_Valley_National_P_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  us navy, us military,  military jet crashes, military jet crashes in national park, us navy jet crashes, f/a-18 jets, f/a-18 fighter jets,  f/a-18 navy fighter jets, f/a-18 fighter jet crashes, us navy f/a-18E Super Hornet jet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870827</guid>
      <title>Church of the Apostles may have been unearthed near Sea of Galilee</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArchaeologists have discovered an early Christian church rumored to be built over the house of the apostles Peter and Andrew.According to a press release from the Center for the Study of Ancient Judaism and Christian Origins, a large church from the Byzantine period has been unearthed at Beit Habek, near the northern shore of the Sea of Galilee.Archaeologists believe the structure is the Church of the Apostles, which Christian tradition indicates was built over the home of Jesus' disciples Peter and Andrew in the village of Bethsaida.A Bavarian bishop named Willibald had written about the church in 725 C.E., having seen it while traveling from Capernaum to Kursi.According to the press release, the church is part of a monastery complex, but only the southern rooms have been excavated.So far, the team has uncovered ornate mosaic tiles, marble fragments from a chancel screen, and a fragment of a chalk carving showing a cross.They also unearthed a Roman-period home about 100 meters north of the main excavation area, which contained Jewish stone vessels, oil lamps, and over 20 Roman-era coins and lead fishing weights.R. Steven Notley, a New Testament professor at Nyack College who blogged about the excavation, says the archaeologists have been digging at the site for four years, and will need another year to completely excavate the remains of the church. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Remains of church unearthed near Sea of Galilee2. Church of the Apostles built over home of apostles Peter and Andrew3. Parts of the church that have been excavated4. Roman-period house unearthed near church excavation siteVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a press release from the Center for the Study of Ancient Judaism and Christian Origins, a large church from the Byzantine period has been unearthed at Beit Habek, near the northern shore of the Sea of Galilee.""Archaeologists believe the structure is the Church of the Apostles, which Christian tradition indicates was built over the home of Jesus' disciples Peter and Andrew in the village of Bethsaida.""A Bavarian bishop named Willibald had written about the church in 725 C.E., having seen it while traveling from Capernaum to Kursi.""According to the press release, the church is part of a monastery complex, but only the southern rooms have been excavated.""So far, the team has uncovered ornate mosaic tiles, marble fragments from a chancel screen, and a fragment of a chalk carving showing a cross.""They also unearthed a Roman-period home about 100 meters north of the main excavation area, which contained Jewish stone vessels, oil lamps, and over 20 Roman-era coins and lead fishing weights."SOURCES: Haaretz, Center for the Study of Ancient Judaism and Christian Originshttps://www.haaretz.com/archaeology/.premium.MAGAZINE-archaeologists-claim-to-have-found-the-church-of-the-apostles-by-sea-of-galilee-1.7538758https://www.csajco.orghttps://www.prnewswire.com/il/news-releases/the-church-of-the-apostles-discovered-at-bethsaida-says-csajco-300888229.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 11:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/05/3870827/3870827_988CAA5F815E45178A9074923ABE932D_190805_3870827_Church_of_the_Apostles_may_have_been_unearthed_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, church of the apostles, sea of galilee, ancient church, byzantine church, Bethsaida, ancient christian church, early christian church, jesus, apostles, peter's house, peter and andrew's house, apostle's house, apostle house, biblical archaeology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870555</guid>
      <title>North Korea conducts third missile test in eight days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea has launched additional unidentified short-range projectiles on August 2.According to a statement from South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff, the missiles were launched at 2:59 a.m. and 3:23 a.m. from Yonghung in South Hamgyong Province. Both landed in the Sea of Japan.The statement didn't mention the exact number of missiles that were fired.This is the third time North Korea has fired projectiles in the past eight days, according to Reuters.On July 25, North Korea launched two short-range ballistic missiles, identified as KN-23 off its east coast, according to the Korean Herald.The first missile flew around 430 kilometers while the second flew around 690 kilometers. Both flew at an estimated altitude of 50 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan.On July 31, North Korea fired two more unidentified ballistic missiles from its eastern port of Wonsan.Both of the missiles were estimated to have flown around 250 kilometers at an approximate altitude of 30 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan, according to the Korea Times. South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff said they are monitoring the situation and are "maintaining a readiness posture."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korea and the missiles launched2.Clock showing what time those missiles were launched3. North Korea firing missiles on July 254. North Korea firing missiles on July 315. Where those missiles landedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a statement from South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff, North Korea has launched additional unidentified short-range projectiles on August 2.""The statement didn't mention the exact number of missiles that were fired.""The missiles were launched at 2:59 a.m. and 3:23 a.m. from Yonghung in South Hamgyong Province. Both landed in the Sea of Japan.""This is the third time North Korea has fired projectiles in the past eight days, according to Reuters.""On July 25, North Korea launched two short-range ballistic missiles, identified as KN-23 off its east coast, according to the Korean Herald.""The first missile flew around 430 kilometers while the second flew around 690 kilometers. Both flew at an estimated altitude of 50 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan.""On July 31, North Korea fired two more unidentified ballistic missiles from its eastern port of Wonsan.""According to the Korea Times, both of the missiles were estimated to have flown around 250 kilometers at an approximate altitude of 30 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan."SOURCES: The Guardian, Reuters, BBC News, The Korea Herald, Yonhap News Agency https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/01/third-round-of-short-range-missiles-fired-by-north-korea-says-southhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles-usa/trump-plays-down-new-apparent-north-korea-test-still-open-to-talks-idUSKCN1UR5KLhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles-usa-ballistic/north-korean-projectiles-believed-to-be-short-range-ballistic-missiles-kyodo-idUSKCN1UR5XE?il=0https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49199157http://www.koreaherald.com/view.php?ud=20190802000013https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20190802000700325https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20190802000752325***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/05/3870555/3870555_EDEA169E588D48638B71E21BEA4F92E2_190805_3870555_North_Korea_conducts_third_missile_test_in_eight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea missile launch, north korea missile, kim jong un, north korea, north korea fires missile, north korea fires ballistic missile, north korean ballistic missile, short range missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870538</guid>
      <title>Rare, brain-infecting virus being spread by mosquitoes in Florida</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHealth officials in Orange County, Florida have issued a public advisory warning residents of an increase of mosquitoes carrying the Eastern equine encephalitis virus.According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the virus is spread from avian hosts such as chickens to mosquitoes. The mosquitoes carry the virus and transmit it to humans.Florida officials had found that sentinel chickens in the county tested positive for the disease.Symptoms include sudden headache, high fever, chills, vomiting and swelling of the brain. After contracting the virus, symptoms take around four to 10 days to develop. The CDC's website states that there is currently no human vaccine available against the disease.Florida's health officials advised the public to drain standing water to prevent mosquitoes from multiplying. Officials also advised the public to wear long-sleeved clothing, apply mosquito repellent and close the windows to prevent mosquito bites.According to the CDC, an average of seven human cases of the deadly virus are reported in the U.S. every year. Most of the cases reported have been from Florida, Massachusetts, New York and North Carolina. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where mosquitoes are spreading this virus 2. How the virus is spread3. Symptoms of the virus4. Precautions against the diseaseVOICEOVER (in English): "Health officials in Orange County, Florida have issued a public advisory warning residents of an increase of mosquitoes carrying the Eastern equine encephalitis virus.""According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the virus is spread from avian hosts such as chickens to mosquitoes. The mosquitoes carry the virus and transmit it to humans.""Florida officials had found that sentinel chickens in the county tested positive for the disease.""Symptoms include sudden headache, high fever, chills, vomiting and swelling of the brain. After contracting the virus, symptoms take around four to 10 days to develop.""The CDC's website states that there is currently no human vaccine available against the disease.""Florida's health officials advised the public to drain standing water to prevent mosquitoes from multiplying.""Officials also advised the public to wear long-sleeved clothing, apply mosquito repellent and close the windows to prevent mosquito bites."SOURCES: Florida Department of Health in Orange County, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, ABC News, CNN http://orange.floridahealth.gov/newsroom/2019/07/mosquito-borne.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/easternequineencephalitis/tech/epi.htmlhttps://abcnews.go.com/US/florida-health-officials-announce-uptick-mosquito-borne-virus/story?id=64631958https://edition.cnn.com/2019/07/28/health/eastern-equine-encephalitis-mosquito-outbreak-chickens-florida-trnd/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 02:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/05/3870538/3870538_2C0C3410312F4EEB94CC1E5E3A3729E4_190805_3870538_Rare__brain_infecting_virus_being_spread_by_mosq_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mosquitoes, mosquitoes florida, brain virus, mosquitoes brain virus, EEEV, eastern equine encephalitis virus, mosquito virus brain, mosquito borne disease, human EEEV]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871548</guid>
      <title>Teen activist Greta Thunberg to sail to America for UN climate summit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGreta Thunberg will be sailing across the Atlantic on a zero-emissions sailboat in order to attend climate talks in New York.According to the New York Times, the 60-foot racing yacht Malizia II is a zero-emissions vessel that generates electricity using solar panels and underwater turbines.CNN reports that in mid-August, 16-year-old Greta Thunberg and the crew of the Malizia II will sail from the U.K. to New York, where Thunberg will attend the UN Climate Action Summit on September 23.She will also go to Canada and Mexico, and plans to attend the UN COP25 climate conference in Santiago, Chile in December.The journey to New York will take roughly two weeks, according to the Times, with zero comfort onboard.Boris Hermann, the boat's skipper, says he warned Thunberg that she will likely eat freeze-dried and vacuum-packed meals, and that the crossing may be choppy, as peak Atlantic hurricane season is in August and September.Thunberg doesn't fly due to the high carbon emissions associated with air travel.Citing German nonprofit Atmosfair, Graphic News reports that a London to New York flight generates 3,408 kilograms of CO2 per person, which is double the annual carbon footprint per capita in India.According to the New York Times, the Malizia II will only be taking Thunberg to New York City. Arrangements have not yet been made for her return to Sweden.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How Malizia II yacht generates electricity with zero emissions2. Greta Thunberg's sailing route to New York, other stops in North and South America3. Zero comfort journey on the Malizia II4. Carbon emissions associated with air travelVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the New York Times, the 60-foot racing yacht Malizia II is a zero-emissions vessel that generates electricity using solar panels and underwater turbines.""CNN reports that in mid-August, 16-year-old Greta Thunberg and the crew of the Malizia II will sail from the U.K. to New York, where Thunberg will attend the UN Climate Action Summit on September 23.""She will also go to Canada and Mexico, and plans to attend the UN COP25 climate conference in Santiago, Chile in December.""The journey to New York will take roughly two weeks, according to the Times, with zero comfort onboard.""Boris Hermann, the boat's skipper, says he warned Thunberg that she will likely eat freeze-dried and vacuum-packed meals, and that the crossing may be choppy, as peak Atlantic hurricane season is in August and September.""Thunberg doesn't fly due to the high carbon emissions associated with air travel.""Citing German nonprofit Atmosfair, Graphic News reports that a London to New York flight generates 3,408 kilograms of CO2 per person, which is double the annual carbon footprint per capita in India."SOURCES: New York Times, Graphic Newshttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/29/climate/greta-thunberg-sailing-climate-summit.htmlhttps://www.graphicnews.com/en/pages/39388/Thunberg_to_sail_to_climate_talks***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/07/3871548/3871548_A7298EA86AEA4966884C66DA27253BCF_190807_3871548_Teen_activist_Greta_Thunberg_to_sail_to_America__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Greta Thunberg, zero emissions yacht, low carbon footprint, climate change, global warming, UN climate summit, Greta Thunberg sailing route, Greta Thunberg sailing, sailing across Atlantic, carbon emissions, flight emissions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871081</guid>
      <title>China building powerful laser radar to research the atmosphere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is building a powerful laser radar facility to help researchers study atmospheric particles that protect against cosmic rays and solar winds.The laser radar will have a range of 1,000 kilometers, according to a statement by the Chinese Academy of Science. Atmospheric lasers typically have an estimated range of 100 kilometers, according to the South China Morning Post. The radar will send out a high-energy laser beam that will penetrate through clouds and reach the edge of the earth's atmosphere, the South China Morning Post reports. The beam will then hit atmospheric particles such as high-altitude atoms.Several large optical telescopes will then be used to pick up and analyze faint signals reflected by these particles.According to the South China Morning Post, the laser radar is part of China's Meridian Space Weather Monitoring Project which started in 2008. The project consists of multiple ground-based observatories that monitor and forecast solar activities. The project plans to build facilities in the Arctic, the South China Sea, Central Asia and South America among other places by 2025.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The laser radar facility2. The radar's range in comparison to atmospheric lasers3. The radar sending out a beam to the earth's atmosphere and hitting an atmospheric particle4. A large optical telescope picking up and analyzing signals from the particleVOICEOVER (in English): "China is building a powerful laser radar facility to help researchers study atmospheric particles that protect against cosmic rays and solar winds.""The facility is expected to be ready within four years.""According to a statement by the Chinese Academy of Science, the laser radar will have a range of 1,000 kilometers.""According to the South China Morning Post, atmospheric lasers typically have an estimated range of 100 kilometers.""The radar will send out a high-energy laser beam that will penetrate through clouds and reach the edge of the earth's atmosphere, the South China Morning Post reports.""The beam will then hit atmospheric particles such as high-altitude atoms.""Several large optical telescopes will then be used to pick up and analyze faint signals reflected by these particles." SOURCES: South China Morning Post, Chinese Academy of Science https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3021365/china-building-worlds-most-powerful-laser-radar-study-earthshttp://english.cas.cn/newsroom/news/201908/t20190805_213901.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 02:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/06/3871081/3871081_5A9B7F26E2B447599C2A1EB5878CA88A_190806_3871081_China_building_powerful_laser_radar_to_research__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, radar, china laser radar, chinese radar technology, powerful laser radar, laser beam, high energy laser beam, laser radar, china's new laser radar, atmospheric particles, cosmic rays, solar winds, World's most powerful laser radar, chinese laser radar]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871071</guid>
      <title>Cross-border cable car planned for Russia and China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDutch architectural firm UNStudio has been chosen to design a cable car terminal in Russia that will connect the Russian city of Blagoveshchensk to the Chinese city of Heihe.The terminal will be a multi-layer structure that will overlook the Amur River, a natural boundary between Russia and China.According to UNStudio's project website, the cable car system will consist of two lines, with four cable car cabins each. Each cabin will have a capacity of 60 passengers. The cable cars are designed for travelers to have a clear view of the river, which is often frozen during winter time.The cable car terminal will also include an urban green space and terraces for passengers.Russian consulting company Strelka KB is helping UNStudio to manage the project.Ben van Berkel, founder of UNStudio, explained to Dezeen that the new cable car system will be the first to join two countries and cultures.UNStudio told CNN that construction of the site is expected to begin in 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cable car terminal2. Cable crossing the Amur River3. Other features included in the cable car terminal VOICEOVER (in English): "Dutch architectural firm UNStudio has been chosen to design a cable car terminal in Russia that will connect the Russian city of Blagoveshchensk[d][e] to the Chinese city of Heihe[f].""The terminal will be a multi-layer structure that will overlook the Amur River, a natural boundary between Russia and China.""According to UNStudio's project website, the cable car system will consist of two lines, with four cable car cabins each. Each cabin will have a capacity of 60 passengers.""The cable cars are designed for travelers to have a clear view of the river, which is often frozen during winter time.""The cable car terminal will also include an urban green space and terraces for passengers."SOURCES: UN Studio, New Atlas, Travel and Leisure, CNN, Arch Daily, Design Boom, Dezeen, Inhabitat https://www.unstudio.com/en/page/12353/blagoveshchensk-cable-car-terminalhttps://newatlas.com/un-studio-russia-china-cable-car/60840/https://www.travelandleisure.com/trip-ideas/bus-train/cable-car-will-connect-russia-and-chinahttps://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/russia-china-cable-car-scli/index.htmlhttps://www.archdaily.com/921960/unstudio-designs-worlds-first-international-cable-car-connecting-china-and-russiahttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/unstudio-russia-china-blagoveshchensk-cable-car-07-29-2019/https://www.dezeen.com/2019/07/29/worlds-first-international-cable-car-blagoveshchensk-russia-heihe-china-unstudio/https://inhabitat.com/unstudio-designs-terminal-for-worlds-first-cross-border-cable-car-connecting-russia-with-china/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 02:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/06/3871071/3871071_6829D74D9C454B48ABE6BCFF7D8008A5_190806_3871071_Cross_border_cable_car_planned_for_Russia_and_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cable car, russia-china cable car, Blagoveshchensk Cable Car Terminal,russia china cable car system, Amur River,  Blagoveshchensk - Heihe cable car, international cable car, UNStudio, cross-border cable car, cross-border cable car russia china, transportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871984</guid>
      <title>Pentagon testing surveillance balloons across the Midwest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Pentagon is using high-altitude balloons to conduct surveillance test in six Midwestern states, the Guardian reports.The U.S. military is using the balloons surveil vehicles in the midwestern states of South Dakota, Minnesota, Iowa, Wisconsin, Missouri and Illinois, according to documents from the Federal Communication Commission.The surveillance balloons are carrying small-satellite-like vehicles with synthetic aperture radars, sensors and communications equipment, the Guardian reports. The balloons travel at altitudes of up to 65,000 feet and are able to track vehicles via the synthetic radars in all kinds of weather.The documents reveal that the tests are being conducted to "provide a persistent surveillance system to locate and deter narcotic trafficking and homeland security threats."The balloons use an advanced mesh networking technologies which allows them to share data and communicate with one another, reports the Guardian. They are also able to relay the data to receivers on the ground.According to the documents, the U.S. military has acquired a license to operate the surveillance balloons from mid-July until September.The tests are being commissioned by the U.S. Southern Command, or Southcom, which is responsible for disaster response, intelligence and security operations in the Carribbean and Latin America.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where the surveillance balloons are deployed2. Equipment carried by the balloons3. Balloons tracking a car4. Balloons sharing data with each other and with ground receiversVOICEOVER (in English): "The Pentagon is using high-altitude balloons to conduct surveillance tests in the Midwestern states of South Dakota, Minnesota, Iowa, Wisconsin, Missouri and Illinois, according to documents from the Federal Communication Commission.""The Guardian reports the surveillance balloons are carrying small satellite-like vehicles with synthetic aperture radars, sensors and communications equipment.""The surveillance balloons travel at altitudes of up to 65,000 feet and are used to track vehicles via the synthetic radars in all kinds of weather.""The Guardian reports that the balloons use an advanced mesh networking technologies, which allows them to share data and communicate with one another.""They are also able to relay the data to receivers on the ground."SOURCES: The Guardian, Federal Communications Commission https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/aug/02/pentagon-balloons-surveillance-midwesthttps://apps.fcc.gov/els/GetAtt.html?id=233815&x=.***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 13:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/07/3871984/3871984_6D71DA88D0C940B4A43303AAE429568F_190807_3871984_Pentagon_testing_surveillance_balloons_across_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pentagon, pentagon surveillance balloons, surveillance pentagon, high-altitude balloons, solar-powered balloons pentagon, balloon radar, surveillance balloon tests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872468</guid>
      <title>U.S. planning to build new naval base in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe United States could be putting up a new military port in Australia.According to Reuters, Australian Foreign Minister Marise Payne said Tuesday that the U.S. Navy plans to build military infrastructure in the country, once Congress approves $211.5 million in funding.While Payne did not specify the type of infrastructure, Australian media reported that Washington's plans are for a new port.Multiple officials told the ABC the facility would be in Darwin's Glyde Point, and could eventually accommodate large amphibious warships like Australia's Landing Helicopter Docks, and vessels such as the USS Wasp.Each year, 2,500 U.S. marines are deployed to Australia in an annual rotation for training, and are housed at an Australian army base in Darwin. With the new facility, American marines could operate more readily in the region, according to ABC.Reuters reports that the plan comes amid increasing concerns with China's expansion in the Pacific.The existing Port of Darwin is currently leased to Chinese company Landbridge for 99 years, and is located just 40 kilometers from the future U.S. port in Glyde Point.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. plans to build military infrastructure in Australia2. U.S. port in Glyde Point, Darwin3. Annual U.S. marine training in Australia4. Chinese expansion in the PacificVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, Australian Foreign Minister Marise Payne said Tuesday that the U.S. Navy plans to build military infrastructure in the country, once Congress approves $211.5 million in funding.""While Payne did not specify the type of infrastructure, Australian media reported that Washington's plans are for a new port.""Multiple officials told the ABC the facility would be in Darwin's Glyde Point, and could eventually accommodate large amphibious warships like Australia's Landing Helicopter Docks, and vessels such as the USS Wasp.""Each year, 2,500 U.S. marines are deployed to Australia in an annual rotation for training, and are housed at an Australian army base in Darwin.""According to ABC, with the new facility, American marines could operate more readily in the region.""Reuters reports that the plan comes amid increasing concerns with China's expansion in the Pacific.""The existing Port of Darwin is currently leased to Chinese company Landbridge for 99 years, and is located just 40 kilometers from the future U.S. port in Glyde Point."SOURCES: Reuters, ABC, The Australianhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-usa/australia-says-u-s-plans-to-build-military-infrastructure-idUSKCN1UP0GYhttps://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-06-23/navy-port-us-darwin-glyde-point-gunn-marines-gunn-military/11222606https://www.theaustralian.com.au/nation/defence/us-military-to-spend-300m-on-darwin-infrastructure-upgrade/news-story/c61faf17bdb886ebf0a0e707a21404f7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 10:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/08/3872468/3872468_B6C509378A77420D8D3704F9F8297219_190808_3872468_U_S__planning_to_build_new_naval_base_in_Austral_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, us naval base, us base, us base australia, port of darwin, glyde point port, glyde point base, australia naval base, us military base]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872451</guid>
      <title>Philippines declares national dengue epidemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDengue is now a national epidemic in the Philippines. According to the Philippine News Agency, health authorities declared a national dengue epidemic on Tuesday, after more than 100,000 cases from January to July this year, and 622 deaths.The country's Health Secretary Francisco Duque said the declaration will allow local government units in badly hit places to access quick response funds to help fight the outbreak.Government agencies will also be carrying out a campaign to destroy mosquito breeding sites.According to the Guardian, the mosquito-borne viral infection is found in tropical countries, and can cause joint pain, high fevers, and a rash, among other symptoms.Nature reports that in severe cases, it can cause plasma to leak out of the capillaries, leading to breathing problems, hemorrhagic fever, and organ failure.Dengue has no specific treatment, but according to The Guardian, medical care is necessary as it is critical to maintain a person's fluid levels.An existing vaccine called Dengvaxia has been banned in the Philippines after several dozen children died during a government immunization campaign in 2017.The U.S. FDA approved the Dengvaxia vaccine this year, with several restrictions. The New York Times reports that other vaccines are currently being developed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Number of dengue cases and deaths in the Philippines2. Local government units access quick response funds to improve outbreak response3. Dengue cleanup campaign4. Dengue symptoms5. Dengue treatmentVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Philippine News Agency, health authorities declared a national dengue epidemic on Tuesday, after more than 100,000 cases from January to July this year, and 622 deaths.""The country's Health Secretary Francisco Duque said the declaration will allow local government units in badly hit places to access quick response funds to help fight the outbreak.""Government agencies will also be carrying out a campaign to destroy mosquito breeding sites.""According to the Guardian, the mosquito-borne viral infection is found in tropical countries, and can cause joint pain, high fevers, and a rash, among other symptoms.""Nature reports that in severe cases, it can cause plasma to leak out of the capillaries, leading to breathing problems, hemorrhagic fever, and organ failure.""Dengue has no specific treatment, but according to The Guardian, medical care is necessary as it is critical to maintain a person's fluid levels.""An existing vaccine called Dengvaxia has been banned in the Philippines after several dozen children died during a government immunization campaign in 2017."SOURCES: Philippine News Agency, The Guardian, New York Times, Naturehttps://www.pna.gov.ph/articles/1077121https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/07/philippines-declares-epidemic-after-dengue-fever-kills-more-than-600https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/06/world/asia/philippines-dengue.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/scitable/topicpage/what-is-dengue-fever-22399100***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 10:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/08/3872451/3872451_4E00B5B380344B6AAD267F0DECF53DA9_190808_3872451_Philippines_declares_national_dengue_epidemic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dengue, dengue epidemic, dengue virus, philippine dengue epidemic, mosquito virus, viral infection, dengvaxia, dengue vaccine, dengue symptoms, dengue treatment, severe dengue, plasma leakage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872272</guid>
      <title>North Korea stole US$2 billion in cyberattacks, UN report finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea has conducted cyberattacks to steal an estimated US$2 billion to fund its nuclear weapons program, Reuters reports, citing a confidential U.N. report.The report says North Korea continued to strengthen its weapons program over the past six months, even though they have not conducted any nuclear tests or intercontinental ballistic missile launches.According to Reuters, experts said North Korean hackers used "sophisticated attacks" to target financial institutions and cryptocurrency exchanges to generate income. The U.N. was investigating at least 35 cyberattacks by North Korean military intelligence in approximately 17 countries. Experts are also investigating whether North Korea took part in cryptocurrency mining activities to earn money.North Korea has recently been in the news for launching projectiles into the Sea of Japan four times in a span of two weeks. The country has said the consecutive missile launches are a warning against the U.S. and South Korea for carrying out joint military exercises, according to Yonhap News Agency.Reuters says that the U.N. report was completed before North Korea's missile launches last week.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korean flag, a hacked laptop, a pile of U.S. dollars and a North Korean missile2. North Korea targeting bank and cryptocurrency exchanges3. North Korea conducting cyber attacks on other countries4. A room full of hackers and cyber miningVOICEOVER (in English): "North Korea has conducted cyberattacks to steal an estimated US$2 billion to fund its nuclear weapons program, Reuters reports, citing a confidential U.N. report.""The report says North Korea continued to strengthen its weapons program over the past six months, even though they have not conducted any nuclear tests or intercontinental ballistic missile launches.""According to Reuters, experts said North Korean hackers used "sophisticated attacks" to target financial institutions and cryptocurrency exchanges to generate income.""The U.N. was investigating at least 35 cyberattacks by North Korean military intelligence in approximately 17 countries.""Experts who wrote the report are also investigating to find out whether North Korea took part in cryptocurrency mining activities to earn foreign money."SOURCES: BBC.com. CNN, Reuters, 38 North, The South China Morning Post, Yonhap News Agency, Bloomberg   https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49259302https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49244654https://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/06/asia/north-korea-cryptocurrency-missile-tests-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-cyber-un/north-korea-took-2-billion-in-cyberattacks-to-fund-weapons-program-u-n-report-idUSKCN1UV1ZXhttps://www.38north.org/2019/08/rpotter080519/https://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/3021558/north-korean-hackers-have-stolen-us2-billion-fund-weaponshttps://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20190802000752325https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-06/north-korea-hacks-banks-cryptocurrencies-for-funds-un-finds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 06:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/08/3872272/3872272_F07EF5023E21454FA400B841734B87B0_190808_3872272_North_Korea_stole_US_2_billion_in_cyberattacks___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea, cyber attacks, north korean cyber attacks, North korean cyber attacks, north korea weapons, north korea news,  kim jong un, north korea weapons cyber attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872954</guid>
      <title>Europe launches laser satellite to space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe European Space Agency and Airbus have launched their second space laser satellite, the EDRS-C. It was sent into space on an Ariane 5 rocket from Kourou in French Guiana on Aug 6.The EDRS-C will join its sister satellite, the EDRS-A, and operate in geostationary orbit, according to the European Space Agency.  This is approximately 35,786 kilometers above the surface of the Earth, according to Science Direct.Both form part of the European Data Relay System, a satellite constellation.The BBC reports that they will use lasers to collect data from lower orbit Earth satellites called Sentinels. These watch over the planet and capture images of the surface."According to the ESA, the Sentinel-1 orbits at 693 kilometers high, while Sentinel-2 orbits at 786 kilometers.The EDRS can relay data back to Earth at a rate of up to 1.8 gigabits per second. According to the ESA, these satellites were previously only able to transmit information to earth whenever they were in direct line of sight with a ground station. This was every 90 minutes.The addition of EDRS-C cuts that delay to almost nothing, allowing satellites to send data to Earth in almost real-time. The ESA explained that the technology would allow for a faster response to emergency situations.According to the BBC, a third satellite, EDRS-D, is expected to launch before 2025.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. EDRS-C satellite in space2. The EDRS satellites collecting data3. The EDRS satellites sending data to earth's ground station4. The Sentinel-2 sending data to earth's ground stationVOICEOVER (in English): "The EDRS-C will join its sister satellite, the EDRS-A, and operate in geostationary orbit, according to the European Space Agency.  "This is approximately 35,786 kilometers above the surface of the Earth, according to Science Direct.""Both form part of the European Data Relay System, a satellite constellation.""The BBC reports that they  will use lasers to collect data from lower orbit Earth satellites called Sentinels. These watch over the planet and capture images of the surface.""According to the ESA, the Sentinel-1 orbits at 693 kilometers high, while Sentinel-2 orbits at 786 kilometers. ""The EDRS can relay data back to Earth at a rate of up to 1.8 gigabits per second.""According to the ESA, these satellites were previously only able to transmit information to earth whenever they were in direct line of sight with a ground station. This was every 90 minutes.""The addition of EDRS-C cuts that delay to almost nothing, allowing satellites to send data to Earth in almost real-time."SOURCES: BBC News, European Space Agency, Space.com, Airbus   https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-49240745https://m.esa.int/Our_Activities/Telecommunications_Integrated_Applications/EDRS-C_successfully_launchedhttps://www.space.com/ariane5-rocket-intelsat-edrs-launch-success.htmlhttps://www.airbus.com/newsroom/press-releases/en/2019/08/successful-launch-of-the-second-spacedatahighway-satellite-on-ariane-5.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 08:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/09/3872954/3872954_72FB2CCF3E50477EB301FC5A60218E66_190809_3872954_Europe_launches_laser_satellite_to_space_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, europe, space, space launch, space exploration, EDRS space laser satellite, european satellite, space laser satellite, europe space agency, european space agency, European Data Relay System, european space exploration, europe's second satellite, EDRS-C, EDRS-A]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872800</guid>
      <title>Chinese classrooms using brain-scanning headbands to measure students' focus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese schools are using U.S.- based startup company BrainCo's brain-scanning headbands to measure students' attention spans, the South China Morning Post reports.The Focus 1 headband uses electroencephalography sensors, or EEGs, to detect students' brain signals. These signals are then translated by an AI algorithm in real time to determine how focused a student is.Signals from the headbands are able to be monitored through a dashboard in real time, according to BrainCo's website. The students' attention levels will be indicated by the color appearing on their headset, the South China Morning Post reports. Blue means the student is relaxed, yellow means the student is focused, and red means the student is extremely focused.BrainCo explained in a statement on Weibo that the headbands are only being used on a trial basis in a few schools in China and that their only purpose is to help students increase their attention span.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The headband, a child wearing the headband while studying2. The headband using EEGs to detect brain signals3. Brain signals being monitored on a dashboard4. Students in a classroom with different colors on their headset. The colors represents how attentive the student is VOICEOVER (in English): "Chinese schools are using U.S.- based startup company BrainCo's brain scanning headbands to measure students' attention spans, the South China Morning Post reports.""The Focus 1 headband uses electroencephalography sensors, or EEGs, to detect students' brain signals. These signals are then translated by an AI algorithm in real time to determine how focused a student is.""According to BrainCo's website, signals from the headbands are able to be monitored through a dashboard in real time.""The South China Morning reports that the students' attention levels will be indicated by the color appearing on their headset." "Blue means the student is relaxed, yellow means the student is focused, and red means the student is extremely focused."SOURCES: The South China Morning Post, The Independent, Digital Trends, PR Newswire https://www.scmp.com/tech/start-ups/article/3005448/brainwave-tracking-start-china-schoolchildren-controversy-workinghttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/china-schools-scan-brains-concentration-headbands-children-brainco-focus-a8728951.htmlhttps://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/focus-brainwave-headband-concentrating-in-class/https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/harvard-university-backed-startup-brainco-inc-gets-the-biggest-purchase-order-in-brain-machine-interface-bmi-industry-300460485.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 04:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/09/3872800/3872800_4ED46E36782047E1A6D542FDED815484_190809_3872800_Chinese_classrooms_using_brain_scanning_headband_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, china surveillance, headbands, brain-reading headbands, chinese surveillance, china mass surveillance, china ai system, surveillance, surveillance state, china surveillance, police state, china surveillance system, total surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872781</guid>
      <title>Tardigrades may be alive on moon following Beresheet crash landing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe moon may now be home to Earth's most resilient organisms.CNN reports that thousands of micro creatures called tardigrades were onboard Israel's Beresheet spacecraft when it crash landed on the moon in April.According to the BBC, tardigrades are about a millimeter-long, with eight legs, claws, and a sucker-like pharynx to spear prey. They are more commonly known as water bears or moss piglets.CNN reports that they live in water or on plants like lichen or moss, can withstand being heated to 150 degrees Celsius, and frozen to almost absolute zero.The non-profit Arch Mission Foundation dehydrated the water bears, which caused the organisms to enter a state of suspended animation, where metabolism lowers to 0.01% of the normal rate.They were then encased in amber and loaded onto the Beresheet, along with a 30-million page archive of human history called the lunar library.Since the tardigrades are resilient, researchers say it's likely they survived the crash. But they will need to be reintroduced to water in order to reanimate.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Beresheet spacecraft crash landing on moon2.Tardigrades can withstand extreme heat and cold3. Crashed Beresheet lunar lander carrying tardigrades in suspended animation 4. Tardigrades likely survived crash, but need water to be reanimatedVOICEOVER (in English): "CNN reports that thousands of micro creatures called tardigrades were onboard Israel's Beresheet spacecraft when it crash landed on the moon in April.""According to the BBC, tardigrades are about a millimeter-long, with eight legs, claws, and a sucker-like pharynx to spear prey. They are more commonly known as water bears or moss piglets.""CNN reports that they live in water or on plants like lichen or moss, can withstand being heated to 150 degrees Celsius, and frozen to almost absolute zero.""The non-profit Arch Mission Foundation dehydrated the water bears, which caused the organisms to enter a state of suspended animation, where metabolism lowers to 0.01% of the normal rate.""They were then encased in amber and loaded onto the Beresheet, along with a 30-million page archive of human history called the lunar library.""Since the tardigrades are resilient, researchers say it's likely they survived the crash. But they will need to be reintroduced to water in order to reanimate."SOURCES: CNN, BBChttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/07/world/water-bear-space-intl-scli-scn/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/newsbeat-49265125https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47879538http://www.bbc.com/earth/story/20150313-the-toughest-animals-on-earth***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 03:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/09/3872781/3872781_786E9E61D8E341AF9FE787515A5E12B7_190809_3872781_Tardigrades_may_be_alive_on_moon_following_Beres_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, tardigrades, water bears, water bears in space, tardigrades in space, moss piglets in space, moss piglets, Beresheet spacecraft, tardigrades on moon, moss piglets on moon, water bears on moon, moon creatures, Beresheet crash land]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874531</guid>
      <title>Scientists develop vaccine to help stop cat allergies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists in Switzerland have developed a vaccine that can help stop people from having allergic reactions to cats.According to a study published in the Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, cat allergies are typically caused by the protein Fel d 1, which is found in feline saliva, tears, and pelt.When the protein enters the system of someone with a cat allergy, it triggers a reactive rush of histamines, leading to itching, wheezing, and other symptoms.Ten percent of the general human population suffers from cat allergies, but there is no safe or efficient therapy currently available. The usual recourse for patients is to treat allergy symptoms and avoid cats.Three point four million cats are abandoned at U.S. cat shelters each year, and allergies suffered by owners, family, and friends are a leading cause of the abandonment.According to a news release from Hypopet, scientists in Zurich have developed a vaccine, which when injected into a cat instructs the immune system to produce antibodies that target and destroy the Fel d 1 protein.Testing on 54 cats in four different studies found that the antibodies successfully neutralized the allergens. The vaccine, called Hypocat, was also reported to be well-tolerated without any over toxicity.According to Fox 13, the vaccine could be available within three years, with both humans and animals benefiting from the treatment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fel d 1 protein as main allergen for people with cat allergies2. Current treatments for cat allergies3. Cat vaccine triggers production of antibodies in cats4. Antibodies neutralize Fel d 1 proteinVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, cat allergies are typically caused by the protein Fel d 1, which is found in feline saliva, tears, and pelt.""When the protein enters the system of someone with a cat allergy, it triggers a reactive rush of histamines, leading to itching, wheezing, and other symptoms.""Ten percent of the general human population suffers from cat allergies, but there is no safe or efficient therapy currently available.""The usual recourse for patients is to treat allergy symptoms and avoid cats.""According to a news release from Hypopet, scientists in Zurich have developed a vaccine, which when injected into a cat instructs the immune system to produce antibodies that target and destroy the Fel d 1 protein.""Testing on 54 cats in four different studies found that the antibodies successfully neutralized the allergens. The vaccine, called Hypocat, was also reported to be well-tolerated without any over toxicity."SOURCES: Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, Hypopet, Fox 13https://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091-6749(19)30349-5/abstracthttps://www.hypopet.ch/newshttp://www.fox13news.com/health/new-cat-vaccine-could-help-relieve-humans-allergic-reactions-to-them***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 16:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/13/3874531/3874531_E262EAB6C84444829872B1185D5BE2A8_190813_3874531_Scientists_develop_vaccine_to_help_stop_cat_alle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cat allergy, cat allergy vaccine, animal allergy, feline allergy, cat allergy cure, cat vaccine, hypocat, hypopet, cat allergen, allergens, histamines, allergies, how allergies work]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874151</guid>
      <title>Study finds increased toxic mercury levels in tuna and cod</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has linked an increase of toxic mercury in marine life to global warming and overfishing.Research by Harvard scientists analyzed data from the Gulf of Maine in the Atlantic Ocean.  According to Reuters, it found a 23 percent increase of methylmercury, a type of organic mercury, in cod fish and 27 percent in bluefin tuna over the past 30 years.The study, published in the journal Nature, found that as the climate warms the oceans, bigger fish such as bluefin tuna eat more because they need more energy. This means they consume more prey with higher levels of methylmercury."Researchers also found that overfishing of smaller herring and sardines had changed the diet of Atlantic cod, with the fish now eating larger herrings and lobsters. Both contain higher levels of methylmercury.The research notes that the consumption of contaminated fish could impact human health. It says that methylmercury has been associated with long-term neurocognitive dysfunction in children that were exposed to methylmercury while in the womb.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Atlantic cod, bluefin tuna, and methylmercury 2. The sea becoming warmer, tuna ingesting smaller fish3. Methylmercury being passed on from prey to predator4. How methylmercury in fish could impact a child VOICEOVER (in English): "Research by Harvard scientists analyzed data from the Gulf of Maine in the Atlantic Ocean. "According to Reuters, it found a 23 percent increase of methylmercury, a type of organic mercury, in cod fish and 27 percent in bluefin tuna over the past 30 years.""The study, published in the journal Nature, found that as the climate warms the oceans, bigger fish such as bluefin tuna eat more because they need more energy. "This means they consume more prey with higher levels of methylmercury." "Researchers also found that overfishing of smaller herring and sardines had changed the diet of Atlantic cod, with the fish now eating larger herrings and lobsters. "Both contain higher levels of methylmercury.""The research notes that the consumption of contaminated fish could impact human health." It says that methylmercury has been associated with long-term neurocognitive dysfunction in children that were exposed to methylmercury while in the womb."SOURCES: Reuters, The Atlantic, Science Daily, Nature https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-fish-health/toxic-mercury-in-fish-rising-with-climate-change-and-overfishing-idUSKCN1UX21Shttps://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/08/why-changing-climate-means-more-mercury-seafood/595663/https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/08/190807131917.htmhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1468-9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 03:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/12/3874151/3874151_CCFCC971227B43B3A109E0B199A87584_190812_3874151_Study_finds_increased_toxic_mercury_levels_in_tu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, tuna, climate change, toxic fish, fish climate change, overfishing, cod, tuna overfishing, effects of climate change, climate change marine line, climate change fish, impact of climate change on fisheries, toxic mercury tuna]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875081</guid>
      <title>End of El Nino could bring active Atlantic hurricane season</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe chances of an above-normal Atlantic hurricane season in 2019 have increased now that El Nino is over.According to the NOAA, El Nino occurs when sea-surface temperatures in the equatorial Pacific are warmer than average, and east winds blow weaker than usual.The agency declared Thursday that El Nino has ended and transitioned into a neutral state, bringing normal water temperatures and atmospheric conditions to the central and eastern Pacific.El Nino typically suppresses hurricane activity in the Atlantic, so its end could mean a busier hurricane season.The NOAA says oceanic and atmospheric conditions are now favorable for an above-normal Atlantic hurricane season.It is expecting 10 to 17 named storms, 5 to 9 of which will become hurricanes, and two to four major hurricanes with winds of 111 miles per hour or greater.However, Colorado State University tropical scientist Phil Klotzbach has noted that continuing warmth in the central Pacific over the next few months could prevent winds from becoming too hurricane-favorable in the Atlantic and Caribbean.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Explanation of El Nino2. El Nino transitions into neutral state3. El Nino suppressing hurricane activity in Atlantic4. 2019 Atlantic hurricane season outlookVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the NOAA, El Nino occurs when sea-surface temperatures in the equatorial Pacific are warmer than average, and east winds blow weaker than usual.""The agency declared Thursday that El Nino has ended and transitioned into a neutral state, bringing normal water temperatures and atmospheric conditions to the central and eastern Pacific.""El Nino typically suppresses hurricane activity in the Atlantic, so its end could mean a busier hurricane season.""The NOAA says oceanic and atmospheric conditions are now favorable for an above-normal Atlantic hurricane season.""It is expecting 10 to 17 named storms, 5 to 9 of which will become hurricanes, and two to four major hurricanes with winds of 111 miles per hour or greater. "SOURCES: NOAA, CNN, The Weather Channelhttps://www.noaa.gov/media-release/noaa-increases-chance-for-above-normal-hurricane-seasonhttps://www.noaa.gov/education/resource-collections/weather-atmosphere-education-resources/el-ninohttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/08/us/hurricane-season-2019-forecast-noaa-update-wxc/index.htmlhttps://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2019-08-08-el-nino-enso-neutral-fall-winter-atlantic-hurricane-season***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 14:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/13/3875081/3875081_3AAE938210094331AC0814C1702089DE_190813_3875081_End_of_El_Nino_could_bring_active_Atlantic_hurri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, El Nino, ENSO, ENSO neutral, La Nina, weather, weather patterns, extreme weather patterns, atlantic hurricanes, hurricane season, atlantic hurricane season, storms, atlantic storms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874688</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong police fire tear gas, rubber bullets into metro station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANActivists in Hong Kong continued to protest the Hong Kong government for the tenth weekend in a row.The protests are against an extradition bill that would allow suspects to be extradited for trial to mainland China. Those against the bill believe that Beijing may use it as a way to extradite political activists, dissidents and other critics in the city.The Hong Kong government has suspended the bill, but protesters are calling for the government to withdraw it altogether.On Sunday, protesters were taking part in a peaceful rally in Hong Kong's Victoria Park when they defied police orders and starting marching along Cheung Sha Wan Road, a major thoroughfare in the city.Activists used the flash-mob strategy to appear in different parts of the city, Reuters reports. As the protesters made their way to a metro station in Kwai Chung, an urban area in Hong Kong, police attempted to disperse the crowd by firing tear gas and rubber bullets, according to Hong Kong Free Press. Other police officers were filmed chasing people and using batons to hit them while on the metro escalator, reports the BBC. Peaceful protests have been taking place at Hong Kong's International Airport since August 9 as an attempt to seek international support for Hong Kong's ongoing protests.Activists have called for Hong Kong's leader Carrie Lam to resign. They are also pushing for an independent investigation into alleged police brutality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Peaceful protests in Victoria Park then the crowd marches on the roads2. Flash mob 3. Police firing tear gas and rubber bullets into the metro station4. Police hitting protesters with batons while on the escalatorVOICEOVER (in English): "On Sunday, protesters were taking part in a peaceful rally in Hong Kong's Victoria Park when they defied police orders and starting marching along Cheung Sha Wan Road, a major thoroughfare in the city.""Reuters reports activists used the flash-mob strategy to appear in different parts of the city.""As the protesters made their way to a metro station in Kwai Chung, an urban area in Hong Kong, police attempted to disperse the crowd by firing tear gas and rubber bullets, according to Hong Kong Free Press.""The BBC reports that other police officers were filmed chasing people and using batons to hit them while on the metro escalator."SOURCES: Reuters, BBC News, Hong Kong Free Press, The South China Morning Post, The Straits Times https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-hongkong-protests/hong-kong-mops-up-after-weekend-of-violence-braces-for-more-protests-idUSKCN1V201Bhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-49312752https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/08/11/clashes-tear-gas-hong-kong-protesters-defy-police-ban-descend-upon-sham-shui-po-north-point/https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3022206/illegal-anti-government-march-sets-hong-konghttps://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/hong-kong-braces-for-a-weekend-of-demonstrations-airport-sit-in***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 03:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/13/3874688/3874688_9BD9AEF6BB4944C7ADBAFB520BA44F51_190813_3874688_Hong_Kong_police_fire_tear_gas__rubber_bullets_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, HK mass protest, Hong Kong mass protest, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong,  hong kong police fire tear gas, hong kong protests metro, hong kong metro tear gas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874673</guid>
      <title>Eco-friendly park with 'solar trees' planned for Ho Chi Minh City</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAustralian architectural firms LAVA Architects and Aspect Studios have partnered together and won a competition to design Ho Chi Minh City's new sustainable Central Park.The park will replace the existing September 23 Park, which is in the city's central urban district, according to LAVA Architects' project website. The sustainable public park will include artificial plants and futuristic "solar trees" with angled solar panels to generate renewable energy to power the park's digital information screens and Wi-Fi system.The park will also feature "water purification trees" and "ventilation trees." The "water purification trees" will gather and recycle rainwater for watering purposes, drinking fountains and fire hydrants, while the "ventilation trees" will be used to generate fresh air and reduce heat in the park.Central Park will include open green spaces with music and theater performance pavilions, playgrounds and sculpture gardens for the general public.The architects plan to link the park with Ho Chi Minh City's new Ben Thanh metro station, which is still under construction.LAVA Architect's website states that construction on the park is to begin in 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The sustainable public park2. Artificial plants and "solar trees"3. The park's "water purification trees" and "ventilation trees"4. The park's open green spacesVOICEOVER (in English): "Australian architectural firms LAVA Architects and Aspect Studios have partnered together and won a competition to design Ho Chi Minh City's new sustainable Central Park.""According to LAVA Architects' project website, the park will replace the existing September 23 Park, which is in the city's central urban district.""The sustainable public park will include artificial plants and futuristic 'solar trees' with angled solar panels to generate renewable energy to power the park's digital information screens and Wi-Fi system.""The park will also feature 'water purification trees' and 'ventilation trees.'" "The 'water purification trees' will gather and recycle rainwater for watering purposes, drinking fountains and fire hydrants, while the 'ventilation trees' will be used to generate fresh air and reduce heat in the park.""Central Park will include open green spaces with music and theater performance pavilions, playgrounds and sculpture gardens for the general public."SOURCES: Inhabitat, LAVA, Aspect Studios, Design Boom, Arch Daily https://inhabitat.com/sustainable-central-park-with-energy-producing-trees-unveiled-for-ho-chi-minh-city/http://www.l-a-v-a.net/projects/central-park-hcmc/https://www.aspect-studios.com/https://www.designboom.com/architecture/lava-aspect-studios-win-competition-ho-chi-minh-city-central-park-vietnam-08-08-2019/https://www.archdaily.com/922558/lava-plus-aspect-design-the-central-park-of-ho-chi-minh-city***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 03:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/13/3874673/3874673_05FF1B9E558944C7AB61B6937FC8EF0E_190813_3874673_Eco_friendly_park_with__solar_trees__planned_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, infrastructure, architecture, sustainable architecture, ho chi minh city central park, Aspect Studios, Laboratory for Vision Architecture, ho chi minh city architecture, Vietnam Central Park]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875294</guid>
      <title>Banana plantations in Colombia threatened by deadly fungus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOfficials from the Colombian Agricultural and Livestock Authority have confirmed that the tropical race 4 fungus has spread to the country's Cavendish banana plantations.Cavendish bananas dominate the global export market. The Cavendish are a monoculture, meaning they have identical genetics and are therefore equally vulnerable to the fungus.Food producers tend to raise crops with little to no gene diversity in order to grow fruits and vegetables efficiently and at a lower cost.Panama disease Tropical Race 4, also called TR4, is spread through infected planting material as well as infested soil and water, according to Promusa.org, a platform that shares information related to bananas.Once the fungus is in the soil of the Cavendish banana plant, it stops water from entering the plant, essentially disrupting its vascular system. The infected plants eventually stop producing fruit.According to Promusa.org, the TR4 fungus cannot be removed from the plantation soil by use of fumigants, a type of pesticide for fields, or by fungicides, a type of chemical to destroy fungus.The website suggests rotating the banana plants with fungus-resistant crops such as leeks in order for bananas to continue to be produced in the same soil.The TR4 fungus was first identified in Taiwan and has since been found in Southeast Asia, Australia, the Middle East, Africa and now in Latin America, according to the National Geographic. This is not the first time the banana industry has faced this kind of crisis. In the 1950s, the Gros Michel[a][b][c] was the main variety of banana grown for export. It was declared commercially extinct in 1965 due to a different strain of Panama disease. Gros Michel trees were burned down and it was replaced by the Cavendish, which was immune to that disease.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tropical race 4 fungus, banana plantation, cavendish bananas with identical genes2. How the fungus is spread3. How the fungus disrupts the plant's vascular system4. A banana plantation, fumigants and fungicidesVOICEOVER (in English): "Officials from the Colombian Agricultural and Livestock Authority have confirmed that the tropical race 4 fungus has spread to the country's Cavendish banana plantations.""Cavendish bananas dominate the global export market. The Cavendish are a monoculture, meaning they have identical genetics and are therefore equally vulnerable to the fungus.""Panama disease Tropical Race 4, also called TR4, is spread through infected planting material as well as infested soil and water, according to Promusa.org, a platform that shares information related to bananas.""Once the fungus is in the soil of the Cavendish banana plant, it stops water from entering the plant, essentially disrupting its vascular system.""The infected plants eventually stop producing fruit.""According to Promusa.org, the TR4 fungus cannot be removed from the plantation soil by use of fumigants, a type of pesticide for fields, or by fungicides, a type of chemical to destroy fungus."SOURCES: National Geographic, CNN, Science Magazine, Promusa.org, Colombian agriculture and livestock authority  https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2019/08/banana-fungus-latin-america-threatening-future/https://edition.cnn.com/2015/07/22/africa/banana-panama-disease/index.html?no-st=1565662961https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/08/colombia-confirms-dreaded-fungus-has-hit-its-banana-plantationshttp://www.promusa.org/Tropical+race+4+-+TR4https://www.ica.gov.co/home?lang=en-us***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 05:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/14/3875294/3875294_40E8B12C55874676A6031DDAC8505B11_190814_3875294_Banana_plantations_in_Colombia_threatened_by_dea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, banana, banana fungus, banana fungus columbia, tropical race 4, tropical race 4 banana, cavendish banana, cavendish banana extinction]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875265</guid>
      <title>Archaeologists find evidence of Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArchaeologists may have unearthed evidence to confirm the Biblical account of Jerusalem's destruction by the Babylonians.Haaretz reports that an international team led by the University of North Carolina at Charlotte has uncovered layers of ash deposits on Mount Zion, which contained artifacts such as a rare piece of jewelry and arrowheads.According to UNC Charlotte professor Shimon Gibson, this combination of artifacts indicates some kind of destruction or devastation at the site, since "Nobody abandons gold jewelry and nobody has arrowheads in their domestic refuse."Haaretz reports that the ash layers were dated to the Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem in 587 or 586 B.C.E. using pottery fragments and oil lamps typical of the period.The arrowheads were identified as Scythian, made of copper alloy and iron. They are known to have been used by Babylonian archers, according to Ancient Origins.Haaretz reports that the discoveries support the hypothesis that Jerusalem was a sprawling and rich city when it was besieged by the Babylonians, and not a small hilltop citadel like some have suggested.The UNC Charlotte team may have also found what may be a significant structure from the Iron Age. As the building lies beneath layers from different periods, it has yet to be excavated. Archaeologists say they will likely begin in 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rare jewelry fragment and arrowheads found in ash layers on Mount Zion2. Depiction of Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem3. Pottery fragments date to Iron Age Jerusalem; arrowheads linked to Babylonians4. Iron Age Jerusalem as rich, sprawling cityVOICEOVER (in English): "Haaretz reports that an international team led by the University of North Carolina at Charlotte has uncovered layers of ash deposits on Mount Zion, which contained artifacts such as a rare piece of jewelry and arrowheads.""According to UNC Charlotte professor Shimon Gibson, this combination of artifacts indicates some kind of destruction or devastation at the site, since 'Nobody abandons gold jewelry and nobody has arrowheads in their domestic refuse.'""Haaretz reports that the ash layers were dated to the Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem in 587 or 586 B.C.E. using pottery fragments and oil lamps typical of the period.""The arrowheads were identified as Scythian, made of copper alloy and iron. They are known to have been used by Babylonian archers, according to Ancient Origins.""Haaretz reports that the discoveries support the hypothesis that Jerusalem was a sprawling and rich city when it was besieged by the Babylonians, and not a small hilltop citadel like some have suggested."SOURCES: Haaretz, University of North Carolina at Charlotte (via EurekAlert)https://www.haaretz.com/archaeology/.premium-rare-jewel-found-on-mt-zion-reveals-babylonian-destruction-of-jerusalem-1.7658563https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-08/uonc-eot080819.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 04:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/14/3875265/3875265_DE9D20E63A4348BBB7BE7B5C5A9ADD4F_190814_3875265_Archaeologists_find_evidence_of_Babylonian_conqu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, archeology, mount zion, ancient jerusalem, Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem, Babylonian destruction of Jerusalem, old Jerusalem, Iron Age Jerusalem, David's Jerusalem, Biblical archaeology, Bible]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876266</guid>
      <title>How could China intervene in the Hong Kong protests?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs the Chinese government continues to strongly criticize the now months-long protests in Hong Kong, many wonder what Beijing will do to quiet the dissent.According to CNN, Chinese military forces seen near the border city of Shenzhen are fueling speculation that China could use them to quell protests in Hong Kong.But the BBC reports that under the city's Basic Law, direct military intervention is possible only if the Hong Kong government requests it. Instead, the South China Morning Post reports China is putting pressure on Hong Kong's police force to end the protests.According to the BBC, China could also turn to political intervention, since Hong Kong's Legislative Council is only partly democratic, and largely pro-Beijing.China is already showing its power by refusing to accept Chief Executive Carrie Lam's resignation and refusing to let her formally withdraw the controversial extradition bill.Another possibility is for Beijing to target activists, as even without the extradition law, China is capable of detaining individual citizens.According to the South China Morning Post, some Hong Kong residents have had China immigration officers at the border check photos and messages on their phones.Despite fears of direct intervention, however, the BBC reports that Beijing's most effective tool may be economic. It can target the Hong Kong economy by redirecting investments to other Chinese cities, effectively making them more reliant on China.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese military intervention in Hong Kong2. Chinese political intervention in Hong Kong3. China targeting individual activists, inspecting phones at border4. China targeting Hong Kong economyVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNN, Chinese military forces seen near the border city of Shenzhen are fueling speculation that China could use them to quell protests in Hong Kong.""But the BBC reports that under the city's Basic Law, direct military intervention is possible only if the Hong Kong government requests it. Instead, the South China Morning Post reports China is putting pressure on Hong Kong's police force to end the protests.""According to the BBC, China could also turn to political intervention, since Hong Kong's Legislative Council is only partly democratic, and largely pro-Beijing.""China is already showing its power by refusing to accept Chief Executive Carrie Lam's resignation and refusing to let her formally withdraw the controversial extradition bill.""Another possibility is for Beijing to target activists, as even without the extradition law, China is capable of detaining individual citizens.""According to the South China Morning Post, some Hong Kong residents have had China immigration officers at the border check photos and messages on their phones.""Despite fears of direct intervention, however, the BBC reports that Beijing's most effective tool may be economic. It can target the Hong Kong economy by redirecting investments to other Chinese cities, effectively making them more reliant on China."SOURCES: BBC, CNN, South China Morning Posthttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-49148762https://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/14/asia/paramilitary-force-china-hong-kong-hrk-intl/index.html?no-st=1565837699https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3022828/chinese-immigration-officials-inspect-hongkongers-phoneshttps://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3022665/beijing-unlikely-intervene-hong-kong-police-under-pressure***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/16/3876266/3876266_55F9EA33156E4662A94E4F5F1F5EB354_190816_3876266_How_could_China_intervene_in_the_Hong_Kong_prote_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hong kong protests, hk protests, hk extradition protest, China military intervention, hk police, China military forces, hong kong unrest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875935</guid>
      <title>How toxic blue-green algae can poison dogs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSeveral dogs have become fatally ill after swimming in lakes and ponds and ingesting water contaminated with toxic algae.According to the North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services, toxic blue green algae or cyanobacteria blooms typically infest bodies of stagnant fresh water during warm weather.The New York Times reports that while they can look like floating green sand or scum, some are found beneath the surface or attach to plants, and may not be immediately visible. Winds can also blow algae from one area into another.Dogs swimming in contaminated lakes or ponds can drink in the algae while in the water, or lick pieces of it off their wet fur.Those playing near the water can also nibble at or eat toxic algae that have dried into clumps on the shore.According to Blue Cross for Pets, toxins produced by blue-green algal blooms can stop a dog's liver from functioning properly.Exposure to toxic algae is almost always fatal, with some types capable of killing a dog just 15 minutes to an hour after ingestion.The dangers of exposing pets to blue-green algae gained national attention this year when a woman in North Carolina lost her three dogs after they went swimming in a pond.Pet owners in Texas and Georgia have also reported dog deaths following exposure to algal toxins.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Conditions for blue-green algal bloom2. Toxic algal bloom can be floating on water's surface or lurking underwater3. How dogs can be exposed to toxic algae4. How toxic algae can kill dogsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services, toxic blue green algae or cyanobacteria blooms typically infest bodies of stagnant fresh water during warm weather." "The New York Times reports that while they can look like floating green sand or scum, some are found beneath the surface or attach to plants, and may not be immediately visible.""Winds can also blow algae from one area into another.""Dogs swimming in contaminated lakes or ponds can drink in the algae while in the water, or lick pieces of it off their wet fur.""Those playing near the water can also nibble at or eat toxic algae that have dried into clumps on the shore.""According to Blue Cross for Pets, toxins produced by blue-green algal blooms can stop a dog's liver from functioning properly.""Exposure to toxic algae is almost always fatal, with some types capable of killing a dog just 15 minutes to an hour after ingestion."SOURCES: New York Times, CNN, North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services, Blue Cross for Petshttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/12/us/blue-green-algae-dogs.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/12/health/toxic-algae-dog-deaths-trnd/index.htmlhttps://epi.dph.ncdhhs.gov/oee/algae/protect.htmlhttps://www.bluecross.org.uk/pet-advice/blue-green-algae-and-its-dangers-dogs***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 07:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/15/3875935/3875935_158ADE2F59E047549DA806D984AAF257_190815_3875935_How_toxic_blue_green_algae_can_poison_dogs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, toxic algae, blue green algae, cyanobacteria, algae dogs, can algae poison dogs, algae ponds, toxic algae ponds, toxic algae warning, blue green algae warning, algae poisoning, cyanobacteria poisoning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875811</guid>
      <title>Tiny magnetic coils could be used to clean up microplastics in the ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA university of Adelaide-led research team has created a carbon nanotube that could help fight microplastic pollution in our oceans.Their research was presented in a study published in the journal Matter and was a collaboration between Australia's University of Adelaide, Curtin University, Edith Cowan University and China's Guangdong University of Technology.The carbon nanotubes are spiral in shape and have magnetic properties. The nanotubes are coated with nitrogen and embedded with manganese in their interior.The nanotubes are then mixed with peroxymonosulfate, a compound used as an oxidizing agent, to generate reactive oxygen species, or chemical reactions, to break down marine microplastics. The result is that the microplastics are converted into salt compounds, carbon dioxide and water.During a trial, researchers found that the spiral nanotubes were able to reduce the volume of microplastics present in polluted water between 30 to 50 percent in the span of eight hours.The nanotubes are retrieved using magnets for later use.Professor of Chemical Engineering from the University of Adelaide, Shaobin Wang, senior author of the study, explained in a news release from the university that the nanotubes are strong enough to break the microplastics down into compounds that aren't harmful to the ocean's ecosystem.Wang said that the byproducts of microplastics could be recycled and turned into an energy source for microorganisms, such as food for algae growth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Carbon nanotube and microplastic particles in the ocean2. What the carbon nanotube is made out of and how it works3. What the microplastics are broken down into4. Carbon nanotubes being retrieved by a magnetVOICEOVER (in English): "A university of Adelaide-led research team has created a carbon nanotube that could help fight microplastic pollution in our oceans.""Their research was presented in a study published in the journal Matter and was a collaboration between Australia's University of Adelaide, Curtin University, Edith Cowan University and China's Guangdong University of Technology.""The carbon nanotubes are spiral in shape and have magnetic properties. The nanotubes are coated with nitrogen and embedded with manganese in their interior.""The nanotubes are then mixed with peroxymonosulfate, a compound used as an oxidizing agent, to generate reactive oxygen species, or chemical reactions, to break down marine microplastics.""The result is that the microplastics are converted into salt compounds, carbon dioxide and water.""During a trial, researchers found that the spiral nanotubes were able to reduce the volume of microplastics present in polluted water between 30 to 50 percent in the span of eight hours.""The nanotubes are retrieved using magnets for later use."SOURCES: Sustainability Times, Matter, Science News, University of Adelaide https://www.sustainability-times.com/environmental-protection/tiny-spirals-could-help-rid-the-oceans-of-microplastics/https://www.cell.com/matter/fulltext/S2590-2385(19)30056-6#%20https://www.sciencenews.org/article/tiny-magnetic-coils-could-help-break-down-microplastic-pollutionhttps://www.adelaide.edu.au/news/news108382.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 04:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/15/3875811/3875811_97380372CE89463586DC5EDFEEB047F8_190815_3875811_Tiny_magnetic_coils_could_be_used_to_clean_up_mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, plastic particles, microplastics pollution,  plastic bags, plastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, tiny spirals, microplastics, tiny spirals microplastics, microplastic pollution, microplastic ocean pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876387</guid>
      <title>Scientists find microplastic particles in rainwater collected from the Rocky Mountains</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the U.S. Geological Survey has found microscopic plastic fibers present in rainwater from Rocky Mountain National Park in Colorado.According to a study published by the U.S. Geological Survey, researchers involved in the study obtained rainwater samples from different altitudes from the Front Range of the Rocky Mountains. The samples were collected using buckets lined with plastic bags. Scientists analyzed the rainwater samples with binocular microscope fitted with a digital camera.Plastic was found in more than 90 percent of the sampled rainwater, according to the study.Researchers discovered that the samples mostly contained plastic fibers in a wide range of colors such as red, silver, purple, green and yellow. They also found beads and shards in the rainwater samples.Microplastics have previously been found in the depths of oceans, lakes and rivers across the U.S. and even the Pyrenees mountains, the Guardian reports. According to the U.S. National Library of Medicine, microplastics are able to absorb and give off chemicals and pollutants. These may build up over time and persist in the environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rocky Mountains, rain and microscopic plastic fibers 2. Where and how the samples were collected 3. How the samples were analyzed4. Microplastics found in the samples VOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the U.S. Geological Survey has found microscopic plastic fibers present in rainwater from Rocky Mountain National Park in Colorado.""Researchers involved in the study obtained rainwater samples from different altitudes from the Front Range of the Rocky Mountains.""The samples were collected using buckets lined with plastic bags." "Scientists analyzed the rainwater samples with binocular microscope fitted with a digital camera.""According to the study, plastic was found in more than 90 percent of the sampled rainwater.""Researchers discovered that the samples mostly contained plastic fibers in a wide range of colors such as red, silver, purple, green and yellow.""They also found beads and shards in the rainwater samples."SOURCES: The Guardian, U.S. Geological Survey, The Independent, U.S. National Library of Medicinehttps://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/aug/12/raining-plastic-colorado-usgs-microplasticshttps://pubs.usgs.gov/of/2019/1048/ofr20191048.pdfhttps://www.independent.co.uk/environment/plastic-microplastics-pollution-rocky-mountains-remote-planet-a9055506.htmlhttps://toxtown.nlm.nih.gov/sources-of-exposure/microplastics***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/16/3876387/3876387_EAAB013059DD4758A893A44AA649241F_190816_3876387_Scientists_find_microplastic_particles_in_rainwa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Microscopic fibers, rocky mountains, plastic pollution,  microplastics, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic bags, plastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877635</guid>
      <title>A massive collision with a planet bigger than earth may be the answer to Jupiter's unusual core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA cosmic collision between Jupiter and a protoplanet billions of years ago could explain the unexpected readings from NASA's Juno space probe.According to a press release by Rice University, data from NASA's Juno space probe reported gravitational readings that suggest Jupiter's core is less dense and more extended than expected. Rice astronomer Andrea Isella said the readings are puzzling, and that something happened that may have "stirred up the core".After running thousands of computer simulations, the research team deduced that a fast-growing young Jupiter from some 4.5 billion years ago could have "perturbed" nearby embryo planets, resulting in a massive impact.  Isella said that because of Jupiter's, "strong gravitational focusing," head-on collisions were more common during the simulations. The dense high energy impactor would have been, "like a bullet", cutting the atmosphere and hitting the core of Jupiter directly.Isella stated that before an impact, the core is extremely dense as it is surrounded by an atmosphere. A head-on collision would "spread things out" and "dilute the core".RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A diagram showing Jupiter's layers and core2. A planet is inbound for Jupiter3. A planet collides for Jupiter4. A diagram shows Jupiter's core after the explosionVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a press release by Rice University, data from NASA's Juno space probe reported gravitational readings that suggest Jupiter's core is less dense and more extended than expected." "Rice astronomer Andrea Isella said the readings are puzzling, and that something happened that may have 'stirred up the core'.""After running thousands of computer simulations, the research team deduced that a fast-growing young Jupiter from some 4.5 billion years ago could have 'perturbed' nearby embryo planets, resulting in a massive impact."  "Isella said that because of Jupiter's, 'strong gravitational focusing,' head-on collisions were more common during the simulations. The dense high energy impactor would have been, 'like a bullet', cutting the atmosphere and hitting the core of Jupiter directly.""Isella stated that before an impact, the core is extremely dense as it is surrounded by an atmosphere. A head-on collision would 'spread things out' and 'dilute the core'.SOURCES: Rice University, https://news.rice.edu/2019/08/14/young-jupiter-was-smacked-head-on-by-massive-newborn-planet-2/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 23:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/19/3877635/3877635_7042A0C1E5A64E1D90BBAEE97080CC1A_190819_3877635_A_massive_collision_with_a_planet_bigger_than_ea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Jupiters core, Jupiter collision with planet, NASA's Juno, Jupiter's strange core, collision made Jupiter's core weird, planetary collision, Jupiter simulation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877984</guid>
      <title>Mysterious radio waves detected from outer space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew radio waves from outer space have been detected by the Canadian Hydrogen Intensity Mapping Experiment radio telescope, also known as CHIME.The findings were submitted to the Astrophysical Journal Letters. It described eight new repeating signals that were detected by the radio telescope.According to the EU Research & Innovation Magazine, these fast radio bursts, or FRBs, typically last only a few milliseconds but are able to emit more energy than 500 million suns.The telescope consists of four cylindrical reflectors, each of which are lined with 256 antennas. It continuously scans separate points in the sky, 24 hours a day, seven days a week, searching for FRBs, according to CHIME's website. In a separate study published in the journal Nature in January, CHIME had previously detected 13 fast radio bursts, only one of which was repeating.Researchers noticed that among the radio bursts studied, those that sent off signals multiple times tended to send out bursts that lasted a bit longer than radio bursts that only sent out signals once.These repeating FRBs could shed new light on the origin of these radio waves and what exactly causes them, according to the newly submitted paper. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Radio waves from outer space and the CHIME telescope2. How long these radio waves last and how much energy it emits3. How the telescope works4. Fast radio bursts previously detected by the telescopeVOICEOVER (in English): "New radio waves from outer space have been detected by the Canadian Hydrogen Intensity Mapping Experiment radio telescope, also known as CHIME.""The findings were submitted to the Astrophysical Journal Letters. It described eight new repeating signals that were detected by the radio telescope.""According to the EU Research & Innovation Magazine, these fast radio bursts, or FRBs, typically last only a few milliseconds but are able to emit more energy than 500 million suns.""The telescope consists of four cylindrical reflectors, each of which are lined with 256 antennas.""According to CHIME's website, the telescope continuously scans separate points in the sky, 24 hours a day, seven days a week, searching for FRBs.""In a separate study published in the journal Nature in January, CHIME had previously detected 13 fast radio bursts, only one of which was repeating.""Researchers noticed that among the radio bursts studied, those that sent off signals multiple times tended to send out bursts that lasted a bit longer than radio bursts that only sent out signals once."SOURCES: EU Research & Innovation Magazine , Science Magazine, Fox News, The Astrophysical Journal Letters, BBC News, Nature, Chime https://horizon-magazine.eu/article/why-hunting-fast-radio-bursts-exploding-field-astronomy.htmlhttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/08/observatory-bags-haul-mysterious-repeating-radio-burstshttps://arxiv.org/abs/1908.03507https://www.foxnews.com/science/astronomers-intercept-radio-signal-from-galaxy-billion-light-years-awayhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-46811618https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-00049-5https://chime-experiment.ca/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 11:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/19/3877984/3877984_5AA3D03FFF124B98868C0EBFE9F97D9C_190819_3877984_Mysterious_radio_waves_detected_from_outer_space_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, radio waves, radio telescope, mysterious radio waves from space, astronomy radio waves, fast radio bursts, Canadian Hydrogen Intensity Mapping Experiment, CHIME telescope, CHIME]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877928</guid>
      <title>Unprecedented heat wave causes massive salmon die-offs in Alaska</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANClimate change and warming waters have caused the mass deaths of salmon in some parts of Alaska. CNN reports that large amounts of salmon are dying off in Alaska due to the unprecedented heat wave that gripped the state in July and caused water temperatures to reach up to 81.7 degrees Fahrenheit.In a Twitter post, Yukon Inter-Tribal Fish Commission Director Stephanie Quinn-Davidson said she and other scientists counted 850 dead chum salmon when they checked a 200 mile stretch of river during a July expedition.According to the Independent, it's normal for salmon to die off after they spawn. But since most of the dead fish were found with healthy eggs still in their bodies, scientists believed they died of heat stress before reaching their spawning grounds.According to Sue Mauger, science director for the Cook Inletkeeper, fish can't get oxygen moving through their bellies in warm water.Temperature can also affect metabolism and organ function, making the fish less able to fight off parasites and pathogens.The Independent reports that scientists stopped seeing dead salmon as soon as the temperatures cooled back down.According to CNN, extreme heat brought about by climate change isn't the only thing stressing North American salmon populations.In southwestern Canada and Northwestern Washington, salmon are being threatened by overfishing. A mining project in Alaska that's no longer being opposed by the EPA could also devastate one of the world's most valuable wild salmon fisheries.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Salmon die-offs in Alaska due to warming temperatures2. Salmon died from heat stress before reaching spawning grounds3. How warm temperatures can affect salmon4. Salmon stopped dying once temperatures cooled downVOICEOVER (in English): "CNN reports that large amounts of salmon are dying off in Alaska due to the unprecedented heat wave that gripped the state in July and caused water temperatures to reach up to 81.7 degrees Fahrenheit.""According to the Independent, it's normal for salmon to die off after they spawn. But since most of the dead fish were found with healthy eggs still in their bodies, scientists believed they died of heat stress before reaching their spawning grounds.""According to Sue Mauger, science director for the Cook Inletkeeper, fish can't get oxygen moving through their bellies in warm water.""Temperature can also affect metabolism and organ function, making the fish less able to fight off parasites and pathogens.""The Independent reports that scientists stopped seeing dead salmon as soon as the temperatures cooled back down."SOURCES: CNN, The Independent, Cook Inletkeeperhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/16/us/alaska-salmon-hot-water-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.independent.co.uk/environment/alaska-heatwave-salmon-rivers-july-temperatures-climate-change-a9063461.htmlhttps://inletkeeper.org/2019/07/10/salmon-stream-temperatures-off-the-charts/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 10:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/19/3877928/3877928_82EBCEE5E7E74481BD814290211709D3_190819_3877928_Unprecedented_heat_wave_causes_massive_salmon_di_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, salmon die off, salmon dying off, Alaska heat wave, Alaska salmon, Alaskan salmon, salmon heat wave, salmon climate change, climate change, dead salmon, salmon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877833</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover new pain-sensing organ in the skin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSwedish scientists have discovered a new organ under the skin that helps process certain kinds of pain.According to National Geographic, mechanical pain was typically thought to be perceived through sensitive nerve cell endings in the epidermis.Unlike other nerve cells, these lacked a protective layer and was thus believed to be responsible for pain sensation.But researchers from Sweden's Karolinska Institutet recently uncovered a sensory organ between the skin's outer and inner layers, consisting of a mesh-like network of glial cells with multiple long protrusions.This newly discovered organ has been dubbed the nociceptive glio-neural complex, and is highly sensitive to mechanical stimuli such as pinpricks or pressure. It is less sensitive to discomfort caused by heat or cold.To test the organ's functionality, the team genetically modified mice so that glial cells on the skin of their feet could be stimulated by light.When light was shone on the cells, the mice exhibited behavior that indicated pain, including lifting their feet, and licking, shaking, or guarding their paws.While the organ has been identified in mice, scientists have yet to confirm that it exists in humans, though the probability is high.Assuming it functions the same way in humans, the findings could change the way we think about how pain starts and progresses. It may also be significant in the understanding of chronic pain.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mechanical pain thought to be perceived by sensitive nerve endings2. Network of glial cells discovered within skin3. Glial cell network sensitive to mechanical stimuli4. Testing on miceVOICEOVER (in English): "According to National Geographic, mechanical pain was typically thought to be perceived through sensitive nerve cell endings in the epidermis.""Unlike other nerve cells, these lacked a protective layer and was thus believed to be responsible for pain sensation.""But researchers from Sweden's Karolinska Institutet recently uncovered a sensory organ between the skin's outer and inner layers, consisting of a mesh-like network of glial cells with multiple long protrusions.""This newly discovered organ has been dubbed the nociceptive glio-neural complex, and is highly sensitive to mechanical stimuli such as pinpricks or pressure. It is less sensitive to discomfort caused by heat or cold.""To test the organ's functionality, the team genetically modified mice so that glial cells on the skin of their feet could be stimulated by light.""When light was shone on the cells, the mice exhibited behavior that indicated pain, including lifting their feet, and licking, shaking, or guarding their paws."SOURCES: National Geographic, Karolina Institutet via EurekAlerthttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/08/newly-discovered-organ-may-be-lurking-uinder-your-skin-senses-pain/https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-08/ki-npo081319.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 08:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/19/3877833/3877833_55B731A608FF46EF8A3B5B117C0585E3_190819_3877833_Scientists_discover_new_pain_sensing_organ_in_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pain organ, new pain organ, pain perception, mechanical pain, glio neural complex, schwann cells, nociceptive schwann cells, nerve endings, nerve cells, sensory organ, new organ]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877686</guid>
      <title>The search for Amelia Earhart's plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have long wondered what really happened to Amelia Earhart, the first ever female aviator to fly solo.A group of researchers led by National Geographic Explorer Robert Ballard are embarking on a mission on the E/V Nautilus ship to waters off Nikumaroro Island to search for the remnants of Amelia Earhart's plane.The ship is equipped with multiple exploration tools, including an autonomous surface vehicle developed by the University of New Hampshire called Bathymetric Explorer and Navigator, or BEN.According to a news release by the university, the vehicle includes features such as the Kongsberg EM2040P multibeam echo-sounder and the Applanix POS/ MV navigation system. This allows the self-driving vehicle to create 3D topographic maps and acoustic backscatter maps of the ocean floor.Once the autonomous surface vehicle returns to the ship, researchers will analyze data from the maps and then deploy two remotely operated vehicles called Hercules and Argus, according to National Geographic. These are typically launched at night and can reach depths of 4,000 meters.Hercules is able to provide a first person view of the seabed, while the Argus is a smaller vehicle that captures footage of Hercules. Hercules can collect samples found in the seabed and store them in a container in its side for researchers to analyze.The mission is the subject of a two-hour documentary titled Expedition Amelia and will air on National Geographic on October 20.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. E/V Nautilus ship, autonomous surface vehicle, and Nikumaroro Island on a map2. Features of the autonomous surface vehicle3. Two remotely operated vehicles, Hercules and Argus, being sent under the sea4. Hercules collects samples while Argus films HerculesVOICEOVER (in English): "A group of researchers led by National Geographic Explorer Robert Ballard are embarking on a mission on the E/V Nautilus ship to waters off Nikumaroro Island to search for the remnants of Amelia Earhart's plane.""The ship is equipped with multiple exploration tools, including an autonomous surface vehicle developed by the University of New Hampshire called Bathymetric Explorer and Navigator, or BEN.""According to a news release by the university, the vehicle includes features such as the Kongsberg EM2040P multibeam echo-sounder and the Applanix POS/ MV navigation system.""This allows the self-driving vehicle to create 3D topographic maps and acoustic backscatter maps of the ocean floor.""According to National Geographic, once the autonomous surface vehicle returns to the ship, researchers will analyze data from the maps and then deploy two remotely operated vehicles called Hercules and Argus.""These are typically launched at night and can reach depths of 4,000 meters.""Hercules is able to provide a first person view of the seabed, while the Argus is a smaller vehicle that captures footage of Hercules.""Hercules can collect samples found in the seabed and store them in a container in its side for researchers to analyze."SOURCES: University of New Hampshire, National Geographic, New Atlas, Science Daily, BBC News  https://www.unh.edu/unhtoday/news/release/2019/08/13/unh-technology-helps-map-way-solve-mystery-pilot-amelia-earharthttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/culture/2019/08/inside-search-for-amelia-earhart-airplane/https://newatlas.com/autonomous-boat-amelia-earhart/61082/https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/08/190814140507.htmhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49231625***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 03:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/19/3877686/3877686_C0B25FA142FA4BF49CDED61BF5B3E6A1_190819_3877686_The_search_for_Amelia_Earhart_s_plane_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, amelia earhart, amelia earhart mystery, amelia earhart plane, autonomous watercraft, Bathymetric Explorer and Navigator, airplane mysteries, Nikumaroro Islands, airplane mysteries]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878474</guid>
      <title>Pentagon tests missile previously banned under the INF treaty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWashington has conducted its first test of a missile that was previously banned under the Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces Treaty, INF, after the U.S. President Donald Trump's administration formally withdrew from the treaty on August 2.On August 18, the Pentagon conducted a flight test of a conventionally configured ground-launched cruise missile from San Nicolas Island, California.In a statement sent to Newsweek, a Pentagon spokesperson said that the missile "was a variant of the Tomahawk Land Attack Missile."The test missile was launched from a ground mobile launcher and precisely hit its target after flying more than 500 kilometers, according to a news release by the U.S. Department of Defense. The missile used a conventional warhead, not a nuclear warhead, the Associated Press reports, citing the Pentagon. The Tomahawk Land Attack Missile has a range of around 1,600 kilometers, according to the U.S. Navy. The Pentagon said that it intends to begin testing of another non-nuclear ballistic missile with an estimated range of around 3,000 to 4,000 kilometers.The U.S. Department of Defense said in a news release that data collected from this missile test will "inform our development of future intermediate-range capabilities."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The missile being launched and a map of where it was launched2. The missile in the sky3. The range of the missile4. A non-nuclear ballistic missile and its estimated range5. INF treaty, flag of the former U.S.S.R. and the U.S.6. The treaty bans missiles with a certain rangeVOICEOVER (in English): "On August 18, the Pentagon conducted a flight test of a conventionally configured ground-launched cruise missile from San Nicolas Island, California.""In a statement sent to Newsweek, a Pentagon spokesperson said that the missile 'was a variant of the Tomahawk Land Attack Missile.'""According to a news release by the U.S. Department of Defense, the test missile was launched from a ground mobile launcher and precisely hit its target after flying more than 500 kilometers.""Citing the Pentagon, the Associated Press reports that the missile used a conventional warhead, not a nuclear warhead.""According to the U.S. Navy, the Tomahawk Land Attack Missile has a range of around 1,600 kilometers.""The Pentagon said that it intends to begin testing of another non-nuclear ballistic missile with an estimated range of around 3,000 to 4,000 kilometers.""The Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces Treaty, or INF, was signed between the Soviet Union and the U.S. 30 years ago.""The treaty banned the use of nuclear and non-nuclear missiles between the ranges of 500 and 5,500 kilometers."SOURCES: The Associated Press, U.S. Department of Defense, Defense News, U.S. Department of State, CNN, Newsweek, U.S. Navy, The Guardian, The Washington Posthttps://apnews.com/a21db991b4004d14a40c6d095ad9dda5https://www.defense.gov/Newsroom/Releases/Release/Article/1937624/dod-conducts-ground-launch-cruise-missile-test/https://www.defensenews.com/pentagon/2019/08/19/pentagon-tests-first-land-based-cruise-missile-in-a-post-inf-treaty-world/https://www.state.gov/u-s-withdrawal-from-the-inf-treaty-on-august-2-2019/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/19/politics/test-ground-launch-cruise-missile/index.htmlhttps://www.newsweek.com/us-tests-missile-banned-decades-ignoring-warnings-russia-1455083https://www.navy.mil/navydata/fact_display.asp?cid=2200&tid=1300&ct=2https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/us-inf-russia-nuclear-treaty-deadlinehttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/trump-administration-gives-russia-60-days-to-comply-with-inf-treaty-or-the-us-will-move-to-withdraw/2018/12/04/64c5bec2-f74a-11e8-8642-c9718a256cbd_story.html?noredirect=on&utm_term=.83afcb6db0ed***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 11:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/20/3878474/3878474_8C5DBE2031E248D9B195C214DA6287EE_190820_3878474_Pentagon_tests_missile_previously_banned_under_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, INF treaty, US, Russia, us russia inf treaty, pentagon missile test, pentagon tests missile banned under the inf treaty, tomahawk missile test, nuclear arms agreement, intermediate-range nuclear forces treaty, inf treaty explained, inf treaty withdrawal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878462</guid>
      <title>Ocean Cleanup to deploy updated version of its plastic-catching barriers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Ocean Cleanup, a non-profit organization developing technologies to rid the oceans of plastic, has launched the second version of its cleanup system.The Ocean Cleanup has redesigned its cleanup system and added a parachute for the system to collect plastic waste at a more consistent speed.In the new system, called System 001/B, the parachute will work to slow down the cleanup system and allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system. This is to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system.According to the Ocean Cleanup, the previous system, called System 001, would sometimes travel faster than the plastic and sometimes travel slower than the plastic.This means that the plastic would float into the cleanup system, only to float out again.The system's plastic-collecting screen has also been moved forward to prevent fracturing to the system's floating barrier. The floats of the current cork line are 15 centimeters long and are used to hold the screen in place.The company will add bigger floats to the cork line to increase its buoyancy. Each float will be 32 centimeters in diameter, according to the Ocean Cleanup's website. These are to be stacked on one another in order to prevent plastic from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier.The company said on its website that the new cleanup system is ready and will soon be deployed to the oceans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ocean Cleanup system and a parachute 2. How the parachute would work in the system3. Plastic-collecting screen has been moved forward4. Bigger floats for the systemVOICEOVER (in English): "The Ocean Cleanup has redesigned its cleanup system and added a parachute for the system to collect plastic waste at a more consistent speed.""In the new system, called System 001/B, the parachute will work to slow down the cleanup system and allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system." "This is to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system.""The system's plastic-collecting screen has also been moved forward to prevent fracturing to the system's floating barrier.""The floats of the current cork line are 15 centimeters long and are used to hold the screen in place.""According to the Ocean Cleanup's website, the company will add bigger floats to the cork line to increase its buoyancy. Each float will be 32 centimeters in diameter.""These are to be stacked on one another in order to prevent plastic from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier."SOURCES: New Atlas, The Ocean Cleanup, Dezeen https://newatlas.com/ocean-cleanup-parachutes-plastic/61119/https://theoceancleanup.com/updates/into-the-twilight-zone/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=knfUyJO0TGAhttps://www.dezeen.com/2019/06/24/ocean-cleanup-redeployed-great-pacific-garbage-patch-news/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 11:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/20/3878462/3878462_BD67A24721E8409284ADD997B056E267_190820_3878462_Ocean_Cleanup_to_deploy_updated_version_of_its_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ocean, ocean cleanup 2019, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup technology,  ocean cleanup project 2019, ocean cleanup, plastic pollution, polluted oceans, technology, cleaning up the oceans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878237</guid>
      <title>Microplastics found in Arctic sea ice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers aboard the Swedish Icebreaker Oden as part of the Northwest Passage Project, an 18-day expedition through the Northwest Passage, have found microplastics polluting ice from the Arctic Ocean.The researchers first used a helicopter to land on ice floes, Reuters reports. They then used a drill to obtain a total of 18 ice core samples from four locations. The team shared images of the sampled ice containing visibly different shapes and sizes of plastic beads and filaments.The team plans to analyze the ice samples to get a better understanding of how plastic particles in ice could affect fish, seabirds and large ocean mammals in the Arctic.The Northwest Passage Project's main aim is to make assessments on how climate change is impacting the Arctic. According to the project's website, the mission specifically focused on four research areas. Scientists gathered data on water mass and circulation inside the Canadian Arctic Archipelago to analyze how the water column chemistry affects greenhouse gas accumulation.They also examined how microscopic habitats are transitioning because of climate conditions and monitored marine bird distribution in the Arctic region.The expedition took place between July 18 to August 4.In a separate study published in the journal Science Advances, scientists found microplastics present in Arctic sea ice, as well as the Arctic water column and its surface waters. Researchers in the study assessed that the plastic particles found in the Arctic are transported by the wind.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Icebreaker Oden and microplastics in Arctic ice2. Scientists obtaining ice core samples3. An ice sample with plastic particles in it, being analyzed to find out its effects on fish,  seabirds and whales 4. How microplastics could be transporting to the ArcticVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers aboard the Swedish Icebreaker Oden as part of the Northwest Passage Project, an 18-day expedition through the Northwest Passage, have found microplastics polluting ice from the Arctic Ocean.""Reuters reports the researchers first used a helicopter to land on ice floes. They then used a drill to obtain a total of 18 ice core samples from four locations.""The team shared images of the sampled ice containing visibly different shapes and sizes of plastic beads and filaments.""The team plans to analyze the ice samples to get a better understanding of how plastic particles in ice could affect fish, seabirds and large ocean mammals in the Arctic.""In a separate study published in the journal Science Advances, scientists found microplastics present in Arctic sea ice, as well as the Arctic water column and its surface waters.""Researchers in the study assessed that the plastic particles found in the Arctic are transported by the wind."SOURCES: Phys.org, Reuters, Science Advances https://phys.org/news/2019-08-arctic-sea-ice-microplastics.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/video/2019/08/17/scientists-find-microplastics-deep-in-ar?videoId=587718020https://www.reuters.com/article/us-environment-arctic-plastic/punch-in-the-gut-as-scientists-find-micro-plastic-in-arctic-ice-idUSKCN1V41V2https://advances.sciencemag.org/content/5/8/eaax1157***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 05:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/20/3878237/3878237_E155411C81EC4416AC05E25DAE2DE67C_190820_3878237_Microplastics_found_in_Arctic_sea_ice_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Arctic, arctic ice, arctic sea, arctic ocean, microplastic in arctic sea ice, microplastic arctic sea, arctic sea ice microplastics, climate change, microplastics, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, microplastic particles, microplastics in the arctic, microplastic pollution, microplastic arctic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878896</guid>
      <title>Florida palms suffering from Lethal Bronzing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPalm trees in Florida are under severe threat from a condition known as Lethal Bronzing Disease, an illness that can kill the trees in months. University of Florida researchers detail the condition as being caused by parasitic bacteria and spread by common sap-sucking insects.Brian Bahderm, an assistant professor at the University of Florida, explained to the Miami Herald that Lethal Bronzing is transmitted through the saliva of sap-sucking insects when they feast on the palm's leaves.Lethal Bronzing occurs when the bacteria known as phytoplasmas, multiply in the bottom of the tree and "clog the circulatory system." This build-up creates a blockage, resulting in the tree being starved from sufficient nutrients, giving it the tell-tale shade of bronze leaves.  Researchers from the University of Florida identified four more palms that are susceptible to the disease; the Pindo palm, Carpentaria palm, Coconut palm, and the Chinese fan palm, bringing the tally now to 16.They also state that Lethal Bronzing has spread statewide to include eight new Florida counties, with tens of thousands of palms already dead as a result.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Palm tree diagram showing disease2. Insect transmitting the disease to the tree3. X-ray example of how Lethal Bronzing works4. A line-up of palm trees affectedVOICEOVER (in English): "Palm trees in Florida are under severe threat from a condition known as Lethal Bronzing Disease, an illness that turns palms to a crisp in months. The University of Florida details the condition as being caused by parasitic bacteria and spread by common sap-sucking insects.""Brian Bahderm, an assistant professor at the University of Florida explained to the Miami Herald that Lethal Bronzing is transmitted through the saliva of sap-sucking insects when they feast on the palm's leaves.""Lethal Bronzing occurs when the bacteria known as phytoplasmas, multiply in the bottom of the tree and 'clog the circulatory system.'" This build-up creates a blockage, resulting in the tree being starved from sufficient nutrients, giving it the tell-tale shade of bronze leaves."   "Researchers from the University of Florida identified four more palms that are susceptible to the disease; the Pindo palm, Carpentaria palm, Coconut palm, and the Chinese fan palm, bringing the tally now to 16.""They also state that Lethal Bronzing has spread statewide to include eight new Florida counties, with tens of thousands of palm's already dead as a result." SOURCES: University of Florida, Miami Herald, The New York Timeshttp://epi.ufl.edu/news/lethal-bronzing-expands-hosts-and-range.htmlhttp://edis.ifas.ufl.edu/pdffiles/PP/PP16300.pdfhttps://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article234143902.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2019/08/19/us/ap-us-florida-palms-endangered.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 09:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/21/3878896/3878896_2042163EC80B4642B419F084B7649050_190821_3878896_Florida_palms_suffering_from_Lethal_Bronzing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  Florida's palm disease, Florida's palms threatened, Lethal Bronzing disease, Florida lethal bronzing, palm tree disease Florida, Florida palm disease, Palm tree disease in Florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878850</guid>
      <title>Even nicotine-free e-cigarettes can harm blood flow, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that vaping temporarily is enough to impact the body's blood vessels.Scientists from the University of Pennsylvania asked 31 nonsmoking participants to inhale electronic cigarettes 16 times for three seconds each. The e-cigarettes included ingredients such as propylene glycol, glycerol and flavoring, but did not contain any nicotine.Researchers involved in the study, published in the journal Radiology, took MRI scans of the participants after they vaped. They found that all of the participants' blood vessels in the brain, heart vessels and femoral arteries had become constricted by 30 percent.In comparison, a separate study from the British Journal of Pharmacology found that smoking cigarettes reduced blood flow by 31 percent.In a statement emailed to Wired, Juul, an e-cigarette company that controls over 70 percent of the vaping market in the U.S., noted that the study called for the participants to inhale an unrealistic number of times in a short period of time.This caused a reduction of oxygen flow in the blood vessels by 20 percent.In an email to Reuters, lead author of the study, Alessandra Caporale from the University's Perelman School of Medicine, explained that the usage of e-cigarettes is not equivalent to inhaling water vapor, even if the e-cigarette does not contain any nicotine.Caporale said that the impact of vaping on the blood vessels was temporary. Though, she added, long-term effects of vaping could include inflammation and deterioration of blood vessels.The researchers are planning another study that would take an in-depth look into the impact of vaping on e-cigarette users, cigarette smokers and non-smokers over time, according to Reuters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A participant inhaling an e-cigarette and ingredients of the e-cigarettes2. How vaping affected the blood vessels of the participants3. Vaping reducing oxygen flow in the blood vessels4. E-cigarettes not equivalent to inhaling water vaporVOICEOVER (in English): "New research has found that vaping temporarily is enough to impact the body's blood vessels.""Scientists from the University of Pennsylvania asked 31 nonsmoking participants to inhale electronic cigarettes 16 times for three seconds each.""The e-cigarettes included ingredients such as propylene glycol, glycerol and flavoring, but did not contain any nicotine.""Researchers involved in the study, published in the journal Radiology, took MRI scans of the participants after they vaped.""They found that all of the participants' blood vessels in the brain, heart vessels and femoral arteries had become constricted by 30 percent.""This caused a reduction of oxygen flow in the blood vessels by 20 percent.""In an email to Reuters, lead author of the study, Alessandra Caporale from the University's Perelman School of Medicine, explained that the usage of e-cigarettes is not equivalent to inhaling water vapor, even if the e-cigarette does not contain any nicotine."SOURCES: CNN, Radiology, Reuters, British Journal of Pharmacology, Wiredhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/20/health/vaping-cardiovascular-study/index.htmlhttps://pubs.rsna.org/doi/10.1148/radiol.2019190562https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-vaping/vaping-impacts-blood-vessels-even-without-nicotine-idUSKCN1VA29Thttps://bpspubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1476-5381.1972.tb09571.xhttps://www.wired.com/story/vaping-may-harm-your-blood-flow-even-without-nicotine/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 08:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/21/3878850/3878850_8D16B9EE37FD46CF89FF7009C7586F0E_190821_3878850_Even_nicotine_free_e_cigarettes_can_harm_blood_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, vaping side effects, vaping, effects of vaping, how vaping affects the body, e-cigarettes, nicotine free e-cigarettes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878836</guid>
      <title>NASA announces mission to study Jupiter's moon Europa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has announced plans to launch the Europa Clipper space mission to examine Jupiter's icy moon Europa by 2025.The mission aims to identify whether or not life could exist on Europa, according to the U.S. space agency's website.The Europa Clipper spacecraft will orbit around Jupiter and make 45 flybys to Europa from altitudes ranging from 25 kilometers to 2,700 kilometers above the moon's surface.The Europa Clipper mission will consist of a Europa Clipper spacecraft that would carry instruments such as an ice-penetrating radar to determine the thickness of the moon's outer crust. A thermal instrument will also be carried onboard to search for recent eruptions of warmer water on the moon's surface. The ice-penetrating radar will also look for subsurface lakes underneath Europa's frozen surface.In 2012, NASA's Hubble Space Telescope detected water vapor above Europa's south polar region, providing strong evidence that there could be water plumes  and potentially a subsurface ocean  on Europa.The mission will also search for evidence of tiny particles and water in Europa's atmosphere. Cameras and spectrometers are to be taken onboard to take images of Europa's surface and to determine its composition.According to NASA, the space agency is targeting to have the Europa Clipper spacecraft ready as soon as 2023, in order for the mission to be cost-effective. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Europa Clipper spacecraft and Europa2. The spacecraft orbiting Jupiter and then making a flyby to Europa3. Instruments the spacecraft would carry, cross section of Europa4. Tiny particles, a drop of water from Europa and a camera taking pictures of EuropaVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA has announced plans to launch the Europa Clipper space mission to examine Jupiter's icy moon Europa by 2025.""According to the U.S. space agency's website, the mission aims to identify whether or not life could exist on Europa.""The Europa Clipper spacecraft will orbit around Jupiter and make 45 flybys to Europa from altitudes ranging from 25 kilometers to 2,700 kilometers above the moon's surface.""The Europa Clipper mission will consist of a Europa Clipper spacecraft that would carry instruments such as an ice-penetrating radar to determine the thickness of the moon's outer crust." "A thermal instrument will also be carried onboard to search for recent eruptions of warmer water on the moon's surface.""The ice-penetrating radar will also look for subsurface lakes underneath Europa's frozen surface.""The mission will also search for evidence of tiny particles and water in Europa's atmosphere.""Cameras and spectrometers are to be taken onboard to take images of Europa's surface and to determine its composition."SOURCES: New Atlas, NASA https://newatlas.com/nasa-confirms-europa-clipper/61133/https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7480https://europa.nasa.gov/https://europa.nasa.gov/about-clipper/overview/https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/missions/europa-clipper/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 08:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/21/3878836/3878836_0F00ACF4EBCD4E589109E05AAC798BAF_190821_3878836_NASA_announces_mission_to_study_Jupiter_s_moon_E_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, nasa, space exploration, europa clipper mission, jupiter, jupiter's icy moon, nasa europa mission, Europa, jupiter europa, jupiter icy moon, jupiter icy moon mission, NASA, mission, astrobiology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879386</guid>
      <title>U.S. approves $8 billion F16 sale to Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLockheed Martin details their new-build Block 70 F16 as having a speed of 1,500 miles per hour, a wingspan of 31 feet and an empty weight of 20,300 pounds.The latest F16s have received upgrades such as the Active Electronically Scanned Array radar, which provides pilots with superior target detail, greater "situational awareness" and digital maps to its high-resolution 6"x 8" screen which can be customized with "slew" and zoom features.The fighter also comes with a structural upgrade that extends the aircraft's lifespan by more than 50 percent compared to the previous model.Most crucially, the F16 commands the Automatic Ground Collision Avoidance System, which is designed to reduce incidents of controlled flight into terrain which is responsible for 75 percent of all F-16 pilot fatalities.The system predicts imminent collision and performs flight maneuvers to avoid ground impact.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Details of F162. F16 flying and using its radar system3. A cutaway of the F164. F16 software avoids ground impactVOICEOVER (in English): "Lockheed Martin details their new-build Block 70 F16 as having a speed of 1,500 miles per hour, a wingspan of 31 feet and an empty weight of 20,300 pounds.""The latest F16's have received upgrades such as the Active Electronically Scanned Array radar, which provides pilots with superior target detail, greater 'situational awareness' and digital maps to its high-resolution 6"x 8" screen which can be customized with 'slew' and zoom features.""The fighter also comes with a structural upgrade that extends the aircraft's lifespan by more than 50 percent compared to the previous model.""Most crucially, the F16 commands the Automatic Ground Collision Avoidance System, which is designed to reduce incidents of controlled flight into terrain which is responsible for 75 percent of all F-16 pilot fatalities.""The system predicts imminent collision and performs flight maneuvers to avoid ground impact."SOURCES:  Lockheed Martin,https://www.lockheedmartin.com/en-us/products/f-16.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 08:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/22/3879386/3879386_84F43F088DBC4CBABDADA19BD38A1C63_190822_3879386_U_S__approves__8_billion_F16_sale_to_Taiwan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, F16, US sells F16 Taiwan, Taiwan wants F16's, F16 top speed, F16 specs, F16 crash, F16V, F16 model, Trump approves F16 sale]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879826</guid>
      <title>Vulnerabilities found in Google's Indoor Nest camera: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report by Cisco Talos, a cyber security intelligence and research group, has found eight different vulnerabilities in Google's Indoor Nest cameras.One of the bugs, called CVE-2019-5043, allowed multiple connection attempts to the camera's TCP, or Transmission Control Protocol, which would cause the camera's system to crash. While another bug allowed attackers to acquire and read sensitive information from the cameras.Two code security vulnerabilities, named CVE-2019-5038 and CVE-2019-5039, allowed attackers to exploit the camera's security system by luring users to open a malicious command on Google's open source network Weave, which is used by Google's Indoor Nest cameras. The researchers also found a bug in which attackers could potentially gain control over the security camera devices.In a statement to ZDNet, a spokesperson from Google said that they have fixed all the bugs and are in the process of updating all the Nest Camera IQs. The company added that the devices will automatically update so that users don't have to update it themselves.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Google's security camera being hacked2. Information being sent from the camera to a laptop3. A malicious command 4. Attacker controlling the security cameraVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report by Cisco Talos, a cyber security intelligence and research group, has found eight different vulnerabilities in Google's Indoor Nest cameras.""One of the bugs, called CVE-2019-5043, allowed multiple connection attempts to the camera's TCP, or Transmission Control Protocol, which would cause the camera's system to crash.""Another bug allowed attackers to acquire and read sensitive information from the cameras.""Two code security vulnerabilities, named CVE-2019-5038 and CVE-2019-5039, allowed attackers to exploit the camera's security system by luring users to open a malicious command on Google's open source network Weave, which is used by Google's Indoor Nest cameras.""The researchers also found a bug in which attackers could potentially gain control over the security camera devices."SOURCES: Cisco Talos, ZDNet https://blog.talosintelligence.com/2019/08/vuln-spotlight-nest-camera-openweave-aug-2019.htmlhttps://www.zdnet.com/article/vulnerabilities-in-google-nest-cam-iq-can-be-used-to-hijack-your-camera/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 02:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/23/3879826/3879826_F20F0A6C3C5947FC8955BB47E70D16D7_190823_3879826_Vulnerabilities_found_in_Google_s_Indoor_Nest_ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  google, google nest cam indoor, nest indoor cam, google security camera, nest cam indoor security camera, nest cam, google nest cam security, google nest cam vulnerabilities, Nest Cam IQ Indoor camera]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881550</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong police fire gun, use water cannons on protesters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHong Kong police and demonstrators faced off for the twelfth weekend in a row, with police firing a gun and deploying water cannon trucks, the BBC reports.The protests began in June as the Hong Kong government proposed an extradition bill that would allow suspects to be extradited for trial to mainland China.Those against the bill believe that Beijing may use it as a way to extradite political activists, dissidents and other critics in the city. The Hong Kong government has since suspended the bill, but protesters are calling for the government to withdraw it altogether.The protests have since morphed into a larger movement calling for greater autonomy in the territory.On Sunday, protests started in Hong Kong's Tsuen Wan district and spread to Tsim Sha Tsui. Some of the demonstrators threw bricks and petrol bombs at the police, BBC News reports. Protesters were also seen chasing the police with metal pipes, while four police officers were filmed drawing their guns and pointing them towards a group of people, CNN reports. One Hong Kong police officer fired a gunshot into the air on Sunday night as a warning to the protesters.The police deployed two water cannon trucks equipped with surveillance cameras and multiple nozzles, against the demonstrators for the first time, according to the Hong Kong Free Press. Activists are calling for the resignation of Hong Kong's leader Carrie Lam and are also pushing for an investigation into alleged police brutality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A group of protesters and what some of the protesters threw at the police2. Demonstrators running after the police with metal pipes, four police officers drawing their guns 3. A police officer firing to the air4. Water cannon trucks passing by protestersVOICEOVER (in English): "On Sunday, protests started in Hong Kong's Tsuen Wan district and spread to Tsim Sha Tsui.""BBC News reports some of the demonstrators threw bricks and petrol bombs at the police.""CNN reports protesters were also seen chasing the police with metal pipes, while four police officers were filmed drawing their guns and pointing them towards a group of people.""One Hong Kong police officer fired a gunshot into the air on Sunday night as a warning to the protesters.""According to Hong Kong Free Press, the police deployed two water cannon trucks equipped with surveillance cameras and multiple nozzles, against the demonstrators for the first time."SOURCES: BBC News, The Guardian, CNN, Hong Kong Free Presshttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-49465836https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/25/hong-kong-protests-fears-of-clashes-with-triad-gangsters-loom-in-latest-marchhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/25/asia/hong-kong-protest-aug-25-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/08/25/hong-kong-police-deploy-water-cannon-protesters-first-time-clashes-break-tsuen-wan/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 14:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/26/3881550/3881550_FC055758BF1542BC849234E1777230C6_190826_3881550_Hong_Kong_police_fire_gun__use_water_cannons_on__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, China extradition, China extradition protests, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong,  hong kong police fire gun, hong kong police water cannons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881320</guid>
      <title>Enormous asteroid to fly past Earth in September</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA massive asteroid will fly past earth early next month.Asteroid 2000 QW7, also known as 467317, will fly by earth on September 14, according to NASA's Center for Near Earth Object Studies. The approaching asteroid is currently moving at a speed of around 14,400 miles per hour.The asteroid had previously passed by our planet on September 1, 2000.According to the agency, Asteroid 2000 QW7 will be around 0.03563 astronomical units, or 3.3 million miles from earth as it approaches our planet. The asteroid's diameter is estimated to be around 950 feet to 2,132 feet.The asteroid orbits the sun and only occasionally passes by earth, according to NASA. It is next expected to fly by our planet on October 19, 2038.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The asteroid flying past earth2. How far the asteroid will be from earth3. The asteroid's diameter4. The asteroid orbiting the sunVOICEOVER (in English): "Asteroid 2000 QW7, also known as 467317, will fly by earth on September 14, according to NASA's Center for Near Earth Object Studies.""The approaching asteroid is currently moving at a speed of around 14,400 miles per hour.""According to the agency, Asteroid 2000 QW7 will be around 0.03563 astronomical units, or 3.3 million miles, from earth as it approaches our planet.""The asteroid's diameter is estimated to be around 950 feet to 2,132 feet.""According to NASA, the asteroid orbits the sun and only occasionally passes by earth."SOURCES:  Live Science, NASA, Center for Near Earth Object Studies, BGRhttps://www.livescience.com/asteroid-fly-by-september-2019.htmlhttps://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?orb=1;sstr=467317https://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?orb=1;sstr=467317;old=0;cov=0;log=0;cad=1#cadhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/asteroidwatch/fastfacts.phphttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/ca/https://bgr.com/2019/08/21/asteroid-flyby-2019-potentially-hazardous/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 07:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/26/3881320/3881320_EF14D54C720C42D4A774749FFBC8F886_190826_3881320_Enormous_asteroid_to_fly_past_Earth_in_September_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, space exploration, asteroid, asteroid in space, asteroid 2000 QW7, giant asteroid,  CNEOS, giant asteroid, nasa giant asteroid, asteroid 467317, space rocks, asteroid to fly past earth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882440</guid>
      <title>China is getting ready to collect DNA samples from its citizens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is gearing up to collect DNA from its citizens on a nationwide scale.According to a Radio Free Asia report, local governments in China are spending millions of yuan on DNA sampling kits, testing instruments, sequencers, and other tools.Online records of government contracts and tenders shows that U.S. firm Thermo Fisher is supplying most of the DNA instrument analyzing technology.Authorities are believed to be focusing on identifying male relatives and building family trees.In Hubei, a male DNA database project is expected to trace the male line across five generations, as well as identify adoptions, and children born outside officially sanctioned limits and norms.In the RFA report, China analyst Willy Lam said the DNA collection may be linked to plans to open up the hukou or Chinese household registration system.Any DNA database will also likely be used alongside existing AI systems, facial recognition technology, and the social credit system, making it convenient for government surveillance.DNA collection is also being extended to newborns. In June 2018, authorities in Guangzhou issued the first electronic birth certificate with a DNA barcode.In this instance, a consent form was part of the process to collect the babies' DNA. But that isn't always the case.Human Rights Watch previously reported that in Xinjiang, DNA samples, fingerprints, iris scans, and blood types are being collected from all citizens aged 12 to 65.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese local governments buying DNA sampling, testing equipment 2. Authorities tracing male line across five generations3. DNA database used with facial recognition tech, social credit system4. DNA collected from newbornsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a Radio Free Asia report, local governments in China are spending millions of yuan on DNA sampling kits, testing instruments, sequencers, and other tools.""Online records of government contracts and tenders shows that U.S. firm Thermo Fisher is supplying most of the DNA instrument analyzing technology.""Authorities are believed to be focusing on identifying male relatives and building family trees.""In Hubei, a male DNA database project is expected to trace the male line across five generations, as well as identify adoptions, and children born outside officially sanctioned limits and norms.""In the RFA report, China analyst Willy Lam said the DNA collection may be linked to plans to open up the hukou or Chinese household registration system.""Any DNA database will also likely be used alongside existing AI systems, facial recognition technology, and the social credit system, making it convenient for government surveillance.""DNA collection is also being extended to newborns. In June 2018, authorities in Guangzhou issued the first electronic birth certificate with a DNA barcode."SOURCES: Radio Free Asia, Human Rights Watchhttps://www.rfa.org/english/news/china/collect-08232019115209.htmlhttps://www.hrw.org/news/2017/05/15/china-police-dna-database-threatens-privacy***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 09:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/28/3882440/3882440_284708F164F2471A83591C4F90B64FD9_190828_3882440_China_is_getting_ready_to_collect_DNA_samples_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, DNA collection, DNA database, China DNA database, China DNA, DNA samples, China surveillance state, facial recognition tech, China surveillance, hukou, household registration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882437</guid>
      <title>Feeding cows pink seaweed could reduce their methane emissions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAustralian scientists have found a pink seaweed that can help reduce methane emissions from cows.According to the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, microbes in cows' stomachs produce methane as part of normal digestive processes.The gas can pass through either end of the animal, but does so primarily through the mouth, in the form of burping.As a greenhouse gas, methane may not be as prevalent in the atmosphere as carbon dioxide. But it is far more effective at trapping radiation, and is 25 times more potent than CO2.To combat methane emissions from cattle, researchers from Australia's University of the Sunshine Coast turned to a pink seaweed called Asparagopsis, which grows naturally off the Queensland coast.When added to cattle feed at a ratio of two percent, the seaweed reduced microbes in the cows' guts, which eliminated methane production by up to 99 percent.According to USC Associate Professor Nick Paul, who heads the Seaweed Research Group, Asparagopsis is not a particularly abundant species.As such, the team is currently trying to determine the perfect growing conditions for the seaweed, with the goal of growing it sustainably, at a much larger scale.If enough pink seaweed can be grown and fed to every cow in the country, Professor Paul says Australia could cut its greenhouse gas emissions by 10 percent.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How methane is produced by cows2. Methane more potent than carbon dioxide3. Pink seaweed reduces methane-producing microbes in cows, eliminates emissions4. Seaweed not abundant in nature, needs to be farmedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, microbes in cows' stomachs produce methane as part of normal digestive processes.""The gas can pass through either end of the animal, but does so primarily through the mouth, in the form of burping.""As a greenhouse gas, methane may not be as prevalent in the atmosphere as carbon dioxide. But it is far more effective at trapping radiation, and is 25 times more potent than CO2.""To combat methane emissions from cattle, researchers from Australia's University of the Sunshine Coast turned to a pink seaweed called Asparagopsis, which grows naturally off the Queensland coast.""When added to cattle feed at a ratio of two percent, the seaweed reduced microbes in the cows' guts, which eliminated methane production by up to 99 percent.""According to USC Associate Professor Nick Paul, who heads the Seaweed Research Group, Asparagopsis is not a particularly abundant species.""As such, the team is currently trying to determine the perfect growing conditions for the seaweed, with the goal of growing it sustainably, at a much larger scale."SOURCES: University of the Sunshine Coast, The Age, ABC, EPAhttps://www.usc.edu.au/explore/usc-news-exchange/news-archive/2019/august/burp-free-cow-feed-drives-seaweed-science-at-uschttps://www.theage.com.au/national/queensland/sprinkle-of-seaweed-could-give-relief-for-gassy-cattle-20190814-p52h1z.htmlhttps://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-08-15/seaweed-for-cows-could-be-mass-farmed-reduce-methane/11414724https://www.epa.gov/ghgemissions/sources-greenhouse-gas-emissions#agriculture***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 09:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/28/3882437/3882437_E7F8D7B000624C2481BD4A6B73269362_190828_3882437_Feeding_cows_pink_seaweed_could_reduce_their_met_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pink seaweed, methane reduction, methane emissions, cow methane emissions, cow seaweed diet, greenhouse gases, climate change, global warming, cow burp, asparagopsis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882192</guid>
      <title>Enormous floating pumice raft could help save the Great Barrier Reef</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn enormous floating raft of volcanic rocks is drifting along the Pacific Ocean towards Australia, where it could help with the recovery of the Great Barrier Reef's corals.According to NASA's Earth Observatory, an underwater volcano near Tonga is believed to have erupted on August 7, spewing out pumice stones of different sizes.The BBC reports that over a trillion pieces of pumice are floating together on the Pacific Ocean, stretched out over 150 square kilometers.According to CNN, the pumice raft is roughly the size of Manhattan.Queensland University of Technology Associate Professor Scott Bryan told the BBC that the pumice is currently drifting west toward Fiji. It will likely pass New Caledonia and Vanuatu and possibly reach Australia in about a year.According to CNN, the pumice will bring with it microorganisms and other marine life as it drifts across the ocean. This could potentially bring in diverse colonies of corals or barnacles that could help restock the damaged Great Barrier Reef.Experts say pumice fields are one way the ocean can redistribute sea life. They aren't uncommon, and are typically spotted every five years or so.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Underwater volcano eruption spews out pumice rocks of different sizes2. Floating raft of pumice the size of Manhattan3. Pumice raft's projected route towards Australia4. Sea organisms on pumice could help restock Great Barrier ReefVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA's Earth Observatory, an underwater volcano near Tonga is believed to have erupted on August 7, spewing out pumice stones of different sizes.""The BBC reports that over a trillion pieces of pumice are floating together on the Pacific Ocean, stretched out over 150 square kilometers." "According to CNN, the pumice raft is roughly the size of Manhattan.""Queensland University of Technology Associate Professor Scott Bryan told the BBC that the pumice is currently drifting west toward Fiji. It will likely pass New Caledonia and Vanuatu and possibly reach Australia in about a year.""According to CNN, the pumice will bring with it microorganisms and other marine life as it drifts across the ocean. This could potentially bring in diverse colonies of corals or barnacles that could help restock the damaged Great Barrier Reef."SOURCES: NASA Earth Observatory, CNN, BBChttps://earthobservatory.nasa.gov/images/145490/a-raft-of-rockhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/25/asia/pumice-stone-underwater-volcano-great-barrier-reef-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-49469446***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 01:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/28/3882192/3882192_E8754290D9374152B47699BD4A73A0F7_190828_3882192_Enormous_floating_pumice_raft_could_help_save_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pumice, pumice raft, floating pumice, great barrier reef, volcano eruption, underwater volcano eruption, underwater volcano, save the great barrier reef, coral restocking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883199</guid>
      <title>Indonesia to relocate capital city to Borneo island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPresident Joko Widodo has announced plans to shift Indonesia's capital city from Jakarta to the province of East Kalimantan on Borneo island.Part of the new capital will be in the province's North Penajam Paser regency while the other half will be in the Kutai Kartanegara regency, reports the Jakarta Post. The region was chosen for being relatively free from earthquakes and volcanoes.Indonesia plans to relocate from its current capital, Jakarta, as the city is overpopulated and faces severe congestion, according to Reuters. Jakarta is also sinking 10 to 20 centimeters per year due to severe land subsidence, reports the Guardian.The Indonesian government said it wants to build a smart, green city. A government official was quoted by the South China Morning Post as saying that they would not disturb any existing protected forest as the island is filled with tropical rainforests.If President Widodo's plan is approved by the Indonesian parliament, the new capital will begin construction across a plot of around 40,000 hectares next year.In a televised speech, the Indonesian president said that the location is strategic and explained that the shift would ease Jakarta's burden as the center of business, finance, trade and government.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of Indonesia, where the capital will be moved2. Crowded and congested Jakarta3. Cross section of Jakarta depicting that the city is sinking4. Indonesian flag, small plot showing a smart, green city and Borneo island with rainforestsVOICEOVER (in English): "President Joko Widodo has announced plans to shift Indonesia's capital city from Jakarta to the province of East Kalimantan on Borneo island.""The Jakarta Post reports part of the new capital will be in the province's North Penajam Paser regency while the other half will be in the Kutai Kartanegara regency.""The region was chosen for being relatively free from earthquakes and volcanoes.""According to Reuters, Indonesia plans to relocate from its current capital, Jakarta, as the city is overpopulated and faces severe congestion.""The Guardian reports Jakarta is also sinking 10 to 20 centimeters per year due to severe land subsidence.""The Indonesian government said it wants to build a smart, green city. A government official was quoted by the South China Morning Post as saying that they would not disturb any existing protected forest as the island is filled with tropical rainforests.""If President Widodo's plan is approved by the Indonesian parliament, the new capital will begin construction across a plot of around 40,000 hectares next year."SOURCES: Reuters, The Guardian, NPR, BBC News, Jakarta Post, South China Morning Post   https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-politics-capital/indonesia-plans-to-move-capital-city-out-of-crowded-java-island-idUSKCN1S50RRhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/26/indonesia-new-capital-city-borneo-forests-jakartahttps://www.npr.org/2019/08/26/754291131/indonesia-plans-to-move-capital-to-borneo-from-jakartahttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49470258https://www.thejakartapost.com/news/2019/08/26/breaking-jokowi-announces-east-kalimantan-as-site-of-new-capital.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/news/asia/southeast-asia/article/3024352/indonesia-announces-site-new-capital-city-reduce-jakartas***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 13:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/29/3883199/3883199_A512F359145F41A184BE61A14BB1426B_190829_3883199_Indonesia_to_relocate_capital_city_to_Borneo_isl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, indonesia, indonesia capital, indonesia new capital, indonesia capital city change, indonesia capital sinking, indonesia capital relocation,  indonesia capital city sinking, indonesia new capital borneo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883041</guid>
      <title>U.S. preparing against cyber attacks for 2020 elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. government is increasing its efforts to protect election databases and electoral systems from hackers in the run-up to next year's presidential elections, Reuters reports.The Cybersecurity Infrastructure Security Agency, CISA, which is a part of the Department of Homeland Security, issued a statement and a set of guidelines in order to prevent next year's elections from being compromised.The agency warned that hackers may try to target voter databases and attempt to manipulate, disrupt or even destroy voting data by conducting ransomware cyber attacks.In an ransomware attack, hackers lock a computer with malicious software until someone remits money, usually in the form of cryptocurrency, to the attacker.CISA said in the statement that they will be working with the Election Infrastructure Information Sharing and Analysis Center to provide remote vulnerability scanning and risk assessments for state governments upon request.CISA issued a set of guidelines urging local governments to regularly back up critical data on the system and to store backup files offline.However, an unnamed senior Homeland Security official told Reuters that there is no standard regulation stating how often backups should be created.CISA also urged local governments to have a clear plan to address the cyber attacks and to request assistance from their agency or the Election Infrastructure Information Sharing and Analysis Center if an attack occurs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of the U.S., the White House, an election ballot, a voting database and a hacked laptop2. What happens in a ransomware attack3. How CISA and the Election Infrastructure Information Sharing and Analysis Center will work to prevent such attacks4. Data being backed up and stored offlineVOICEOVER (in English): "The Cybersecurity Infrastructure Security Agency, CISA, which is a part of the Department of Homeland Security, issued a statement and a set of guidelines in order to prevent next year's elections from being compromised.""The agency warned that hackers may try to target voter databases and attempt to manipulate, disrupt or even destroy voting data by conducting ransomware cyber attacks.""In an ransomware attack, hackers lock a computer with malicious software until someone remits money, usually in the form of cryptocurrency, to the attacker.""CISA said in the statement that they will be working with the Election Infrastructure Information Sharing and Analysis Center to provide remote vulnerability scanning and risk assessments for state governments upon request.""CISA issued a set of guidelines urging local governments to regularly back up critical data on the system and to store backup files offline."SOURCES: Reuters, CISA, Fox News, FBI https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-cyber-election-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-officials-fear-ransomware-attack-against-2020-election-idUSKCN1VG222?utm_source=reddit.com&utm_source=reddit.comhttps://www.us-cert.gov/Ransomwarehttps://www.dhs.gov/cisa/news/2019/07/25/joint-gcc-scc-statement-senate-intelligence-committees-first-russianhttps://www.us-cert.gov/resources/federalhttps://www.dhs.gov/cisa/blog/2019/08/21/cisa-insights-ransomware-outbreakhttps://www.foxnews.com/tech/us-eyes-ransomware-threat-to-voter-databases-2020-electionhttps://www.fbi.gov/file-repository/ransomware-prevention-and-response-for-cisos.pdf/view***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 09:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/29/3883041/3883041_6BF09DC2815F42A5A8C7A46A123A65CE_190829_3883041_U_S__preparing_against_cyber_attacks_for_2020_el_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US elections, US elections 2020, ransomware attack, CISA, ransomware outbreak, US fears cyber attack on US elections, 2020 presidential elections]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883856</guid>
      <title>Tattoo needles leave behind metal particles that spread to lymph nodes, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in the journal Particle and Fiber Toxicology has found that tattoo needles deposit metal particles such as nickel and chromium into the skin during the tattooing process.These particles are then transported from the tattoo site to the body's lymph nodes, where their sizes ranged from 50 nanometers to 2 micrometers, according to a news release by the European Synchrotron Radiation Facility.Researchers analyzed a tattoo needle by using a scanning electron microscopy to take a closer look at the needle before and after the tattoo process.They found that the needle showed abrasions from certain tattoo inks that contain titanium dioxide, a white pigment that is usually mixed in bright colors such as green or blue. Researchers did not find the same result with carbon black ink.The news release noted that further studies would be needed to understand the metal particles' impact on tattoo allergy formation and long-term impact on human health.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A person getting a tattoo and metal particles entering his skin2. Cross section of the particles entering the skin and spreading to lymph nodes3. The tattoo needle being scanned4. Certain tattoo inks causes the needle to wear down.VOICEOVER (in English): "A new study published in the journal Particle and Fiber Toxicology has found that tattoo needles deposit metal particles such as nickel and chromium into the skin during the tattooing process.""According to a news release by the European Synchrotron Radiation Facility, these particles are then transported from the tattoo site to the body's lymph nodes, where their sizes ranged from 50 nanometers to 2 micrometers.""Researchers analyzed a tattoo needle by using a scanning electron microscopy to take a closer look at the needle before and after the tattoo process.""They found that the needle showed abrasions from certain tattoo inks that contain titanium dioxide, a white pigment that is usually mixed in bright colors such as green or blue.""Researchers did not find the same result with carbon black ink."SOURCES: New Atlas, Particle and Fibre Toxicology, Scientific Reports, European Synchrotron Radiation Facility, Science Alert  https://newatlas.com/medical/metal-particles-tattoo-needles-human-lymph-nodes/https://newatlas.com/tiny-tattoo-particles-lymph-nodes/51324/https://particleandfibretoxicology.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12989-019-0317-1#Abs1https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-11721-zhttps://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-08/esrf-mpa_1082619.phphttps://www.sciencealert.com/metal-particles-from-tattoo-needles-have-been-found-in-human-lymph-nodes***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 13:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/30/3883856/3883856_90DC06FBC2DD44BFAC3D467335FC9B4E_190830_3883856_Tattoo_needles_leave_behind_metal_particles_that_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, tattoos, European Synchrotron Radiation Facility, tattoo needles, tattoo needles metal particles, tattoo metal particles lymph nodes, tattoo lymph nodes, lymph node tattoo pigment, tattoo needle lymph nodes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883805</guid>
      <title>U.S. tries to block 8,000-mile Google &amp; Facebook undersea cable over security concerns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoogle's 8,000-mile subsea cable, known as the Pacific Light Cable Network, plans to provide ultra high capacity internet transmissions between Los Angeles and Hong Kong by using new fiber optics with a capacity of up to 120 terabytes of data per second.However, The Wall Street Journal reports that a panel led by the Justice Department known as "Team Telecom" has signaled opposition over national security concerns with the cable's private Chinese backer, the telecommunications company, Dr. Peng.Business Insider states that many Chinese companies maintain a close relationship with the Chinese government to ensure a "favorable business environment," thus making them susceptible to being utilized by the CCP.If successful, the cable could grant U.S. companies greater access to other developing markets in Asia, such as the Philippines and Malaysia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cable details2. Team Telecom disagreeing3. Chinese governments close relationship with a Chinese company 4. U.S interest in Asian marketsVOICEOVER (in English): "Google's 8,000-mile subsea cable, known as the Pacific Light Cable Network, plans to provide ultra high capacity internet transmissions between L.A. and Hong Kong by using new fiber optics with a capacity of up to 120 terabytes of data per second.""However, The Wall Street Journal reports that a panel led by the Justice Department known as 'Team Telecom' has signaled opposition over national security concerns with the cable's private Chinese backer, the telecommunications company, Dr. Peng.""Business Insider states that many Chinese companies maintain a close relationship with the Chinese government to ensure a 'favorable business environment,' thus making them susceptible to being utilized by the CCP.""If successful, the cable could grant U.S. companies greater access to other developing markets in Asia, such as the Philippines and Malaysia." SOURCES: Business Insiderhttps://www.businessinsider.com/us-officials-may-undersea-cable-china-google-facebook-backed-wsj-2019-8***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 12:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/30/3883805/3883805_8D1EEA7A848E41A8A0FE54950C8626EA_190830_3883805_U_S__tries_to_block_8_000_mile_Google___Facebook_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, google subsea cable, google facebook sea cable, national security threat, china google, LA to HK google cable, Google cable, US try to block Goggle cable, LA to Hong Kong cable]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883417</guid>
      <title>Nestle plans to take 1.1 million gallons of water from Florida spring</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNestle sparked outrage among environmentalists over plans to take water from a spring in Florida.According to the Guardian, Nestle is seeking permission to pump over 1.1 million gallons of water a day from Ginnie Springs in Florida's Sante Fe river, to sell as bottled water.Opponents of the plan say the river system is in recovery, and cannot withstand the proposed pumping. Residents also say taking that much water will harm the springs and its ecosystem, and deplete their own drinking supply.Nestle denies all these, claiming that spring water is a rapidly renewable resource. The Guardian reports that Nestle has spent millions buying and upgrading a nearby water bottling plant, anticipating that permission would be granted.But in order to proceed, it would need the Suwannee River Water Management District to renew an expired water use permit held by local company Seven Springs, from which it plans to buy the water.Though Nestle has promised a "robust" management plan for the spring, local environmentalists don't trust the company's intentions.They are also worried that the plan might threaten the 11 native turtle species and four non-native species who call the spring system home, and rely on vigorous water flow and river levels.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nestle to take 1.1 million gallons of water a day from Ginnie Springs2. Damage from over pumping spring3. Nestle bought water bottling plant but needs water use permit to be granted4. Nestle plans threaten turtle speciesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Guardian, Nestle is seeking permission to take over 1.1 million gallons of water a day from Ginnie Springs in Florida's Sante Fe river, to sell as bottled water.""Opponents of the plan say the river system is in recovery, and cannot withstand the proposed pumping. Residents also say taking that much water will harm the springs and its ecosystem, and deplete their own drinking supply.""The Guardian reports that Nestle has spent millions buying and upgrading a nearby water bottling plant, anticipating that permission would be granted.""But in order to proceed, it would need the Suwannee River Water Management District to renew an expired water use permit held by local company Seven Springs, from which it plans to buy the water.""Though Nestle has promised a 'robust' management plan for the spring, local environmentalists don't trust the company's intentions.""They are also worried that the plan might threaten the 11 native turtle species and four non-native species who call the spring system home, and rely on vigorous water flow and river levels."SOURCES: The Guardian, The Independenthttps://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/aug/26/nestle-suwannee-river-ginnie-springs-plan-permithttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/nestle-florida-water-spring-bottle-santa-fe-river-a9079791.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 03:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/30/3883417/3883417_E7406A5B6A744AF4BDE453930F77FE35_190830_3883417_Nestle_plans_to_take_1_1_million_gallons_of_wate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, nestle, nestle spring water, nestle bottled water, ginnie springs, spring water, boycott nestle, santa fe river, florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883409</guid>
      <title>What is prorogation and what does it mean for Brexit?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson has asked the Queen to prorogue parliament. Here's what that means and why it's important.According to The Guardian, prorogation is a formal mechanism to end a session of parliament. When this happens, the House of Commons is suspended, and any unfinished legislation from the current session stops progressing.Prorogation must be approved by the Queen, following guidance from her Privy Council. It typically lasts only a short time, with the start of a new session marked by a speech from the Queen detailing the government's new agenda.While these proceedings are normal and happen yearly, the five-week prorogation requested by Boris Johnson is unusually long.It is set to begin no earlier than September 9 and no later than September 12, and will last until October 14.With the Brexit deadline set for October 31, MPs have just a little over two weeks to scrutinize Johnson's Brexit plans. Such a long prorogation would likewise restrict MPs from pushing legislation to block a no-deal Brexit.Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn has called Johnson's move a "smash and grab" on the country's democracy.The BBC reports that hundreds protested the prorogation outside Westminster Wednesday night, with more demonstrations slated over the weekend.More than a million have also signed a petition appealing for parliament not to be prorogued.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of prorogation2. Prorogation approved by the Queen following guidance from Privy Council3. Boris Johnson's requested prorogation unusually long at five weeks4. Prorogation could block anti-no deal Brexit legislationVOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Guardian, prorogation is a formal mechanism to end a session of parliament.""When this happens, the House of Commons is suspended, and any unfinished legislation from the current session stops progressing.""Prorogation must be approved by the Queen, following guidance from her Privy Council.""It typically lasts only a short time, with the start of a new session marked by a speech from the Queen detailing the government's new agenda.""While these proceedings are normal and happen yearly, the five-week prorogation requested by Boris Johnson is unusually long.""It is set to begin no earlier than September 9 and no later than September 12, and will last until October 14.""With the Brexit deadline set for October 31, MPs have just a little over two weeks to scrutinize Johnson's Brexit plans. Such a long prorogation would likewise restrict MPs from pushing legislation to block a no-deal Brexit."SOURCES: The Guardian, Channel 4, BBChttps://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/aug/28/what-is-prorogation-prorogue-parliament-boris-johnson-brexithttps://www.channel4.com/news/factcheck/factcheck-parliament-prorogation-explainedhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-49493632***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 03:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/30/3883409/3883409_D984790946954AF19C4578053B0717C8_190830_3883409_What_is_prorogation_and_what_does_it_mean_for_Br_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, prorogation, UK, paused parliament, proroguing parliament, suspended parliament, boris johnson, brexit, no deal brexit, brexit deadline, UK parliament]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883399</guid>
      <title>NASA attaches autonomous mini helicopter to Mars 2020 rover mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's engineers have connected a small helicopter to the bottom of the Mars 2020 rover.A cover will shield the mini helicopter from debris as the rover lands on Mars' surface, according to NASA.The aircraft will be deployed over the Red Planet once the Mars rover finds a suitable area to conduct test flights. The helicopter will be carrying a camera to capture photos of the Martian surface for transmission back to Earth.NASA's website explains that the main body of the Mars helicopter will be the size of a softball and weigh under four pounds. The helicopter will use two sets of rotor blades that are four feet long. These will spin at 2,400 rotations per minute to allow the helicopter to fly as high as 15 feet above the Red Planet.The Mars helicopter will include a solar array to recharge its batteries that are to be used to rotate the blades and keep the vehicle warm throughout the night.If the test flights are successful, second-generation helicopters could be used for future Mars missions.The Mars 2020 rover will be launched in July next year from Cape Canaveral Air Force Station in Florida.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where the helicopter will be placed2. The rover carrying the helicopter landing on Mars' surface3. The helicopter flying across Mars4. The helicopter carrying a camera and analyzing Mars' surface5. How big the helicopter will be and how it will operate6. A solar array is included on the helicopter to recharge its batteriesVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's engineers have connected a small helicopter to the bottom of the Mars 2020 rover.""According to NASA, a cover will shield the mini helicopter from debris as the rover lands on Mars' surface.""The aircraft will be deployed over the Red Planet once the Mars rover finds a suitable area to conduct test flights.""The helicopter will be carrying a camera to capture photos of the Martian surface for transmission back to Earth.""NASA's website explains that the main body of the Mars helicopter will be the size of a softball and weigh under four pounds.""The helicopter will use two sets of rotor blades that are four feet long. These will spin at 2,400 rotations per minute to allow the helicopter to fly as high as 15 feet above the Red Planet.""The Mars helicopter will include a solar array to recharge its batteries that are to be used to rotate the blades and keep the vehicle warm throughout the night."SOURCES: NASA, CNet https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7489https://www.nasa.gov/feature/nasa-is-with-you-when-you-fly-even-on-marshttps://www.cnet.com/news/nasa-has-officially-attached-a-freakin-helicopter-to-the-mars-2020-rover/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/08/30/3883399/3883399_56408E37CC784542919C6BC39A25D4AA_190830_3883399_NASA_attaches_autonomous_mini_helicopter_to_Mars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mars helicopter, Mars 2020, Mars rover, Mars mission, NASA helicopter, NASA, helicopter on Mars, Mars, NASA's Mars Helicopter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
