<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3790811</guid>
      <title>FedEx robots could soon be delivering packages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFedEx could soon be carrying packages to your home via a delivery robot.FedEx plans to use robots to automate its delivery system, the Washington Post reports.The company is teaming up with DEKA Development & Research Corp to create the delivery robot, which is to be tested this summer. The robot, called FedEx SameDay Bot, is powered by batteries that are attached to its wheels. Cameras and software to avoid obstacles will be incorporated into the robot. The self-driving vehicle will be able to travel up to speeds of 10 miles per hour as it drives on sidewalks and roadways.According to Reuters, the robots will be used to handle home deliveries for companies such as Walmart and Pizza Hut.The robot will complement the company's SameDay City service, according to a FedEx press release.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. FedEx's delivery robot2. Features of the self-driving vehicle3. The delivery robot on the road4. The delivery robot delivering a packageVOICEOVER (in English): "The Washington Post reports FedEx plans to use robots to automate its delivery system.""The robot, called FedEx SameDay Bot, is powered by batteries that are attached to its wheels. Cameras and software to avoid obstacles will also be incorporated into the robot.""The self-driving vehicle will be able to travel up to speeds of 10 miles per hour as it drives on sidewalks and roadways.""According to Reuters, the robots will be used to handle home deliveries for companies such as Walmart and Pizza Hut."SOURCES: The Washington Post, Reuters, FedEx press release, FedEx SameDay Bot, https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/02/27/your-next-fedex-delivery-could-be-pizza/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.7a5c31285daehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-fedex-autonomous-idUSKCN1QG1M7https://about.van.fedex.com/newsroom/thefuturefedex/https://thefuturefedex.com/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 10:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/04/3790811/3790811_64DCC77F8F734EB0843C69C874BBCB06_190304_3790811_FedEx_robots_could_soon_be_delivering_packages_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, fedex, fedex delivery robot,home deliveries, automation,delivery robot,automated delivery vehicle, autonomous delivery system, autonomous vehicles, autonomous vehicle technology, robot delivery service]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790779</guid>
      <title>SpaceX Dragon capsule docks with space station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn unmanned SpaceX Dragon capsule has successfully docked with the International Space Station as part of its demonstration mission. According to Reuters, the 16-foot-tall (4.9 meter) Crew Dragon capsule was launched atop a Falcon 9 rocket from Florida's Kennedy space Center at 2:49 a.m. on Saturday and deployed into orbit 11 minutes later. According to the BBC, the Dragon test vehicle autonomously attached itself to the international docking adapter. The BBC reports the Crew Dragon approached the ISS using lasers and software to guide itself in, while astronauts aboard the space station monitored the docking.  According to BBC, the capsule's "soft capture" contact with the space station occurred at 10:51 GMT, with a full and secure docking confirmed around 10 minutes later. According to Reuters, the capsule was carrying 400 pounds of supplies and test equipment, and a test dummy named "Ripley."Ripley is equipped with sensors around the head, neck and spine to monitor how a flight would feel for a human. The Crew Dragon is scheduled to stay at the ISS for five days, while the three crew members of the space station perform tests on the capsule to see how it is holding up in space. On Friday morning, after being checked out and loaded with cargo, the capsule will undock from the ISS and then plunge back toward Earth. Parachutes will deploy during the capsule's decent, where it should plunge into the Atlantic Ocean near Florida for retrieval. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dragon capsule being launched and floating in space2. Dragon capsule docking with ISS3. Dragon capsule cargo and Ripley test dummy4. Dragon capsule being testedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, the 16-foot-tall Crew Dragon capsule was launched atop a Falcon 9 rocket from Florida's Kennedy space Center at 2:49 a.m. and deployed into orbit 11 minutes later." "According to the BBC, the Dragon test vehicle autonomously attached itself to the international docking adapter." "The BBC reports the Crew Dragon approached the ISS using lasers and software to guide itself in, while astronauts aboard the space station monitored the docking." "According to Reuters, the capsule is carrying 400 pounds of supplies and test equipment, and a test dummy named 'Ripley.'""Ripley is equipped with sensors around the head, neck and spine to monitor how a flight would feel for a human." "The Crew Dragon is scheduled to stay at the ISS for five days, while the three crew members of the space station perform tests on the capsule to see how it is holding up in space." SOURCES: Reuters, BBC, Space,com, Vergehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-spacex/spacex-rocket-with-unmanned-us-capsule-blasts-off-for-space-station-idUSKCN1QI554https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47430432https://www.space.com/spacex-launches-crew-dragon-test-flight.htmlhttps://www.theverge.com/2019/3/2/18244499/spacex-crew-dragon-launch-first-capsule-iss-nasa-passenger-flight***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 09:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/04/3790779/3790779_2769AA266CEF44469EEC9EB750A812E8_190304_3790779_SpaceX_Dragon_capsule_docks_with_space_station_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, SpaceX, SpaceX Dragon capsule, SpaceX ISS, SpaceX docks ISS, SpaceX Crew Dragon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790710</guid>
      <title>Canada monitoring negative behavior of 'at risk' people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCanadian authorities are using databases to track 'at risk' individuals.According to a Motherboard investigation, Canadian authorities are using a shared database called 'The Risk-driven Tracking Database' or RTD to track 'at risk' individuals. The RTD is part of a larger Canadian pre-crime policing network called 'The Hub' that partners law enforcement, school staff, social workers, healthcare workers and local governments.Police and civilian agencies can access this database to gather information of individuals believed to be at risk, which includes people living in dangerous neighborhoods and those who could become criminals or victims, allowing them to intervene in case of emergencies.Individuals are registered into the RTD if local authorities report abnormal behavior to The Hub. This data can then be used to request intervention from other law enforcement agencies or institutions.Authorities can input an individual's sex, location and age group including other 'risk factors' such as mental health, criminal involvement, negative behavior and physical health status.Currently, there are only two RTDs, one in Ontario and the other in Saskatchewan. However, according to the Correctional Service of Canada, there are roughly 100 active Hubs in the country as of 2016.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Canadian authorities using the database; other authorities with access to the database2. Type of behavior logged into the database3. Type of information gathered in the database4.  Active Risk-driven Tracking Databases: Ontario and CanadaVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a Motherboard Investigation, Canadian authorities are using a shared database called 'The Risk-driven Tracking Database' or RTD to track so-called 'at risk' individuals." "The RTD is part of a larger Canadian pre-crime policing network called 'The Hub' that partners law enforcement, school staff, social workers, healthcare workers, and local governments.""Police and civilian agencies can access this database to gather information of individuals believed to be at risk which includes people living in dangerous neighborhoods and those that could become criminals or victims, allowing them to intervene in case of emergencies.""Individuals are registered into the RTD if local authorities report abnormal behavior to The Hub. This data can then be used to request intervention from other law enforcement agencies or institutions.""Authorities can input an individual's sex, location and age group including other 'risk factors' such as mental health, criminal involvement, negative behavior, and physical health status.""Currently, there are only two RTDs, one in Ontario and the other in Saskatchewan. However, according to the Correctional Service of Canada, there are roughly 100 active Hubs in the country as of 2016."SOURCES: Motherboard, Correctional Service of Canadahttps://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/kzdp5v/police-in-canada-are-tracking-peoples-negative-behavior-in-a-risk-databasehttps://www.csc-scc.gc.ca/research/rr-17-02-eng.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 07:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/04/3790710/3790710_43890207630043E2952BBE87D902A412_190304_3790710_Canada_monitoring_negative_behavior_of__at_risk__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Canada,  Risk driven Tracking Database, surveillance, law enforcement, canada police, canada authorities, database]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790659</guid>
      <title>New evidence suggests Planet Nine could be seen within a decade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from suggests we might be able to spot the mysterious Planet Nine sooner than we thought.In 2016 scientists from California Institue of Technology published research in the Astronomical Journal that found new evidence of the existence of Planet Nine. The scientists used mathematical models and computer simulations to map out the hypothetical planet's orbit after finding abnormal alignments of six objects in the Kuiper Belt suggesting that a larger object's gravity was pulling them.The Kuiper Belt is a ring of icy objects located beyond the orbit of Neptune. Within it are several thousand celestial bodies, several of which have their own moons.Planet Nine remains unseen. However, a paper published last month by the same Caltech team in the journal Physics Reports suggests that it could be detected within a decade.Results also showed that its mass is probably five to 10 times the mass of Earth.They estimate Planet Nine to be about 400 astronomical units away from the sun, which is the equivalent of 60 billion kilometers or 37 billion miles. These new estimates suggest that the planet is closer and potentially brighter than previously thought, making it easier to detect in the coming years.In a second paper published in the Astronomical Journal, the same group of researchers calculated the percentage of potential bias of their observations. Results showed the probability was just one in 500.In a Caltech press release, Konstantin Batygin, one of the lead researchers of both papers said, quote, 'The prospect of one day seeing real images of Planet Nine is absolutely electrifying. Although finding Planet Nine astronomically is a great challenge, I'm very optimistic that we will image it within the next decade.'RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Planet Nine orbit2. Kuiper belt3. Planet Nine has ten times the mass of Earth4. Planet Nine's distance from EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "In 2016 they published research in the Astronomical Journal that found new evidence of the existence of Planet Nine." "The scientists used mathematical models and computer simulations to map out the hypothetical planet's orbit after finding abnormal alignments of six objects in the Kuiper Belt suggesting that a larger object's gravity was pulling them.""The Kuiper Belt is a ring of icy objects located beyond the orbit of Neptune. Within it are several thousand celestial bodies, several of which have their own moons.""Planet Nine remains unseen. However, a paper published last month by the same Caltech team in the journal Physics Reports suggests that it could be detected within a decade.""Results also showed that its mass is probably five to 10 times the mass of Earth.""They estimate Planet Nine to be about 400 astronomical units away from the sun, which is the equivalent of 60 billion kilometers or 37 billion miles." "These new estimates suggest that the planet is closer and potentially brighter than previously thought, making it easier to detect in the coming years."SOURCES: Physics Reports, Caltech, LiveScience, Space, Astronomical Journalhttps://arxiv.org/pdf/1902.10103.pdfhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S037015731930047X?via=ihubhttps://www.livescience.com/64884-planet-nine-where-is-it.htmlhttps://www.space.com/planet-nine-easier-find-than-thought.htmlhttps://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/1538-3881/aaf051/meta***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 06:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/04/3790659/3790659_05D445DB9EB44456AF092D7CEE44A345_190304_3790659_New_evidence_suggests_Planet_Nine_could_be_seen__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, planet nine, caltech, california technology instute, planet 9, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790578</guid>
      <title>Nanotechnology allows mice to see infrared light</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from China and the U.S. used nanoparticles to enhance the vision of mice, according to a new study published in the journal Cell.A team of researchers from the University of Science and Technology of China and the University of Massachusetts Medical School injected nanoparticles into the eyes of mice that gave them the ability to see infrared light without compromising their normal vision.Humans and mice are not able to see infrared light naturally. Both species can only see to light in the visible spectrum.According to the study, the pupils of the mice that received the nanoparticles injection were constricted. This meant their eyes were able to detect infrared light even during the day. Mice that only received a buffer solution did not have constricted pupils.Jin Bao, one of the researchers from the University of Science and Technology of China, explained in the study that nanoparticles were able to anchor to the photoreceptor cells in the eyes, also known as the rods and the cones, and convert the infrared light to make it appear as a green color.The nanoparticles do this by capturing the longer infrared wavelengths and sending out shorter wavelengths in the visible spectrum. This is then absorbed by a rod or a cone, which then sends sends a signal to the brain, tricking the brain into believing that visible light has hit the retina.This technology could be used in security and military operations in the future, according to the study.Senior author Tian Xue said in the study this technology is exciting because it could "eventually enable human beings to see beyond our natural capability."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Syringe, nanoparticles, mice being injected with nanoparticles2. Pupils of the injected mice becoming constricted3. Nanoparticles converting infrared light to appear as a green color4. Nanoparticles capturing infrared rays and turning them into short wavelengths in the visible spectrumVOICEOVER (in English): "A research team at the University of Science and Technology of China and the University of Massachusetts Medical School injected nanoparticles into the eyes of mice that gave them the ability to see infrared light without compromising their normal vision.""Humans and mice are not able to see infrared light naturally. Both species are only limited to light in the visible spectrum.""According to a study published in the journal Cell, the pupils of the mice that received the nanoparticles injection were constricted." "This meant their eyes were able to detect infrared light even during the day.""Mice that only received a buffer solution did not have constricted pupils.""Jin Bao, one of the researchers from the University of Science and Technology of China, explained in the study that nanoparticles were able to anchor to the photoreceptor cells, also known as the rods and the cones, in the eyes and convert the infrared light to make it appear as a green color.""The nanoparticles do this by capturing the longer infrared wavelengths and sending out shorter wavelengths in the visible spectrum." "This is then absorbed by a rod or a cone which then sends sends a signal to the brain, tricking the brain into believing that visible light has hit the retina."SOURCES: Cell journal, Phys.orghttps://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(19)30101-1?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0092867419301011%3Fshowall%3Dtruehttps://phys.org/news/2019-02-nanotechnology-mice-infrared.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/04/3790578/3790578_818F35F91AC14D52835C7BD13C33F990_190304_3790578_Nanotechnology_allows_mice_to_see_infrared_light_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, usa, nanotechnology, mice, infrared light, seeing infrared light, nanotechnology mice, injecting nanoparticles into mice, nanoparticles, enhancing vision, infrared light nanoparticles, infrared light mice]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791488</guid>
      <title>U.S. deploys THAAD missile system to Israel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. deployed its most advanced air and missile defense system in Israel for the first time, according to U.S. and Israeli military officials on Monday, Reuters reports. The Terminal High Altitude Area Defense system, or THAAD, deployment was intended to test the U.S. military's ability to rapidly deploy such weapons around the world, according to a spokeswoman for U.S. European Command. According to Reuters, Lockheed Martin builds and integrates the THAAD system, which is designed to shoot down short- medium- and intermediate-range ballistic missiles. Raytheon builds its advanced radar. According to Army Technology, the THAAD system is designed to protect against incoming ballistic missiles at ranges of 200 kms and altitudes of up to 150 kms. According to Army Technology, the THAAD battery typically operates nine launch vehicles each carrying eight missiles, with two tactical operations centers and a ground-based radar. THAAD intercepts incoming ballistic missiles in their final phase of flight, according to Reuters. Radar first detects incoming threats, identifies the target and engages. An interceptor missile is fired from the launcher, and then uses kinetic energy to destroy the incoming missile.  According to Reuters, the deployment comes amid rising tensions between Israel and Iran over Israel's bombing campaign in Syria and comments in which Iran's foreign minister said he could not rule out the possibility of military conflict between the two countries.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. THAAD missile system and representational range2. THAAD system components3. THAAD system detecting incoming ballistic missile threat4. THAAD system launching interceptor missile to eliminate missile threatVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, Lockheed Martin builds and integrates the THAAD system, which is designed to shoot down short- medium- and intermediate-range ballistic missiles. Raytheon builds its advanced radar." "According to Army Technology, the THAAD system is designed to protect against incoming ballistic missiles at ranges of 200 kms and altitudes of up to 150 kms." "According to Army Technology, the THAAD battery typically operates nine launch vehicles each carrying eight missiles, with two tactical operations centers and a ground-based radar." "THAAD intercepts incoming ballistic missiles in their final phase of flight, according to Reuters. Radar first detects incoming threats, identifies the target and engages." "An interceptor missile is fired from the launcher, and then uses kinetic energy to destroy the incoming missile."  SOURCES: Reuters, Army Technologyhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-israel-military/u-s-says-deployed-thaad-missile-defense-system-to-israel-idUSKCN1QL1B8https://www.reuters.com/article/us-datadive-thaad/data-dive-how-does-the-thaad-anti-missile-defense-work-idUSKBN18R2JQhttps://www.army-technology.com/projects/thaad/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 13:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/05/3791488/3791488_14AE6222069B4B818A54E75446E35EB0_190305_3791488_U_S__deploys_THAAD_missile_system_to_Israel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, THAAD, THAAD system, US deploys THAAD, Israel THAAD system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791091</guid>
      <title>Deep sleep important for brain to clear out toxins, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe depth of one's sleep can affect the brain's ability to adequately remove waste and toxic proteins, according to a new study published in the journal Science Advances.An increase of toxic proteins such as beta amyloid and tau in the brain are often linked with Alzheimer's disease, according to a University of Rochester Medical Center news release.The researchers injected six mice with six different anesthetic regimens to replicate different stages of sleep.This was to identify if a certain phase of sleep could be associated with the glymphatic system, which the brain uses to clear waste.The scientists determined the best glymphatic system activity takes place in the stage that was most similar to a human's deep, non REM, short-wave sleep, efficiently stimulating the cleaning process of the brain.Mice that were given anesthetics which did not lead to slower brain activity had a decline in glymphatic activity, according to the study.The study reinforces the link between poor sleep and Alzheimer's disease, and the importance of deep sleep for the brain's cleaning system to work effectively.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Monochrome avatar sleeping and the inside of the brain2. Brain and an inset of beta amyloid and tau protein3. Six mice and six syringes, brain and sleep waves4. We see a brain and brain waves going through itVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the journal Science Advances, the depth of one's sleep can affect the brain's ability to adequately remove waste and toxic proteins.""An increase of toxic proteins such as beta amyloid and tau in the brain are often linked with Alzheimer's disease, according to a University of Rochester Medical Center news release.""The researchers injected six mice with six different anesthetic regimens to replicate different stages of sleep.""This was to identify if a certain phase of sleep could be associated with the glymphatic system which the brain uses to clear waste.""The scientists determined the best glymphatic system activity takes place in the stage that was most similar to a human's deep, non REM, short-wave sleep, efficiently stimulating the cleaning process of the brain.""Mice that were given anesthetics that didn't lead to slower brain activity had a decline in glymphatic activity, according to the study."SOURCES: Journal of Science Advances, University of Rochester Medical Center news release, New Atlas, http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/5/2/eaav5447https://www.urmc.rochester.edu/news/story/5508/not-all-sleep-is-equal-when-it-comes-to-cleaning-the-brain.aspxhttps://newatlas.com/deep-slow-wave-sleep-brain-cleaning-alzheimers-dementia/58671/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 02:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/05/3791091/3791091_3D8AEB03C0234D6D9DF292DC4024016F_190305_3791091_Deep_sleep_important_for_brain_to_clear_out_toxi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sleep, toxic proteins, beta amyloid, toxic proteins, tau, sleeping, brain waves, alzheimer's, REM, glymphatic system, brain]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791949</guid>
      <title>London patient may be second in the world to be cured of HIV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA case study published in the journal Nature details the successful treatment of a patient in London, who is now in long-term HIV remission.CNN reports that a man known as the London patient has become the second person in the world to be cleared of HIV after the Berlin patient more than a decade ago.According to the New York Times, the two men achieved the milestones after undergoing bone marrow stem cell transplants intended to treat their cancer.In both instances, patients received stem cells from donors with a rare genetic mutation of the protein CCR5, making them HIV-resistant.HIV typically uses the CCR5 on the surface of immune cells to enter those cells, but is unable to latch on to the mutated version of the protein.According to the New York Times, the transplanted immune cells replaced the London patient's vulnerable cells, and destroyed the cancer without any harmful side effects.He remained on antiretroviral drugs until stopping in September 2017. The Guardian reports that blood tests have shown no signs of the virus for the past 18 months.Anton Pozniak, president of the International Aids Society, says the findings reaffirm the belief that AIDS is curable.He told the Guardian that the hope is there will eventually be a safe, cost-effective, and easy way to achieve results with gene technology or antibody techniques.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. London patient and Berlin patient both received bone marrow transplants for cancer2. London patient received stem cells from donor with mutated CCR5 protein3. HIV uses CCR5 to enter immune cells, but unable to latch on to mutated versions4. London patient in HIV remission for 18 months after stopping anti-HIV drugsVOICEOVER (in English): "CNN reports that a man known as the London patient has become the second person in the world to be cleared of HIV after the Berlin patient more than a decade ago.""According to the New York Times, the two men achieved the milestones after undergoing bone marrow stem cell transplants intended to treat their cancer.""In both instances, patients received stem cells from donors with a rare genetic mutation of the protein CCR5, making them HIV-resistant.""HIV typically uses the CCR5 on the surface of immune cells to enter those cells, but is unable to latch on to the mutated version of the protein.""According to the New York Times, the transplanted immune cells replaced the London patient's vulnerable cells, and destroyed the cancer without any harmful side effects.""He remained on antiretroviral drugs until stopping in September 2017. The Guardian reports that blood tests have shown no signs of the virus for the past 18 months."SOURCES: New York Times, The Guardian, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/04/health/aids-cure-london-patient.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/mar/05/london-patient-becomes-second-man-to-be-cleared-of-aids-virushttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/03/04/health/hiv-remission-london-patient-study-bn/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 08:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/06/3791949/3791949_0B3A22D6CD194BD8A44B4CEAEAE28153_190306_3791949_London_patient_may_be_second_in_the_world_to_be__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, HIV, AIDS, HIV cure, London patient, Berlin patient, cancer, Hodgkin's lymphoma, cancer cure, stem cell transplant, bone marrow transplant, stem cells]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791939</guid>
      <title>'Broken Heart' syndrome linked to the brain, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in the European Heart Journal says that the brain might be linked to broken heart syndrome.Also known as takotsubo syndrome, a broken heart is often caused by shock usually after a stressful or emotional event.The syndrome has similar symptoms to a heart attack such as breathlessness and chest pain, according to the study.The study goes on to suggest that an increase of stress hormones could be linked to the broken heart syndrome.The researchers looked at brain scans of 15 patients with broken heart and found decreased connectivity between the limbic system, which processes emotions, and the autonomic nervous system which controls breathing and heartbeat.Jelena Ghadri, a researcher involved with the study, was quoted by the BBC as saying "Emotions are processed in the brain so it is conceivable that the disease originates in the brain with top-down influences on the heart."According to the BBC, it could take weeks, days or even months for the heart muscle to recover from the syndrome. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Brain, heart, broken heart2. MRI scan, the limbic system and the autonomic nervous system3. Heart and brain 4. Different parts of the brain and a beating heartVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study published in the European Heart Journal says that the brain might be linked to broken heart syndrome.""Also known as takotsubo syndrome, a broken heart is often caused by shock usually after a stressful or emotional event.""According to the study, the syndrome has similar symptoms to a heart attack such as  breathlessness and chest pain.""The study goes on to suggest that an increase of stress hormones could be linked to the broken heart syndrome.""The researchers looked at brain scans of 15 patients with broken heart and found decreased connectivity between the limbic system, which processes emotions, and the autonomic nervous system which controls breathing and heartbeat."SOURCES: BBC News, European Heart Journal, Science Dailyhttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-47440622https://academic.oup.com/eurheartj/advance-article/doi/10.1093/eurheartj/ehz068/5366976https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/03/190304195238.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 08:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/06/3791939/3791939_36F1C6908FB847AE9F1DA50F7BA89289_190306_3791939__Broken_Heart__syndrome_linked_to_the_brain__stu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, broken heart syndrome, broken heart, broken heart science, broken heart linked with brain, broken heart syndrome symptoms, stress, heart broken, heartbreak, takotsubo syndrome, brain heart connection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791871</guid>
      <title>Self powered sensor can track firefighters in burning buildings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have created a motion-powered, fireproof sensor that can track movements of people who work in high-risk environments like firefighters, steelworkers and miners, according to a McMaster University press release.  McMasters researchers, working with partners at other colleges, have created a low-cost sensor that is about the size of a button-cell battery. According to the release, the sensors can be incorporated into the sole of a boot or under the arm of a jacket, wherever motion creates a pattern of constant contact and release to generate the energy the sensor needs to function. By harvesting electricity from movement, the sensor uses triboelectric, or friction-generated, charging for power.The sensors can track the movement and location of a person in a burning building, a mineshaft or other hazardous locations, alerting those outside if movement stops. The key material in the sensor, a new carbon aerogel nanocomposite, is fireproof and never needs charging from a power source. The sensors have been successfully tested at temperatures up to 300 degrees Celsius without any loss of function. The development teamfrom McMaster, UCLA and University of Chemistry and Technology Praguedescribes the new device in a paper published in the journal Nano Energy. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Workers being tracked in high-risk environments2. Sensors can be placed in boots or jackets and use triboelectric charging3. Sensors tracking firefighters in burning buildings4. Sensors tracking steelworkersVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers have created a motion-powered, fireproof sensor that can track movements of people who work in high-risk environments like firefighters, steelworkers and miners." "According to a McMasters University press release, the low-cost sensor is about the size of a button-cell battery." "The sensors can be incorporated into the sole of a boot or under the arm of a jacket, wherever motion creates a pattern of constant contact and release to generate the energy the sensor needs to function." "By harvesting electricity from movement, the sensor uses triboelectric, or friction-generated, charging for power.""The sensors can track the movement and location of a person in a burning building, a mineshaft or other hazardous locations, alerting those outside if movement stops." "The key material in the sensor, a new carbon aerogel nanocomposite, is fireproof and never needs charging from a power source." "The sensors have been successfully tested at temperatures up to 300 degrees Celsius without any loss of function." SOURCES: McMaster Universityhttps://brighterworld.mcmaster.ca/articles/keeping-high-risk-workers-safer/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/06/3791871/3791871_9F27ACE90D934A269880CD8F745A675F_190306_3791871_Self_powered_sensor_can_track_firefighters_in_bu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, self-powered sensor, triboelectric charging, firefighters, steelworkers, miners, high risk environments]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791832</guid>
      <title>China plans solar power plant in space and Mars mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina plans to build the first solar power plant in space and embark on a mission to Mars.China intends to build a solar power station that would orbit earth at a distance of 36,000 kilometers, according to Science and Technology Daily. Components of the solar power plant would be sent to space to be assembled, according to CNN.Pang Zhihao, a researcher, said the station would be able to draw energy from the sun without any interference from Earth's atmosphere. A receiving station will be built in Xian. The electricity could be beamed to Earth via microwaves or laser beams.China also has plans to send a rover to Mars. China's Mars mission is called the Mars Global Remote Sensing Orbiter and Small Rover, or HX-1. The lander will touch down on Mars' northern hemisphere and will contain a rover to explore Mars, according to the State Council of the People's Republic of China's website.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Solar power station in space2. Station being assembled3. Absorbing sun rays4. Sending sun rays, a receiving station and an electrical grid5. Solar power station and a Mars rover6. Mars simulation base7. Lander touching down on Mars8. Lander, roverVOICEOVER (in English): "According to reports from China's Science and Technology Daily, China intends to build a solar power station that would orbit earth at a distance of 36,000 kilometers.""According to CNN, components of the solar power plant would be sent to space where they would then be assembled .""Pang Zhihao, a researcher from the China Academy of Space Technology, told the newspaper the solar station would be able to draw energy from the sun without any interference from Earth's atmosphere.""A receiving station will be built in the northern Chinese city of Xian. The electricity could hypothetically be beamed to Earth via microwaves or lasers, although more research needs to be done on the effects these would have on humans and animals.""In addition to the orbital power plant, China also has plans to send a rover to Mars.""According to Global Times, the country has opened its first Mars simulation base in China's Qinghai Province. The area resembles the Martian surface with its dry and arid climate." "China's Mars mission is being called the Mars Global Remote Sensing Orbiter and Small Rover, or HX-1.""According to the State Council of the People's Republic of China's website, the lander is expected to touch down on the northern hemisphere of Mars.""The lander will contain a rover with six wheels and four solar panels and will explore Mars."SOURCES: CNN, Science & Technology Daily, Global Times, PRC State Council, Xinhuahttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/03/03/asia/china-plans-solar-power-in-space-intl/index.htmlhttp://www.stdaily.com/index/kejixinwen/2019-02/14/content_750019.shtmlhttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1140707.shtmlhttp://english.gov.cn/news/video/2016/08/24/content_281475424665899.htmhttp://english.cas.cn/newsroom/mutimedia_news/201608/t20160824_166702.shtmlhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-01/14/c_137743306.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/06/3791832/3791832_F8D3B56BF5224D8E97A81DB7EA560027_190306_3791832_China_plans_solar_power_plant_in_space_and_Mars__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Next Animation, Next Media, video, explainer, illustration, graphic, china, mars mission, china solar power station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791813</guid>
      <title>China planning solar power plant in space and Mars mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina plans to build the first solar power plant in space and embark on a mission to Mars.China intends to build a solar power station that would orbit earth at a distance of 36,000 kilometers, according to China's Science and Technology Daily.Components of the solar power plant would be sent to space to be assembled, according to CNN.Pang Zhihao, a researcher from the China Academy of Space Technology, told the newspaper the solar station would be able to draw energy from the sun without any interference from Earth's atmosphere.A receiving station will be built in the northern Chinese city of Xian. The electricity could hypothetically be beamed to Earth via microwaves or lasers, although more research needs to be done on the effects these would have on humans and animals.In addition to the orbital power plant, China also has plans to send a rover to Mars.The country has opened a Mars simulation base in China's Qinghai Province. The area resembles the Martian surface with its dry and arid climate, according to Global Times.China's Mars mission is being called the Mars Global Remote Sensing Orbiter and Small Rover, or HX-1.The lander will touch down on the northern hemisphere of Mars, according to the State Council of the People's Republic of China's website.The lander will contain a rover with six wheels and four solar panels and will explore Mars..RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Solar power station in space2. Station being assembled3. Station absorbing sun rays4. Station sending sun rays, a receiving station and an electrical grid5. Solar power station and a Mars rover6. Mars simulation base7. Lander touching down on Mars8. Lander with a roverVOICEOVER (in English): "According to reports from China's Science and Technology Daily, China intends to build a solar power station that would orbit earth at a distance of 36,000 kilometers.""According to CNN, components of the solar power plant would be sent to space where they would then be assembled .""Pang Zhihao, a researcher from the China Academy of Space Technology, told the newspaper the solar station would be able to draw energy from the sun without any interference from Earth's atmosphere.""A receiving station will be built in the northern Chinese city of Xian. The electricity could hypothetically be beamed to Earth via microwaves or lasers, although more research needs to be done on the effects these would have on humans and animals.""In addition to the orbital power plant, China also has plans to send a rover to Mars.""According to Global Times, the country has opened its first Mars simulation base in China's Qinghai Province. The area resembles the Martian surface with its dry and arid climate." "China's Mars mission is being called the Mars Global Remote Sensing Orbiter and Small Rover, or HX-1.""According to the State Council of the People's Republic of China's website, the lander is expected to touch down on the northern hemisphere of Mars.""The lander will contain a rover with six wheels and four solar panels and will explore Mars."SOURCES: CNN, WCJB,Science & Technology Daily, Global Times, State Council of the People's Republic of China, Xinhua,https://edition.cnn.com/2019/03/03/asia/china-plans-solar-power-in-space-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.wcjb.com/content/news/China-makes-plans-for-a-space-power-plant-and-a-mission-to-Mars-506644311.htmlhttp://www.stdaily.com/index/kejixinwen/2019-02/14/content_750019.shtmlhttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1140707.shtmlhttp://english.gov.cn/news/video/2016/08/24/content_281475424665899.htmhttp://english.cas.cn/newsroom/mutimedia_news/201608/t20160824_166702.shtmlhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-01/14/c_137743306.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 05:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/06/3791813/3791813_6A487F37AD174C729DB6390C5D717F9A_190306_3791813_China_planning_solar_power_plant_in_space_and_Ma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, mars, mars mission, china solar power station, space solar power station, solar energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793589</guid>
      <title>Genetically engineered bacteria can produce plastic from plants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA genetically engineered microbe is the key to producing biodegradable plastics from a common plant waste material.According to research from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, N. aromaticivorans is a type of soil bacteria that can digest lignin from plant cells and turn them into smaller hydrocarbons.Lignin is a polymer found in the cell walls of woody plants, which although abundant, is difficult to break down. It has such little value that paper mills that have been stripping lignin from wood for centuries merely dispose of it in boilers.During digestion, the bacteria turns lignin into 2-pyrone-4, 6-dicarboxylic acid, or PDC. By removing three genes from the microbe, University of Wisconsin-Madison scientists were able to make PDC the end point for the digestion process.UWM researcher Miguel Perez says bioengineers in Japan used PDC to make a variety of materials for consumer products, and found it performs the same or better than petroleum-based additives in PET polymers, like plastic bottles or synthetic fibers.As a plastic alternative, PDC would naturally break down in the environment, and also wouldn't leach compounds as it degrades.Researchers have so far managed to turn 59 percent of lignin's compounds into PDC, but suggest greater efficiency might be achieved with further gene-tweaking.The study is published in the journal Green Chemistry.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Soil bacteria N. aromaticivorans can break down lignin into smaller compounds2. Lignin found in cell walls of woody plants, cheap but difficult to process3. Bacteria tweaked so PDC production becomes end point for digestion4. PDC as alternative to plasticVOICEOVER (in English): "According to research from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, N. aromaticivorans is a type of soil bacteria that can digest lignin from plant cells and turn them into smaller hydrocarbons.""Lignin is a polymer found in the cell walls of woody plants, which although abundant, is difficult to break down.""It has such little value that paper mills that have been stripping lignin from wood for centuries merely dispose of it in boilers.""During digestion, the bacteria turns lignin into 2-pyrone-4, 6-dicarboxylic acid, or PDC. By removing three genes from the microbe, University of Wisconsin-Madison scientists were able to make PDC the end point for the digestion process.""UWM researcher Miguel Perez says bioengineers in Japan used PDC to make a variety of materials for consumer products, and found it performs the same or better than petroleum-based additives in PET polymers, like plastic bottles or synthetic fibers.""As a plastic alternative, PDC would naturally break down in the environment, and also wouldn't leach compounds as it degrades."SOURCES: University of Wisconsin Madison (via Science Daily), Green Chemistryhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/03/190306171239.htmhttps://pubs.rsc.org/en/Content/ArticleLanding/2019/GC/C8GC03504K***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/08/3793589/3793589_3C7CED5FEAB04670A3B4F632B9C9462F_190308_3793589_Genetically_engineered_bacteria_can_produce_plas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic from plants, plant plastic, biodegradable plastic, plastic alternative, plastic, lignin, soil bacteria, genetically engineered microbe, genetically engineered bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793565</guid>
      <title>China leaked chat logs expose scope of state surveillance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA leak of around 364 million online records in a Chinese database has exposed the massive scope of state surveillance in China, according to the Financial Times. According to security researcher Victor Gevers at Dutch non-profit GDI Foundation, who found the database, the files show GPS locations, file transfers, identity card numbers and chat logs. According to Gevers, the database was freely accessible online to anyone with the IP address, and user profiles were stored together with photographs, addresses and locations. He also added that the main database was providing information to 17 other servers depending on which area the data came from. According to the Financial Times, a large number of the records had the names and addresses of internet cafes on them. According to AFP, Chinese law requires internet cafes to record the identities and "relevant" online activity of users, and provide them to the public security bureau on request. This has lead to the growth of internet cafe monitoring software. The records in the databases have labels referring to Chinese social-media apps like WeChat and QQ, in addition to WeChat payment records and QQ account numbers. According to the AFP, Gevers also found another publicly accessible database that contained personal information such as ethnicity and GPS tracking data of 2.6 million people in Xinjiang. Access to this database, however, has since been closed.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Leaked online records on database2. Database accessibility and information stored 3. Internet cafe4. Xinjiang databaseVOICEOVER (in English): "A leak of around 364 million online records in a Chinese database has exposed the massive scope of state surveillance in China." "According to security researcher Victor Gevers at Dutch non-profit GDI Foundation, who found the database, the files show GPS locations, file transfers, identity card numbers, and chat logs." "According to Gevers, the database was freely accessible online to anyone with the IP address, and user profiles were stored together with photographs, addresses and locations." "The records in the databases also have labels referring to Chinese social-media apps like WeChat and QQ, in addition to WeChat payment records and QQ account numbers." "According to the Financial Times, a large number of the records had the names and addresses of internet cafes on them." "According to AFP, Chinese law requires internet cafes to record the identities and 'relevant' online activity of users, and provide them to the public security bureau on request. This has lead to the growth of internet cafe monitoring software." "According to the AFP, Gevers also found another publicly accessible database that contained personal information such as ethnicity and GPS tracking data of 2.6 million people in Xinjiang. Access to this database, however, has since been closed."   SOURCES: Financial Times, France 24https://www.ft.com/content/1e0365f0-3e73-11e9-b896-fe36ec32aecehttps://www.france24.com/en/20190307-china-chat-log-leak-shows-scope-surveillance***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/08/3793565/3793565_625A2C1C5F464D27B8F26B3D5C3ECE0F_190308_3793565_China_leaked_chat_logs_expose_scope_of_state_sur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china surveillance, china chat log leak, china online surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793332</guid>
      <title>Kim Jong Nam murder suspect to testify in Malaysian court</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOne of the women suspected of murdering Kim Jong Un's elder half-brother, Kim Jong Nam is set to testify in court next week.According to the AFP, one of the women suspected of murdering Kim Jong Un's elder half-brother, Kim Jong-Nam is set to testify in court next week.In February 2017, Kim Jong-Nam was traveling from Kuala Lumpur to Macau when he was reportedly poisoned by two women, now identified as Doan Thi Huong from Vietnam and Siti Aisyah from Indonesia. Citing unnamed police sources, state news agency Bernama reported that one woman sprayed chemicals on Kim Jong-Nam's face and immediately after, the second woman held a cloth over his face for 10 seconds. Reuters reported that traces of the deadly nerve agent VX was found on the women's clothing. VX blocks signals between the nervous system and the body's muscles. This causes muscular paralysis which results in death via asphyxiation.Malaysian officials also identified four other men at the airport who are suspected of being North Korean agents that directed the attack.The Washington Post reports that U.S. officials believe Huong and Aisyah were following direct orders from Pyongyang while Huong claims that she thought she was participating in a prank television show. Huang is believed to have been recruited by North Korean officials while working at a bar in Hanoi. North Korea has denied any type of involvement, however, the four agents who were identified by Malaysian officials fled the country soon after the attack took place.Kim Jong Nam and Kim Jong Un are both sons of former North Korean leader Kim Jong Il, however, they were born to different mothers.\RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  Doan Thi Huong testifying in court2. Kim Jong-Nam traveling from Kuala Lumpur to Macau3. Kim Jong-Nam is poisoned by two women 4. Effects of nerve agent VX5.Malaysian officials identify four other men suspected to be North Korean agents6. Women are suspected to be following direct orders from North Korea7.Huang is recruited by North Korean officials8. North Korean agents disappear after assassination takes placeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the AFP, one of the women suspected of murdering Kim Jong Un's elder half-brother, Kim Jong-Nam is set to testify in court next week.""The Washington Post reports that U.S. officials believe Huong and Aisyah were following direct orders from Pyongyang while Huong claims that she thought she was participating in a prank television show." "Huang is believed to have been recruited by North Korean officials while working at a bar in Hanoi." "North Korea has denied any type of involvement, however, the four agents who were identified by Malaysian officials fled the country soon after the attack took place."SOURCES: The Washington Post, Agence France Presse, The Telegraph, The Guardian, The Star Online, Reutershttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2019/02/23/vietnams-unspoken-link-kim-jong-un-woman-accused-assassinating-his-half-brother/http://www.nationmultimedia.com/detail/asean-plus/30365297http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/15/exclusive-two-female-secret-agents-behind-murder-kim-jong-unsbrother/https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/feb/15/kim-jong-nam-malaysian-police-arrest-female-suspect-over-deathhttp://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/02/15/kim-jong-nam-was-killed-outside-immigration-checkpoint-area-say-immigration-dg/http://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-malaysia-kim-idUSKBN15U02Shttp://af.reuters.com/article/worldNews/idAFKBN15V06N***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 08:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/08/3793332/3793332_51E004253E8C4DBF9C2770FE45C37735_190308_3793332_Kim_Jong_Nam_murder_suspect_to_testify_in_Malays_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, kim jong nam, kim jong un, murder, kim jong nam murder, north korea, malaysia, kuala lumpur]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794888</guid>
      <title>Ethiopian Airlines 737 plane crashes, killing 157</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Ethiopian Airlines plane headed for Nairobi crashed minutes after take-off on Sunday, killing all 157 people on board. According to Reuters, Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 left Bole Airport in Addis Ababa at 8:38 a.m. local time, before losing contact with the control tower at 8:44 a.m. According to data published by FlightRadar24, the plane took off in good weather and clear visibility and struggles to ascend at a stable speed. According to data published by FlightRadar24 on Twitter, during the first three minutes of flight, the vertical speed was unstable after take-off. According to chief executive of the airline Tewolde GebreMariam, the pilot had sent out a distress call and was cleared to return to the airport. After losing contact with air traffic controllers, the plane crashed into the ground near Bishoftu, a town southeast of the capital. Passengers from 33 countries were aboard the flight, said GebreMariam. According to Reuters, the aircraft, a 737 MAX 8, is the same Boeing model as the Lion Air flight that crashed in the Java Sea after take-off from Jakarta on Oct. 29, killing all 189 people on board.Boeing has said it is sending a technical team to help with the Ethiopian-led crash investigation. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flight path and location of crash2. Plane struggling to ascend at stable speed3. Pilot issuing a distress call4. Crash siteVOICEOVER (in English): "An Ethiopian Airlines plane headed for Nairobi crashed minutes after take-off on Sunday, killing all 157 people on board." "According to Reuters, Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 left Bole Airport in Addis Ababa at 8:38 a.m. local time, before losing contact with the control tower at 8:44 a.m." "According to data published by FlightRadar24, the plane took off in good weather and clear visibility and struggled to ascend at a stable speed." "According to data published by FlightRadar24 on Twitter, during the first three minutes of flight, the vertical speed was unstable after take-off." "According to chief executive of the airline, the pilot had sent out a distress call and was cleared to return to the airport." "After losing contact with air traffic controllers, the plane crashed into the ground near Bishoftu, a town southeast of the capital." "Passengers from 33 countries were aboard the flight." SOURCES: Reuters, New York Times, FlightRadar24, CNN https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-airplane/ethiopian-airlines-flight-crashes-killing-157-idUSKBN1QR07Vhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/10/world/africa/ethiopian-airlines-plane-crash.htmlhttps://twitter.com/flightradar24/status/1104676048317362177https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/ethiopian-airlines-plane-crash/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 12:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/11/3794888/3794888_DE7C8FC5CA764330B8CF45A46F0AB2E6_190311_3794888_Ethiopian_Airlines_737_plane_crashes__killing_15_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ethiopian Airlines, Ethiopian Airlines crash, Boeing 737 MAX 8, Boeing 737 crash, Boeing 737 MAX 8 crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794802</guid>
      <title>China rebuilding its cities into water absorbent urban areas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina plans to address faulty drainage systems, urban flooding and water scarcity by building 'sponge cities'. In 2013, China announced that its major cities would undergo water infrastructure development that would enable them to absorb and process water. The on-going project is called the Sponge City program and began in the Central City of Wuhan in Hubei province.All cities participating in the program have to guarantee that 20 percent of their urban areas have sponge features by 2020. These sponge features must be able to retain 70 percent of the city's stormwater, according to The Guardian.These sponge features include rain gardens, green space, artificial wetlands, swales and new drainage systems.In the city of Wuhan, 20 percent of the city's urban land would cover roughly 170 square kilometers out of its total urban area of 860 square kilometers.The program currently includes 30 cities. The new target requires them to ensure that 80 percent of their urban land will be capable of absorbing and re-using rain and stormwater.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sponge city; Location of Wuhan, China. 2. Sponge cities must retain 70 percent of their stormwater.3. Sponge features4. Wuhan City, China: how much the sponge city area would coverVOICEOVER (in English): "In 2013, China announced that its major cities would undergo water infrastructure development that would enable them to absorb and process water. The on-going project is called the Sponge City program and began in the Central City of Wuhan in Hubei province.""All cities participating in the program have to guarantee that 20 percent of their urban areas have sponge features by 2020. These sponge features must be able to retain 70 percent of the city's stormwater, reports The Guardian.""These sponge features include rain gardens, green space, artificial wetlands, swales and new drainage systems.""In the city of Wuhan, 20 percent of the city's urban land would cover roughly 170 square kilometers out of its total urban area of 860 square kilometers."SOURCES: The Guardian, Business Insider, Arcadis https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/jan/23/inside-chinas-leading-sponge-city-wuhans-war-with-waterhttps://www.businessinsider.com/china-is-building-sponge-cities-that-absorb-water-2017-11https://www.arcadis.com/en/global/what-we-do/our-projects/asia/china/wuhan-sponge-city/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 09:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/11/3794802/3794802_05FA4C3169844121AFF5C2B6E0D03CB6_190311_3794802_China_rebuilding_its_cities_into_water_absorbent_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, environmentalism, environmental engineering, china, china infrastructure, china sponge cities, wuhan china, china architecture, china urban planning, china city planning, sponge city, city planning, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794777</guid>
      <title>New AI technology able to 'read' ones facial impressions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew tech developed by a US-based AI company can scan your face and read your emotions.Affectiva has developed emotional detection technology that can be used to translate human facial expressions. This technology uses two main techniques: computer vision and supervised learning, The Guardian reports.Computer vision is used to clearly identify facial expressions while supervised learning is used to train the algorithm to recognize expressions it has already seen.The company has already gathered data from 7.5 million faces in 87 countries, according to Affectiva's website.The company uses EMFACS or Emotion Facial Action Coding System to recognize facial expressions such as a scowling face for anger or a smiling face for happiness.The Guardian quotes Meredith Whittaker, from the research institute AI Now, as saying that recruiting companies and schools are already using this technique to assess facial expressions of candidates or students.She added that the technology could harm an individual if the analysis isn't completely accurate.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. AI emotional detection technology2. Showing computer vision and supervised learning3. The Emotional Facial Action Coding System4. Recruiting company icon, school icon, AI technology reading a faceVOICEOVER (in English): "Affectiva has developed emotional detection technology that can be used to translate human facial expressions.""The Guardian reports this technology uses two main techniques: computer vision and supervised learning.""Computer vision is used to clearly identify facial expressions while supervised learning is used to train the algorithm to recognize expressions it has already seen.""The company uses EMFACS or Emotion Facial Action Coding System to recognize facial expressions such as a scowling face for anger or a smiling face for happiness.""The Guardian quotes Meredith Whittaker, from the research institute AI Now, as saying that recruiting companies and schools are already using this technique to assess facial expressions of candidates or students.""Adding that the technology could harm an individual if the analysis isn't completely accurate."SOURCES: The Guardian, MIT Technology Review, Affectiva website, https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/06/facial-recognition-software-emotional-sciencehttps://www.technologyreview.com/s/613019/when-our-devices-can-read-our-emotions-affectivas-gabi-zijderveld/https://www.affectiva.com/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 09:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/11/3794777/3794777_17D8047F0A8E4BBCACE7E91B83DEB110_190311_3794777_New_AI_technology_able_to__read__ones_facial_imp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, AI, technology, surveillance, facial emotions, surveillance technology, Affectiva, affectiva ai, affectiva emotion recognition, affectiva emotion ai, artificial intelligence, Ai emotions, artificial emotional intelligence, artificial emotional intelligence affectiva]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794652</guid>
      <title>Berlin pursues 'sponge city' strategy to deal with climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs heatwaves and urban flooding become increasingly common across northern Europe, Berlin's local government is pursuing a "sponge city" approach to address the effects of climate change.According to a report by Deutsche Welle, municipal officials are taking steps to transform Berlin into an urban sponge to allow nature itself to help cool temperatures and reduce runoff from storms.Moss and grass are being planted on rooftops to absorb rainwater. Buildings are being painted in light colors to reflect heat instead of absorbing it.Carlo Becker, the architect of Berlin's Sponge City strategy, explained to Bloomberg that the idea is to use rain water to cool the city naturally by imitating the natural water cycle.The city also plans to add more green spaces and urban wetlands to efficiently absorb rain water.Heike Stock, the official in charge of managing the program, told Deutsche Welle the idea of the urban sponge is to "avoid sealing up too much of the ground surface with concrete or tarmac" and to allow water to be absorbed into the ground through permeable surfaces.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. City becoming green2. Grass appearing on rooftops3. Light-colored buildings reflecting sun rays 4. Green space, urban wetlands and rain VOICEOVER (in English): "Officials in Berlin are taking steps to transform the city into an urban sponge to allow nature itself to help cool temperatures and reduce runoff from storms.""Moss and grass are being planted on rooftops to absorb rainwater.""Buildings are being painted in light colors to reflect heat instead of absorbing it.""The city also plans to add more green spaces and urban wetlands to efficiently absorb rain water."SOURCES: Deutsche Welle, Water Bucket News, Bloomberg, https://www.dw.com/en/sponge-city-berlin-plans-for-a-hotter-climate/a-19420517https://waterbucket.ca/rm/2017/08/22/towards-a-water-resilient-future-video-released-by-the-senate-of-berlin-in-august-2017-the-plan-step-klima-konkret-seeks-to-mimic-nature-and-tackle-extreme-conditions-by-making-b/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2017-08-18/sponge-city-making-berlin-cooler-video***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 04:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/11/3794652/3794652_19F824EE441449B38F1F27871EC21FB1_190311_3794652_Berlin_pursues__sponge_city__strategy_to_deal_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, germany, berlin, sponge city, architecture, german architecture, sponge city berlin, sponge city germany, sponge city concept, sponge city project, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795465</guid>
      <title>All you need to know about the Boeing 737 Max 8</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe United States has told airlines the Boeing 737 Max 8 is safe to fly as investigators found two black box recorders from Sunday's downed Ethiopian Airlines jet, according to Reuters. According to Reuters, China and Indonesia have both grounded their 737 Max 8 fleets on Monday, citing safety concerns. Investigators in Ethiopia found two black box recorders early on Monday that will help authorities figure out what brought the plane down in a crash that killed 157 people. The accident comes months after the same model jet crashed in Indonesia killing 189 people. According to Boeing, the 737 Max 8 is a single-aisle plane that has a quieter cabin, more legroom for passengers and was designed to be more fuel efficient. The plane measures 39.52 meters long, with a wingspan of 35.9 meters. It is equipped with LEAP-1B engines and has a range of 6,550 kilometers.  According to the New York Times, the 200-seat Boeing 737 Max 8 has been a popular plane after being introduced in 2017, with more than 4,000 planes ordered in the first six months. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 737 Max 8 interior2. 737 Max 8 length and wingspan3. 737 Max 8 engines and range4. 737 Max 8 flyingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Boeing, the 737 Max 8 is a single-aisle plane that has a quieter cabin, more legroom for passengers and was designed to be more fuel efficient." "The plane measures 39.52 meters long, with a wingspan of 35.9 meters.""It is equipped with LEAP-1B engines and has a range of 6,550 kilometers."  "According to the New York Times, the 200-seat Boeing 737 Max 8 has been a popular plane after being introduced in 2017, with more than 4,000 planes ordered in the first six months." SOURCES: Reuters, New York Times, Boeinghttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-airplane/after-ethiopia-crash-horror-some-nations-ground-boeing-737-max-8s-idUSKBN1QS15Fhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/11/travel/flying-boeing-737-max-8.htmlhttps://www.boeing.com/commercial/737max/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 11:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/12/3795465/3795465_FF9D05E0E7D941079BC76CCEDEE81946_190312_3795465_All_you_need_to_know_about_the_Boeing_737_Max_8_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing, Boeing 737 Ethiopian Airlines, 737 Max 8]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795267</guid>
      <title>Coral Reef in the northern Red Sea surprisingly resistant to rising sea temperatures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCoral reefs near the Israeli city of Eilat are thriving despite years of extensive farm fishing and climate change.Scientists in Israel have found that coral reefs in the northern Red Sea are unusually  resistant to rising sea temperatures and acidification, according to a study published in the Journal of Experimental Biology last month.Coral in the Red Sea was damaged by cages that were used for fish farming from 1995 to 2008. The cages have since been removed and the coral has flourished, even as coral reefs are in decline nearly everywhere else around the world.Researchers at the Inter-University Institute for Marine Sciences in Eilat theorize that the coral's resistance came about due to natural selection 18,000 years ago, when corals that were able to survive in warmer water migrated from the Indian Ocean through the Bab al-Mandab strait, where water temperatures were higher.The Associated Press quotes Jacqueline De La Cour, from the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration's Coral Reef Watch, as saying this gives us hope that species would be able to adapt to survive.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Coral in the Red Sea and coral found in other parts of the world2. Cages used for fish farm being dissolved and coral thriving3. Healthy coral4. Where the Red Sea coral migrated from VOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists in Israel have found that coral reefs in the northern Red Sea are unusually  resistant to rising sea temperatures and acidification, according to a study published in the Journal of Experimental Biology last month.""Coral in the Red Sea had been damaged by cages that were used for fish farming from 1995 to 2008. The cages have since been removed and the coral has flourished, even as coral reefs are in decline nearly everywhere else around the world.""Researchers at the Inter-University Institute for Marine Sciences in Eilat theorize that the coral's resistance came about due to natural selection 18,000 years ago,""when corals that were able to survive in warmer water migrated from the Indian Ocean through the Bab al-Mandab strait, where water temperatures were higher."SOURCES: Times of Israel, Haaretz, Y Net news, News 24, Jewish News, The Associated Press, https://www.timesofisrael.com/eilat-coral-reef-defies-expectations-and-regenerates-after-fish-farming-damage/https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/crowned-one-of-world-s-top-spots-by-nyt-tourism-now-threatens-eilat-s-coral-reef-1.6830088https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium.MAGAZINE-scientists-surveyed-eilat-s-seabed-and-found-more-than-expected-1.6934906https://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-5458388,00.htmlhttps://www.news24.com/Green/News/northern-red-sea-coral-reefs-may-survive-a-hot-grim-future-20190220https://jewishnews.timesofisrael.com/israeli-scientists-hope-red-sea-discovery-gives-hope-for-worlds-coral-reefs/https://www.apnews.com/9ad467ad04c94666b856b4d37a9fbcc6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 07:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/12/3795267/3795267_9963E553B7AF463E9C1C4F632126494C_190312_3795267_Coral_Reef_in_the_northern_Red_Sea_surprisingly__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coral reef, red sea coral reef, abandoned oil pipeline, israel coral reef, israel coral, eilat israel coral reef, eilat, coral reef conservation, climate change, global warming, rising sea temperatures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795113</guid>
      <title>Mercury in retrograde explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWhen Mercury is in retrograde, it appears as if the planet is moving backwards when viewed from Earth's sky.This is because Mercury completes an orbit faster than Earth does, according to reports from NASA.According to Vox, as Mercury passes Earth, Earth's line of sight will shift so that Mercury will appear to retrograde for around three weeks when viewed from our planet.This is because both Mercury and Earth are orbiting the solar system at different speeds, creating an illusion that the planet is moving backwards.Mercury is currently retrograding from March 5 to March 28 and will retrograde two more times later this year, according to Newsweek.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mercury retrograding as seen from Earth's sky2. Mercury orbiting faster than Earth in Space3. Depiction of Earth's line of sight when Mercury passes Earth4. The two planets orbiting the solar system at different speeds at the same time and three calendar iconsVOICEOVER (in English): "When Mercury is in retrograde, it appears as if the planet is moving backwards when viewed from Earth's sky.""According to reports from NASA, this is because Mercury completes an orbit faster than Earth does.""According to Vox, as Mercury passes Earth, Earth's line of sight will shift so that Mercury will appear to retrograde for around three weeks when viewed from our planet.""This is because both Mercury and Earth are orbiting the solar system at different speeds, creating an illusion that the planet is moving backwards.""According to Newsweek, Mercury is currently retrograding from March 5 to March 28 and will retrograde two more times later this year."SOURCES: NASA, Vox, Newsweekhttps://starchild.gsfc.nasa.gov/docs/StarChild/questions/question46.htmlhttps://solarsystem.nasa.gov/planets/mercury/in-depth/https://www.vox.com/videos/2018/11/16/18098729/what-is-mercury-retrograde-meaninghttps://www.newsweek.com/what-does-it-mean-when-mercury-retrograde-astrology-terminology-explained-1353988***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 03:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/12/3795113/3795113_25391B3CB87E48ECB33B8DD77DD2D1FF_190312_3795113_Mercury_in_retrograde_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mercury, retrograde, mercury retrograde, mercury in retrograde, astronomy, mercury retrograde explained, retrograde motion, planet retrograding, solar system, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795960</guid>
      <title>Ethiopian Airlines plane smoked and shuddered before crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWitnesses have come out to describe what they saw moments before the deadly crash that killed all 157 passengers on board Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302.The CEO of Ethiopian Airlines told CNN that pilots of Flight 302 reported 'flight control problems' to air traffic control. This suggests the plane wasn't responding to inputs, and pilots were losing control of the aircraft.Witnesses interviewed by Reuters said they had seen smoke billowing out behind the plane, and heard a loud rattling noise, like straining and shaking metal.The farmer whose field the plane crashed in said it made a sharp turn above a field of panicked cows, while another eyewitness claimed it was trailing clothes and papers as well as smoke.The aircraft was trying to climb and lift its nose, according to two other witnesses, but failed and crashed nose-first into the ground before then exploding.According to Reuters, the debris field was roughly the size of two soccer fields.Reuters reports that investigators have recovered the flight data recorder and cockpit voice recorder, which will be sent overseas for scrutiny. It's unclear at the moment where or when the data will be analyzed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flight control problems on Ethiopian Airlines Flight 3022. Witnesses saw plane smoking, giving off loud rattling sound3. Plane made sharp turn above field, trailing clothes, papers, as well as smoke4. Aircraft failed to climb, crashed nose-first on the ground before explodingVOICEOVER (in English): "The CEO of Ethiopian Airlines told CNN that pilots of doomed Flight 302 reported 'flight control problems' to air traffic control.""This suggests the plane wasn't responding to inputs, and pilots were losing control of the aircraft.""Witnesses interviewed by Reuters said they had seen smoke billowing out behind the plane, and heard a loud rattling noise, like straining and shaking metal.""The farmer whose field the plane crashed in said it made a sharp turn above a field of panicked cows, while another eyewitness claimed it was trailing clothes and papers as well as smoke.""The aircraft was trying to climb and lift its nose, according to two other witnesses, but failed and crashed nose-first into the ground before then exploding.""According to Reuters, the debris field was roughly the size of two soccer fields."SOURCES: CNN, Reutershttps://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/boeing-737-max-8-ethiopia-airlines-crash/h_9dee508ccc0a80f533a2bdafb8d5b536https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-airplane-witnesses/ethiopian-plane-smoked-and-shuddered-before-deadly-plunge-idUSKBN1QS1LJ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 08:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/13/3795960/3795960_9A7C60AE30154E86B56F6A5B96099DD0_190313_3795960_Ethiopian_Airlines_plane_smoked_and_shuddered_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plane crash, ethiopia crash, ethiopian airlines crash, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing Max, Boeing, Ethiopian Airlines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795910</guid>
      <title>What caused Lion Air's Boeing 737 Max to go down last year?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBoeing is under scrutiny as two of its aircrafts have crashed in less than a year.In October of 2018, Lion Air Flight JT610 flew from Jakarta and crashed in the waters off of Java.The aircraft was a Boeing 737 Max 8 which ended up killing all 189 passengers and crew members aboard, according to the Washington Post.An investigative report release in November of last year says a malfunctioning sensor was one of the reasons the flight crashed.The aircraft's sensor sent faulty data to the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which caused an alert that the plane was in danger when it was not.This led the system to automatically position the plane's nose downward in order to prevent a stall.Since the reading was erroneous, the pilot had to struggle to correct the plane's position.The pilot was unsuccessful in his attempts to save the plane, which crashed into the sea 11 minutes after take off.According to the Washington Post, investigators are looking to see if there are similarities between the Lion Air crash and the recent plane crash in Ethiopia as both flights crashed shortly after take-off and at low altitudes.China, Indonesia and Singapore have now banned all 737 Max 8 aircrafts from their airspaces in the wake of the two plane crashes, The New York Times reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Aircraft in the sky2. Plane sensors3. Automatic system sense the plane is in danger when it isn't 4. Pilot trying to save the planeVOICEOVER (in English): "In October of 2018, Lion Air Flight JT610 flew from Jakarta and crashed in the waters off of Java.""According to the Washington Post , the aircraft was also a Boeing 737 Max 8 which ended up killing all 189 passengers and crew members aboard.""An investigative report release in November of last year says a malfunctioning sensor was one of the reasons the flight crashed.""The aircraft's sensor sent faulty data to the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which caused an alert that the plane was in danger when it was not.""This led the system to automatically position the plane's nose downward in order to prevent a stall.""Since the reading was erroneous, the pilot had to struggle to correct the plane's position.""The pilot was unsuccessful in his attempts to save the plane, which crashed into the sea 11 minutes after take off."SOURCES: The Washington Post, The New York Times https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/trafficandcommuting/report-on-airline-crash-that-killed-189-people-draws-few-conclusions/2018/11/27/a07b833c-f274-11e8-80d0-f7e1948d55f4_story.html?utm_term=.425e686f871fhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2019/03/10/with-ethiopian-airlines-crash-another-new-boeing-max-jet-goes-down/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.5203fbfb448bhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/12/world/africa/boeing-ethiopian-airlines-plane-crash.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/09/world/asia/air-lion-crash-610.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 08:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/13/3795910/3795910_A3B623741FEB4C14838B14AEC9549653_190313_3795910_What_caused_Lion_Air_s_Boeing_737_Max_to_go_down_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Indonesia plane crash, plane crash indonesia, indonesia plane crash survivors, lion air, indonesia plane crash 2018, java plane crash, jakarta, boeing, lion air crash latest news, plane crash, boeing 737 Max,boeing 737 Max,  boeing 737 Max 8 crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795885</guid>
      <title>FAA demands Boeing improve 737 MAX 8 model</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUS regulators are demanding Boeing make modifications to improve the 737 MAX 8 following two crashes of the same model.   According to Al Jazeera, the US Federal Aviation Administration is demanding Boeing make improvements to anti-stalling software and the aircrafts' maneuvering system. The FAA has given Boeing until the end of April to finalize the improvements.In an open letter to civil aviation authorities, the FAA stated that Boeing is also updating training requirements and flight crew manuals to go with the new updates to the maneuvering system. These updates include changes to the airplane flight manual, flight crew operations manual and airplane maintenance manual.According to CNN, some airlines are temporarily suspending 737 MAX 8s from flying following last Sunday's crash. These include airlines from China, Singapore, Indonesia, Mexican airline Aeromexico, Argentine airline Aerolneas Argentinas, Cayman Airways and Comair Airways. American Airlines, Southwest Airlines among other airways have announced they will not suspend the aircraft. According to the FAA, there are currently 387 737 MAX 8 and 9 jets flying worldwide, 74 of which are registered in the U.S.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lionair plane crash2. Ethiopian Airlines crash3. US Federal Aviation Administration demands Boeing make changes4. Boeing updating training requirements and flight crew manuals5. Other manuals that will be updated according to Boeing6. Airlines and countries that have suspended  737 MAX 8VOICEOVER (in English): "In October 2018 an Indonesian plane carrying 188 passengers and crew crashed into the Java Sea. There were no survivors.""Last Sunday, an Ethiopian plane crashed minutes after take-off killing all onboard. Both of these flights were on a Boeing 737 MAX 8 jet.""According to Al Jazeera, the US Federal Aviation Administration is demanding Boeing make improvements to anti-stalling software and the aircrafts' maneuvering system. The FAA has given Boeing until the end of April to finalize the improvements.""In an open letter to civil aviation authorities, the FAA stated that Boeing is also updating training requirements and flight crew manuals to go with the new updates to the maneuvering system." "These updates include changes to the airplane flight manual, flight crew operations manual and airplane maintenance manual.""According to CNN, some airlines are temporarily suspending 737 MAX 8s from flying following last Sunday's crash." "These include airlines from China, Singapore, Indonesia, Mexican airline Aeromexico, Argentine airline Aerolneas Argentinas, Cayman Airways and Comair Airways." "American Airlines, Southwest Airlines among other airways have announced they will not suspend the aircraft." SOURCES: Al Jazeera, Quartz, FAA,  Boeing, CNNhttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/03/regulator-demands-boeing-modify-737-max-ethiopia-crash-190312020507489.htmlhttps://qz.com/1570960/boeing-will-update-the-737-maxs-flight-software-by-april/https://www.faa.gov/news/updates/media/CAN_2019_03.pdfhttps://boeing.mediaroom.com/news-releases-statements?item=130402\https://boeing.mediaroom.com/2019-01-30-Boeing-Reports-Record-2018-Results-and-Provides-2019-Guidancehttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/03/11/africa/max-8-operations-roundup-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 07:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/13/3795885/3795885_89CF5F20D00546E3AF1B50C025F7290D_190313_3795885_FAA_demands_Boeing_improve_737_MAX_8_model_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ethiopian Airlines, Ethiopian Airlines crash, Boeing 737 MAX 8, Boeing 737 crash, Boeing 737 MAX 8 crash, Indonesia plane crash, lion air, java plane crash, jakarta, boeing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795841</guid>
      <title>NYC to open tallest observation deck in the Western Hemisphere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe newest addition to New York's skyline costs a whopping $28 billion and will include more than 100 retail shops, cultural venues among other amenities. According to CNN, New York's newest skyscraper, named Edge, will be the tallest outdoor observation deck in the Western Hemisphere and the fifth-tallest in the world.Edge will stand at over 1,100 feet tall, around 335 meters. Its biggest attraction is a 7,500-square-foot or 697-square-meter observation deck that protrudes from the building. The edges of the deck are lined by 6-foot-tall glass walls, providing visitors with a full view of New York City's skyline.Once opened, Edge's observation deck will stand taller than the Empire State Building and the Top of the Rock at the Rockefeller Center, which measure 1,050 feet or 320 meters above street level and 850 feet or 260 meters above street level respectively.The building is set to open in the first quarter if 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of Edge2. Height of Edge3. The height of the glass walls surrounding Edge's observation deck4. Height comparison between Edge, Empire State Building and Rockefeller Center.  VOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNN, New York's newest skyscraper, named Edge, will be the tallest outdoor observation deck in the Western Hemisphere and the fifth-tallest in the world.""Edge will stand at over 1,100 feet tall, around 335 meters. Its biggest attraction is a 7,500-square-foot or 697-square-meter observation deck that protrudes from the building.""The edges of the deck are lined by 6-foot-tall glass walls, providing visitors with a full view of New York City's skyline.""Once opened, Edge's observation deck will stand taller than the Empire State Building and the Top of the Rock at the Rockefeller Center, which measure 1,050 feet or 320 meters above street level and 850 feet or 260 meters above street level respectively."SOURCES: CNN, NJ.comhttps://www.cnn.com/travel/article/new-york-edge-observation-deck/index.htmlhttps://www.nj.com/news/2019/03/the-tallest-observation-deck-in-the-western-hemisphere-is-coming-to-new-york-knee-buckling-views-of-nj-included.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 06:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/13/3795841/3795841_8F49A33E58354F1E9A9631C3C177052A_190313_3795841_NYC_to_open_tallest_observation_deck_in_the_West_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, New york, building, skyscraper, observation deck, edge, new york city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795809</guid>
      <title>NASA discovers 'hopping' water on moon's surface</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANData from NASA's lunar orbiter has shed light on water movement on the moon's surface.According to NASA, scientists previously thought moon was arid, with water existing mainly as ice pockets in craters near the poles. But in recent years, they have identified surface water in sparse molecule populations bound to regolith, or lunar soil.Observations gathered by an instrument on NASA's Lunar Reconnaissance Orbiter indicate that water moves around the dayside of the moon.Water molecules remain bound to the regolith until surface temperatures peak during lunar noon. They then thermally desorb and either bounce to a nearby location that is cold enough, or stick to the moon's weak atmosphere until temperatures drop and they can return to the surface.Scientists have hypothesized that hydrogen ions in the solar wind may be generating most of the moon's water. But as the supply doesn't decrease even when the moon is shielded from solar winds, it suggests water builds up over time instead of raining directly down.A paper detailing the findings has been published in the journal Geophysical Research LettersPlanetary Science Institute senior scientist and lead author Amanda Hendrix says lunar water can be used to make fuel or for radiation shielding or thermal management. This could make future missions more affordable as these materials don't need to be launched from Earth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Moon previously thought arid, but surface water recently found bound to lunar soil2. Lunar Reconnaissance Orbiter observed that water moves around, with water molecules bound to soil until lunar noon3. Water molecules desorb, hop to a cold enough location or to atmosphere, return when temperatures drop4. Hydrogen ions in solar winds may be generating moon's waterVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA, scientists previously thought moon was arid, with water existing mainly as ice pockets in craters near the poles.""But in recent years, they have identified surface water in sparse molecule populations bound to regolith, or lunar soil.""Observations gathered by an instrument on NASA's Lunar Reconnaissance Orbiter indicate that water moves around the dayside of the moon.""Water molecules remain bound to the regolith until surface temperatures peak during lunar noon.""They then thermally desorb and either bounce to a nearby location that is cold enough, or stick to the moon's weak atmosphere until temperatures drop and they can return to the surface.""Scientists have hypothesized that hydrogen ions in the solar wind may be generating most of the moon's water.""But as the supply doesn't decrease even when the moon is shielded from solar winds, it suggests water builds up over time instead of raining directly down."SOURCES: NASA, Spacehttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2019/lro-sheds-light-on-lunar-water-movementhttps://www.space.com/water-on-the-moon-is-moving.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 05:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/13/3795809/3795809_6ADBF160E70A40FFB892B4720BD30C7F_190313_3795809_NASA_discovers__hopping__water_on_moon_s_surface_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, moon, hopping water, water on moon, moving water, lunar water, lunar orbiter, lunar reconnaissance orbiter, LRO]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796915</guid>
      <title>US, Canada ground Boeing 737 Max 8 planes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. and Canada have joined a growing list of countries that have banned the Boeing 737 Max 8 aircraft, following two fatal crashes that took the lives of 346 people.CBS reports that Canada's transport authority banned all Boeing 737 Max 8 and 9 planes from its airspace on Tuesday. A day later, the U.S. announced it would also be grounding the aircrafts.President Trump told reporters at the White House that planes currently in the air will go their destinations, and then be grounded until further notice.According to CNBC, the Federal Aviation Administration cited new satellite evidence showing that the flight track of Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 was similar to the Lion Air flight that crashed in October.According to CBS, investigators of the Lion Air crash believe pilots battled the aircraft's automated anti-stall system, which repeatedly pushed the plane's nose down, possibly due to wrong information from sensors.Whether or not the same is true for the Ethiopian Airlines crash has yet to be determined.CNBC reports that investigators have recovered Flight 302's black boxes, and will be sending them to France for analysis this week. Over 40 countries and regions, including the EU, China, India, Australia, Mexico, and Brazil, had already grounded the 737 Max 8 and 9 due to safety concerns days before the U.S. decision.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Canada, US ground Boeing 737 Max 8 and 9 aircrafts2. Flight track of crashed Ethiopian Airlines and Lion Air flights similar3. Anti-stall system pushed plane's nose down in Lion Air crash4. Other countries that have grounded Boeing 737 Max 8 and 9VOICEOVER (in English): "CBS reports that Canada's transport authority banned all Boeing 737 Max 8 and 9 planes from its airspace on Tuesday. A day later, the U.S. announced it would also be grounding the aircrafts.""President Trump told reporters at the White House that planes currently in the air will fly their destinations, and then be grounded until further notice.""According to CNBC, the Federal Aviation Administration cited new satellite evidence showing that the flight track of Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 was similar to the Lion Air flight that crashed in October.""According to CBS, investigators of the Lion Air crash believe pilots battled the aircraft's automated anti-stall system, which repeatedly pushed the plane's nose down, possibly due to wrong information from sensors.""Over 40 countries and regions, including the EU, China, India, Australia, Mexico and Brazil, had already grounded the 737 Max 8 and 9 due to safety concerns days before the U.S. decision."SOURCES:CNBC, CBS https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/13/boeing-shares-fall-after-report-says-us-expected-to-ground-737-max-fleet.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/boeing-737-max-8-grounded-by-more-countries-heres-the-list/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 17:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/15/3796915/3796915_D653FCC9A3134ECE85239B8E61AE892D_190315_3796915_US__Canada_ground_Boeing_737_Max_8_planes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Boeing 737 Max, 737 Max 8, 737 Max 9, Ethiopian Airlines crash, Lion Air crash, Boeing 737 Max ban, plane crash, MCAS, anti-stall system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796555</guid>
      <title>JAXA and Toyota collaborate to create lunar rover</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan's space agency and Toyota are teaming up to build a lunar exploration vehicle as part of the country's plan to get astronauts on the moon by 2029, The Japan Times reports.Toyota and the Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency are to construct a pressurized self-driving moon rover that will use the car manufacturer's fuel cell vehicle technology.According to Forbes, a fuel cell vehicle or FCV uses a fuel cell of compressed hydrogen and oxygen. These molecules react with each other to create electricity for the vehicle.Toyota said in a press release, that these fuel cells only emit water and can generate a lot of energy.The rover will be six meters wide and 3.8 meters tall. This is around the size of two microbuses, according to a JAXA news release.With 13 cubic meters of space, the vehicle is expected to have a 2 to 4 passenger carry capacity.According to Toyota, the rover will be able to travel more than 10,000 km on the moon's surface. The country is planning a series of manned missions to the moon between 2029 and 2034, The Japan Times reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Moon rover and the technology it will use to create electricity2. The dimensions of the lunar rover3. How much space the rover will have4. The rover exploring the moon's surfaceVOICEOVER (in English): "Toyota and the Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency are to construct a pressurized self-driving moon rover that will use the car manufacturer's fuel cell vehicle technology.""According to Forbes, a fuel cell vehicle or FCV uses a fuel cell of compressed hydrogen and oxygen. These molecules react with each other to create electricity for the vehicle.""Toyota said in a press release, that these fuel cells only emit water and can generate a lot of energy.""According to a JAXA news release, the rover will be six meters wide and 3.8 meters tall. This is around the size of two microbuses.""With 13 cubic meters of space, the vehicle is expected to have a 2 to 4 passenger carry capacity.""According to Toyota, the rover will be able to travel more than 10,000 km on the moon's surface." SOURCES: Reuters, Toyota press release, Japan Times,  Forbes, JAXA press release, The Asahi Shimbun,  https://www.reuters.com/article/us-toyota-space/toyota-japan-space-agency-join-forces-to-develop-moon-rover-idUSKBN1QT1UUhttps://global.toyota/en/newsroom/corporate/27059582.htmlhttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/03/12/national/toyota-jaxa-plan-send-space-rover-moon-2029/#.XIiTVoiFNjUhttps://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2019/03/12/toyota-reveals-self-driving-moon-car-as-japan-prepares-to-land-astronauts-on-the-moon/#696f8df46dc8http://global.jaxa.jp/press/2019/03/20190312a.htmlhttp://www.asahi.com/ajw/articles/AJ201903130037.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 08:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/14/3796555/3796555_7097C0D3B5F84E97A4EC4979515C8C3E_190314_3796555_JAXA_and_Toyota_collaborate_to_create_lunar_rove_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan, toyota, moon rover, japanese space agency, JAXA, toyota space vehicle, space exploration,lunar exploration, space vehicle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797351</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's ban on plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe island nation of Taiwan is all set to implement a complete ban on plastic by 2030.According to Taiwan's Environmental Protection Administration, the government will limit the use of plastic by implementing a plastic ban in phases, and is encouraging the public to use reusable straws and bags to help combat plastic pollution.Starting later this year, stores are to be prohibited from providing in-store customers with single-use straws.In 2020, stores will face fines if they provide customers with disposable utensils. Stores will also be restricted from providing plastic straws for take-outs.Customers could choose to purchase plastic straws or bags if they are willing to pay extra to the store till 2025.By the year 2030, Taiwan's plastic ban will be fully implemented, with stores completely banned from providing any plastic bags, disposable utensils, plastic cups, bottles and straws.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Plastic bag and pie chart depicting phases2. A store and plastic straws3. Disposable utensils and plastic straws in a plastic cup4. All the items that will be banned VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Taiwan's Environmental Protection Administration, the government will limit the use of plastic by implementing a plastic ban in phases.""Starting later this year, stores are to be prohibited from providing in-store customers with single-use straws.""In 2020, stores will face fines if they provide customers with disposable utensils.""Stores will also be restricted from providing plastic straws for take-outs.""By the year 2030, Taiwan's plastic ban will be fully implemented, with stores completely banned from providing any plastic bags, disposable utensils, plastic cups, bottles and straws."SOURCES: Taiwan Environmental Protection Administration, Taiwan News,  Focus Taiwan, https://enews.epa.gov.tw/enews/fact_Newsdetail.asp?InputTime=1070213135101https://www.epa.gov.tw/eng/F7AB26007B8FE8DF/fea08fd0-3afe-4ba9-a9c2-d5f6efd337d8https://www.epa.gov.tw/eng/F7AB26007B8FE8DF/74e17d56-5833-497e-b0e2-e57fd26204c2https://www.epa.gov.tw/eng/F7AB26007B8FE8DF/6a4f590b-e2d1-4c03-b74b-0a19fb7507d8https://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3559765https://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3452133http://focustaiwan.tw/news/asoc/201903110013.aspx***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/15/3797351/3797351_EA1EB143ADB64847BC4DC92277223EFB_190315_3797351_Taiwan_s_ban_on_plastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, plastic pollution, plastic ban, taiwan plastic ban, taiwan bans plastic, comprehensive plastic ban]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796990</guid>
      <title>Recent Boeing 737 Max 8 crashes unrelated says aviation expert</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEthiopian Airlines Flight 302 crashed on Sunday shortly after takeoff, killing all 157 people on board. The Boeing 737 Max 8 aircraft was the same type involved in the Indonesia Lion Air Flight 610 crash five months earlier. Despite some similarities between the two crashes, aviation expert Peter Lemme talking to Scientific American believes they are unrelated.Both flights appeared to have difficulties sustaining a normal climb, and fell shortly after takeoff.A possible cause of the Indonesia crash was a malfunction in the automated anti-stalling feature called the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, or MCAS. According to Scientific American, because Boeing outfitted the Max with bigger engines, their placement relative to the plane's center of gravity causes a tendency for the nose to tip upward. The MCAS is designed to automatically push the nose back down when this happens, preventing the aircraft from stalling, or losing lift.  In the case of Lion Air, experts suspect a faulty sensor may have triggered MCAS to engage when the plane was flying normally, causing the nose to repeatedly dip. Using data from FlightRadar24, Lemme studied how Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 flew in the six minutes before disappearing from radar. With Flight 302, the plane got to 1,000 feet, which at that point lost about 400 feet of altitude. The plane then flew level for about 30 seconds, about 500 to 600 feet above the ground, which according to Lemme is not normal.  The airspeed continued to increase to over 300 knots at under 1,000 feet above ground. After that 30-second period, the plane began to climb normally until they disappeared from radar. Now that the black boxes have been recovered from Flight 302, investigators will see what information they reveal about the cause of the crash. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Aviation expert says recent 737 Max 8 crashes unrelated2. Lion Air flight having problems with the MCAS system3. Ethiopian Airlines flight struggling to climb after takeoff4. Flight 302 flying level before finally climbing before crashVOICEOVER (in English): "Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 crashed on Sunday shortly after takeoff, killing all 157 people on board. The Boeing 737 Max 8 aircraft was the same type involved in the Indonesia Lion Air Flight 610 crash five months earlier." "Despite some similarities between the two crashes, aviation expert Peter Lemme talking to Scientific American believes they are unrelated.""A possible cause of the Indonesia crash was a malfunction in the automated anti-stalling feature called the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, or MCAS." "In the case of Lion Air, experts suspect a faulty sensor may have triggered MCAS to engage when the plane was flying normally, causing the nose to repeatedly dip." "With Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302, the plane got to 1,000 feet, which at that point lost about 400 feet of altitude. The plane then flew level for about 30 seconds, about 500 to 600 feet above the ground, which according to Lemme is not normal."  "The airspeed continued to increase to over 300 knots at under 1,000 feet above ground. After that 30-second period, the plane began to climb normally until they disappeared from radar." SOURCES: Scientific Americanhttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/despite-similarities-are-the-2-recent-737-max-8-crashes-a-coincidence/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 03:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/15/3796990/3796990_F0F1594E1ADD4581A8EEB9E46BB9C50C_190315_3796990_Recent_Boeing_737_Max_8_crashes_unrelated_says_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing 737 Max 8 crashes, Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302, Lion Air Flight 610]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797695</guid>
      <title>Asteroid Bennu found to be rotating faster over time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAsteroid Bennu has been found to revolve quicker over time, according to research published in Geophysical Research Letters.NASA's OSIRIS-REx began approaching the asteroid last year. It travelled 2.2 million kilometers from Earth and stationed itself 19 kilometers from Bennu.The discovery was made by ground-based telescopes and the Hubble Space Telescope. Scientists looked at previous data and observed that the asteroid was increasing its rotational speed over time. The OSIRIS-REx spacecraft will independently determine Bennu's speed of rotation by flying closer to the asteroid.Scientists believe that sunlight may be causing Bennu to spin faster as it hits the asteroid from various angles, also known as the YORP effect.The asteroid is traveling across space at 101,000 kilometers per hour and is able to complete a rotation every 4.3 hours. Its speed of rotation has increased around 1 second per century. It is estimated to be around 4.5 billion years old.OSIRIS-REx will collect data and sample the asteroid using the Osiris Visible and Infrared Spectrometer and Osiris Thermal Emission Spectrometer. The spacecraft will use its Touch-and-Go Sample Acquisition Mechanism to extract rocks and dirt from the surface of Bennu in July of 2020.It is expected to travel back to Earth and drop off a capsule containing asteroid samples in September 2023.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid Bennu revolving2. OSIRIS REx approaching the asteroid3. How the discovery was made4. What causes the asteroid to spin faster5. Asteroid in space 6. OSIRIS REx collecting data 7. Spacecraft taking samples 8. Spacecraft going back VOICEOVER (in English): "According to research published in Geophysical Research Letters, asteroid Bennu has been found to revolve quicker over time.""NASA's OSIRIS-REx began approaching the asteroid last year. The spacecraft travelled 2.2 million kilometers from Earth and stationed itself 19 kilometers from Bennu.""The discovery was made via ground-based telescopes and the Hubble Space Telescope.""Scientists looked at data from 1999, 2005 and 2013 and observed that the asteroid was increasing its rotational speed over time.""According to the study, the OSIRIS-REx spacecraft will independently determine Bennu's speed of rotation by flying closer to the asteroid.""The scientists believe that sunlight may be causing Bennu to spin faster as it hits the asteroid from various angles. This is known as the YORP effect.""Asteroid Bennu is currently traveling across space at 101,000 kilometers per hour and is able to complete a rotation every 4.3 hours.""According to the study, Bennu's speed of rotation has increased by around 1 second per century.""The asteroid is estimated to be around 4.5 billion years old.""OSIRIS-REx was sent to collect data and sample the asteroid using the Osiris Visible and Infrared Spectrometer and Osiris Thermal Emission Spectrometer.""The spacecraft will use its Touch-and-Go Sample Acquisition Mechanism to extract rocks and dirt from the surface of asteroid Bennu in July of 2020.""It is expected to travel back to Earth and drop off a capsule containing asteroid samples in September 2023." SOURCES: Geophysical Research Letters, Advancing Earth and Space Science press release, NASA, https://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1029/2018GL080658https://news.agu.org/press-release/asteroid-bennu-target-of-nasas-sample-return-mission-is-rotating-faster-over-time/https://www.nasa.gov/osiris-rex***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 07:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/16/3797695/3797695_ED8AD714DA7045FDB8C6F57EA0602D59_190316_3797695_Asteroid_Bennu_found_to_be_rotating_faster_over__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Animation, nasa asteroid sampling mission, NASA, asteroid Bennu, OSIRIS REx mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797660</guid>
      <title>Scientists reverse time using a quantum computer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team from the Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology used a quantum system program to reverse the state of a quantum computer a fraction of a second into the past.According to the paper published in the journal Scientific Reports, they performed the experiments on two quantum bits, also known as qubits. Qubits are represented by a one, a zero or both at the same time.During the first stage of the experiment, the two qubits were unaltered. In the second stage, scientists used a computer program to alter the order of the previous stage, causing the qubits to become a random assortment of ones and zeros.This process is then followed by the time reversal stage during which the program reverses the chaotic effect on the qubits. Finally, the qubit reverts to the original state before it had been altered by the program. The program restored 85 percent of the cases where two qubits where involved.The team was able to create a state that evolved against the second law of thermodynamics, which states that the state of entropy in the universe increases over time. Changes of a state in a closed system can remain static but cannot be reversed.The researchers used the example of cue balls on a pool table. Imagine them formed in a pyramid shape at the center and then being hit, causing them to disperse.Imagine the same process in reverse. The balls retrace the path they took and return to the original triangular formation. This is similar to what the researchers accomplished with qubits.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Quantum system program2. Qubits3. First two stages of the reversal process4. Time reversal stage and regeneration stage5. Success rate of reversal process6. Experiment defies law of thermodynamics7. Cue balls on pool table analogy I8.  Cue balls on pool table analogy IIVOICEOVER (in English): "A team of researchers from the Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology used a quantum system program to reverse the state of a quantum computer a fraction of a second into the past.""According to the paper published in the journal Scientific Reports, they performed the experiments on two quantum bits, also known as qubits.""Qubits are represented by a one, a zero or both at the same time.""During the first stage of the experiment, the two qubits were unaltered. In the second stage, called 'degradation,' scientists used a computer program to alter the order of the previous stage, causing the qubits to become a random assortment of ones and zeros.""This process is then followed by the time reversal stage. At this time the program reverses the chaotic effect on the qubits. Finally, during the 'regeneration' stage, the qubit reverts to the same original state before it had been disrupted by the computer program.""The program was able to successfully restore 85 percent of the cases where two qubits where involved.""Through this program, the researchers were able to create a state that evolved against the second law of thermodynamics, which states that the state of entropy or disruption of the universe increases over time. Meaning that changes of a state in a closed system can remain static but cannot be reversed.""The researchers used the example of cue balls on a pool table. Imagine them formed in a pyramid shape at the center and then being hit, causing them to disperse.""Now imagine the process in reverse. The balls retrace the path they took when they were hit and return to the original triangular formation. This is similar to what the researchers accomplished with quantum bits."SOURCES: EurekaAlert, Phys.org  https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-03/miop-prt031119.phphttps://phys.org/news/2019-03-physicists-reverse-quantum.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/16/3797660/3797660_5969D7856BB14002ACFA939C7C9489AC_190316_3797660_Scientists_reverse_time_using_a_quantum_computer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, time travel, reverse time, scientists reverse time, scientists go back in time, physicists reverse time]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798779</guid>
      <title>How the Christchurch mosque shootings unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFifty people are dead, and many more injured after a gunman opened fire in two mosques in Christchurch, New Zealand.According to the BBC, Brenton Tarrant live-streamed the attack via a head-mounted camera. At 1:40 p.m., he walked into the mosque through the front entrance and began shooting at people inside, killing 42. Afterwards, he got into his car and drove to another mosque in Linwood, where he killed eight.Stuff.co.nz reports that police officers later forced Tarrant's car from the road, dragging him out of the vehicle and taking him into custody.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman drives to Al Noor mosque, selects weapon from several in the boot of his car2. Gunman walks into mosque through front entrance, opens fire3. Gunman's route through Al Noor mosque4. Man tries to overpower gunman but fails5. Gunman drives to Linwood mosque five kilometers away6. Gunman shoots people outside mosque7. Man chases gunman, manages to scare him away8. Gunman chased off the road, arrested by police9. Number of casualties in each mosqueVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, gunman Brenton Tarrant live-streamed the attack via a head-mounted camera. Footage shows him driving to Al Noor mosque in Christchurch, and selecting a weapon from the boot of the car.""At around 1:40 p.m., he walked into the mosque through the front entrance and began shooting at people inside, who were there for Friday prayers.""Based on the footage, the BBC reports that Tarrant opened fire inside the women's prayer hall, and then the men's before returning to his car to change weapons. He then re-entered the mosque and shot at bodies in the men's hall before leaving.""The Washington Post reports that 50-year-old Naeem Rashid had tried to overpower the gunman, but was shot and later died from his wounds.""After leaving the mosque, Tarrant got into his car and drove five kilometers to another mosque in Linwood.""Linwood's acting imam Latef Alabi told Stuff that he was leading prayers for a congregation of over 80 when he heard a voice outside at about 1:55 p.m.""He looked out the window to find a man in a helmet holding a large gun and bodies on the ground, and told everyone to get down.""According to the New York Times, Tarrant was firing through a window when Abdul Aziz, a member of the congregation, ran out and threw a credit card machine at him.""Aziz followed the attacker and picked up a discarded gun. He later threw the gun at Tarrant's windshield, prompting him to drive away.""Stuff reports that police officers managed to force Tarrant's car from the road soon after. Video taken by a resident shows officers dragging the suspect out of the vehicle and taking him into custody.""According to the BBC, a total of 42 casualties were reported in the Al Noor Mosque, while eight were killed at the Linwood mosque shooting, including one who died later in the hospital."SOURCES: BBC, New York Times, Stuff, Washington Post, CNNhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-47582183https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/17/world/asia/new-zealand-shootings-police-response.htmlhttps://www.stuff.co.nz/national/111343093/man-who-scared-away-gunman-at-christchurch-mosque-hailed-a-herohttps://www.washingtonpost.com/local/lets-get-this-party-started-new-zealand-gunman-narrated-his-chilling-rampage/2019/03/15/fb3db352-4748-11e9-90f0-0ccfeec87a61_story.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/03/15/asia/christchurch-mosque-shooting-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 14:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/18/3798779/3798779_49B360CD96A24E3385A928E5F72A3CEE_190318_3798779_How_the_Christchurch_mosque_shootings_unfolded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Christchurch shooting, Christchurch attack, mosque shooting, mosque attack, New Zealand]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798603</guid>
      <title>Russia testing new nuclear submarine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRussia's state media has announced that its navy will begin testing a submarine capable of carrying six thermonuclear warheads.According to The Barents Observer, Russia's new naval submarine called 'Belgorod' will be the world's longest submarine ever built, measuring 184 meters.Russian state media, TASS, reports that the Belgorod will be able to carry six underwater 'Poseidon' drones.Each of these drones is capable of carrying nuclear warheads weighing up to two megatons. Their operational depth is 1,000 meters, making them difficult to intercept.Foreign Minister of Norway Ine Eriksen Soreide told The Barents Observer that it was "worrying that countries are developing new nuclear capabilities."According to Russian state media, the Belgorod will be deployed by summer 2019.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Russian submarine, 'Belgorod' dimensions2. Six underwater drones carried by Belgorod3. Weight of each drone4. Operational depth of the submarineVOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Barents Observer, Russia's new war submarine called 'Belgorod' will be the world's longest submarine ever built, measuring 184 meters.""Russian state media, TASS, reports that the Belgorod will be able to carry six underwater drones called 'Poseidon'.""Each of these drones is capable of carrying nuclear warheads weighing up to two megatons." "Their operational depth is 1,000 meters, making them difficult to intercept."SOURCES: TASS, The Barents Observer, Business Insiderhttp://tass.com/defense/1047634https://thebarentsobserver.com/en/security/2019/03/russias-most-secret-sub-soon-be-launched-terrifying-weaponhttps://www.businessinsider.com/russia-to-arm-a-secretive-submarine-with-6-nuclear-doomsday-devices-2019-3***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/18/3798603/3798603_A370AE82651348159C64B44A3B9A79CC_190318_3798603_Russia_testing_new_nuclear_submarine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, russia, russia submarines, russia belgarod, russia poseidon, russia torpedo, russia navy, putin, vladimir putin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798556</guid>
      <title>Mayor Bill de Blasio has announced plans to protect Manhattan from climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew York's mayor has plans to expand Manhattan's coastline to safeguard the island from the effects of climate change.Mayor Bill de Blasio wants to artificially extend the southern tip of Manhattan to protect it from rising sea levels and storm surges, the New York Times reports.According to a Lower Manhattan Climate Resilience Study, 37 percent of Lower Manhattan will be at risk from a storm surge by 2050.In an op-ed published in New York Magazine, de Blasio said the coastline of Lower Manhattan will be extended as much as 500 feet into the East River.Landfill will be used to extend the coastline. This would create a rising berm that would be above future sea levels, according to the New York Times.He added that grassy berms in parks and removable barriers will also be used to protect the island from storm surges.According to de Blasio's op-ed in New York Magazine, the coastal extension project will cost around US$10 billion.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Manhattan coastline2. The area where Manhattan's coastline will be extended3. A rising berm will be used to expand Manhattan's coastline4. Grassy berms and removable barriersVOICEOVER (in English): "The mayor of New York City has plans to expand Manhattan's coastline to  to safeguard the island from the effects of climate change.""The New York Times reports Mayor Bill de Blasio wants to artificially extend the southern tip of Manhattan to protect it from rising sea levels and storm surges.""In an op-ed published in New York Magazine, de Blasio said the coastline of Lower Manhattan will be extended as much as 500 feet into the East River.""Landfill will be used to extend the coastline. This would create a rising berm that would be above future sea levels, according to the New York Times.""He added that grassy berms in parks and removable barriers will also be used to protect the island from storm surges."SOURCES: New York Magazine, The New York Times, The Guardian, Lower Manhattan Coastal Resiliency,https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/03/bill-de-blasio-my-new-plan-to-climate-proof-lower-manhattan.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/14/nyregion/manhattan-climate-change-hurricane-sandy.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/mar/14/de-blasio-manhattan-new-york-climate-changehttps://www.nycedc.com/project/lower-manhattan-coastal-resiliency***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 08:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/18/3798556/3798556_13BB63B91C1D4E148C0F51EA7B4DCCBA_190318_3798556_Mayor_Bill_de_Blasio_has_announced_plans_to_prot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, manhattan, rising sea levels, climate change, climate change, manhattan climate change, lower manhattan, increasing manhattan coastline, rising sea levels manhattan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798498</guid>
      <title>Green tea found to reduce obesity risk in mice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch from Ohio State University has found that green tea lowered the risk of obesity in mice.The scientists tested their hypothesis on a group of male mice. Half of the mice were fed a high-fat diet while the rest were fed healthy meals.They further separated the two groups into two sub-groups.Half of the mice that were fed a high-fat diet had a green tea extract mixed into their foods while the other half did not. The extract was also placed in the meals of 50 percent of the mice that were fed a normal diet.Researchers observed that mice on a high-fat diet mixed with green tea had gained around 20 percent less weight than those whose diet didn't consist of any green tea.The green tea fed mice were also found to have lower insulin resistance and healthier microbes in their body, according to the study.Lead author of the study Professor Richard Bruno, speaking on the Ohio State University website, said, "This study provides evidence that green tea encourages the growth of good gut bacteria, and that leads to a series of benefits that significantly lower the risk of obesity."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mouse, green tea extract2. Groups of mice and a depiction of a high fat diet and a healthy diet3. Green tea extract being added to the high fat diet and the healthy diet4. Benefits of the green tea extract on the miceVOICEOVER (in English): "Research from Ohio State University has found that mice provided with a green tea extract had a lower obesity risk than those without.""The scientists tested their hypothesis on a group of male mice. Half of the mice were fed a high-fat diet while the rest were fed healthy meals.""They further separated the two groups into two sub-groups.""Half of the mice that were fed a high-fat diet had a green tea extract mixed into their foods while the other half did not.""The extract was also placed in the meals of 50 percent of the mice that were fed a normal diet.""Researchers observed that mice on a high-fat diet mixed with green tea had gained around 20 percent less weight than those whose diet didn't consist of any green tea.""According to the study, the green tea fed mice were also found to have lower insulin resistance and healthier microbes in their body."SOURCES: The Journal of Nutritional Biochemistry, The Ohio State University news release, Science Daily, Science Daily, New Atlas, https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S095528631830723Xhttps://news.osu.edu/green-tea-cuts-obesity-health-risks-in-mice/https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/03/190314075804.htmhttps://newatlas.com/green-tea-healthy-gut-obesity-mice/58882/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 06:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/18/3798498/3798498_26081344C61E4F5BB7E3DD1CF537A334_190318_3798498_Green_tea_found_to_reduce_obesity_risk_in_mice_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, health, mice, obesity, green tea, green tea benefits, green tea study, green tea health benefits, green tea extract]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799275</guid>
      <title>Gunman kills three in Utrecht tram shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Turkish man has been arrested following a possible shooting on a tram in Utrecht.The BBC reports that the shooting took place around 10:45 a.m. on board a tram in Utrecht's 24 Oktoberplein junction.According to the New York Times, witness accounts indicate that someone had activated the emergency brakes, as passengers screamed and clamored to escape.Reuters reports that at least three people were killed and nine others injured. According to the New York Times, some were wounded by shattering glass.After the gunman stepped off the tram, the Telegraph reports that he escaped in a stolen red Renault Clio. Police conducted house-to-house raids and arrested the suspect after an eight-hour manhunt.Authorities initially said the shooting was a terrorist incident, but later said they were not ruling out a personal motive.According to Turkey's Anadolu news agency, relatives of 37-year-old suspect Gokmen Tanis said the shooting was due to a family dispute. They alleged that only one person  possibly his former wife  was the intended target.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Shooting inside Utrecht tram2. Emergency brake activated, passengers running from tram3. Three people killed, nine injured4. Suspect arrested after manhuntVOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports that the shooting took place at around 10:45 a.m. on board a tram in Utrecht's 24 Oktoberplein junction.""According to the New York Times, witness accounts indicate that someone had activated the emergency brakes, as passengers screamed and clamored to escape.""Reuters reports that at least three people were killed and nine others injured. According to the New York Times, some were wounded by shattering glass.""After the gunman stepped off the tram, the Telegraph reports that he escaped in a stolen red Renault Clio.""Police conducted house-to-house raids and arrested the suspect after an eight-hour manhunt."SOURCES: BBC, New York Times, Telegraph, Reutershttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47615231https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/18/world/europe/utrecht-shooting.htmlhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/18/utrecht-shooting-several-injured-shooting-utrecht-tram/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-netherlands-shooting-casualties/three-dead-nine-injured-in-utrecht-shooting-mayor-idUSKCN1QZ1NI***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 11:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/19/3799275/3799275_12D8EBC264D04B6BAFEE1C0230D3DA19_190319_3799275_Gunman_kills_three_in_Utrecht_tram_shooting_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, utrecht shooting, utrecht tram shooting, utrecht tram, dutch tram shooting, gokeman tanis, utrecht]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799143</guid>
      <title>Moisturizer reduces risk of age-related diseases, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found that using a skin moisturizer might reduce the risk of developing diseases such as Alzheimer's and diabetes.A small pilot study by the University of California, San Francisco found that inflammation of the skin may play a role in chronic illnesses.Around age 50, our skin begins to lose moisture and the skin's permeability barrier starts to break down. The barrier acts as a shield to retain water in our bodies and keep pathogens out.In younger skin, inflammatory cytokines are released to help repair cracks in the barrier.As the skin ages and the barrier weakens, more cytokines are released by the immune system.Cytokines eventually enter the bloodstream, and according to the study can cause inflammation that affects the rest of the body.The study had 33 participants between the ages of 58 and 95. They were asked to apply moisturizer twice a day for a month.The moisturizer contained cholesterol, free fatty acids and ceramides  all of which are essential for skin health.The scientists observed that the cytokine levels of the participants were found to be nearly equivalent with people in their thirties at the end of one month.In a news release the University of California, San Francisco said the researchers now plan to conduct a large scale study to test if moisturizing creams can actually delay or prevent age-related diseases caused by inflammation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Skin inflammation on face2. Cross section of skin showing the skin's permeability barrier3. Cytokines causing inflammation of the body4. Moisturizer, contents of the moisturizer, and cytokine levels of participantsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a small pilot study by the University of California, San Francisco, inflammation of the skin may play a role in chronic illnesses.""Around age 50, our skin begins to lose moisture and the skin's permeability barrier starts to break down.""The barrier acts as a shield to retain water in our bodies and keep pathogens out.""In younger skin, inflammatory cytokines are released to help repair cracks in the barrier.""As the skin ages and the barrier weakens, more cytokines are released by the immune system.""Cytokines eventually enter the bloodstream, and according to the study can cause inflammation that affects the rest of the body.""The study had 33 participants between the ages of 58 and 95. They were asked to apply moisturizer twice a day for a month.""The moisturizer contained cholesterol, free fatty acids and ceramides  all of which are essential for skin health.""The scientists observed that the cytokine levels of the participants were found to be nearly equivalent with people in their thirties at the end of one month."SOURCES: Medical News Today, Journal of the European Academy of Dermatology and Venereology, San Francisco Chronicle, University of California San Francisco, https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/324717.phphttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/epdf/10.1111/jdv.15540?referrer_access_token=S-WCGJ60cKFMb2d7FpiJ14ta6bR2k8jH0KrdpFOxC67kdqa5-Q_Q8ltT6uQSa3kUEZMm6mEN7_8mvDywkPe9AOCn7aCLNi_CV3iAMck0BQxAu1SyLpdlTkFwF7hXxUCRmRzGzj18drzFWaV3FZmAhQ%3D%3Dhttps://www.sfchronicle.com/science/article/UCSF-study-skin-moisturizer-inflamation-disease-13691930.phphttps://www.ucsf.edu/news/2019/03/413576/skin-repair-eliminates-inflamm-aging-linked-chronic-disease***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 08:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/19/3799143/3799143_C42018EA267E453B991F42A82B7897AF_190319_3799143_Moisturizer_reduces_risk_of_age_related_diseases_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, moisturizer, skin moisturizer, heart disease, diabetes, alzheimer's disease, skin, age-related chronic disease, Cytokines, skin moisturizer, inflammation, dermatology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799094</guid>
      <title>Scientists find new solar system forming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of researchers have detected planets forming around a young star similar to the sun. According to the paper published in Astrophysical Journal Letters, DM Tau is located in the Taurus constellation 470 light-years away from Earth. It is between three and five million years old and weighs roughly half the mass of the sun.The researchers spotted the system forming using the Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array known as ALMA. ALMA is a radio telescope that captures radio waves from the universe. It is located in the Atacama Desert in northern Chile.Using the ALMA, scientists were able to view two rings of dust forming around the star. The inner ring is 4 astronomical units, known as AU,  from the star and the second ring is 20 AU away. Scientists believe this is where the planets are forming.The team hopes to gain a better understanding of the origin of planets like Earth by studying the formation of this neighboring solar system.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Comparison between DM Tau and the sun.2. Location of DM Tau. 3. ALMA telescopes location and use.4. Two rings of dust forming around DM Tau. VOICEOVER (in English): "A team of researchers have detected planets forming around a young star similar to the sun. The star is called DM Tau, and it weighs roughly half the mass of the sun.""According to the paper published in Astrophysical Journal Letters, DM Tau is located in the Taurus constellation 470 light-years away from Earth. It is between three and five million years old.""The researchers spotted the system forming using the Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array known as ALMA.""ALMA is a radio telescope that captures radio waves from the universe. It is located in the Atacama Desert in northern Chile.""Using the ALMA, scientists were able to view two rings of dust forming around the star. The inner ring is 4 astronomical units, known as AU, from the star and the second ring is 20 AU away. Scientists believe this is where the planets are forming."SOURCES: ALMA, The Astrophysical Journal Letters https://alma-telescope.jp/en/news/press/dmtau-201903https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/2041-8213/aaeb1c***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 07:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/19/3799094/3799094_3A6F52119FEC4692A8C0AF627F19923B_190319_3799094_Scientists_find_new_solar_system_forming_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798989</guid>
      <title>'Clear similarities' between Ethiopian and Lion Air crashes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThere are "clear similarities" between Indonesia's Lion Air and Ethiopian Air crashes, according to the Ethiopian government.AFP reports that Ethiopia's transport minister, Dagmawit Moges, told a press conference on Sunday that flight data recorders from Ethiopian Airlines flight 302 have been recovered in good condition. So far the data extracted shows similarities between the Ethiopian Airlines crash and the Lion Air crash that occurred in October 2018.According to the AFP,  both aircrafts experienced irregular climbs and descents as well as fluctuations in altitude before crashing minutes after take off. Experts also identified issues with the plane's automated Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which stops the plane from stalling.According to the New York Times, new evidence suggests that the stabilizers on the Ethiopian Airlines flight were tilted upwards and forcing down the nose of the plane.Flight recordings and cockpit voice recordings from the Ethiopian Airlines flight have been sent to France's air safety agency for further analysis. They are working in collaboration with American and Ethiopian investigators. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ethiopian Airlines flight 302 flight recorder2. Plane experiences irregular climbs and descents 3. Plane's stabilizers tilt upwards causing the plane's nose to tip downwards4. France analyzing black box content in collaboration with American and Ethiopian investigators VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the AFP, Ethiopia's transport minister, Dagmawit Moges told a press conference on Sunday that flight data recorders from Ethiopian Airlines flight 302 have been recovered in good condition.""So far, the data extracted shows similarities between the Ethiopian Airlines crash and the Lion Air crash that occurred in October 2018 .""According to the AFP,  both aircrafts experienced irregular climbs and descents as well as fluctuations in altitude before crashing minutes after take off.""Experts also identified issues with the plane's automated Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System which stops the plane from stalling.""According to the New York Times, new evidence suggests that the stabilizers on the Ethiopian Airlines flight were tilted upwards and forcing down the nose of the plane.""Flight recordings and cockpit voice recordings from the Ethiopian Airlines flight have been sent to France's air safety agency for further analysis. "They are working in collaboration with American and Ethiopian investigators. "SOURCES: AFP, The Guardian, New York Times, BBC https://www.afp.com/en/news/3954/black-boxes-show-clear-similarities-indonesia-crash-ethiopia-says-doc-1er0704https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/17/ethiopian-airlines-crash-thousands-turn-out-for-funeral-servicehttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/15/business/boeing-ethiopian-crash.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-47605265***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 03:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/19/3798989/3798989_4FEB679C483D498E8719E0BE09A63838_190319_3798989__Clear_similarities__between_Ethiopian_and_Lion__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Indonesia plane crash, plane crash indonesia, indonesia plane crash survivors, lion air, indonesia plane crash 2018, java plane crash, jakarta, boeing, lion air crash latest news, plane crash, boeing 737 Max,boeing 737 Max,  boeing 737 Max 8 crash, Ethiopian Airlines, Ethiopian Airlines crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799883</guid>
      <title>UK</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of researchers from the University of Bath have developed bacon fibers using pig stem cells and blades of grass, reports the BBC.First, they take a tissue sample from a pig and extract stem cells from the tissue. Stem cells have the capacity of turning into different kinds of cells including muscle, fat or ligaments.After the cells are isolated they are placed in a container for cultivation. They are then placed on blades of grass where they continue to grow into meat fibers.Millions of muscle, fat, and ligament cells are required to make a single fiber of bacon. This makes it difficult for cultured meat to be produced at a large scale and sold commercially.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pig and grass used to develop bacon fiber2. Extracting stem cells from pig3. Stem cells cultivated on blades of grass4. Fat, muscle and ligaments cultivated in stem cells to make bacon. VOICEOVER (in English): "A team of researchers from the University of Bath have developed bacon fibers using pig stem cells and blades of grass, reports the BBC.""First, they take a tissue sample from a pig and extract stem cells from the tissue. Stem cells have the capacity of turning into different kinds of cells including muscle, fat or ligaments.""After the cells are isolated they are placed in a container for cultivation. They are then placed on blades of grass where they continue to grow into meat fibers.""Millions of muscle, fat and ligament cells are required to make a single fiber of bacon. This makes it difficult for cultured meat to be produced at a large scale and sold commercially."SOURCES: BBChttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47611026***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 10:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/20/3799883/3799883_783DDE73DEA4473FBFCFFD3206369B8C_190320_3799883_UK_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, lab grown meat, tube meat, vegan meat, lab grown meath how is it made, fake meat, clean meat, cruelty free meat, slaughter free meat, meat from lab, grown meat, meat, cultured cells, artificial meat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799786</guid>
      <title>Stanford researchers generate hydrogen fuel from seawater</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANStanford researchers have developed a water-splitting system that can produce clean hydrogen fuel using saltwater.According to a Stanford University press release, hydrogen fuel can be generated via electrolysis, which splits water into hydrogen and oxygen using electricity. The process typically uses fresh or purified water, as saltwater has been known to corrode.A new system developed by a team of Stanford scientists uses solar cells to power two electrodes in water, causing hydrogen gas comes out of the cathode, and oxygen to come out of the anode.To prevent corrosion from the chloride in saltwater, negatively charged nickel layers were coated on to the anode to create a barrier.Nickel foam conducts electricity, and nickel-iron hydroxide sparks electrolysis. Nickel sulfide, repels chloride and prevents it from getting to the core metal.The multi-layer device can run for more than a thousand hours, compared to just 12 without the negatively charged coating. It can also conduct 10 times more electricity and help generate hydrogen from seawater at a faster rate.According to the team, the technology have other applications beyond generating energy, such as generating breathable oxygen underwater for divers or submarines.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Process of electrolysis used to generate hydrogen fuel2. How the Stanford water-splitting system works3. Negatively charged nickel coating on anode to prevent corrosion4. Device can run for more than a thousand hours, conduct 10 times more electricityVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a Stanford University press release, hydrogen fuel can be generated via electrolysis, which splits water into hydrogen and oxygen using electricity.""The process typically uses fresh or purified water, as saltwater has been known to corrode.""A new system developed by a team of Stanford scientists uses solar cells to power two electrodes in water, causing hydrogen gas comes out of the cathode, and oxygen to come out of the anode.""To prevent corrosion from the chloride in saltwater, negatively charged nickel layers were coated on to the anode to create a barrier.""Nickel foam conducts electricity, and nickel-iron hydroxide sparks electrolysis. Nickel sulfide, repels chloride and prevents it from getting to the core metal.""The multi-layer device can run for more than a thousand hours, compared to just 12 without the negatively charged coating. It can also conduct 10 times more electricity and help generate hydrogen from seawater at a faster rate."SOURCES: Stanford University, PNAShttps://news.stanford.edu/press-releases/2019/03/18/new-way-generateen-fuel-seawater/https://www.pnas.org/content/early/2019/03/12/1900556116***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 09:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/20/3799786/3799786_8F3A72DADD4E4882B130ED2866D55F29_190320_3799786_Stanford_researchers_generate_hydrogen_fuel_from_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hydrogen fuel, clean fuel, fuel from seawater, clean hydrogen, green energy, electrolysis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799737</guid>
      <title>Meteor explodes in Earth's atmosphere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA fireball entered Earth's atmosphere and exploded with the energy of 173 kilotons of TNT, according to data collected by NASA.The US Air Force reported a massive explosion just 25.6km above the Earth's atmosphere off the coast of Russia over the Bering Strait. The BBC reports the explosion took place last year on December 18.According to NASA, the meteor entered Earth's atmosphere at 32 kilometers per second with an impact energy of roughly 173 kilotons. This is ten times the energy released by the Hiroshima atomic bomb.Using NASA data, meteor specialist Peter Brown at Western University in Canada calculated that the meteor was 10 meters wide and weighed 1,400 tons. According to The Guardian, the explosion was recorded by a network of infrasound sensors which are used to detect covert nuclear bomb tests.This meteor explosion was the third largest fireball to enter Earth's atmosphere in modern times, following the 2013 Chelyabinsk explosion and the Tunguska fireball in 1908. All of these explosions have occurred in Russia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Meteor enters Earth's atmosphere2. Meteor impact and explosion3. Size and weight of the meteor4. Network of infrasound sensors VOICEOVER (in English): "The US Air Force reported a massive explosion just 25.6km above the Earth's atmosphere off the coast of Russia over the Bering Strait. The BBC reports the explosion took place last year on December 18.""According to NASA, the meteor entered Earth's atmosphere at 32 kilometers per second with an impact energy of roughly 173 kilotons. This is ten times the energy released by the Hiroshima atomic bomb.""Using NASA data, meteor specialist Peter Brown at Western University in Canada calculated that the meteor was 10 meters wide and weighed 1,400 tons.""According to The Guardian, the explosion was recorded by a network of infrasound sensors which are used to detect covert nuclear bomb tests."SOURCES: CNN, NASA, The Guardianhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47607696https://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/fireballs/https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/mar/18/meteor-blast-over-bering-sea-was-10-times-size-of-hiroshima***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 08:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/20/3799737/3799737_FA59B29A64C545C998731BBE4ACC9E58_190320_3799737_Meteor_explodes_in_Earth_s_atmosphere_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, meteor, explosion, russia, bering strait, meteor explosion, fireball, Earth, atmosphere]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799566</guid>
      <title>Design issues with the Boeing 737 Max 8</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe crashes of Lion Air Flight 610 on October 29, 2018, and Ethiopian Airlines Flight 409 on March 10 have brought attention to the design and software of the Boeing 737 Max 8. According to Asia Times, the 737 Max series is equipped with new CFM Leap-1B engines, which forced re-engineering of part of the airplane. Fitting the new engines meant moving them forward and lengthening the front landing gear to keep the engines from scraping the ground. This changed the plane's center of gravity and also altered the airflow on the wings.  The new, heavier and larger engines resulted in Max planes having a strong tendency to pitch nose up, which is why the MCAS, or Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, was introduced. According to Asia Times, MCAS was a suboptimal fix to the pitch problem created by relocating the newer engines. It is designed to push the nose down and prevent the plane from going into a stall. MCAS was intended to deal only with a specific flight risk.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boeing 737 Max 8 plane and LEAP 1B engines2. New engines caused parts of the plane to be re-engineered 3. Heavier engines causing nose to pitch up leading to the MCAS4. MCASVOICEOVER (in English): "The crashes of Lion Air Flight 610 on October 29, 2018, and Ethiopian Airlines Flight 409 on March 10 have brought attention to the design and software of the Boeing 737 Max 8." "According to Asia Times, the 737 Max series is equipped with new CFM Leap-1B engines, which forced re-engineering of part of the airplane." "Fitting the new engines meant moving them forward and lengthening the front landing gear to keep the engines from scraping the ground. This changed the plane's center of gravity and also altered the airflow on the wings."  "The new, heavier and larger engines resulted in Max planes having a strong tendency to pitch nose up, which is why the MCAS, or Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, was introduced." "According to Asia Times, MCAS was a suboptimal fix to the pitch problem created by relocating the newer engines. It is designed to push the nose down and prevent the plane from going into a stall. MCAS was intended to deal only with a specific flight risk."    SOURCES: Wired, The Air Current, Boeing, Asia Timeshttps://www.wired.com/story/boeing-safety-warning-737-max-nosedive/https://theaircurrent.com/aviation-safety/what-is-the-boeing-737-max-maneuvering-characteristics-augmentation-system-mcas-jt610/http://www.boeing.com/commercial/aeromagazine/aero_12/attack_story.htmlhttps://www.asiatimes.com/2019/03/article/was-the-737-max-problem-just-bad-software/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 03:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/20/3799566/3799566_F333DC5DB078415D9D3B84CEC7568AC3_190320_3799566_Design_issues_with_the_Boeing_737_Max_8_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing 737 Max 8 engines, 737 Max 8 MCAS, 737 Max 8 LEAP 1B engines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800616</guid>
      <title>Ocean circulation patterns foretold abrupt climate change by four centuries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn the Atlantic Ocean, a giant 'conveyor belt' carries warm waters from the tropics into the North Atlantic, where they cool and sink and then return south to the deep ocean.Ocean water circulation affects global climate, regulating weather patterns in the Arctic, Europe and around the world. More and more research suggests this conveyor belt system is slowing down, causing some scientists to fear it could cause temperatures to plummet in Europe and warming waters off the east coast of the U.S.According to a Columbia University press release, a new study published in Nature Communications has provided insight into how quickly changes in Atlantic Ocean circulation could affect major climate changes.  The study was carried out by researchers at Columbia's Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory, working with the Norwegian Research Center. It was the first to precisely calculate the time lags between past changes to the ocean conveyor belt and major climate changes.The study looked at the Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation, or AMOC, and specifically focused on a section where water sinks from the surface to the bottom of the North Atlantic. Researchers took sediment core samples drilled from the bottom of the Norwegian Sea, a lake sediment core from southern Scandinavia, and ice cores from Greenland. Comparing data from the three cores revealed that the AMOC started weakening about 400 years before a major cold snap 13,000 years ago. It began strengthening again about 400 years before an abrupt warming 11,000 years ago.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation or AMOC2. Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation close up3. Sediment core samples taken from 3 locations4. AMOC foretelling major climate changesVOICEOVER (in English): "In the Atlantic Ocean, a giant 'conveyor belt' carries warm waters from the tropics into the North Atlantic, where they cool and sink and then return south to the deep ocean."  "This ocean water circulation affects global climate. More and more research suggests this conveyor belt system is slowing down, causing some scientists to fear its effects on climate change.""According to a Columbia University press release, a new study published in Nature Communications has provided insight into how quickly changes in Atlantic Ocean circulation could affect major climate changes."  "The study was carried out by researchers at Columbia's Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory, working with the Norwegian Research Center. It was the first to precisely calculate the time lags between past changes to the ocean conveyor belt and major climate changes." "The study looked at the Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation, or AMOC, and specifically focused on a section where water sinks from the surface to the bottom of the North Atlantic. "Researchers took sediment core samples drilled from the bottom of the Norwegian Sea, a lake sediment core from southern Scandinavia, and ice cores from Greenland." "Comparing data from the three cores revealed that the AMOC started weakening about 400 years before a major cold snap 13,000 years ago. It began strengthening again about 400 years before an abrupt warming 11,000 years ago." SOURCES: Columbia Universityhttps://blogs.ei.columbia.edu/2019/03/20/amoc-ocean-conveyor-belt-climate-change/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/21/3800616/3800616_04703CBB243B4967AF8A392E0C005D30_190321_3800616_Ocean_circulation_patterns_foretold_abrupt_clima_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ocean conveyor belt, Atlantic ocean conveyor belt, AMOC, Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800413</guid>
      <title>China to build island city in Woody Island in the Paracels</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Chinese government has announced plans to build up a strategic island in the Paracels, despite strong opposition from the U.S.The South China Morning Post reports that China is planning to build an 'island city' on Woody Island and neighboring islets Tree and Drummond. According to the Communist Party secretary of Sansha, the aim is to turn the island and two islets into a national key strategic service and logistics base.According to the Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, Woody Island is China's main military base in the Paracels, and is equipped with an airstrip, aircraft hangars, ports, and missiles.Woody Island is also home to a settlement of about 1,000 people, and serves as the administrative capital of the three island chains it claims in the South China Sea.The U.S. has long criticized China's expansion and militarization of the disputed region, and challenges territorial claims with freedom of navigation operations, despite protests from Beijing.According to the South China Morning Post, two American B-52H Stratofortress bombers capable of carrying nuclear weapons flew over the South China Sea on March 14 for the second time in 10 days.U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo also spoke out last week criticizing China's 'illegal island-building in international waterways.' He also accused Beijing of using coercive means to block energy development in the South China Sea.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Island city on Woody Island and neighboring Tree and Drummond islets2. Woody Island as China's main military base in the Paracels3. Woody Island human settlement, China's administrative center in South China Sea4. U.S. freedom of navigation operations to object to China expansion5. U.S. strategic bombers flying over South China SeaVOICEOVER (in English): "The South China Morning Post reports that China is planning to build an 'island city' on Woody Island and neighboring islets Tree and Drummond.""According to the Communist Party secretary of Sansha, the aim is to turn the island and two islets into a national key strategic service and logistics base.""According to the Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, Woody Island is China's main military base in the Paracels, and is equipped with an airstrip, aircraft hangars, ports, and missiles.""Woody Island is also home to a settlement of about 1,000 people, and serves as the administrative capital of the three island chains it claims in the South China Sea."The U.S. has long criticized China's expansion and militarization of the disputed region, and challenges territorial claims with freedom of navigation operations, despite protests from Beijing.""On March 14, two American B-52H Stratofortress bombers, which can carry nuclear weapons, flew over the South China Sea for the second time in 10 days."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, Asia Maritime Transparency Initiativehttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3002229/beijing-plans-strategic-service-and-logistics-base-woodyhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3001655/us-b-52-bombers-fly-over-disputed-south-china-sea-second-timehttps://amti.csis.org/paracels-beijings-other-buildup/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 09:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/21/3800413/3800413_A6C00DAC89704EE08824004C7B885198_190321_3800413_China_to_build_island_city_in_Woody_Island_in_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, south china sea, china, woody island, sansha, paracels, island city, tree islet, drummond islet, south china sea expansion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3801146</guid>
      <title>China to build 33,000-ton nuclear-powered ship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is looking to build a massive nuclear-powered vessel described as an 'experimental platform,' which some speculate could be a nuclear icebreaker.According to the South China Morning Post, the China General Nuclear Power Group is looking to build a nuclear powered ship measuring 498 feet long and 98 feet wide, with a displacement of 33,069 tons.The vessel could be fitted with two 25 megawatt compact pressurized water reactors to propel it to a maximum speed of 11.5 knots.China has not specified what the ship will be used for, referring to it only as an 'experimental ship platform.'The vessel's size has been described by Hong Kong-based military commentator Song Zhongping as similar to that of Russian nuclear icebreakers.Russia is the only country that operates nuclear-powered icebreakers, which is used to plow through thick ice-covered waters to maintain and develop the Northern Sea route.China already has a conventionally powered polar icebreaker, which was launched last year to boost its polar research and expedition capacity.But having a nuclear icebreaker is important for expanding its presence in the Arctic Ocean.Song told the South China Morning Post that if experiments using icebreakers go well, the technology could be used to develop next-generation aircraft carriers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dimensions of China's nuclear-powered ship2. Vessel's maximum speed3. Vessel similar in size to Russian icebreakers4. Depiction of Russian Leader icebreaker5. China icebreaker important to expand operations in the Arctic OceanVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the South China Morning Post, the China General Nuclear Power Group is looking to build a nuclear powered ship measuring 498 feet long and 98 feet wide, with a displacement of 33,069 tons.""The vessel could be fitted with two 25 megawatt compact pressurized water reactors to propel it to a maximum speed of 11.5 knots.""China has not specified what the ship will be used for, referring to it only as an 'experimental ship platform.'""The vessel's size has been described by Hong Kong-based military commentator Song Zhongping as similar to that of Russian nuclear icebreakers." "Russia is the only country that operates nuclear-powered icebreakers, which is used to plow through thick ice-covered waters to maintain and develop the Northern Sea route.""China already has a conventionally powered polar icebreaker, which was launched last year to boost its polar research and expedition capacity.""But having a nuclear icebreaker is important for expanding its presence in the Arctic Ocean."SOURCES: South China Morning Posthttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3002455/china-build-30000-tonne-nuclear-powered-ship-described***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/22/3801146/3801146_4A32451A00994BE7A739E5C3D69CE5FD_190322_3801146_China_to_build_33_000_ton_nuclear_powered_ship_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, nuclear icebreaker, icebreaker, nuclear ship, nuclear vessel, china nuclear icebreaker, russia nuclear icebreaker, experimental ship,  russia icebreaker, russia leader icebreaker, northern sea route, russia arktika icebreaker]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3801074</guid>
      <title>Restaurant makes 3D sushi using bodily fluids of diners</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Japanese restaurant is making customized 3D-printed sushi for each of its diners by studying samples of their bodily fluids, reports KXAN.The Tokyo restaurant, called Sushi Singularity, will ask its customers to send in samples of their saliva, urine, and stools and use them to create 3D-printed sushi tailored to meet their dietary needs.After clients make a reservation at the restaurant they will receive a health test kit containing vials to collect samples of their feces, urine, and saliva. Once completed, the kit is then sent back to the restaurant for analysis.Using the data gathered through the samples, the restaurant then creates customized sushi recipes in order to meet the client's dietary needs. Using the recipe, a 3D-printing machine makes the sushi and injects the raw vitamins, proteins, and minerals the client needs.Sushi Singularity is one of many ventures by a Japanese culinary innovation company called Open Meals.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 2. 3. 4. VOICEOVER (in English): "According to KXAN, a restaurant in Tokyo called Sushi Singularity will ask its customers to send in samples of their saliva, urine, and stools and use them to create 3D-printed sushi tailored to meet their dietary needs.""After clients make a reservation at the restaurant they will receive a health test kit containing vials to collect samples of their feces, urine, and saliva. Once completed, the kit is then sent back to the restaurant for analysis.""Using the data gathered through the samples, the restaurant then creates customized sushi recipes in order to meet the client's dietary needs.""Using the recipe, a 3D-printing machine makes the sushi and injects the raw vitamins, proteins, and minerals the client needs."SOURCES: KXAN, Design Boom, Mental Flosshttps://www.kxan.com/news/local/austin/3d-printed-sushi-japanese-company-brings-restaurant-idea-to-sxsw/1839895853https://www.designboom.com/technology/open-meals-3d-printed-sushi-based-on-customers-saliva-and-urine-03-15-2019/http://mentalfloss.com/article/577039/sushi-restaurant-customizes-meals-with-biological-data***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 09:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/22/3801074/3801074_7467A887FF6C46AC9B66070B06E1A1BB_190322_3801074_Restaurant_makes_3D_sushi_using_bodily_fluids_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 3d printed food, 3d printer, 3d printed sushi, 3d print sushi, japan, 3d printed foods, japanese food, sushi teleportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800892</guid>
      <title>The 1989 US Exxon Oil Spill: Animated explainer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Exxon Valdez oil spill in Alaska was one of the biggest U.S. oil spills ever to occur, according to the Atlantic.It's been thirty years since the waters of Bligh Reef in Alaska were contaminated with more than 11 million gallons of crude oil after an Exxon oil tanker impacted the reef's seabed. Today we revisit how the Exxon Valdez Oil Spill happened.According to The Atlantic, on March 24, 1989, the Exxon Valdez oil tanker was entering Alaska's Prince William Sound. It had departed from the Trans Alaska Pipeline terminal on March 23 at 9:12 pm and was carrying 53.1 million gallons of oil.At 12:04 am the tanker slammed into Bligh Reef, tearing open its hull and spilling 11 million gallons of oil into the water and the surrounding environment. That's the equivalent of 17 Olympic-sized swimming pools.According to Scientific American, nearly 2,000 kilometers of the shoreline were contaminated. Wildlife in the area was also severely damaged. Thousands of otters, harbor seals, seabirds and fish were killed.According to the Environmental Protection Agency, three methods were used to clean up the spill: burning the oil on the water's surface, mechanical cleanup via oil skimmers and chemical dispersants.High-pressure hot water was also used to clean the surrounding beaches until it was determined that it was cooking microorganisms present in the shores which in turn damaged the soil.According to a case study by the International Tanker Owners Pollution Federation Limited, Exxon Mobil had to pay $4.3 billion as a consequence of the spill in addition to the $2 billion it spent the first year on clean-up efforts.The Exxon Valdez oil spill is the second largest spill in history second to the Deepwater Horizon oil spill in the Gulf of Mexico, where an explosion at a BP oil rig killed eleven workers and spilled 53,000 barrels of oil per day for three months.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Exxon Valdez oil tanker route 2. Exxon Valdez tanker hull breaks open spilling 11 million gallons of oil3. Shoreline and wildlife damage4. Methods used to clean oil spill VOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Atlantic, on March 24, 1989, the Exxon Valdez oil tanker was entering Alaska's Prince William Sound. It had departed from the Trans Alaska Pipeline terminal on March 23 at 9:12 pm and was carrying 53.1 million gallons of oil.""At 12:04 am the tanker slammed into Bligh Reef, tearing open its hull and spilling 11 million gallons of oil into the water and the surrounding environment. That's the equivalent of 17 Olympic-sized swimming pools.""According to Scientific American, nearly 2,000 kilometers of the shoreline were contaminated. Wildlife in the area was also severely damaged. Thousands of otters, harbor seals, seabirds and fish were killed.""According to the Environmental Protection Agency, three methods were used to clean up the spill: burning the oil on the water's surface, mechanical cleanup via oil skimmers and chemical dispersants."SOURCES: The Atlantic, Scientific American, EPA,  International Tanker Owners Pollution Federation Limitedhttps://www.theatlantic.com/photo/2014/03/the-exxon-valdez-oil-spill-25-years-ago-today/100703/https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/environmental-effects-of/https://www.epa.gov/emergency-response/exxon-valdez-spill-profilehttp://www.itopf.org/in-action/case-studies/case-study/exxon-valdez-alaska-united-stated-1989/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 05:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/22/3800892/3800892_6C62802398D54CABBBA3EDFECF8A3902_190322_3800892_The_1989_US_Exxon_Oil_Spill__Animated_explainer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  exxon valdez oil spill, oil spill, exxon valdez, exxon oil spill, exxon oil spill video, exxon oil spill clean up, oil spill cleanup]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800881</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong to build artificial islands in massive land reclamation project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHong Kong has announced plans to spend $79 billion to construct one of the world's largest artificial island projects.The Guardian reports that Hong Kong is planning to build 1,000 hectares of artificial islands off the coast of Lantau Island.The project, called 'Lantau Vision Tomorrow,' is more than twice the size of Dubai's Palm Jumeirah, which was also created by land reclamation.According to the South China Morning Post, the first phase will provide up to 260,000 residential units, 70 percent of which will be reserved for public housing.A new transport network is also being built, which will include road and rail links to connect the future man-made islands to Hong Kong Island, Lantau, and Tuen Mun.The plan has received criticism from environmental groups, who say the building work will be damaging to local species such as the endangered pink dolphin.The Guardian reports that Greenpeace and the World Wildlife Fund have argued that authorities should instead develop former industrial areas called brownfield sites, arguing that it is cheaper and less harmful to the environment.Reclamation work on 'Lantau Vision Tomorrow' is scheduled to begin in 2025, with the first residents expected to move in by 2032.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Artificial islands off the coast of Lantau Island in Hong Kong2. 260,000 residential units to be built on the artificial islands3. New transport network connecting islands to Hong Kong Island, Lantau, Tuen Mun4. Criticisms of artificial island projectVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that Hong Kong is planning to build 1,000 hectares of artificial islands off the coast of Lantau Island.""The project, called 'Lantau Vision Tomorrow,' is more than twice the size of Dubai's Palm Jumeirah, which was also created by land reclamation.""According to the South China Morning Post, the first phase will provide up to 260,000 residential units, 70 percent of which will be reserved for public housing.""A new transport network is also being built, which will include road and rail links to connect the future man-made islands to Hong Kong Island, Lantau, and Tuen Mun.""The plan has received criticism from environmental groups, who say the building work will be damaging to local species such as the endangered pink dolphin.""The Guardian reports that Greenpeace and the World Wildlife Fund have argued that authorities should instead develop former industrial areas called brownfield sites, arguing that it is cheaper and less harmful to the environment."SOURCES: Hong Kong Civil Engineering and Development Department, South China Morning Post, The Guardianhttps://www.lantau.gov.hk/download/leaflet_e1.pdfhttps://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/hong-kong-economy/article/3002583/lantau-tomorrow-vision-arguably-hong-kongs-mosthttps://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/hong-kong-economy/article/3002404/new-hk624-billion-lantau-housing-project-will-seehttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/20/hong-kong-to-build-one-of-worlds-largest-artificial-islands***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 05:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/22/3800881/3800881_999EA5BDFA7F43D3B34F348FFE132CE1_190322_3800881_Hong_Kong_to_build_artificial_islands_in_massive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hong kong, lantau island, lantau vision tomorrow, hong kong reclamation, land reclamation, lantau island reclamation, hong kong housing, hong kong housing crisis, reclaimed land]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3802236</guid>
      <title>Crashed 737 Max planes lacked safety features that Boeing sold as extras</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe doomed 737 Max jets in Indonesia and Ethiopia were not equipped with two notable safety features because Boeing charged an additional cost to install them.According to the New York Times, the MCAS software on the Boeing 737 Max takes readings from one of two angle of attack sensors on the plane that aligns itself with oncoming airflow.If MCAS detects that the plane is pointed up at a dangerous angle, it automatically swivels the horizontal stabilizer and pushes the nose down to prevent stalling.Two optional safety features could have kept the MCAS in check: the angle of attack indicator displays readings from both sensors, and the disagree light activates when the sensors' data do not match.Both features were sold by Boeing as optional extras and were not included on the crashed Lion Air and Ethiopian Airlines planes.According to the New York Times, the safety features could have helped pilots detect any erroneous readings. This would have also allowed a manual override of the system.The Times, citing a Boeing bulletin, says this can be done by temporarily counteracting the MCAS movement, cutting off electrical power to the stabilizers, and then cranking a wheel to manually pull them back to the correct position.Experts told the newspaper that the two features are vital for flight safety. But because neither is mandated by the FAA, Boeing was able to sell them as upgrades.The company has since announced that it will make the disagree light standard on all new 737 aircrafts, but the angle of attack indicator will remain an optional extra that airlines can buy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the MCAS on the Boeing 737 Max works2. Depiction of angle of attack indicator and disagree light3. Safety features sold as extras, not included in crashed Ethiopian and Lion Air planes4. How the pilot can manually override MCASVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the New York Times, the MCAS software on the Boeing 737 Max takes readings from one of two angle of attack sensors on the plane that aligns itself with oncoming airflow.""If MCAS detects that the plane is pointed up at a dangerous angle, it automatically swivels the horizontal stabilizer and pushes the nose down to prevent stalling.""Two optional safety features could have kept the MCAS in check: the angle of attack indicator displays readings from both sensors, and the disagree light activates when the sensors' data do not match.""Both features were sold by Boeing as optional extras and were not included on the crashed Lion Air and Ethiopian Airlines planes.""According to the New York Times, the safety features could have helped pilots detect any erroneous readings. This would have also allowed a manual override of the system.""The Times, citing a Boeing bulletin, says this can be done by temporarily counteracting the MCAS movement, cutting off electrical power to the stabilizers, and then cranking a wheel to manually pull them back to the correct position."SOURCES: The New York Timeshttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/21/business/boeing-safety-features-charge.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2018/11/16/world/asia/lion-air-crash-cockpit.html?smid=tw-share***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 04:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/25/3802236/3802236_59BAB04518884A8A83B262885956FBC7_190325_3802236_Crashed_737_Max_planes_lacked_safety_features_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, boeing 737 max, boeing safety features, boeing crash, ethiopia airlines, lion air, boeing 737 crash, angle of attack indicator, disagree light, safety upgrades, optional extra]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803114</guid>
      <title>China to build first floating nuclear power stations in the South China Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is planning to build 20 floating nuclear power plants in the South China Sea. Construction for the first one starts this year.According to Asia Times, Chinese authorities have officially announced plans to start building the first floating nuclear power plant in the South China Sea. These are designed to power surrounding artificial islands being built in the region.Floating nuclear power plants are offshore platforms containing small nuclear reactors built to power hard to reach islands or islets.Roughly 20 floating nuclear stations could be built to power troops and residents in the  Spratly and Paracel islands. These regions are disputed between China, Taiwan, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Vietnam.Asia Times reports that the first floating nuclear reactor will be functional and sea-worthy by 2021. A prototype is currently being tested off the coast of China's Shandong province.According to Chinese state news agency, Xinhua Net, the first floating nuclear power platform would cost roughly US$2.1 billion.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  Floating nuclear power plant in the South China Sea. 2.  Islands being powered by the floating nuclear power plant.3. Countries disputing over South China Sea4. Prototype of floating nuclear power plant being tested in Shandong. VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Asia Times, Chinese authorities have officially announced plans to start building the first floating nuclear power plant in the South China Sea. These are designed to power surrounding artificial islands being built in the region.""Floating nuclear power plants are offshore platforms containing small nuclear reactors built to power hard to reach islands or islets.""Roughly 20 floating nuclear stations could be built to power troops and residents in the  Spratly and Paracel islands. These regions are disputed between China, Taiwan, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Vietnam.""Asia Times reports that the first floating nuclear reactor will be functional and sea-worthy by 2021. A prototype is currently being tested off the coast of China's Shandong province."SOURCES: Asia Times, Xinhua Nethttps://www.asiatimes.com/2019/03/article/ocean-going-nuclear-plants-for-south-china-sea/http://www.xinhuanet.com/politics/2018-11/01/c_129984070.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 13:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/26/3803114/3803114_DD2AB0D918424751AF1E9A5C93AB6FCB_190326_3803114_China_to_build_first_floating_nuclear_power_stat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  floating nuclear power plant, floating power station, floating power plant, nuclear power, south china sea, spratlys, paracels, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803054</guid>
      <title>Greenland's melting Jakobshavn glacier is growing again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study has found that Greenland's fastest-thinning glacier is growing again, but scientists say that it may just be temporary.According to NASA JPL, the Jakobshavn glacier in Greenland has been thinning and retreating over the last 20 years.But research published in Nature Geoscience has found that since 2016, the glacier's melting has slowed.NASA reports that it also grew taller by 100 feet between 2016 and 2017.Researchers suspected that this was due to a climate pattern known as the North Atlantic Oscillation, which cools then warm the North Atlantic Ocean every five to 20 years. In 2016, the water temperature in Disko Bay cooled, reaching temperatures that were lower than in the late 1980s.The team used an ocean model to trace the cool water to a current that carries water around Greenland's southern tip, and northward along its west coast.The Associated Press reports that according to study co-author and NASA climate scientist Josh Willis, the findings indicate that glacier retreats and advances are much more sensitive to ocean temperatures than previously thought.  Temperatures are still rising slowly from global warming, and with over 90 percent of heat trapped by greenhouse gases going to the oceans, melting will be worse in the long run.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Jakobshavn glacier melting2. Jakobshavn glacier thickening, melting more slowly since 20163. Water temperature changes in Disko Bay 4. Depiction of North Atlantic Oscillation VOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA JPL, the Jakobshavn glacier in Greenland has been thinning and retreating over the last 20 years.""But research published in Nature Geoscience has found that since 2016, the glacier's melting has slowed.""NASA reports that it also grew taller by 100 feet between 2016 and 2017.""Researchers suspected that this was due to a climate pattern known as the North Atlantic Oscillation, which cools then warm the North Atlantic Ocean every five to 20 years.""In 2016, the water temperature in Disko Bay cooled, reaching temperatures that were lower than in the late 1980s.""The team used an ocean model to trace the cool water to a current that carries water around Greenland's southern tip, and northward along its west coast."SOURCES:Nature Geoscience, NASA JPLhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41561-019-0329-3https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7356***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 11:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/26/3803054/3803054_D0004F3C50904EF4967954A149491B1E_190326_3803054_Greenland_s_melting_Jakobshavn_glacier_is_growin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Greenland glacier, Jakobshavn glacier, Greenland ice sheets, Greenland ice melt, Jakobshavn, Sermeq Kujalleq, melting glaciers, North Atlantic Oscillation, climate change, global warming, Greenland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803049</guid>
      <title>NASA to send autonomous mini helicopter on Mars 2020 mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Mars 2020 mission will include a mini helicopter that is set to be the first heavier-than-air vehicle to fly within the Red Planet's thin atmosphere.According to NASA, an autonomous rotorcraft called the Mars Helicopter will fly with the Mars Rover in 2020. The small helicopter will be carrying a camera to capture photos of the Martian surface for transmission back to Earth.The atmospheric pressure on the surface the rover is targeted to land on is equivalent to 100,000 feet above the surface of the Earth  over twice as high as any helicopter has reached.To generate enough lift, the Mars Helicopter's main body will be the size of a softball and weigh just four pounds.It will fly up to 15 feet off the surface using two sets of four-feet-long rotor blades spinning at 2,400 rotations per minute  ten times faster than any Earth helicopter.The Mars Helicopter will attempt up to five flights, each time flying a little farther and lasting up to 90 seconds.A solar array will recharge the lithium-ion batteries that will be used to rotate the blades and keep the vehicle warm through the frigid Martian night.Scientists at NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory say that if the rotorcraft works as planned, future missions to Mars could deploy more helicopters to extend the reach of the landers they arrive on.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mars Helicopter launched with Mars Rover in 20202. Atmospheric pressure on Mars surface not ideal for Earth helicopters  3. Size and capabilities of helicopter body, rotor blades4. Planned flights on MarsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA, an autonomous rotorcraft called the Mars Helicopter will fly with the Mars Rover in 2020.""The small helicopter will be carrying a camera to capture photos of the Martian surface for transmission back to Earth.""The atmospheric pressure on the surface the rover is targeted to land on is equivalent to 100,000 feet above the surface of the Earth  over twice as high as any helicopter has reached.""To generate enough lift, the Mars Helicopter's main body will be the size of a softball and weigh just four pounds.""It will fly up to 15 feet off the surface using two sets of four-fee-long rotor blades spinning at 2,400 rotations per minute  ten times faster than any Earth helicopter.""The Mars Helicopter will attempt up to five flights, each time flying a little farther and lasting up to 90 seconds.""A solar array will recharge the lithium-ion batteries that will be used to rotate the blades and keep the vehicle warm through the frigid Martian night."SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/nasa-is-with-you-when-you-fly-even-on-mars***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 11:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/26/3803049/3803049_00E4B21C8DE34268AF67C183EDE7C7E8_190326_3803049_NASA_to_send_autonomous_mini_helicopter_on_Mars__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mars helicopter, Mars 2020, Mars rover, Mars mission, NASA helicopter, NASA, helicopter on Mars, Mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3802877</guid>
      <title>Nokia says 7 Plus phones sent user data to China by mistake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFinland's Data Protection Ombudsman is investigating HMD Global over claims that its Nokia 7 Plus phones sent user data to China.NRK reports that based on a tip from a phone owner, Nokia 7 Plus phones sent out unencrypted data, which includes location, sim card, and the phone's serial number.The data packages were sent to a server in China owned by China Telecom.According to Nokia, phones purchased in regions like the EU, U.S., and India send data for phone warranty and diagnostics to HMD Global servers in Singapore. Data from phones bought in China are sent to servers in China in order to comply with the country's Cyber Security Law.According to a statement from HMD Global, the Chinese device activation client was mistakenly installed on a single batch of Nokia 7 Plus phones that were meant for countries outside China.Reuters reports that the Finnish investigation would look into whether any data rules that involved personal information were breached and if there has been a legal justification for it.The company says no personally identifiable data was processed or shared to a third party, and claim the error was fixed in February by switching the client to the correct country variant.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nokia 7 Plus phones send unencrypted data to server in China2. Nokia's data collection policies 3. Chinese activation client mistakenly installed on single batch of phones meant for other countries4. No personally identifiable information shared to third party; error fixedVOICEOVER (in English): "NRK reports that based on a tip from a phone owner, Nokia 7 Plus phones sent out unencrypted data, which includes location, sim card and the phone's serial number." "The data packages were sent to a server in China owned by China Telecom.""According to Nokia, phones purchased in regions like the EU, U.S. and India send data for phone warranty and diagnostics to HMD Global servers in Singapore.""Data from phones bought in China are sent to servers in China, to comply with the country's Cyber Security Law.""According to a statement from HMD Global, the Chinese device activation client was mistakenly installed on a single batch of Nokia 7 Plus phones that were meant for countries outside China.""The company says no personally identifiable data was processed or shared to a third party, and claim the error was fixed in February by switching the client to the correct country variant."SOURCES:Nokia, NRK, Reutershttps://www.nokia.com/phones/en_int/privacy-infohttps://nrkbeta.no/2019/03/21/norske-telefoner-sendte-personopplysninger-til-kina/https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-finland-telecoms/finland-to-investigate-nokia-branded-phones-after-data-breach-report-idUKKCN1R20XO***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/26/3802877/3802877_261A43216FA34775B8732BEDCFA108DB_190326_3802877_Nokia_says_7_Plus_phones_sent_user_data_to_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, nokia, nokia 7 plus, nokia data breach, nokia data leak, data sent to China, nokia phones, China server, HMD global, China Telecom]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3802740</guid>
      <title>Record-breaking bridge in Taiwan set to open by 2024</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANConstruction has begun on Danjiang Bridge, the world's longest, single-mast, asymmetric cable-stayed bridge.According to Zaha Hadid Architects, Taiwan's 920-meter long Danjiang bridge will span the mouth of the Tamsui river that flows through Taipei.The bridge will be supported by a slender 200-meter tall concrete mast, which is positioned so that it does not obstruct the waterway, or the scenic views. The single-mast design also minimizes disruption to the riverbed and local habitat.The new crossing will reduce congestion on local roads as it links two major highways on opposite sides of the river. It is also set to improve connectivity with the Port of Taipei and Taoyuan International Airport.Dedicated road, cycle and pedestrian lanes will be built on the bridge. Also included are plans to  accommodate the future expansion of the Danhai Light Rail network.The Danjiang bridge construction project has a budget of $405.2 million. It will be constructed in 68 months and expected to open by 2024.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Danjiang bridge location and dimensions2. Single concrete mast to support the bridge3. Bridge to link highways, reduce traffic on congested local roads4. Road, cycle, and pedestrian lanes and future Danhai Light Rail link on the bridgeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Zaha Hadid Architects, Taiwan's 920-meter long Danjiang bridge will span the mouth of the Tamsui river that flows through Taipei.""The bridge will be supported by a slender 200-meter tall concrete mast, which is positioned so that it does not obstruct the waterway, or the scenic views.""The single-mast design also minimizes disruption to the riverbed and local habitat.""Archinect reports that the new crossing will reduce congestion on local roads as it links two major highways on opposite sides of the river.""It is also set to improve connectivity with the Port of Taipei, and Taoyuan International Airport.""Dedicated road, cycle, and pedestrian lanes will be built on the bridge. Also included are plans to  accommodate the future expansion of the Danhai Light Rail network."SOURCES: Zaha Hadid Architects, Archinecthttp://www.zaha-hadid.com/architecture/danjiang-bridge/https://archinect.com/news/bustler/7174/zaha-hadid-designed-danjiang-bridge-in-taiwan-scheduled-for-2024-opening***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 02:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/26/3802740/3802740_179989AA42B642F0B2ABF283AF1E3B1C_190326_3802740_Record_breaking_bridge_in_Taiwan_set_to_open_by__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, danjiang bridge, taiwan bridge, single mast bridge, asymmetric cable stayed bridge, tamsui river, zaha hadid architects, record breaking bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803772</guid>
      <title>Southwest Boeing 737 Max 8 makes emergency landing due to engine problems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Southwest Airlines Boeing 737 Max 8 plane was forced to make an emergency landing on Tuesday afternoon at Orlando International Airport. According to the Orlando Sentinel, there were no passengers on board. Two pilots were flying the plane to California for storage, when they experienced a performance issue with one of the engines 10 minutes after takeoff. The aircraft turned around and landed safely. The incident occurred around 3 p.m.The plane was being ferried to Victorville, California for storage. According to Dan Landson, a spokesman for Southwest, "the Boeing 737 Max 8 will be moved to our Orlando maintenance facility for a review." According to a March 13 FAA order that grounded all Boeing 737 Max aircraft, airlines are allowed to fly the planes without passengers to locations for storage and maintenance. The emergency landing comes as federal regulators continue to investigate two deadly crashes involving 737 Max 8 aircraft in Ethiopia and Indonesia. According to the Orlando Sentinel, Southwest has 34 Max planes. On Saturday, the airline began flying them to Victorville to free up space at airports where they have been temporarily parked. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Southwest 737 Max taking off 2. Southwest plane was not carrying passengers, experiences problem in one engine3. Southwest plane turning, plane landing back at airport4. Southwest planes at Victorville AirportVOICEOVER (in English): "A Southwest Airlines Boeing 737 Max 8 plane was forced to make an emergency landing on Tuesday afternoon at Orlando International Airport." "According to the Orlando Sentinel, there were no passengers on board. Two pilots were flying the plane to Victorville, California for storage, when they experienced a performance issue with one of the engines 10 minutes after takeoff." "The aircraft turned around and landed safely. The incident occurred around 3 p.m.""According to Dan Landson, a spokesman for Southwest, 'the Boeing 737 Max 8 will be moved to our Orlando maintenance facility for a review.'" "According to the Orlando Sentinel, Southwest has 34 Max planes. On Saturday, the airline began flying them to Victorville to free up space at airports where they have been temporarily parked." SOURCES: Orlando Sentinel, Reuters https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-southwest-emergency-landing-orlando-20190326-story.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-boeing-airplane-southwest/southwest-737-max-8-passenger-less-flight-lands-safely-after-declaring-emergency-faa-idUSKCN1R72NI***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/27/3803772/3803772_8E593E8D8FFD46519F905F04A912EC86_190327_3803772_Southwest_Boeing_737_Max_8_makes_emergency_landi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Boeing 737 Max 8, Southwest 737 Max 8, Southwest Max emergency landing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803461</guid>
      <title>U.S. military conducts successful salvo missile defense test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. military said it successfully tested a missile defense system to knock down an Intercontinental Ballistic Missile class target on Monday, according to Reuters.  The test was meant to simulate how well the U.S. could respond in the event of a missile threat from a country like North Korea or Iran. The U.S. Missile Defense Agency said two ground-based interceptor missiles were launched in the test. The first interceptor hit and destroyed the re-entry vehicle, and the other "looked at the resulting debris and remaining objects, and, not finding any other re-entry vehicles, selected the next 'most lethal object' it could identify, and struck that," it said. The dummy target was launched from the Reagan Test Site in the Marshall Islands in the Pacific, more than 4,000 miles (6,400 km) from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California, where the two interceptors were launched, the agency said. According to the AP, the Pentagon is putting additional billions of dollars into expanding its arsenal of missile interceptors, which are based largely at Fort Greely in Alaska. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ground based interceptor missile2. Dummy target was launched from Reagan Test Site in the Marshall Islands3. Two ground-based interceptor missiles were launched in test4. Interceptor missiles successfully destroying dummy targetVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, the U.S. military said it successfully tested a missile defense system to knock down an Intercontinental Ballistic Missile class target on Monday."  "The test was meant to simulate how well the U.S. could respond in the event of a missile threat from a country like North Korea or Iran." "According to the U.S. Missile Defense Agency, the dummy target was launched from the Reagan Test Site in the Marshall Islands in the Pacific, more than 4,000 miles from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California, where the interceptors were launched.""The U.S. Missile Defense Agency said two ground-based interceptor missiles were launched in the test." "According to the agency, the first interceptor hit and destroyed the re-entry vehicle, and the other 'looked at the resulting debris and remaining objects, and, not finding any other re-entry vehicles, selected the next most lethal object it could identify, and struck that.'"  SOURCES: Reuters, Associated Presshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-pentagon-missiledefense/u-s-military-says-it-conducts-successful-missile-defense-test-idUSKCN1R62SEhttps://www.apnews.com/c528962332e441c79fabc72e2cc578f9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 06:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/27/3803461/3803461_B878C8BE211C4120B9236C9AA414B7B3_190327_3803461_U_S__military_conducts_successful_salvo_missile__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US missile defense system, US military missile defense system, US salvo missile defense, US interceptor missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803437</guid>
      <title>Construction of a rooftop farm and market is underway in Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Dutch architecture company has begun construction of an open-air market that will feature a roof-top farm in the south of Taiwan, according to design magazine Dezeen. Dutch firm, MVRDV, has started building the Tainan Xinhua Fruit and Vegetable Market in Taiwan's southern city of Tainan. This is being made in collaboration with the county's City Government Agriculture Bureau. The building's main purpose is to become a food supply hub for the city as well as a tourist attraction. The market will cover a total of 80,000 square meters or roughly 862,000 square feet. It will be built as an open space with a crop-terrace-like rooftop. Each level of the terrace will be used to grow different kinds of produce.A closed building will be built on one side of the market, intersecting with the terrace roof. In it will be the market's administrative offices, a restaurant, and an exhibition center.One corner of the east side of the terrace folds down and reaches ground-level. This allows visitors to walk up to the roof which has public seating and recreational areas.The building is scheduled to be complete in late 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Aerial view and inside view of the market 2. View of terrace farm and different crops growing3. View of the open market's administrative building4. View of stairs that guide visitors to the rooftopVOICEOVER (in English): "According to design magazine Dezeen, Dutch firm, MVRDV, has started building the Tainan Xinhua Fruit and Vegetable Market in Taiwan's southern city of Tainan. "This is being made in collaboration with the county's City Government Agriculture Bureau.""The building's main purpose is to become a food supply hub for the city as well as a tourist attraction. ""The market will cover a total of 80,000 square meters or roughly 862,000 square feet. "It will be built as an open space with a crop-terrace-like rooftop. Each level of the terrace will be used to grow different kinds of produce.""A closed building will be built on one side of the market, intersecting with the terrace roof. In it will be the market's administrative offices, a restaurant, and an exhibition center.""One corner of the east side of the terrace folds down and reaches ground-level. This allows visitors to walk up to the roof which has public seating and recreational areas."SOURCES: De Zeen, Inhabitat, MVRDVhttps://www.dezeen.com/2019/03/08/mvrdv-rooftop-farm-tainan-xinhua-fruit-vegetable-market-taiwan/#disqus_threadhttps://inhabitat.com/the-environmental-problem-with-toilet-paper-and-what-to-use-instead/https://www.mvrdv.com/projects/391/tainan-market***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 05:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/27/3803437/3803437_94B0BB3EF5C348F4B81E1753DD69DE9C_190327_3803437_Construction_of_a_rooftop_farm_and_market_is_und_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, green building construction, green building design, building, green building, Taiwan, tainan taiwan, rooftop farm, open market, architecture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804365</guid>
      <title>Rescued migrants hijack merchant ship off Libya</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMigrants have hijacked a merchant ship which rescued them off the coast of Libya and it is now heading toward Malta, Italian Deputy Prime Minister Matteo Salvini and Maltese authorities said on Wednesday. According the FleetMon, the Palau-flagged tanker Elhiblu 1 was traveling from Turkey to Tripoli, Libya on Tuesday when it was diverted to a distressed migrant boat off the Libyan coast. According to DW News, the tanker rescued the migrants and resumed sailing toward Tripoli.  According to Salvini, when the ship was six nautical miles from port, it changed course toward Malta. According to Maltese authorities, the vessel is believed to be carrying 108 migrants made up of 77 men and 31 women. Maltese authorities confirmed the ship had been hijacked and said Maltese authorities were monitoring its progress and would not allow the vessel to dock in Malta.  Malta Today reports that a spokesperson for the Maltese armed forces said attempts to contact the ship's captain had been unsuccessful. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Merchant ship2. Merchant ship rescuing migrants3. Merchant ship heading toward Malta instead of Tripoli4. Ship is carrying 108 migrantsVOICEOVER (in English): "Migrants have hijacked a merchant ship which rescued them off the coast of Libya and are now heading toward Malta, Italian Deputy Prime Minister Matteo Salvini and Maltese authorities said on Wednesday." "According the FleetMon, the Palau-flagged tanker Elhiblu 1 was traveling from Turkey to Tripoli on Tuesday when it was diverted to a distressed migrant boat off the Libyan coast." "According to DW News, the product tanker rescued the migrants and then resumed sailing toward Tripoli." "According to Salvini, when the ship was six nautical miles from port, it changed course toward Malta. " "According to Maltese authorities, the vessel is believed to be carrying 108 migrants made up of 77 men and 31 women." "Maltese authorities confirmed the ship had been hijacked and said Maltese authorities were monitoring its progress and would not allow the vessel to dock in Malta."  SOURCES: Reuters, DW News, BBC, FleetMon Malta Todayhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-hijacking/rescued-migrants-hijack-merchant-ship-off-libya-idUSKCN1R81YFhttps://www.dw.com/en/migrants-hijack-merchant-ship-steer-toward-europe-reports/a-48089026https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47725242https://www.fleetmon.com/maritime-news/2019/25685/108-migrants-hijacked-tanker-which-rescued-them-me/https://www.maltatoday.com.mt/news/national/93917/merchant_ship_hijacked_by_migrants_heading_towards_malta#.XJxSZ88za8o***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/28/3804365/3804365_08109AA589074F7A8B34967A7E711629_190328_3804365_Rescued_migrants_hijack_merchant_ship_off_Libya_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, migrants, migrants hijack ship, migrants hijack merchant ship, Libya, Malta]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804112</guid>
      <title>U.S. condemns Russian military deployment in Venezuela</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. has accused Russia of meddling and aggravating political tensions in crisis-stricken Venezuela.The Guardian reports that two Russian military planes, an Ilyushin Il-62 and an Antonov-124 cargo plane landed at Maiquetia airport near Caracas on Saturday. The two aircrafts were seen guarded by a contingent of Venezuelan national guardsmen.According to the BBC, Venezuelan journalist Javier Mayorca wrote on Twitter that 100 Russian troops disembarked with 35 tonnes of equipment.Russian military experts in the Guardian say the cargo plane may have been carrying spare parts. Venezuela was once one of the largest importers of Russian arms, and has warplanes, missiles and other weapons in its arsenal that require maintenance.According to the Guardian, Russia is one of Venezuela's main allies, and has provided diplomatic, economic and military support to the embattled administration of Nicolas Maduro.In December, Russia signaled its support for the oil-rich country by sending two TU-160 bombers to take part in a joint military exercise.The U.S. has repeatedly called for Maduro to resign, instead recognizing Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido as the country's interim president.According to Reuters, the State Department condemned the Russian military deployment to Caracas, calling it a "reckless escalation of the situation."Secretary of State Mike Pompeo also told his Russian counterpart in a phone call to stop its "unconstructive behavior," warning that the U.S. and its allies "will not stand idly by as Russia exacerbates tensions in Venezuela."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Russian planes land in Caracas, guarded by Venezuelan national guardsmen2. Russian troops and equipment on planes3. Russian support for Nicolas Maduro administration; joint military exercise with Venezuela4. U.S. supporting opposition leader Juan Guaido, condemning Russian military deploymentVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that two Russian military planes, an Ilyushin Il-62 and an Antonov-124 cargo plane landed at Maiquetia airport near Caracas on Saturday.""The two aircrafts were seen guarded by a contingent of Venezuelan national guardsmen.""According to the BBC, Venezuelan journalist Javier Mayorca wrote on Twitter that 100 Russian troops disembarked with 35 tonnes of equipment.""Russian military experts in the Guardian say the cargo plane may have been carrying spare parts. Venezuela was once one of the largest importers of Russian arms, and has warplanes, missiles, and other weapons in its arsenal that require maintenance.""According to the Guardian, Russia is one of Venezuela's main allies, and has provided diplomatic, economic, and military support to the embattled administration of Nicolas Maduro.""In December, Russia signaled its support for the oil-rich country by sending two TU-160 bombers to take part in a joint military exercise.""The U.S. has repeatedly called for Maduro to resign, instead recognizing Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido as the country's interim president.""According to Reuters, the State Department condemned the Russian military deployment to Caracas, calling it a 'reckless escalation of the situation.'"SOURCES: The Guardian, BBC, Reutershttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/25/russian-military-officials-arrive-in-venezuela-to-discuss-training-and-strategyhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-47688711https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-usa-russia/us-calls-russian-military-presence-in-venezuela-reckless-escalation-of-situation-idUSKCN1R62F1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 06:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/28/3804112/3804112_2245DECD41BB418EAA584D11B4AB396B_190328_3804112_U_S__condemns_Russian_military_deployment_in_Ven_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Venezuela, Russia vs US, russian military in venezuela, Nicolas Maduro, Russian planes land in Venezuela, Juan Guaido, Venezuela president]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804052</guid>
      <title>Nuclear accident: The Three Mile Island Accident explained.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOn March 28, 1979, The Three Mile Island Unit 2 reactor, near Middletown, Pennsylvania partially melted down, releasing radioactive fumes into the atmosphere.According to the US Nuclear Regulatory Commission, the plant experienced its first malfunction at 4 a.m. that same day on one of the two reactors on site.A mechanical break down was causing the reactor's cooling system to fail, which in turn caused pressure in its primary system to rise. In order to fight the increasing pressure, a valve located on top of the reactor's pressurizer opened.The valve was supposed to close once the pressure levels were stabilized, however, it jammed and stayed open. Staff did not know the valve had failed to close because instruments in the control room did not indicate otherwise. It wasn't until alarms began to ring that the staff realized the reactor was releasing coolants due to the open valve.The US Nuclear Regulatory Commission reports that roughly 2 million people were exposed to a small amount of radiation, which they claim cannot cause health issues.The reactor is now permanently shut down and 99 percent of its fuel has been removed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of nuclear plant2. Nuclear reactor begins to have failures at 4:00 am.3. Nuclear reactor overheats, pressure release valve opens. 4. Pressure release valve does not close; staff at the nuclear reactor control room do not see any issues.VOICEOVER (in English): "On March 28, 1979, The Three Mile Island Unit 2 reactor, near Middletown, Pennsylvania partially melted down, releasing radioactive fumes into the atmosphere.""According to the US Nuclear Regulatory Commission, the plant experienced its first malfunction at 4 a.m. that same day on one of the two reactors on site.""A mechanical break down was causing the reactor's cooling system to fail, which in turn caused pressure in its primary system to rise." "In order to fight the increasing pressure, a valve located on top of the reactor's pressurizer opened.""The valve was supposed to close once the pressure levels were stabilized, however, it jammed and stayed open.""Staff did not know the valve had failed to close because instruments in the control room did not indicate otherwise." "It wasn't until alarms began to ring that the staff realized the reactor was releasing coolants due to the open valve."SOURCES: US Nuclear Regulatory Commissionhttps://www.nrc.gov/reading-rm/doc-collections/fact-sheets/3mile-isle.html#impact***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 05:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/28/3804052/3804052_DBE5144405284F93AFE1FF05063114CB_190328_3804052_Nuclear_accident__The_Three_Mile_Island_Accident_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  nuclear disaster, us nuclear disaster, worst nuclear disaster, worst nuclear disasters, worst nuclear disasters, nuclear accident, nuclear disaster, united states, us]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804028</guid>
      <title>Pentagon shifting $1 billion to fund border wall construction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Department of Defense shifted $1 billion to begin new wall construction along the U.S.-Mexico border, according to Reuters. According to the BBC, the funds are the first under the national emergency declared by President Trump to bypass Congress in order to fund his promised border wall. According to Reuters, the Pentagon chief said on Monday the money would go toward planning and building a 57-mile section of "pedestrian fencing," improved roads and lighting along the border. According to CNN, the Department of Defense authorized the Army Corp of Engineers to begin planning and construction for the project on Monday night. According to Reuters, acting Secretary of Defense Patrick Shanahan said in a memo to Secretary of Homeland Security Kirsthen Nielsen that the Department of Defense had the authority to support counter-narcotics near international boundaries. Shanahan authorized the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers to begin planning and executing the project that involves building 57-miles of 18-foot-high fencing, constructing and improving roads, and installing lighting within the Yuma and El Paso sections of border. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. US-Mexico border2. Pedestrian fencing, improved roads, border lighting3. Pedestrian fencing construction4. Border roads and border lightingVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Department of Defense shifted $1 billion to begin new wall construction along the U.S.-Mexico border." "According to Reuters, Pentagon Chief Patrick Shanahan said on Monday the money would go toward planning and building a 57-mile section of "pedestrian fencing," improved roads and lighting along the border." "Shanahan authorized the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers to begin planning and executing the project that involves building 57-miles of 18-foot-high fencing," "constructing and improving roads, and installing lighting within the Yuma and El Paso sections of border." SOURCES: Reuters, BBC, CNNhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-pentagon-mexico/pentagon-chief-says-1-billion-of-funding-shifted-to-border-wall-idUSKCN1R707Jhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-47702152https://edition.cnn.com/2019/03/25/politics/pentagon-congress-new-wall-money/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 04:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/28/3804028/3804028_656386C7D80549859736A80ED2B34FFB_190328_3804028_Pentagon_shifting__1_billion_to_fund_border_wall_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Pentagon border wall, Pentagon border fencing, border wall construction, Trump, Donald Trump]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804892</guid>
      <title>Surgeons claim to repair fully severed spinal cords in animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSurgeons from Italy and China claimed that two studies published Wednesday add evidence to their ability to treat irreversible spinal-cord injuries that will someday lead to the world's first human head transplant, according to USA Today. Sergio Canavero and Ren Xiaoping said new work they published in the journal Surgical Neurology International showed that monkeys and dogs were able to walk again after having their spinal cords "fully transected" during surgery and then put back together. The experimental procedures were conducted at Harbin Medical University in China and were supported by video evidence. The procedure involves applying a polyethylene glycol substance, or PEG, "to mend" severed or injured spinal cords.  Further research is needed on PEG in order to establish if it is ultimately able to help patients with spinal cord injuries and paralysis. Canavero and Ren have said previously that they want to use the technique with PEG as a basis for human head transplants. According to USA Today, most medical experts say attempting the procedure in humans would be a long shot. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dog and monkey spine procedures could lead to head transplants2. Dogs and monkeys were able to walk again after procedure3. Surgeons performing procedure on dog4. More research needs to be done on PEG to see if it can help with spine injuriesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to USA Today, surgeons from Italy and China claimed that two studies published Wednesday add evidence to their ability to treat irreversible spinal-cord injuries that will someday lead to the world's first human head transplant.""Sergio Canavero and Ren Xiaoping said new work they published in the journal Surgical Neurology International showed that monkeys and dogs were able to walk again after having their spinal cords 'fully transected' during surgery and then put back together." "The experimental procedures were conducted at Harbin Medical University in China and were supported by video evidence." "The procedure involves applying a polyethylene glycol substance, or PEG, 'to mend' severed or injured spinal cords."  "Further research is needed on PEG in order to establish if it is ultimately able to help patients with spinal cord injuries and paralysis."SOURCES: USA Todayhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/03/27/italian-chinese-surgeons-cite-spinal-cord-repair-head-transplant-canavero-xiaoping/3287179002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 11:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/29/3804892/3804892_450F99E672974CDC8505D3EFA98F726F_190329_3804892_Surgeons_claim_to_repair_fully_severed_spinal_co_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, head transplant, spinal cord repair, spinal cord injury repair, severed spinal cord injury repair, Sergio Canavero]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804638</guid>
      <title>Astronomers make first direct observation of super-Jupiter exoplanet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers have made the first direct observation of an exoplanet using a technique known as optical interferometry.According to a press release from the European Southern Observatory or ESO, the exoplanet HR8799e was discovered in 2010, 129 light years from Earth in the Pegasus constellation.It is one of three planets orbiting around the star HR8799. CNN reports that the exoplanet lies closest to its host star, and takes 40 to 50 years to make a full orbit.Using the GRAVITY instrument on ESO's Very Large Telescope Interferometer, ESO scientists found that HR8799e is a 'super-Jupiter.' It is much more massive than any planet in our solar system, but also younger.Due to leftover energy from its formation and a powerful greenhouse effect, the temperature on HR8799e is an inhospitable 1000 degrees Celsius or about 1,616 Fahrenheit.According to ESO, analysis showed that the exoplanet's atmosphere has more carbon monoxide than methane.Clouds of iron and silicate dust were also found, which when combined with the excess carbon monoxide, suggests a huge, violent storm in HR8799e's atmosphere.CNN reports that researchers are planning long-term follow up observations of HR8799e, and can study it more to learn more about the formation of planets and planetary systems.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. HR8799e exoplanet found orbiting host star in Pegasus constellation2. Super-Jupiter exoplanet more massive but younger than any planet in our solar system3. HR8799e has surface temperature of 1,000 degrees Celsius4. HR8799e's stormy atmosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a press release from the European Southern Observatory or ESO, the exoplanet HR8799e was discovered in 2010, 129 light years from Earth in the Pegasus constellation.""It is one of three planets orbiting around the star HR8799. CNN reports that the exoplanet lies closest to its host star, and takes 40 to 50 years to make a full orbit.""Using the GRAVITY instrument on ESO's Very Large Telescope Interferometer, ESO scientists found that HR8799e is a 'super-Jupiter.' It is much more massive than any planet in our solar system, but also younger.""Due to leftover energy from its formation and a powerful greenhouse effect, the temperature on HR8799e is an inhospitable 1,000 degrees Celsius or about 1,616 Fahrenheit.""According to ESO, analysis showed that the exoplanet's atmosphere has more carbon monoxide than methane.""Clouds of iron and silicate dust were also found, which when combined with the excess carbon monoxide, suggests a huge, violent storm in HR8799e's atmosphere."SOURCES: European Southern Observatory, CNNhttps://www.eso.org/public/news/eso1905/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/03/27/world/new-exoplanet-atmosphere-super-telescope-scn/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 06:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/29/3804638/3804638_009D094CD4764D94BDE8BFCD53623C9A_190329_3804638_Astronomers_make_first_direct_observation_of_sup_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, super Jupiter, exoplanet, new planet, HR8799e, Pegasus constellation, VLTI, European Southern Observatory, ESO]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804518</guid>
      <title>Scientists develop contraceptive jewelry to prevent pregnancies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists from the Georgia Institute of Technology have developed a novel form of birth control that's literally as simple as putting on an earring.A report published in the Journal of Controlled Release describes a technique that administers contraceptive hormones transdermally, via patches that can be mounted on earrings, necklaces, rings, or wristwatches.Contraceptive patches are already available, but the team believe incorporating them into jewelry could allow for a more attractive and discreet method of drug delivery.According to a press release from the Georgia Institute of Technology, researchers tested an earring patch that consisted of three layers.One layer is impermeable and contains an adhesive to hold it onto a piece of jewelry. The middle layer contains the contraceptive hormone in solid form, while the outer layer is a skin adhesive that allows the hormone to be transferred.Once it is in the skin, the contraceptive drug moves into the bloodstream and can then circulate through the body.The earring patches were tested on pigs' ears and the skin of hairless rats by being applied for 16 hours and removed for eight.While drug levels dropped when the earrings were off, the patches were found to produce the necessary amounts of the hormone in the blood.The technology has yet to be tested on humans, but if ultimately used in the future, the patches would have be changed periodically, most likely on a weekly basis.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Transdermal contraceptive patch mounted on jewelry pieces2. Three layers of the contraceptive patch3. Contraceptive drug enters the bloodstream through skin4. Contraceptive patch tested on animalsVOICEOVER (in English): "A report published in the Journal of Controlled Release describes a technique that administers contraceptive hormones transdermally, via patches that can be mounted on earrings, necklaces, rings, or wristwatches.""According to a press release from the Georgia Institute of Technology, researchers tested an earring patch that consisted of three layers.""One layer is impermeable and contains an adhesive to hold it onto a piece of jewelry. The middle layer contains the contraceptive hormone in solid form, while the outer layer is a skin adhesive that allows the hormone to be transferred.""Once it is in the skin, the contraceptive drug moves into the bloodstream and can then circulate through the body.""The earring patches were tested on pigs' ears and the skin of hairless rats by being applied for 16 hours and removed for eight.""While drug levels dropped when the earrings were off, the patches were found to produce the necessary amounts of the hormone in the blood."SOURCES: Georgia Institute of Technology, Journal of Controlled Releasehttps://techxplore.com/news/2019-03-contraceptive-jewelry-family-approach.htmlhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0168365919301609?via%3Dihub#f0035***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 02:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/29/3804518/3804518_A5D8379A25034BE89178386E2B8BA1B6_190329_3804518_Scientists_develop_contraceptive_jewelry_to_prev_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, contraceptive earrings, contraceptive jewelry, pharmaceutical jewelry, birth control earrings, birth control jewelry, contraceptives, contraception, birth control]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804493</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabian farms in California are using water for free</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Saudi Arabian food conglomerate is using Californian land and water for free through a century-old legal loop-hole. According to The Guardian, Fondomonte Farms, a subsidiary from a Saudi Arabian food conglomerate called Almarai, owns 16 percent of the irrigated land in Blythe, California. They use this land to grow alfalfa which is then exported to Saudi Arabia as feed for the company's cows.Blythe is an arid region in California, however, its land is irrigated by the lower Colorado River. This river is also the main water supply for nearly 40 million people. Currently, the river is drying up due to climate change.According to The Guardian, Fondomonte Farms is using a loop-hole from a law dating back to the 1800s to benefit from the scarce water supply in the region for free. An 1877 water claim approved by the government allowed farmers and those living within the district to consume as much water as they needed for free due to the shortage of water in Blythe.The Palo Verde Irrigation District cannot sell the water in the area, they can only charge farmers $77 per acre-foot to cover the water district's overhead.  Apart from owning land in California, Almarai also owns 10,000 acres of land in Arizona that it bought back in 2014 as well as 30,000 acres in Argentina acquired in 2012.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Almarai owns 16 percent of the irrigated land in Blythe, California2. Dry and arid environment in Blythe; Lower Colorado River3. 1877 water claim4. Other land owned by Almarai in Arizona and ArgentinaVOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Guardian, Fondomonte Farms, a subsidiary from a Saudi Arabian food conglomerate called Almarai, owns 16 percent of the irrigated land in Blythe, California.""They use this land to grow alfalfa which is then exported to Saudi Arabia as feed for the company's cows.""Blythe is an arid region in California, however, its land is irrigated by the lower Colorado River. This river is also the main water supply for nearly 40 million people. Currently, the river is drying up due to climate change.""According to The Guardian, Fondomonte Farms is using a loop-hole from a law dating back to the 1800s to benefit from the scarce water supply in the region for free.""An 1877 water claim approved by the government allowed farmers and those living within the district to consume as much water as they needed for free due to the shortage of water in Blythe.""The Palo Verde Irrigation District cannot sell the water in the area, they can only charge farmers $77 per acre-foot to cover the water district's overhead. ""Apart from owning land in California, Almarai also owns 10,000 acres of land in Arizona that it bought back in 2014 as well as 30,000 acres in Argentina acquired in 2012."SOURCES: The Guardian https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/mar/25/california-water-drought-scarce-saudi-arabia***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/29/3804493/3804493_AF8104CAE558473C972ED979658C0FFD_190329_3804493_Saudi_Arabian_farms_in_California_are_using_wate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Saudi Arabia, California, California drought]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
