<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3581905</guid>
      <title>Tesla voluntarily issues its largest recall over Model S power steering bolts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTesla Inc voluntarily issued a recall of Model S sedans built before April 2016 in order to replace power steering bolts last Thursday. It informed customers over email it was a proactive move and that there were no accidents or injuries related to the issue, according to Reuters. Bolts, made by German supplier Bosch, in the power steering component can start to corrode after contact with certain types of road salt in colder climates. The carmaker said 123,000 Model S cars around the world have the bolts. "We have observed excessive corrosion in the power steering bolts, though only in very cold climates, particularly those that frequently use calcium or magnesium road salts, rather than sodium chloride (table salt)," Tesla wrote in an email to customers.If the bolts fail, drivers would still be able to steer the vehicle, they would just have to use more force "due to loss or reduction of power assist," Tesla wrote. According to Tesla, the retrofit takes about an hour. The company said it would inform owners once the retrofit is available in their area. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tesla recalling 123,000 Model S sedans worldwide2. Power steering bolts corroding due to road salt in colder climates3. Driver turning Model S without power steering4. The retrofit takes about an hourVOICEOVER (in English): "Tesla voluntarily issued its largest recall ever of 123,000 Model S sedans worldwide built before April 2016 in order to replace bolts in the power steering component.""Bolts in the power steering component can start to corrode after contact with certain types of road salt in colder climates, particularly calcium or magnesium road salts."  "Tesla said that If the bolts fail, drivers would still be able to steer the vehicle, they would just have to use more force 'due to loss or reduction of power assist.'" "According to Tesla, the retrofit takes about an hour. The company said it would inform owners once the retrofit is available in their area." SOURCES: Reuters, The Vergehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-recall/tesla-voluntarily-recalls-early-model-s-vehicles-over-power-steering-bolts-idUSKBN1H5381https://www.theverge.com/2018/3/29/17177888/tesla-recall-model-s-size-power-steering***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 12:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/02/3581905/3581905_17FA1CF7ECC549F0AA09A25BCF04AEFB_180402_3581905_Tesla_voluntarily_issues_its_largest_recall_over_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C7C/152/C7C15203EF094E80BD4664A9482889CA_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Tesla, Tesla Model S recall, Tesla power steering bolt recall, Tesla voluntary recall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3581863</guid>
      <title>Judge rules coffee sold in California requires cancer warning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA California judge has ruled that consumers must be made aware that their coffee could cause cancer.The New York Times reports that a lawsuit filed by the nonprofit Council for Education and Research on Toxics claims Starbucks, Dunkin Donuts, and other coffee companies failed to warn consumers about acrylamide, a possible carcinogen produced when coffee beans are roasted.According to CBS, previous studies have shown that animals given high levels of the chemical in drinking water developed multiple tumors, but research on the effects on humans are inconclusive.Experts say the amount of acrylamide ingested in coffee is small compared to eating french fries and potato chips, or smoking tobacco.Many studies have even found probable evidence that coffee consumption is associated with a decreased risk of cancer.But because coffee companies failed to show that acrylamide posed no risk or added any health benefits, the judge ruled that coffee sold in California must carry a cancer warning label.Medical experts say a blanket warning linking coffee to cancer could cause unnecessary panic among the general public, especially since there is not enough evidence to suggest that this is in fact the case.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Roasting coffee beans produces possible carcinogen acrylamide2. High doses of Acrylamide caused multiple tumors in lab mice3. Coffee contains only small doses of acrylamide compared to other sources4. Cancer warning labels to be required on coffee sold in CaliforniaVOICEOVER (in English): "A lawsuit filed by a nonprofit organization claims coffee companies failed to warn about acrylamide, a possible carcinogen produced when coffee beans are roasted.""Previous studies have shown that animals given high levels of the chemical in drinking water developed multiple tumors, but research on the effects on humans are inconclusive.""Experts say the amount of acrylamide ingested in coffee is small compared to eating french fries and potato chips, or smoking tobacco.""But because coffee companies failed to show that acrylamide posed no risk or added any health benefits, the judge ruled that coffee sold in California must carry a cancer warning label."SOURCES: CBS, New York Times, Washington Post, American Cancer Societyhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/coffee-cancer-warning-science-acrylamide-risk/https://www.nytimes.com/2018/03/30/business/coffee-cancer-warning.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2018/03/29/coffee-must-carry-cancer-warning-california-judge-rules/?utm_term=.0c81156955a6https://www.cancer.org/cancer/cancer-causes/acrylamide.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 11:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/02/3581863/3581863_03FF79A611474F34AF2B1512506567F3_180402_3581863_Judge_rules_coffee_sold_in_California_requires_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/572/1E1/5721E16C9148450AB3C203A0BBD5DDFA_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, coffee, cancer warning, carcinogenic, acrylamide, cancer, carcinogen, toxic, coffee roasting, california coffee, california, proposition 65]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3581712</guid>
      <title>Taiwan and U.S. sign deal for annual missile shipment: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. and Taiwan have struck a deal worth $130.5 million for an annual shipment of anti-tank missiles, reports the Taipei Times.The arrangement will see the U.S. supply Taiwan with 460 TOW-2B Aero RF (radio frequency) anti tank missiles, the Taipei Times reports, citing a Taiwan Ministry of National Defence source. This will reportedly see the U.S. supply Taiwan with the missiles on a yearly basis from 2018 until 2024.The deal is part of a $1.83 billion arms sales package that Taiwan negotiated with the Obama administration in late 2015.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of missile and Taiwan2. Depiction of missile launch and tank3. Depiction of warhead detonation4. Depiction of tank explosionVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Taipei Times, Popular Mechanics, Reutershttp://www.taipeitimes.com/News/front/archives/2018/03/31/2003690383https://www.popularmechanics.com/military/weapons/a17654/watch-this-tow-2b-missile-pop-the-top-off-a-russian-tank-like-a-bottle-of-beer/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-taiwan-arms/obama-administration-authorizes-1-83-billion-arms-sale-to-taiwan-idUSKBN0TZ2C520151217***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 09:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/02/3581712/3581712_22A5679E80D04337A24B5E0CC743881F_180402_3581712_Taiwan_and_U_S__sign_deal_for_annual_missile_shi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/12E/CAB/12ECAB0B3BAF4CBFB6C77D21D5C37F3B_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tow missile, tow tank missile, tank buster missile, anti-tank missile, tow-2b, taiwan, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3581591</guid>
      <title>South Koreans will soon be able to use cryptocurrency as payment in 6,000 stores</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSouth Koreans are about to get a lot more options on where they can spend their hard-earned virtual currency.Korea JoongAng Daily reports that South Korean cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb recently partnered with a digital payment service operator to allow the widespread adoption of crypto payments.Barcodes built into mobile apps will allow consumers to pay for goods at physical stores using the cryptocurrencies they hold at the exchange, according to a news release from Bitcoin.The payment system is set to be available at 6,000 retail outlets around the country within the first half of the year, and could expand to 8,000 outlets by the end of 2018.On top of this, Bithumb also signed an agreement with a Korean travel website, allowing customers to book hotels and other accommodations via cryptocurrency.Virtual currencies are incredibly popular in South Korea. It's currently the third largest market for cryptocurrency after the U.S. and Japan.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb sign agreement with Korea Pay's Service2. Barcodes built into mobile app to make payments3. Crypto payments to be available in 6,000 to 8,000 outlets4. Bithumb partnership with Korean travel websiteVOICEOVER (in English): "South Korean cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb recently partnered with a digital payment service operator to allow the widespread adoption of crypto payments.""Barcodes built into mobile apps will allow consumers to pay for goods at physical stores using the cryptocurrencies they hold at the exchange.""The payment system is set to be available at 6,000 retail outlets around the country within the first half of the year, and could expand to 8,000 outlets by the end of 2018.""Bithumb has also signed an agreement with a Korean travel website, allowing customers to book hotels and other accommodations via cryptocurrency."SOURCES: Bitcoin, Korea JoongAng Daily, Korea Timeshttps://news.bitcoin.com/bithumb-launching-service-crypto-payments-physical-stores/http://koreajoongangdaily.joins.com/news/article/article.aspx?aid=3046108http://koreatimes.co.kr/www/news/tech/2018/03/129_246252.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 07:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/02/3581591/3581591_FB428B2331CC491C8CBF8AA144C980B7_180402_3581591_South_Koreans_will_soon_be_able_to_use_cryptocur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A48/F9C/A48F9CD936FF46D5B44EDAB8EDFA39E2_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, crypto payment, south korea, cryptocurrency payment, bitcoin, bitcoin payment, bithumb, cryptocurrency, exchange, korea pays services]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3582570</guid>
      <title>China builds large rainmaking system in Tibetan plateau</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is embarking on its largest weather-modification project yet, as it attempts to bring more rain to the Tibetan mountains.Climate models predict that the Tibetan plateau, which holds Asia's biggest freshwater reserve, could see severe drought due to decreased rainfall and rising temperatures, according to the South China Morning Post.In response, the state-owned China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation is building combustion chambers to turn solid fuel into silver iodide for cloud seeding, and placing them on steep mountainsides.Winds help produce an upward draft that sweeps the particles into the clouds, where they then induce rain or snow.The plan is to bring precipitation over an area spanning 1.6 million square kilometers, or three times the size of Spain. Five hundred chambers have so far been deployed in Tibet and Xinjiang.The science behind the project may not be groundbreaking, but it's the first time such a large scale use of the technology will be attempted.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Possible drought in the Tibetan plateau2. Combustion chambers burning solid fuel to produce silver iodide3. Silver iodide seeds clouds to produce rain or snow4. Plan to produce rainfall over an area 3 times the size of SpainVOICEOVER (in English): "Climate models predict that the Tibetan plateau, which holds Asia's biggest freshwater reserve, could see severe drought due to decreased rainfall and rising temperatures.""In response, China is building combustion chambers to turn solid fuel into silver iodide for cloud seeding, and placing them on steep mountainsides.""Winds help produce an upward draft that sweeps the particles into the clouds, where they then induce rain or snow.""The plan is to bring precipitation over an area spanning 1.6 million square kilometers, or three times the size of Spain. Five hundred chambers have so far been deployed in Tibet and Xinjiang."SOURCES: South China Morning Posthttp://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2138866/china-needs-more-water-so-its-building-rain-making-network-three***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 10:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/03/3582570/3582570_98A8B03148A34B6F8391C81783BD6A77_180403_3582570_China_builds_large_rainmaking_system_in_Tibetan__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/762/BEA/762BEAA439544D9DA8F6D530BB8613E3_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cloud seeding, tibet, tibetan plateau, water reserve, rainmaker, rain making, drought, rainfall, artificial rain, weather modification]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3582552</guid>
      <title>New studies link cell phone radiation with cancers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo new studies have found a correlation between cell phone radiation and cancer in lab rats. Smartphones emit non-ionizing radiation, measured in radio-frequency, RF, energy. It's accepted high doses of ionizing radiation, such as X-rays, CT scans and nuclear power plants cause cancer, according to Scientific American.  However, it's still unclear if long-term exposure to non-ionizing radiation can cause cancer. Researchers from the U.S. National Toxicology Program tested 3,000 rats and mice of both sexes for two years, while European scientists at the Ramazzini Institute in Italy studied 2,500 rats from fetal stage to death. The studies found that prolonged exposure to even low levels of RF radiation cause male rats to develop rare heart tumors called schwannoma, which affects a neuron called a Schwann cell.In the Ramazzini study, researchers also found a weaker link between RF exposure and glial cell cancer in the brain of female rats.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. RF radiation causing cancers in lab rats2. Cell phones emitting varying levels of RF radiation3. RF radiation causing male rats to develop heart schwannomas4. RF radiation causing female rats to develop glial cell cancer VOICEOVER (in English): "Two new studies have found a correlation between cell phone radiation and cancer in lab rats. Researchers from the U.S. National Toxicology Program tested 3,000 rats and mice of both sexes for two years, while European scientists at the Ramazzini Institute in Italy studied 2,500 rats from fetal stage to death."  "Smartphones emit non-ionizing radiation, measured in radio-frequency energy. Cell phones and wireless devices emit RF radiation continually, with dose intensity varying with distance from the body.""The studies found that prolonged exposure to even low levels of RF radiation cause male rats to develop rare heart tumors called schwannoma, which affects a neuron called a Schwann cell.""In the Ramazzini study, researchers also found a weaker link between RF exposure and glial cell cancer in the brain of female rats." SOURCES: Scientific American, Quartzhttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/new-studies-link-cell-phone-radiation-with-cancer/https://qz.com/1203070/we-still-dont-know-if-cell-phones-cause-cancer-or-not/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 10:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/03/3582552/3582552_64B19531186C458E83ABD2AF6CE80F1C_180403_3582552_New_studies_link_cell_phone_radiation_with_cance_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/608/D41/608D41C3F44D49898C1E9AFCF9852FD6_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cell phone cancer, cell phone cancer link, cell phone cancer study, radio frequency energy, radio frequency radiation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3582426</guid>
      <title>More space debris to fall to Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMore space debris is expected to fall re-enter Earth's atmosphere this week following the plummet of China's Tiangong-1.According to Space.com, the rocket body of an Indian Polar Satellite Launch Vehicle is expected to fall to Earth around April 3. Part of a European Space Agency satellite called Ariane-5 is also expected to drop to Earth on the same day.Fortune reports that Kazakh spacecrafts Flock 2E-3 and 2E-6 are expected to plummet to Earth on Wednesday and on Friday this week.  Popular Science reports that 200 parts of space debris fell to Earth in 2014, and 400 fell in 2016.  Most land in the Pacific Ocean.The only person known to be hit by falling debris is Lottie Williams. According to NPR, she was walking in a park in Tulsa, Oklahoma in 1997 when a 6-inch chunk of metal travelling at a low speed struck her from behind. Scientists believe it came from a NASA second-stage Delta II rocket.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of 2. Depiction of falling spacecraft re-entering the atmosphere 3. Depiction of falling space debris stats from 2014 and 20164. Depiction of Lottie Williams being struck by spacecraft debris in 1997 VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Space.com, the rocket body of an Indian Polar Satellite Launch Vehicle is expected to fall to Earth around April 3. It weights 901 kg.""Part of a European Space Agency satellite is also expected to drop to Earth on the same day.""Fortune reports that Kazakh spacecrafts Flock 2E-3 and 2E-6 are expected to plummet to Earth on Wednesday and on Friday this week.""Popular Science reports that 200 parts of space debris fell to Earth in 2014, and 400 fell in 2016.""Most land in the Pacific Ocean.""The only person known to be hit by falling debris is Lottie Williams.""She was walking in a park in Tulsa, Oklahoma in 1997 when she was struck by a 6-inch chunk of metal travelling at a low speed from behind.""Scientists believe it came from a NASA second-stage Delta rocket."SOURCES: Space, Fortune, Popular Science, Wired, NPRhttps://www.space.com/40179-china-tiangong-1-next-big-space-junk-crash.htmlhttp://fortune.com/2018/04/02/china-space-station-tiangong-2/http://fortune.com/2018/04/02/china-space-station-tiangong-2/https://www.popsci.com/space-junk-debris-fallshttps://www.wired.com/2009/01/jan-22-1997-heads-up-lottie-its-space-junk/https://www.npr.org/2011/09/21/140641362/where-falling-satellite-lands-is-anyones-guess***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 08:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/03/3582426/3582426_5F65BF75DA7148698E5E03ED9D40F71A_180403_3582426_More_space_debris_to_fall_to_Earth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F02/2B7/F022B73867134E37BC94BB91A8109186_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tiangong-1, space junk falling to Earth, space junk 2018, space debris falling, atmosphere, atmospheric reentry]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3582409</guid>
      <title>Researchers find 29 human footprints in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHumans may have been stomping around Canada as early as 13,000 years ago  and they left footprints.According to a study published in the journal PLOS-ONE, researchers discovered an ancient human footprint along the coast of Canada's Calvert Island in 2014, before then uncovering 28 more in subsequent excavations.The well-preserved prints are believed to have been made by two barefoot adults and one child some 13,000 years ago.The foot impressions were left on light brown clay, which was filled in and preserved by sand, thick gravel, and another layer of clay.The findings lend support to the theory that ancient humans travelled from Asia to North America near the end of the last ice age by following a route along the Pacific coastline.Fossilized tracks are themselves rare, but these particular ones have also earned the distinction of being the oldest known human footprints found in North America.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Twenty-nine ancient human footprints discovered on Calvert Island, Canada2. Footprints believed to belong to two adults and one child3. Footprints possibly covered and preserved by sand, thick gravel, clay4. Theory of ancient humans going from Asia to North AmericaVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers discovered an ancient human footprint along the coast of Canada's Calvert Island in 2014, before then uncovering 28 more in subsequent excavations.""The well-preserved prints are believed to have been made by two barefoot adults and one child some 13,000 years ago.""The foot impressions were left on light brown clay, which was filled in and preserved by sand, thick gravel, and another layer of clay.""The findings lend support to the theory that ancient humans travelled from Asia to North America near the end of the last ice age by following a route along the Pacific coastline."SOURCES: PLOS-ONE, New York Timeshttp://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0193522https://www.nytimes.com/2018/03/28/science/footprints-oldest-north-america.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 07:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/03/3582409/3582409_1356FB12A8F94E7AB76E3A009B4A28D7_180403_3582409_Researchers_find_29_human_footprints_in_Canada_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E25/4DA/E254DA55E90A432F9ED0414860D7E783_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, footprints, oldest footprints, human footprints, preserved footprints, calvert island, ice age, ancient migration, canada, human migration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3582400</guid>
      <title>Radar can pinpoint mosquitoes from 1 mile away: Chinese scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[New radar technology can track the flight path of a mosquito from a mile away, claim Chinese scientists.The device uses technology from Chinaâ€™s missile defence system, reports the South China Morning Post, citing an unidentified researcher. A prototype is being tested at the Beijing Institute of Technology.The device can reportedly identify which species a mosquito belongs to as well as its gender, flight speed and direction.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/03/3582400/3582400_6B82D7197E9B4ED398FCE91E61690285_180403_3582400_More_space_debris_to_fall_to_Earth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E25/4DA/E254DA55E90A432F9ED0414860D7E783_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,News,tiangong-1,space junk falling to Earth,space junk 2018,space debris falling,atmosphere,atmospheric reentry]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3582252</guid>
      <title>Plastic straw pollution drawing global attention</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMunicipalities around the world are increasingly cracking down on plastic pollution, especially single-use straws. According to the National Park Services, Americans use about 500 million straws a day which works out to 1.5 straws a person every 24 hours, according to the Tampa Bay Times. In the U.K., 8.5 billion plastic straws are used each year, according to the Telegraph. Straws are difficult to recycle and usually end up in landfills or being incinerated, but they are increasingly clogging up waterways as well. Cities worldwide are increasingly discouraging the use of straws with some even outright banning them. Others have vowed to phase out plastics over the next decades. Plastic straw alternatives have also started to gain in popularity. They are made from materials like bamboo, metal, glass, paper, potato or corn paste.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People using single-use plastic straws2. Straws end up in landfills, incinerators or waterways3. Some cities have banned straws, while others are planning to in the future4. Straws can be made with alternative materialsVOICEOVER (in English): "Cities are increasingly cracking down on single-use plastic straws.  Americans use about 500 million straws a day which works out to 1.5 straws a citizen every 24 hours. In the U.K., 8.5 billion plastic straws are used each year.""Straws are difficult to recycle and usually end up in landfills or being incinerated, but they are increasingly clogging up waterways and oceans as well." "Cities worldwide are increasingly discouraging the use of straws with some even outright banning them. Others have vowed to phase out plastics over the next decades." "Plastic straw alternatives have also started to gain in popularity. They are made from materials like bamboo, metal, glass, paper, potato or corn paste."   SOURCES: Tampa Bay Times, Telegraphhttp://www.tampabay.com/news/environment/Plastic-straws-Everyone-uses-them-and-that-s-the-problem_166783992https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/04/01/final-straw-drinking-plastic-way/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 04:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/03/3582252/3582252_C7EB048F8ADE43CDAB2AAB72C4B7F788_180403_3582252_Plastic_straw_pollution_drawing_global_attention_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/748/EDE/748EDE934C1141B6B92E340BE8E4D0FD_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, plastics pollution, plastic straw pollution, plastic straw ban, single-use plastic straw, single-use plastic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3583282</guid>
      <title>Dark patches on Venus could be signs of microbial life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study theorizes that the dark patches on Venus may be a sign that there's microbial life in the planet's lower atmosphere. According to a paper published in the journal Astrobiology, climate models suggest Venus had a habitable climate and liquid water for 2 billion years, before a runaway greenhouse gas effect raised surface temperatures and turned the atmosphere toxic.The research suggests that microorganisms may be living in the planet's lower cloud layer, which has a stable temperature and more Earth-like atmospheric pressure.Dark patches on Venus could be microbial blooms made of sulfuric acid and other light-absorbing particles, which can persist for days while changing shape and contrast.Certain bacteria on Earth can survive in high altitudes after being swept into the atmosphere; others have also been known to thrive in extremely harsh environments.Thus far, the probes that have explored Venus have been incapable of distinguishing between organic and inorganic particles.So until a new contraption gets there, no one knows for sure if life does exist on the hottest planet in the solar system.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Venus' runaway greenhouse effect2. Possible microbial life in Venus' lower to middle cloud layer3. Dark patches continuously changing shape and contrast, could be microbial blooms4. Depiction of similar bacteria on EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Climate models suggest Venus had a habitable climate and liquid water for 2 billion years, before a runaway greenhouse gas effect raised surface temperatures and turned the atmosphere toxic.""New research now suggests that microorganisms may be living in the planet's lower cloud layer, which has a stable temperature and more Earth-like atmospheric pressure.""Dark patches on Venus could be microbial blooms made of sulfuric acid and other light-absorbing particles, which can persist for days while changing shape and contrast.""Certain bacteria on Earth can survive in high altitudes after being swept into the atmosphere; others have also been known to thrive in extremely harsh environments."SOURCES: Astrobiology,  University of Wisconsin-Madisonhttps://www.liebertpub.com/doi/full/10.1089/ast.2017.1783https://phys.org/news/2018-03-life-adrift-clouds-venus.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 09:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/04/3583282/3583282_08D0892FF6FE40388051BF11EBAB357D_180404_3583282_Dark_patches_on_Venus_could_be_signs_of_microbia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3E7/805/3E78052CD7B148ED89932BF537F3ABE1_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, venus, life on venus, space, life in space, dark patches, venus dark patches, extremophiles, bacteria, microorganisms, microbes, microbial bloom, microbial life, signs of life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3583220</guid>
      <title>Shooter opens fire at YouTube headquarters, injures 3 before taking her own life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA woman opened fire at YouTube headquarters in San Bruno on Tuesday afternoon, wounding three people before taking her own life. According to law enforcement sources, the shooting was a domestic dispute, with the shooter targeting someone at the campus, according to the L.A. Times. The shooting took place at around 12:46 p.m. in an outdoor cafe on the grounds. It's still unclear if the attacker worked at YouTube. San Bruno Police Chief Ed Barberini told press on Tuesday that one person, believed to be the shooter, was found dead of a self-inflicted gunshot wound, according to the L.A. Times. Three victims were transported to San Francisco General Hospital with gunshot wounds. A 27-year-old woman is in fair condition, a 32-year-old woman is in serious condition  and a 36-year-old man is in critical condition, hospital officials said, according to SFGate. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of YouTube headquarters in San Bruno2. Depiction of shooter entering YouTube campus3. Depiction of shooter firing in outdoor cafe area4. Depiction of police on scene at YouTube headquartersVOICEOVER (in English): "A woman opened fire at YouTube headquarters in San Bruno on Tuesday afternoon, wounding three people before taking her own life." "According to law enforcement sources, the shooting was a domestic dispute, with the shooter targeting someone at the campus.""The shooting took place at around 12:46 p.m. in an outdoor cafe on the grounds. It's still unclear if the attacker worked at YouTube." "Three victims were transported to San Francisco General Hospital with gunshot wounds. A 27-year-old woman is in fair condition, a 32-year-old woman is in serious condition and a 36-year-old man is in critical condition."SOURCES: SFGate, LA Times, OC Registerhttps://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Police-respond-to-reports-of-possible-shooting-at-12802771.phphttp://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-youtube-shooter-20180403-story.htmlhttps://www.ocregister.com/2018/04/03/police-active-shooter-at-youtube-headquarters-in-northern-california/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 08:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/04/3583220/3583220_E17060D51B6949B3B3D59F5E453E76C3_180404_3583220_Shooter_opens_fire_at_YouTube_headquarters__inju_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AF6/3DB/AF63DB9564164EC7B0AAC3AA6DB71ABD_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, YouTube HQ shooting, YouTube headquarters shooting, YouTube shooting, YouTube]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3583163</guid>
      <title>Hubble telescope finds most distant star ever seen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers have sighted the outermost star the in known universe.Icarus, or LS1, is 9 billion years from Earth. Hubble saw it because of gravitational lensing, where distant star light is bent and magnified via the gravity of a passing galaxy. What was sighted came from a time when the universe was 30% of its current age. The star is believed to be a luminous blue supergiant, similar in size to our sun, but twice as hot. Researchers knew it wasn't a supernova because it wasn't exploding.Astronomers also tested its cluster for a dark matter theory that posits primordial black holes constituted much of the early universe, according to NASA. That wasn't shown however, as the Hubble telescope would have observed different light patterns from the star if black holes passed in front of Icarus.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of how Hubble telescope sighted Icarus 2. Depiction of Icarus and the sun3. Depiction of Icarus with black holes4. Depiction of Hubble observing IcarusVOICEOVER (in English): "Icarus, or LS1, is 9 billion years from Earth.""Hubble saw it because of gravitational lensing, where distant star light is bent and magnified via the gravity of a passing galaxy.""What was sighted came from a time when the universe was at 30% of its current age.""The star is believed to be a luminous blue supergiant, similar in size to our sun, but twice as hot.""Researchers knew it wasn't a supernova because it wasn't exploding.""Astronomers also tested its cluster for a dark matter theory.""This posits that primordial black holes constituted much of the early universe.""This wasn't shown however, as the Hubble telescope would have observed different light patterns from the star if black holes passed in front of Icarus."SOURCES: NASA, Hubble Space Telescope, Space.comhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2018/hubble-uncovers-the-farthest-star-ever-seenhttp://www.spacetelescope.org/news/heic1807/https://www.space.com/40171-cosmic-alignment-reveals-most-distant-star-yet.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/04/3583163/3583163_E6F0141BFC0D466F84E3AC8C170AD50D_180404_3583163_Hubble_telescope_finds_most_distant_star_ever_se_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/106/643/1066434E853B481DA05B81BB63937A5D_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, icarus, hubble telescope, ls1, nasa, ls-1, farthest star ever, dark matter, dark matter theory, black hole, primordial black hole, esa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3583089</guid>
      <title>MIT researchers develop imaging system that peers through fog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMIT researchers have developed a new imaging system that can estimate the distance of objects obscured by fog. One of the main challenges to the development of self-driving navigation systems that use visible light is their inability to handle misty or foggy driving conditions. The system uses a time-of-flight camera, which emits short laser bursts at objects and then counts how long it takes for the light to bounce back. Fog normally scatters laser light, which is problematic for autonomous vehicles. But thanks to an algorithm developed by the scientists, the system can find patterns in the scattered light to calculate distance.  Researchers tested the system in fog much denser than cars would encounter in the real world. The team from MIT Media Lab's Camera Culture Group found that the system performed even better than human vision.  The goal is to integrate the system into autonomous vehicles so that even in bad weather, self-driving cars can avoid obstacles.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Autonomous vehicle driving through fog2. The imaging system uses a time-of-flight camera3. View from autonomous vehicle driving through fog4. Self-driving car dodging obstacles in bad weatherVOICEOVER (in English): "MIT researchers have developed an imaging system that can peer through fog. One of the main challenges to the development of self-driving navigation systems that use visible light is their inability to handle misty or foggy driving conditions." "The system uses a time-of-flight camera, which emits short laser bursts at objects and then counts how long it takes for the light to bounce back." "Fog normally scatters laser light, which is problematic for autonomous vehicles. But thanks to an algorithm developed by the scientists, the system can find patterns in the scattered light to calculate distance."  "The goal is to eventually integrate the system into autonomous vehicles so that even in bad weather, self-driving cars can avoid obstacles."  SOURCES: MIT, CNBChttp://news.mit.edu/2018/depth-sensing-imaging-system-can-peer-through-fog-0321https://www.cnbc.com/2018/03/31/mit-developed-imaging-technology-that-can-see-through-fog.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 05:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/04/3583089/3583089_F88E4E7217EF469DA0DA7D2D83D6CA76_180404_3583089_MIT_researchers_develop_imaging_system_that_peer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7E5/FB0/7E5FB06E65904D6AA7D1B04E1DB151BA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, MIT self driving car, MIT self driving imaging system, MIT autonomous imaging system, MIT imaging system fog]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3584133</guid>
      <title>China's first home-built aircraft carrier to carry out maiden sea trial</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBeijing is prepping to get its first domestically-produced aircraft carrier started on sea trials after its unveiling a year ago.The South China Morning Post reports that China's conventionally powered Type 001A aircraft carrier was made using a special Chinese steel, and can carry up to 48 aircraft  eight more than the Liaoning.The ship is set to embark on its maiden sea trial in the northeastern Bohai Sea, just before the PLA Navy's 60th anniversary celebrations on April 23.Basic functions to be tested include power, damage control, radar, and communications systems. The ship may just circle the bay for the trial, but a longer two- to three-day voyage is possible if no issues arise.Unlike the Liaoning aircraft carrier, which is designed to operate independently, the Type 001A is meant to sail with several other vessels as part of a battle group.Getting the ship combat ready will likely take some time, but if all goes as planned, the as yet unnamed carrier might be joining the navy as early as 2019.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of China's Type 001A aircraft carrier 2. Location and approximate date of first Type 001A sea trial3. Basic functions to be checked during trial4. Type 001A designed to be part of a battle groupVOICEOVER (in English): "China's conventionally powered Type 001A aircraft carrier was made using a special Chinese steel, and can carry up to 48 aircraft  eight more than the Liaoning.""The ship is set to embark on its maiden sea trial in the northeastern Bohai Sea, just before the PLA Navy's 60th anniversary celebrations on April 23.""Basic functions to be tested include power, damage control, radar, and communications systems. The ship may just circle the bay for the trial, but a longer two- to three-day voyage is possible if no issues arise.""Unlike the Liaoning aircraft carrier, which is designed to operate independently, the Type 001A is meant to sail with several other vessels as part of a battle group."SOURCES: South China Morning Posthttp://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2139974/chinas-first-home-grown-aircraft-carrier-set-carry-out***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 15:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/05/3584133/3584133_F437058D5F1A4E698FAAB69418CF1EFC_180405_3584133_China_s_first_home_built_aircraft_carrier_to_car_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/184/5EA/1845EA75A812412B96579D8F5D3C4DB8_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China, aircraft carrier, Type 001A, Chinese aircraft carrier, sea trials, maiden voyage, China navy, PLA, Liaoning, Shenyang J-15, fighter jets, helicopters]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3583834</guid>
      <title>Phone hacking activity detected in Washington: Homeland Security</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. government has detected "anomalous" activity from telephone spying equipment in Washington.According to the Associated Press, the Department of Homeland Security detected abnormal activity from international mobile subscriber identity-catchers (IMSI catchers). The DHS did not identify the source of or number of devices.These devices act as a fake cellular tower and attract signals from the target's phone away from the real network. The technology is also used by U.S. intelligence and law enforcement.They can be used to listen in on phone calls, track user location data and read messages. According to the Associated Press, some can infect devices with malware.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of public area with people on cell phones2. Depiction showing how IMSI catchers work3. Depiction showing what information can be obtained via an IMSI catcher4. Depiction of different kinds of IMSI catchersVOICEOVER (in English):  "According to the Associated Press, the Department of Homeland Security detected abnormal activity from phone-hacking technology in Washington D.C.""The department did not identify the source of or number of devices.""Known as international mobile subscriber identity-catchers, or IMSI catcher, the equipment acts as a fake cellular tower.""It attracts signals from the target's phone away from the real network." "The technology is reportedly used by U.S. intelligence and law enforcement.""IMSI catchers can be used to listen in on phone calls, track user location data and read messages. "Reportedly, they can all be used to infect devices with malware.""The devices vary in size from a cell phone to a suitcase. Costs of the equipment reportedly run from $1,000 to to several hundred thousand."SOURCES: Associated Press, CNET,https://apnews.com/d716aac4ad744b4cae3c6b13dce12d7ehttps://www.cnet.com/news/homeland-security-detected-phone-spying-devices-in-dc/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 08:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/05/3583834/3583834_77C5D8FF0F7143A2967EBC372171F702_180405_3583834_Phone_hacking_activity_detected_in_Washington__H_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4E5/CDF/4E5CDF61A3F84D56971B7651A215ED3D_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, imsi catchers, phone hacking, imsi catcher, police imsi catcher, ismi catcher washington, homeland security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3583802</guid>
      <title>Confusing soccer rules explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWhile the World Cup is approaching fast, some people still have a hard time figuring out some of the rules of this popular sport favoured by much of the world.A ball is out of play when the entire ball has crossed the touch-line, regardless of whether it is on the ground or in the air. The ball is in play when it rebounds off a match official, goal post, crossbar or corner flag post and remains in the field of play.If a foul is committed outside the penalty area, but continues inside the penalty area, the referee shall award a penalty kick.A player is "offside" when any part of the player's head, body, or feet is in the opponent's side of the field. A player is also "offside" if he or she is nearer to the opponent's goal line than the ball, and nearer to the opponent's goal line than the second to last opponent, or, if the referee determines that you have participated in area of active play.FIFA has a list of regulations available on their website.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Explanation of out of play and in play.2. Explanation of a foul continues into the penalty area.3. Basic explanation of offside.4. Other examples of offside.VOICEOVER (in English): "A ball is out of play when the entire ball has crossed the touch-line, regardless of whether it is on the ground or in the air. The ball is in play when it rebounds off a match official, goal post, crossbar or corner flag post and remains in the field of play.""If a foul is committed outside the penalty area, but continues inside the penalty area, the referee shall award a penalty kick.""A player is "offside" when any part of the player's head, body, or feet is in the opponent's side of the field.""A player is also "offside" if he or she is nearer to the opponent's goal line than the ball, and nearer to the opponent's goal line than the second to last opponent, or, if the referee determines that you have participated in area of active play."SOURCES: http://www.fifa.com/about-fifa/official-documents/law-regulations/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 07:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/05/3583802/3583802_6842C8E1F60A489EB8F15EBD09D5F266_180405_3583802_Confusing_soccer_rules_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/81A/187/81A187E4A1B54CD4AB226D544EED956F_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3583761</guid>
      <title>'Nightmare bacteria' spreading across U.S. hospitals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN"Nightmare bacteria" that are resistant to almost all antibiotics are spreading across U.S. hospitals, federal health officials said on Tuesday. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention set up a countrywide lab network in 2016 to help hospitals diagnose infections quickly in order to stop them from spreading, according to Scientific American. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention found 221 cases in 2017 of a rare breed of antibiotic-resistant bacteria. One in four germ samples analyzed by the CDC lab network found special genes that allow them to spread resistance to other bacteria. The CDC also said in 11 percent of people tested carried these superbugs without displaying any symptoms.People infected with these bacteria spread the disease to other people in the hospital, such as patients, doctors and nurses. These people can then in turn act as silent carriers and infect others even if they don't become sick.   According to the CDC, every year about two million Americans are sickened from antibiotic-resistant infections, while more than 23,000 patients are killed.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of antibiotic-resistant bacteria in hospitals2. CDC found 221 antibiotic-resistant bacteria cases, and found one in 4 samples had special genes that spread resistance3. 11 percent of people tested carried superbug without displaying symptoms4. Representation of infected patient spreading superbug to other peopleVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, 'nightmare bacteria' that are resistant to almost all antibiotics are spreading across U.S. hospitals." "The CDC found 221 cases in 2017 of a rare breed of antibiotic-resistant bacteria. One in four germ samples analyzed by the CDC found special genes that allow them to spread resistance to other bacteria." "The CDC also said in 11 percent of people tested carried these superbugs without displaying any symptoms.""People infected with these bacteria spread the disease to other people in the hospital, such as patients, doctors and nurses. These people can then in turn act as silent carriers and infect others even if they don't become sick."   SOURCES: CDC, Scientific American, NBC Newshttps://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/67/wr/mm6713e1.htm?s_cid=mm6713e1_ehttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/nightmare-bacteria-widespread-in-u-s-hospitals/https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/nightmare-bacteria-are-trying-spread-u-s-cdc-says-n862436***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 06:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/05/3583761/3583761_D9B072EFFE7245D3A862FBC549E01ABD_180405_3583761__Nightmare_bacteria__spreading_across_U_S__hospi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/27F/E56/27FE5608915449BBB9A9AD0ABE68F9AE_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nightmare bacteria, antibiotic-resistant bacteria, superbugs, hospital superbugs, hospital antibiotic-resistant bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3584885</guid>
      <title>Older people can still produce brain cells even at 79, study says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study claims the brain continues to produce hundreds of new neurons daily, even in older people, in a process called neurogenesis. Scientists from the University of Columbia published their results in the journal Cell Stem Cell on Thursday. Lead researcher Dr. Maura Boldrini and her team examined the brains of 28 dead people age 14 to 79 to see if aging affects neuron production, according to the L.A. Times. The team looked for the presence of neurons in different stages of development, including stem cells, intermediate progenitor cells, immature neurons and new neurons. The study only looked at the hippocampus, partly because previous studies have shown that part of the brain is one of the few areas that can make new neurons into adulthood, according to the L.A. Times. Boldrini and her team found similar numbers of neural progenitor cells and immature neurons, regardless of age. The team concluded that the human brain can produce neurons even as people grow old. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People of various ages producing neurons2. Brain being examined for neuron cells3. The team looking for presence of neurons in different stages of development4. Researchers finding similar numbers of neural progenitor cells and immature neurons, regardless of ageVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study claims the brain continues to produce hundreds of new neurons daily, even in older people, in a process called neurogenesis." "Scientists from the University of Columbia examined the brains of 28 dead people who were 14 to 79 at the age of death to see if aging affects neuron production.""The team looked for the presence of neurons in different stages of development, including stem cells, intermediate progenitor cells, immature neurons and new neurons." "Researchers found similar numbers of neural progenitor cells and immature neurons, regardless of age. This led them to conclude the human brain can produce neurons even in old age."SOURCES: LA Times, Forbeshttp://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-new-brain-cells-20180405-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/07/3584885/3584885_42A2A9A77F6A4295ACB50EEA00446906_180407_3584885_Older_people_can_still_produce_brain_cells_even__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8BA/36A/8BA36ACA2E5F4D7D9EEDB516C449F297_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, neuron, neuron production, adult neuron production, neuron production older people]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3584722</guid>
      <title>Deadly coral toxin released during home fish tank cleaning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn entire family nearly died after the world's second deadliest poison leaked into their home during a recent fish tank cleaning.The Washington Post reports that many home aquariums not only hold exotic fish, but also zoanthid corals, which release a highly toxic substance called palytoxin when provoked.Palytoxin is lethal when ingested or injected into the bloodstream, but can also be dangerous when airborne.According to a report from the Marine Aquarium Societies of North America, scrubbing zoanthids can trigger them to spew the toxin, which spreads as an aerosol and endangers those who inhale it. Vapors released when the coral is boiled in water or broken may also cause damage.Breathing in the toxin typically causes flu-like symptoms that may include a high fever, muscle pain, coughing, difficulty breathing, and eye irritation.Experts recommend handling the deadly corals in a well-ventilated space while wearing gloves, eye protection, and face masks.Pets and small children should also be kept away from any water or substance that has come in contact with zoanthids.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of toxic corals in home aquariums2. Palytoxin lethal when ingested or injected3. Depiction of coral releasing palytoxin when scrubbed, boiled, or broken4. Symptoms of palytoxin poisoningVOICEOVER (in English): "Many home aquariums not only hold exotic fish, but also zoanthid corals, which release a highly toxic substance called palytoxin when provoked.""Palytoxin is lethal when ingested or injected into the bloodstream, but can also be dangerous when airborne.""Scrubbing zoanthids can trigger them to spew the toxin, which spreads as an aerosol and endangers those who inhale it. Vapors released when the coral is boiled in water or broken may also cause damage.""Breathing in the toxin typically causes flu-like symptoms that may include a high fever, muscle pain, coughing, difficulty breathing, and eye irritation."SOURCES: Washington Post, Marine Aquarium Societies of North America, Fox Newshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/speaking-of-science/wp/2017/07/28/homegrown-coral-reefs-are-beautiful-and-potentially-dangerous/?utm_term=.a3cbdeeed8d3http://masna.org/masna-education/palytoxin/http://www.foxnews.com/health/2018/04/05/man-warns-pet-owners-after-fish-tank-releases-second-deadliest-poison-hospitalizes-10.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 11:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/06/3584722/3584722_26ABD912FE5D4E12BAE938F24BBA45E8_180406_3584722_Deadly_coral_toxin_released_during_home_fish_tan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0FF/155/0FF155D03208491FB8AB6C8D5878FC20_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, toxic coral, palytoxin, deadly toxin, deadly coral, poisonous coral, toxin, toxic substance, zoanthid, palythoa, fish tank, home aquarium, aquarium]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3584622</guid>
      <title>Dozens of dinosaur tracks unearthed on Scottish coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFantastically large beasts stomped around the Scottish coast millions of years ago, and very literally made their mark on Earth.According to a study published in the Scottish Journal of Geology, researchers uncovered around 50 dinosaur tracks in a tidal area on Scotland's Isle of Skye.The prints were made by carnivorous two-legged theropods  primitive cousins of the T-rex that were five to six meters long and weighed about a ton.A set of tracks unearthed earlier in 2015 had belonged to sauropods, which were long-necked plant-eating dinosaurs related to the Brontosaurus.Both sets of footprints date back 170 million years to the Middle Jurassic period. They were likely made in muddy, shallow water and washed over by sediments, which solidified and preserved them.The Mid-Jurassic was a critical time for dino evolution, but fossil evidence from this time period is rare, making the footprint discovery a veritable treasure trove of information for scientists studying the era.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 50 dinosaur footprints uncovered on Isle of Skye in Scotland2. Footprints belonged to carnivorous theropods3. Tracks found in 20154. Dinosaur tracks date back to Middle Jurassic periodVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers have uncovered around 50 dinosaur tracks in a tidal area on Scotland's Isle of Skye.""The prints were made by carnivorous two-legged theropods  primitive cousins of the T-rex that were five to six meters long and weighed about a ton.""A set of tracks unearthed earlier in 2015 had belonged to sauropods, which were long-necked plant-eating dinosaurs related to the Brontosaurus.""Both sets of footprints date back 170 million years to the Middle Jurassic period. They were likely made in muddy, shallow water and washed over by sediments, which solidified and preserved them."SOURCES: Scottish Journal of Geology, The Guardian, The Independenthttp://dx.doi.org/10.1144/sjg2017-016https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/apr/03/dinosaur-footprints-found-on-skyehttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/dinosaur-footprints-skye-scotland-island-isle-discovered-sauropod-theropod-a8285886.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 10:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/06/3584622/3584622_6044AAA6A1E443388B868DBF6507E651_180406_3584622_Dozens_of_dinosaur_tracks_unearthed_on_Scottish__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/17C/2AB/17C2AB4A08C4454A90A7DC28BBE2E9CA_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dinosaur footprints, dino footprints, dino footprint, dino tracks, dinosaurs, dinos, fossils, fossilized prints, middle jurassic, jurassic, theropods, sauropods, T-rex, brontosaurus, isle of skye]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3585073</guid>
      <title>Space hotel for tourists to launch in 2021</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANStartup Orion Span announced on Thursday it plans to build a space hotel to launch in late 2021 and start accepting guests by 2022. "We are launching the first-ever affordable luxury space hotel," said Orion Span founder and CEO Frank Bunger, at the Space 2.0 Summit in San Jose, California, according to Space.com. A 12-day stay at Aurora Station will begin at $9.5 million. The space station will be roughly the same size as a large private jet cabin. It will be 43.5 feet long by 14.1 feet wide and have a pressurized volume of 5,650 cubic feet, according to an Orion Span representative. It will orbit at an altitude of 200 miles.   For comparison, the International Space Station is 357 feet long and has an internal pressurized volume of 32,333 cubic feet. The Aurora Station will be able to accommodate four paying guests and two crewmembers. Orion Span is also planning for new modules to be added to the space hotel over time. Long-term, the company says it hopes to sell actual space in new modules for living or subleasing. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Aurora Station in orbit2. Aurora Station in space3. Aurora Station specs4. Aurora Station interiorVOICEOVER (in English): "Startup Orion Span announced on Thursday it plans to build a luxury space hotel to launch in late 2021 and start accepting guests by 2022." "A 12-day stay at Aurora Station will begin at $9.5 million. The space station will be roughly the same size as a large private jet cabin." "It will be 43.5 feet long by 14.1 feet wide and have a pressurized volume of 5,650 cubic feet. It will orbit at an altitude of 200 miles."   "The Aurora Station will be able to accommodate four paying guests and two crewmembers." SOURCES: Space.com, Forbeshttps://www.space.com/40207-space-hotel-launch-2021-aurora-station.htmlhttps://www.forbes.com/sites/jordilippemcgraw/2018/04/05/luxury-space-hotel-aurora-station-opening/#2e8b489c1eee***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 02:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/07/3585073/3585073_5CFBAE3876CF40E0B77D1D8162800A1B_180407_3585073_Space_hotel_for_tourists_to_launch_in_2021_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5A1/DDB/5A1DDBE0F3EC43BFB7F2A8DE1C234B25_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, luxury space hotel, Aurora Station space hotel, space tourists, Orion Span, space hotels, private space travel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3586697</guid>
      <title>RNA-based plant vaccine could supplant chemical pesticides</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANConventional pesticides are a double-edged sword that scientists are now seeking to replace with more natural RNA-based plant vaccines.The U.S. Department of Agriculture estimates that without pesticides, roughly 70 percent of the world's crops would be lost to pests. But such chemicals are toxic  killing insects but also affecting the rest of the environment.New research in the Plant Biology Journal details an approach that involves directly spraying plant leaves with an RNA-based vaccine. Developed in France and Finland, this inoculates against specific pests or pathogens.The vaccine triggers a process called RNA interference, which prevents invading RNA strands from carrying out their functions, thus causing the pest to die.RNA molecules in the vaccine do not negatively affect the host plant. The RNA also has the added benefit of being biodegradable because it breaks down quickly.Instead of chemical synthesis, scientists used a bacteria-eating virus called a bacteriophage to help generate the RNA.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Conventional pesticides crucial to crops, but full of toxic chemicals2. RNA-based vaccine developed to target specific pests3. Vaccine interferes with pest's RNA processes4. Vaccine biodegradable, doesn't accumulate in the environmentVOICEOVER (in English): "Without pesticides, roughly 70 percent of the world's crops would be lost to pests. But such chemicals are toxic  killing insects but also affecting the rest of the environment.""A new approach developed in Finland and France involves directly spraying plant leaves with an RNA-based vaccine that inoculates against specific pests or pathogens.""The vaccine triggers a process called RNA interference, which prevents invading RNA strands from carrying out their functions, thus causing the pest to die.""RNA molecules in the vaccine do not negatively affect the host plant. The RNA also has the added benefit of being biodegradable because it break down quickly."SOURCES: Plant Biology Journal, University of Helsinki, United States Department of Agriculturehttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/pbi.12904https://www.helsinki.fi/en/news/life-science/a-vaccine-for-edible-plants-a-new-plant-protection-method-on-the-horizonhttps://nifa.usda.gov/blog/global-scientists-meet-integrated-pest-management-idea-sharing***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 14:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/09/3586697/3586697_DDC91ADC5D77491AA888DD647A41F1A2_180409_3586697_RNA_based_plant_vaccine_could_supplant_chemical__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BA3/5D5/BA35D52D7A9240899527700D907EBFB0_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, pesticides, RNA vaccine, RNA pesticide, bio pesticide, pests, farm crops, farming, chemical pesticides, toxic chemicals, toxic pesticides]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3586658</guid>
      <title>Mozilla releases tool to make it harder for Facebook to track you online</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMozilla has released a Firefox tool called Facebook Container to stop the social networking site from tracking online habits outside Facebook's own site.  The extension isolates a user's Facebook identity into a separate browser tab making it harder for the site to track the user's activity on other websites using third-party cookies, according to a Mozilla blog post.  After installing the extension it will delete the user's Facebook cookies and log the user out of Facebook. The next time the user logs in, Facebook will open in a new blue-colored browser tab, or container tab. When using Facebook through the Mozilla extension, if the user clicks on a non-Facebook link or goes to a non-Facebook website in the URL bar, these pages load outside of the container. Clicking Facebook Share buttons on other browser tabs will load them within the Facebook Container. Mozilla warns that if people used their Facebook accounts to create an account or as logins to other apps, they may not be able to log in when using the extension.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People installing Facebook Container extension2. Installing the tool will delete Facebook cookies, log the user out of Facebook and open Facebook in separate tab3. Student using Facebook Container4. Clicking on share buttons on other browser tabs loads them in ContainerVOICEOVER (in English): "Mozilla has released a Firefox tool called Facebook Container that isolates your Facebook identity into a separate container, making it harder for the social networking site to track your activity on other websites using third-party cookies." "After installing the extension it will delete your Facebook cookies and log you out of Facebook. The next time you log in, Facebook will open in a new blue-colored browser tab, or container tab.""When using Facebook through the Mozilla extension, if you click on a non-Facebook link or go to a non-Facebook website in the URL bar, these pages load outside of the container." "Clicking Facebook Share buttons on other browser tabs will load them within the Facebook Container." SOURCES: Mozilla, USA Todayhttps://blog.mozilla.org/firefox/facebook-container-extension/https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2018/04/06/how-stop-facebook-recognizing-your-face-and-tracking-your-online-moves/493701002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 13:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/09/3586658/3586658_D93653080AE743ECBE3676A52D73731F_180409_3586658_Mozilla_releases_tool_to_make_it_harder_for_Face_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/399/0BC/3990BC8CBACE47F5B28F037092AB1654_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Mozilla Facebook Container, Facebook Container extension, Facebook tracking, third-party cookies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3586529</guid>
      <title>Dozens killed in suspected chemical attack in Syria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDozens of people were killed in suspected chemical gas attacks on the town of Douma near Damascus on Saturday.According to the U.S.-based Syrian American Medical Society, at least 48 people have died, while the Union of Medical Care and Relief Organizations said that 70 deaths have been confirmed, the BBC reports.The pro-opposition Ghouta Media Center said a helicopter dropped a barrel bomb containing Sarin gas. Rescue workers said hundreds of people were showing signs and symptoms consistent with exposure to an organophosphorus compound. One paramedic was quoted by the Guardian saying, "the attack was near bomb shelters and so it spread quickly in them. The gas was concentrated and in a place where people thought they were safe."The paramedic said many victims had expanded irises and loss of motor control, with a high number suffocating from the gas. Rescue workers said many victims' bodies remain uncollected because of further shelling, lingering toxic gas odor and lack of protective gear. Syrian state media has the denied chemical attacks, saying rebels in Douma were about to collapse and spreading false news. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of suspected gas attack2. Syrian helicopter carrying barrel bombs with Sarin gas3. Victims showing signs of chemical gas exposure4. Victims bodies cannot be retrieved due to shelling, gas and lack of protective gearVOICEOVER (in English): "Dozens of people were killed in suspected chemical gas attacks on the town of Douma near Damascus on Saturday.""Opposition media in Syria say a helicopter dropped a barrel bomb containing Sarin gas. According to the U.S.-based Syrian American Medical Society, at least 48 people have died, while the Union of Medical Care and Relief Organizations said that 70 deaths have been confirmed." "Rescue workers said hundreds of people were showing signs consistent with exposure to an organophosphorus compound. Workers said many victims had expanded irises and loss of motor control, while a high number were suffocating from the gas." "Rescue workers said many victims' bodies remain uncollected because of further shelling, lingering toxic gas odor and lack of protective gear." SOURCES: Guardian, BBChttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/apr/08/syrian-government-accused-of-chemical-attacks-on-civilians-in-eastern-ghoutahttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-43691291***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 10:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/09/3586529/3586529_F9E08D9AE6964CCBA9EC82E7F5D2F221_180409_3586529_Dozens_killed_in_suspected_chemical_attack_in_Sy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F49/737/F497370CABEB4A9C80E7329DCB2E5975_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Syria civil war, Syria chemical attack, Syria chemical gas attack, Douma chemical gas attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3586377</guid>
      <title>Scientists harvest vegetables from Antarctic greenhouse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt a greenhouse in the least hospitable continent on Earth, scientists have successfully farmed their first batch of fresh greens.Deutsche Welle reports that German researchers at Neumayer Station III have developed a method to grow fruits and vegetables without sunlight or soil.A high-tech greenhouse in Antarctica was used to grow produce despite subzero temperatures outside. Optimized lighting, a closed water system, and controlled levels of carbon dioxide were used.The first harvest yielded 3.6 kilograms of fresh greens, 18 cucumbers, and 70 radishes.Scientists are working on several different types of plants, and hope to harvest 4 to 5 kilos of fruits and veggies a week by May of 2018.The Antarctic project, named EDEN-ISS and run by the German Aerospace Center, aims to produce a wider range of produce that could feed future human missions to the moon or Mars.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Plants grown without sunlight or oil 2. Different plants grown in high-tech greenhouse in Antarctica3. Amount of vegetables harvested in Antarctic greenhouse4. Depiction of a greenhouse on MarsVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers finding a way to cultivate plants in space have developed a method to grow fruits and vegetables without sunlight or soil.""A high-tech greenhouse in Antarctica was used to grow produce despite subzero temperatures outside. Optimized lighting, a closed water system, and controlled levels of carbon dioxide were used.""The first harvest yielded 3.6 kilograms of fresh greens, 18 cucumbers, and 70 radishes.""The Antarctic project run by the German Aerospace Center aims to produce a wider range of produce that could feed future human missions to the moon or Mars."SOURCES: EDEN ISS, Deutsche Wellehttp://eden-iss.net/http://www.dw.com/en/scientists-harvest-antarctic-greenhouse-vegetables/a-43265721***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 07:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/09/3586377/3586377_2FAF9402ACC54B2389A1902883C40705_180409_3586377_Scientists_harvest_vegetables_from_Antarctic_gre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/034/492/0344920F69874EE9904144464BC55EAF_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, greenhouse, vegetables, harvest, Antarctica, space farm, space greenhouse, greenhouse vegetables, Antarctic vegetables, veggies, produce]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3586368</guid>
      <title>Area of Great Pacific Garbage Patch 16 times larger than previously estimated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study suggests the Great Pacific Garbage Patch could be 16 times larger than previous estimates.  The results of a three-year study beginning in 2015, commissioned by the Ocean Cleanup Foundation, were published in the journal Scientific Reports on Thursday. With 30 vessels and a C-130 Hercules aircraft, researchers catalogued a sample of over a million pieces of plastic, mostly comprised of microplastics less than 0.5 centimeters in diameter, according to CBC News. The study estimates the patch could contain more than 1.8 trillion pieces of microplastics. Scientists say there are more than 79,000 tonnes of plastic in a 1.6 million square kilometer area of the North Pacific Ocean. Researchers found plastic bottles, containers, packaging straps, lids, ropes and fishing nets among the other refuse that had been collecting for decades. As the plastics breakdown into smaller pieces, they threaten marine life that can eat them and die from them. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Great Pacific Garbage Patch2. Research vessels and a C-130 collecting samples of plastics pollution3. Estimated weight and size of garbage patch4. Researchers pulling plastics garbage out from oceanVOICEOVER (in English): "Results of a new three-year study beginning in 2015 suggests the Great Pacific Garbage Patch could be 16 times larger than previous estimates."  "With 30 vessels and a C-130 Hercules aircraft, researchers catalogued a sample of over a million pieces of plastic, mostly microplastics less than 0.5 centimeters in diameter.""Scientists say there are more than 79,000 tonnes  equal to 500 jumbo jets   of plastic in a 1.6 million square kilometer area  around three times the size of France   of the North Pacific Ocean." "Researchers found plastic bottles, containers, packaging straps, lids, ropes and fishing nets among the other refuse that had been collecting for decades."SOURCES: CBC News, Scientific Reportshttp://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/great-pacific-garbage-patch-1.4582626https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-22939-w***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 07:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/09/3586368/3586368_7FF6EFEA8E564A1392D8563DACBF7DB4_180409_3586368_Area_of_Great_Pacific_Garbage_Patch_16_times_lar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4D2/332/4D2332389310444CB45649A6022D4CCA_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Great Pacific Garbage Patch, ocean plastics pollution, ocean microplastics, microplastics pollution, pacific plastics pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3586341</guid>
      <title>Area of Great Pacific Garbage Patch 16 times larger than previously estimated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study suggests the Great Pacific Garbage Patch could be 16 times larger than previous estimates.  The results of a three-year study beginning in 2015, commissioned by the Ocean Cleanup Foundation, were published in the journal Scientific Reports on Thursday. With 30 vessels and a C-130 Hercules aircraft, researchers catalogued a sample of over a million pieces of plastic, mostly comprised of microplastics less than 0.5 centimeters in diameter, according to CBC News. The study estimates the patch could contain more than 1.8 trillion pieces of microplastics. Scientists say there are more than 79,000 tonnes of plastic in a 1.6 million square kilometer area of the North Pacific Ocean. Researchers found plastic bottles, containers, packaging straps, lids, ropes and fishing nets among the other refuse that had been collecting for decades. As the plastics breakdown into smaller pieces, they threaten marine life that can eat them and die from them. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Great Pacific Garbage Patch2. Research vessels and a C-130 collecting samples of plastics pollution3. Estimated weight and size of garbage patch4. Researchers pulling plastics garbage out from oceanVOICEOVER (in English): "Results of a new three-year study beginning in 2015 suggests the Great Pacific Garbage Patch could be 16 times larger than previous estimates."  "With 30 vessels and a C-130 Hercules aircraft, researchers catalogued a sample of over a million pieces of plastic, mostly microplastics less than 0.5 centimeters in diameter.""Scientists say there are more than 79,000 tonnes  equal to 500 jumbo jets   of plastic in a 1.6 million square kilometer area  around three times the size of France   of the North Pacific Ocean." "Researchers found plastic bottles, containers, packaging straps, lids, ropes and fishing nets among the other refuse that had been collecting for decades."SOURCES: CBC News, Scientific Reportshttp://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/great-pacific-garbage-patch-1.4582626https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-22939-w***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 07:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/09/3586341/3586341_C10C916DB257444EA0C8D057F3D0263A_180409_3586341_Area_of_Great_Pacific_Garbage_Patch_16_times_lar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DD6/B9A/DD6B9A65F81A487CA4B809B966E2D166_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Great Pacific Garbage Patch, ocean plastics pollution, ocean microplastics, microplastics pollution, pacific plastics pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3587459</guid>
      <title>14 killed in Israeli airstrike on Syrian airbase</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSyria and Russia are accusing Israel of targeting a military base where Iranians were stationed.Russia's Defense Ministry claims the T4 airbase in Syria's Homs province was attacked early Monday by two Israeli F-15 warplanes, according to NBC.The aircraft reportedly approached from the Mediterranean Sea and fired eight missiles from Lebanese airspace.Syrian air defense systems shot down five of the missiles. The remaining three hit the western part of the base, killing 14 people. According to the head of British-based monitoring group Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, most of those who died were Iranian or members of Iran-backed groups.The missile raid came just hours after a deadly poison gas attack killed at least 40 people in a rebel-held stronghold near Damascus.Syrian media initially suspected the U.S. to be behind the airstrike, following threats by U.S. President Donald Trump to make the Syrian government pay for the poisoning, but the Pentagon has since denied any involvement.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of T4 air base in Syria, Israeli F-15 2. Depiction of Israeli F-15s launching eight missiles3. Depiction of Syrian air defense systems shooting down five missiles4. Depiction of missiles striking air base, killing 14VOICEOVER (in English): "Russia's Defense Ministry claims the T4 airbase in Syria's Homs province was attacked early Monday by two Israeli F-15 warplanes.""The aircraft reportedly approached from the Mediterranean Sea and fired eight missiles from Lebanese airspace.""Syrian air defense systems shot down five of the missiles.""The remaining three hit the western part of the base, killing 14 people, most of whom were Iranian or members of Iran-backed groups."SOURCES: NBC, New York Times, USA Todayhttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/israel-blamed-airstrike-syria-after-suspected-ghouta-chemical-weapon-attack-n863821https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/09/world/middleeast/syria-russia-israel-air-base.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/04/09/russia-blames-israel-syria-air-base-attack/498171002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 13:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/10/3587459/3587459_3335CE6A07B8439CA1A5A1BB2DFE9836_180410_3587459_14_killed_in_Israeli_airstrike_on_Syrian_airbase_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DE8/99C/DE899CA7CB904082946DE7531CE9C72E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Syria airstrike, air strike, Israel air strike, Israeli air strike on Syria, Syrian air base, t4 air base, Iran Israel conflict, Israeli F15, F15 war planes, Syria air defense systems]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3587392</guid>
      <title>China set up military jamming equipment on Spratly Islands, U.S. says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has installed military jamming equipment on two of its Spratly Islands outposts that can disrupt communications and radar systems, U.S. officials say. Satellite imagery taken by commercial satellite company DigitalGlobe shows a suspected jammer system with its antenna extended on Mischief Reef, one of China's seven artificial islands, the Wall Street Journal reported. Three of its man-made outposts  Fiery Cross, Mischief Reef and Subi Reef   now have 10,000-foot runways, airplane hangars, ammunition depots, barracks and deep-water piers for ships.The new jamming equipment was installed within the last 90 days on Fiery Cross and Mischief Reef, according to U.S. intelligence, the Wall Street Journal reported.  China claims sovereignty over all of the South China Sea, however their territorial claims overlap with those of Taiwan, Brunei, Malaysia, Vietnam and the Philippines. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China has installed jamming equipment on two of its man-made islands2. Satellite imagery from Mischief Reef shows a suspected radar jammer antenna3. Depiction of Chinese jamming equipment on Mischief Reef4. China has airports, hangars, munitions, barracks and ports on three of its artificial islandsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to U.S. officials, China has installed military jamming equipment on two of its Spratly Islands outposts that can disrupt communications and radar systems.""Satellite imagery taken by commercial satellite company DigitalGlobe shows a suspected jammer system with its antenna extended on Mischief Reef, one of China's seven artificial islands.""According to U.S. intelligence, the new jamming equipment was installed within the last 90 days on Fiery Cross and Mischief Reef.""Three of its man-made outposts  Fiery Cross, Mischief Reef and Subi Reef   now have 10,000-foot runways, airplane hangars, ammunition depots, barracks and deep-water piers for ships."SOURCES: Wall Street Journal https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-installed-military-jamming-equipment-on-spratly-islands-u-s-says-1523266320***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 12:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/10/3587392/3587392_E16828F4A32B4326906B19CD1A443980_180410_3587392_China_set_up_military_jamming_equipment_on_Sprat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/02B/4AD/02B4AD537F894C6AA7ED06CFDF69D75E_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, South China Sea, Spratly Islands, China jamming equipment Spratly Islands, China artificial islands, China man-made islands]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3587357</guid>
      <title>How emergency drug Naloxone helps reverse opioid overdoses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. is in the midst of a massive opioid epidemic, with tens of thousands of overdose deaths per year, and millions more addicted to illicit drugs.The New York Times reports that on Thursday, U.S. Surgeon General Jerome Adams issued a rare advisory urging more people to carry the overdose-reversing drug Naloxone. The last advisory had been sent out 13 years ago, when women were told not to consume alcohol while pregnant.During an overdose, synthetic drugs like heroin or fentanyl flood the brain and lock onto the opiate receptors, causing breathing to become dangerously slow.According to the advisory from the Surgeon General's Office, Naloxone can reverse the effects of an overdose and comes in two forms  a nasal spray, and a syringe that should be injected into the muscles of the thigh, buttocks or arms.The emergency medication works by knocking the opioids out of the receptors in the brain  blocking and temporarily reversing their effects for 30 to 90 minutes.Police officers and medical responders are among those who have been using Naloxone to counter overdose deaths.The life-saving drug is also available at local pharmacies and local health departments.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of a synthetic opioid overdose2. Depiction of Naloxone as nasal spray3. Depiction of Naloxone as injectable drug4. How Naloxone reverses an opioid overdoseVOICEOVER (in English): "During an overdose, synthetic drugs like heroin or fentanyl flood the brain and lock onto the opiate receptors, causing breathing to become dangerously slow.""Naloxone can reverse the effects of an overdose and comes in two forms  a nasal spray, and a syringe that should be injected into the muscles of the thigh, buttocks or arms.""The emergency medication works by knocking the opioids out of the receptors in the brain  blocking and temporarily reversing the effects for 30 to 90 minutes."SOURCES: U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, New York Timeshttps://www.surgeongeneral.gov/priorities/opioid-overdose-prevention/naloxone-advisory.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/06/us/naloxone-narcan-opioid-overdose.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 11:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/10/3587357/3587357_09DF187651084AF684B8384807DFAB73_180410_3587357_How_emergency_drug_Naloxone_helps_reverse_opioid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CD4/3EE/CD43EEA85A5441E1AB7A085BE616A9D7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, naloxone, narcan, drug overdose, opioid overdose, how naloxone works, how narcan works, your brain on drugs, how to reverse an overdose, life saving drug]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3587171</guid>
      <title>How to see the 'Jupiter Triangle'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn April, Jupiter will form a special triangle with two bright stars in the night sky, and it'll be visible with the naked eye if you know where to look.Writing in Space.com, Hayden Planetarium astronomy lecturer Joe Rao calls it the "Jupiter Triangle." Jupiter forms a triangle with two bright stars that can be seen this month in the night sky starting around 11 p.m.Face east-southeast and you will see a roughly isosceles triangle comprised of the star Arcturus and the binary system Spica, with Jupiter forming the brightest of the three points.The Arcturus-Jupiter and Arcturus-Spica sides of the triangle measure about 38 degrees in length, while the Jupiter-Spica side is about 30 degrees long.The triangle will narrow in shape throughout the month, as Jupiter moves in the night sky towards Spica.The triangle will be visible until September, when Spica disappears into the sunset. Jupiter will do the same in early November. The gas giant will not reappear in this part of the sky until 2030.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the Jupiter triangle2. Depiction of Jupiter's scale3. Changes in the triangle throughout the month4. Triangle will not be visible again until 2030VOICEOVER (in English): "Jupiter forms a triangle with two bright stars that can be seen this month in the night sky starting around 11 p.m.""Face east-southeast and you will see a roughly isosceles triangle comprised of the star Arcturus and the binary system Spica, with Jupiter forming the brightest of the three points." "The Arcturus-Jupiter and Arcturus-Spica sides of the triangle measure about 38 degrees in length, while the Jupiter-Spica side is about 30 degrees long.""The triangle will narrow in shape throughout the month, as Jupiter moves in the night sky towards Spica.""The triangle will be visible until September, when Spica disappears into the sunset. Jupiter will do the same in early November. The gas giant will not reappear in this part of the sky until 2030."SOURCES: https://www.space.com/33619-visible-planets-guide.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 08:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/10/3587171/3587171_2B9D7B2B9CAE48AC9D07FA352BFA80B7_180410_3587171_How_to_see_the__Jupiter_Triangle__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F11/8D1/F118D1F7A36A4C9E95A465C9F55785AF_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, jupiter triangle, how to see the jupiter triangle, jupiter triangle astronomy, astronomy triangle, jupiter triangle april, stargazing jupiter triangle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3588149</guid>
      <title>Dutch firm conceptualizes drone-based wind turbine system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Netherlands-based company has conceptualized a wind farm where high-altitude drones gather energy. Traditional wind turbines gather most wind energy at the tip of their blades. Dutch firm Ampyx Power instead use a drone tethered to an offshore platform to gather wind energy at higher altitudes.According to reNEWS, the concept-Airborne Wind Energy (AWE) system is deployed on floating platforms. From there, the drone would fly to an altitude of 500 meters, where it creates electricity from high-altitude winds.Ampyx Power says the Energy Center for Research of the Netherlands calculated a virtual AWE wind farm operating near the east coast of Scotland to cost 137 Euros per megawatt hour. The company says this is cost competitive against other floating applications.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of traditional wind turbine and AWE system2. Depiction of AWE system being deployed  3. Depiction of AWE system underwater4. Depiction of larger-scale AWE system as wind farmVOICEOVER (in English): "Traditional wind turbines gather most wind energy at the tip of their blades.""Dutch firm Ampyx Power instead use a drone tethered to an offshore platform to gather wind energy at higher altitudes.""According to reNEWS, the concept-Airborne Wind Energy system is deployed on floating platforms.""From there, the drone would fly to an altitude of 500 meters, where it creates electricity from high-altitude winds.""The system can operate at depths of between 60 and 300 meters and is kept in place by six mooring cables attached to the ocean flower.""A power cable runs from the platform to land.""The company says the Energy Center for Research of the Netherlands calculated a virtual AWE wind farm operating near the east coast of Scotland to cost 137 Euros per megawatt hour.""Ampyx Power says this is cost competitive against other floating applications."SOURCES: Ampyx Power, reNEWShttps://www.ampyxpower.com/2018/04/far-offshore-floating-airborne-wind-energy-systems-possible-and-competitivehttps://www.ampyxpower.com/wp/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/Public-Summary-Final.pdfhttp://renews.biz/110716/dutch-float-airborne-study/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 11:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/11/3588149/3588149_2961846174994D958385B0880082EBE3_180411_3588149_Dutch_firm_conceptualizes_drone_based_wind_turbi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0B7/791/0B7791F8046549CB8321F2AB688A0E5E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, wind turbine drone, drone, renewable energy, amyx power, awe system, airborne wind energy, airborne wind energy system, AWE system, wind energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3587884</guid>
      <title>Study finds bots are behind majority of link-sharing on Twitter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study confirms the pervasiveness of automated accounts on Twitter, but also finds there's less political bias there than most of us think.According to CNET, bots are applications that execute automated tasks. This can refer to applications like Alexa or Siri, or programs with more malicious intentions, like viruses.On Twitter, bots are software-controlled accounts capable of tweeting or retweeting without direct human input.A recent Pew Research Center study that analyzed 1.2 million tweeted links found that only one third were sent by humans. The rest were posted by suspected bots.The study found that 66% of tweeted links to sites covering news were shared by bots, compared to 90% for adult sites, 76% for sports, and 73% for commercial products.Interestingly, the bots' link-sharing behavior wasn't slanted toward a specific political stance. The number of links to sites shared by liberals was roughly the same as to those shared by conservatives.It's worth noting that the researchers didn't assess the accuracy of material being shared, or distinguish between good and bad bots  which means it's still unclear how useful or problematic Twitter bots actually are.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of bots2. Depiction of Twitter bots3. Bots sharing more links on Twitter than human users4. Types of websites bots linked toVOICEOVER (in English): "Bots are applications that execute automated tasks. This can refer to applications like Alexa or Siri, or programs with more malicious intentions, like viruses.""On Twitter, bots are software-controlled accounts capable of tweeting or retweeting without direct human input.""A recent Pew Research Center study that analyzed 1.2 million tweeted links found that only one third were sent by humans. The rest were posted by suspected bots.""The study found that 66% of tweeted links to sites covering news were shared by bots, compared to 90% for adult sites, 76% for sports, and 73% for commercial products."SOURCES: Pew Research Center, CNEThttp://www.pewinternet.org/2018/04/09/bots-in-the-twittersphere/#fn-19964-3https://www.cnet.com/how-to/what-is-a-bot/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 07:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/11/3587884/3587884_5882115A56A44020B681A7DDE7CB769A_180411_3587884_Study_finds_bots_are_behind_majority_of_link_sha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4E9/1A9/4E91A912E71D4BCEA71D5F66488AD8AE_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, twitter, bots, twitterbots, twitter bots, tweets, link sharing, automated accounts, pew research center]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3587852</guid>
      <title>NASA developing robot bees for Mars exploration</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA researchers are working on robot bees to explore Mars.According to new NASA plans for Martian exploration, robot Marsbees would use a rover as a mobile base for operations and charging. They can stay airborne for 4 to 6 hours.The space agency says the Marsbee is the size of a bumble bee, with a wingspan similar to a cicada.According to NASA, the low Martian gravity reduces the power requirements for generating lift. It's because of this researchers have incorporated a flapping wing design, with a torsional spring to absorb wasted energy.The Marsbees will also be equipped with sensors and wireless devices. They'll use these to further map and sample the red planet, as well as search for methane gas  a key indicator of life.The Marsbee proposal is being worked on by a team scientists from the U.S. and Japan.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Marsbees and a Mars Rover2. Depiction of the Marsbee size compared to other insects3. Depiction of the Marsbee wing design and Martian gravity4. Depiction of the Marsbee's equipment and search for methane gasVOICEOVER (in English): "According to new NASA plans for Martian exploration, robot Marsbees would use a rover as a mobile base for operations and charging.""They can stay airborne for 4 to 6 hours.""The space agency says the Marsbee is the size of a bumble bee, with a wingspan similar to a cicada." "According to NASA, the low Martian gravity reduces the power requirements for generating lift.""It's because of this researchers have incorporated a flapping wing design, with a torsional spring to absorb wasted energy.""The Marsbees will also be equipped with sensors and wireless devices." "They'll use these to further map and sample the red planet, as well as search for methane gas  a key indicator of life."SOURCES: NASA, Space.com, The Guardianhttps://www.nasa.gov/directorates/spacetech/niac/2018_Phase_I_Phase_II/Marsbee_Swarm_of_Flapping_Wing_Flyers_for_Enhanced_Mars_Explorationhttps://www.space.com/40212-nasa-plans-robot-bees-on-mars.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/shortcuts/2018/apr/02/planet-of-the-apians-nasa-develops-plan-to-launch-marsbees#img-1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 06:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/11/3587852/3587852_1D8945398528417CB08E43F40980BB98_180411_3587852_NASA_developing_robot_bees_for_Mars_exploration_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C38/B8F/C38B8F448B5E47CB83AE5E497A32917C_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, robot bees, mars exploration rover, mars 2018, marsbee, marsbee swarm, marsbee robot, NASA, cicada, bumble bee, Mars, red planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3587797</guid>
      <title>ESA space junk collector reaches ISS for tests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA spacecraft designed to collect space garbage has arrived at the International Space Station. The RemoveDebris satellite was launched into space on April 2 aboard a SpaceX's Falcon 9 rocket, according to Tech Times.  It was developed by several companies in conjunction with the European Space Agency.The satellite weighs 100 kilograms and comes equipped with a 30 centimeter long 'harpoon' that can be shot towards space debris in order push it away from functioning satellites. It also has a net that can be launched towards objects. After wrapping around the debris, the net can be cut loose to burn while reentering the Earth's atmosphere. After being deployed from the ISS, the satellite will conduct preliminary tests attempting to capture cubesats acting as space junk.  Tests will also be carried out on the spacecraft's ability to use its laser navigation technology to track space fragments that are spinning out of control. Researchers are expected to start testing the spacecraft within the next few weeks. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. RemoveDebris satellite being released from ISS2. RemoveDebris harpoon3. RemoveDebris net4. RemoveDebris carrying out preliminary tests with cubesatsVOICEOVER (in English): "A spacecraft designed to collect space garbage made by several companies in conjunction with the European Space Agency has arrived at the International Space Station.""The RemoveDebris satellite weighs 100 kilograms and is equipped with a 30 centimeter long 'harpoon' that can be shot towards space debris in order push it away from functioning satellites." "It also has a net that can be launched towards objects. After wrapping around the debris, the net can then be cut loose to burn up while reentering the Earth's atmosphere." "After being deployed from the ISS, the satellite will first conduct preliminary tests with cubesats acting as space fragments."SOURCES: Tech Times, The Tecakehttp://www.techtimes.com/articles/224346/20180405/debris-collector-launched-inside-falcon-9-may-help-solve-space-junk-problem.htmhttps://tecake.in/european-space-debris-spacecraft-will-soon-harpoon-the-debris***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 05:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/11/3587797/3587797_937ACBBD59E94540912D4E578D81C8C3_180411_3587797_ESA_space_junk_collector_reaches_ISS_for_tests_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/52D/C37/52DC373E033B4A3593333393EAD77EA0_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, space debris, space pollution, space debris collector, ESA RemoveDebris mission, RemoveDebris satellite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3588992</guid>
      <title>Airbus plans to put sleeping cabins in cargo holds by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAirbus announced it plans to offer luxury sleeping cabins in the cargo holds of their A330 wide-body planes by 2020. The European aircraft company is partnering with Zodiac Aerospace to develop modular compartments that are easily interchangeable with cargo containers, according to the Guardian. The spaces will be separate from the economy and business class seating areas in aircrafts. Passengers will be able to book sleeping compartments, meeting rooms, lounges and children's play areas, according to Wired. Each of the areas fits inside a container that can be inserted into the cargo hold like traditional cargo. According to the Guardian, a Zodiac Aerospace spokesperson said that pods could be removed and changed in about a day. Depending on the model of the A330, three or four cabins could fit into each airplane.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sleeping cabin area2. Sleeping, meeting, lounge and play area modules3. Inside meeting and kid area compartments4. Depending on A330 model, three or four cabins can fit onto each planeVOICEOVER (in English): "Airbus has announced plans with Zodiac Aerospace to develop modular compartments that are easily interchangeable with cargo containers in their A330 wide-body planes by 2020." "Passengers will be able to book sleeping compartments, meeting rooms, lounges and children's play areas.""Each of the areas fits inside a container that can be inserted into the cargo hold like traditional cargo." "Pods could be removed and changed in about a day. Depending on the model of the A330, three or four cabins could fit into an aircraft."SOURCES: The Guardian, Wired, Inhabitathttps://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/apr/11/airbus-to-put-sleeping-berths-in-cargo-holdshttp://www.wired.co.uk/article/airbus-sleeping-pods-naps-cargo-hold-zodiac-330https://inhabitat.com/airbus-is-putting-spacious-sleeping-pods-in-airplane-cargo-holds/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 12:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/12/3588992/3588992_AC8600631FFA435296234B524F73AF84_180412_3588992_Airbus_plans_to_put_sleeping_cabins_in_cargo_hol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B35/7C7/B357C754B05841F39F8B252FD421CFC3_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Airbus sleeping pods, Airbus, Zodiac Aerospace, Airbus lounges, Airbus meeting rooms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3588935</guid>
      <title>Sleep deprivation linked to increase in Alzheimer's protein</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found that just one night of sleep loss could lead to increased beta-amyloid, a brain protein that has been linked to dementia.The study, published in PNAS, reports that Alzheimer's disease has been associated with a buildup of beta-amyloid proteins in the brain, which manifests as plaques.Since sleeping is believed to flush amyloids from the brain, lack of sleep has been correlated with a higher risk of the neurodegenerative disease.In a study conducted by the National Institutes of Health, amyloid levels in the brains of 20 healthy subjects were measured after a full night's sleep.When the subjects were deprived of sleep for more than 24 hours, scans revealed levels of beta-amyloid had increased significantly.While the immediate effects of sleep loss are clear, the study failed to look at the implications over a long period of time.But even without establishing causation between lack of sleep and dementia, it's clear sleep is crucial to a healthy functioning brain.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of amyloid plaque in people with Alzheimer's2. Depiction of brain flushing out toxins during sleep3. Amyloid levels measured in subjects after a full night's sleep4. Depiction of increased amyloid levels after one night of sleep deprivationVOICEOVER (in English): "Alzheimer's disease has been associated with a build-up of beta-amyloid proteins in the brain, which manifests as plaques.""Since sleeping is believed to flush amyloids from the brain, lack of sleep has been correlated with a higher risk of the neurodegenerative disease.""In a study conducted by the National Institutes of Health, amyloid levels in the brains of 20 healthy subjects were measured after a full night's sleep.""When the subjects were deprived of sleep for more than 24 hours, scans revealed that the levels of beta-amyloid had increased significantly."SOURCES: PNAShttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/03/29/1721694115***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 11:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/12/3588935/3588935_7E14C994529045DD8966B34453CFB707_180412_3588935_Sleep_deprivation_linked_to_increase_in_Alzheime_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EFF/381/EFF3816B072F4DAD94179D9A0F27B660_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, alzheimers, dementia, sleep loss, sleep deprivation, alzheimer's, brain plaque, amyloid, beta amyloid, amyloid protein]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3588887</guid>
      <title>NASA to launch new Mars mission in California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCalifornia will play host to the first interplanetary launch from the U.S. west coast next month.NASA will launch their insight mission to Mars from the Vandenberg Air Force in California on the morning of May 5, 2018. The higher it gets, the more visible it'll be to more of the state. NASA reckons 10 million Californians will be able to see it.Protected by an aeroshell, the lander will travel for around 6 months to the red planet.Once close to the atmosphere it'll begin a 6-minute descent around 80 miles from the Martian surface.As it approaches the surfaces, the spacecraft will get rid of its heat shielding and deploy a parachute. Once there, the Insight lander will remain stationary and not move around. NASA will use to probe the Martian surface and analyze soil samples from deep inside the planet.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of takeoff location and where it can be viewed2. Depiction of Insight in space3. Depiction of Insight descending to Martian surface4. Depiction of Insight on the Martian surfaceVOICEOVER (in English): "In a first for the U.S. west coast, NASA will launch their Insight mission to Mars from the Vandenberg Air Force in California on May 5." "The higher it gets, the more visible it'll be. NASA reckons 10 million Californians will be able to see it  .""Protected by an aeroshell, the lander will travel for around 6 months before reaching  Mars." "Once close to the atmosphere it'll begin a 6-minute descent around 80 miles from the surface.""As it descends, the spacecraft will get rid of its heat shielding and deploy a parachute.""Once there, the Insight lander will remain stationary.""NASA will use it to probe the Martian surface and analyze soil samples from deep inside the planet."SOURCES: NASAhttps://mars.nasa.gov/insight/https://www.nasa.gov/feature/jpl/bound-for-mars-countdown-to-first-interplanetary-launch-from-california***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/12/3588887/3588887_71946E42FBDC477F94D1F624229A584E_180412_3588887_NASA_to_launch_new_Mars_mission_in_California_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/825/52B/82552B4DE3C649A1B5E6AEABFC906126_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nasa mission, nasa insight, nasa mission on mars, nasa, insight, mars, red planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3588817</guid>
      <title>Towering 8.8 megawatt wind turbine installed near Aberdeen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOne rotation from Aberdeen's massive new 8.8 megawatt wind turbine can generate 24 hours of power for one house.According to Inhabitat, the first of 11 massive wind turbines have been installed near Aberdeen on the Scottish coast.  When complete it's believed they will generate 70% of Aberdeen's energy needs, displacing 134,128 tonnes of CO2.Each turbine is 191 meters tall, nearly double the size of the Statue of Liberty.The blades measure 80 meters in length, and together with the rotor, make for a circumference larger than that of the London Eye.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of 11 wind turbines on Scottish coast2. Depiction of wind turbine height and scale against Statue of Liberty and London Eye3. Depiction of wind turbine powering house with one turn4. Depiction of wind power displacing CO2 in AberdeenVOICEOVER (in English): "The first of 11 massive wind turbines have been installed near Aberdeen on the Scottish coast.""The turbine is 191 meters tall, nearly double the size of the Statue of Liberty.""It's blades measure 80 meters""One full turn from the 8.8 megawatt wind turbine can reportedly generate 24 hours of power for one house." "When complete, it's believed the machines will generate 70% of Aberdeen's energy needs, displacing 134,128 tonnes of CO2."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Innovators Mag, Business Green, The Mirror, BBChttps://inhabitat.com/worlds-most-powerful-turbine-installed-off-the-coast-of-scotland/https://www.innovatorsmag.com/record-breaking-wind-turbine-installed/https://www.businessgreen.com/bg/news/3029899/worlds-most-powerful-wind-turbine-installed-in-scottish-watershttps://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/worlds-most-powerful-wind-turbine-12337531http://www.bbc.com/news/uk-scotland-north-east-orkney-shetland-43713529***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/12/3588817/3588817_97708D95C50842F1A6D267515224554D_180412_3588817_Towering_8_8_megawatt_wind_turbine_installed_nea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/915/3BC/9153BCCC0FA74C6F856B83ABD34770D3_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, largest wind turbines, wind turbines, Scotland, green energy, wind power, wind energy power, most powerful wind turbine, wind turbines, wind energy, renewable energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3588618</guid>
      <title>Nanoparticles in food packaging could be harmful to digestion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found that nanoparticles in certain food packaging could be negatively affecting digestion.According to the Binghamton University study, the inside of canned goods are typically lined with zinc oxide nanoparticles, which have antimicrobial properties.When looking at how many nanoparticles were transferred to food, researchers found 100 times the recommended daily allowance of zinc oxide.While in the small intestine, the nanoparticles caused the remodelling or loss of microvilli, resulting in fewer nutrients being absorbed into the cells.High doses of zinc oxide also triggered pro-inflammatory signaling. This can increase intestinal permeability and allow harmful compounds to pass into the bloodstream.Since only a cell model was used to demonstrate the effects, it's difficult to determine how long-term ingestion will impact human health. For now, the researchers are looking at the nanoparticles' effect on animals.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Zinc oxide nanoparticles in canned goods2. Canned food contained 100 times the recommended daily allowance of zinc oxide3. Loss of intestinal microvilli caused by nanoparticles decreases nutrient absorption 4. Depiction of increased intestinal permeabilityVOICEOVER (in English): "Canned goods are typically lined with zinc oxide nanoparticles for their antimicrobial properties.""When looking at how many nanoparticles were transferred to food, Binghamton researchers found 100 times the recommended daily allowance of zinc oxide.""While in the small intestine, the nanoparticles caused the remodelling or loss of microvilli, resulting in reduced cell nutrient absorption.""High doses of zinc oxide also triggered pro-inflammatory signaling. This can increase intestinal permeability and allow harmful compounds to pass into the bloodstream."SOURCES: Binghamton Universityhttps://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2018-04/bu-fpc040918.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/12/3588618/3588618_1CDEAA88B052433DBD8394174CDB0A47_180412_3588618_Nanoparticles_in_food_packaging_could_be_harmful_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9D0/2D1/9D02D14342EA41939C007FA5E53675DE_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nanoparticles, zinc oxide, canned food, food packaging, nutrients, digestion, digestive problems, gastrointestinal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3589698</guid>
      <title>How will Kim Jong Un travel for critical Trump meeting?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea may not possess transport capable of getting leader Kim Jong Un to his May meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump, reports the Washington Post. Citing a former CIA analyst, the Post reports that North Korea uses old long range Soviet aircraft. Analysts also told the paper that North Korean airline Koryo has shorter-range Tupolev jets.Unconfirmed reports last month put Kim in China, saying he got there via an armored green train. If true, he could also travel by rail to a European venue via Moscow or to a spot in Russia itself. There are several North Korea to Russia train services in operation, according to travel website Seat61.comAnalysts say Kim could also borrow aircraft from one of its neighbors, or travel with South Korea or Sweden. However, the Post reports these options could be embarrassing for the North Korean leader.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Trump and Kim meeting in the Korean DMZ and potential meeting spots2. Depiction of the Ilyushin Il-62 and its maximum range3. Depiction of rail travel from North Korea to Russia and Europe4. Depiction of Tupolev aircraft being refueledVOICEOVER (in English): "The Washington Post speculates that North Korean leader Kim Jong Un and U.S. President Donald Trump's meeting may take place in the Korean Demilitarized Zone.""Analysts told the Post that North Korea has the Ilyushin Il-62, an old Soviet jetliner.""This plane, from the 1960s has a wingspan of 43m, is 53m long and 12m tall. "It can fly up to 5,400 miles, meaning it could reach Hawaii, or the U.S West Coast if leaving from Pyongyang.""Unconfirmed reports last month put Kim in China, saying he got there via an armored green train." "If true, he could also travel by rail to a European venue via Moscow or to a spot in Russia itself.""Another way is for Kim to travel with a shorter-distance Air Koryo Tupolev jet." "Analysts say Kim could also borrow aircraft from one of North Korea's neighbors, or travel with South Korea or Sweden." "However the Post reports these options could be embarrassing for the North Korean leader."SOURCES: Washington Post, Independent, Seat 61, Airliners, Guardianhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/air-force-un-as-north-koreas-leader-steps-onto-international-stage-a-question-over-his-ability-to-fly/2018/04/09/08c265e2-3c08-11e8-8d53-eba0ed2371cc_story.html?utm_term=.6ae56d59cdb4https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/kim-jong-un-donald-trump-north-korea-us-summit-washington-pyeongchang-americas-asia-a8299906.htmlhttps://www.seat61.com/NorthKorea.htmhttp://www.airliners.net/aircraft-data/ilyushin-il-62/250https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/27/kim-jong-un-and-the-mystery-of-the-special-green-train***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 11:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/13/3589698/3589698_F73A0F9D8E2940BA9CD18F77E45EF0E1_180413_3589698_How_will_Kim_Jong_Un_travel_for_critical_Trump_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B8B/FAB/B8BFAB5022274E26A3385B3D3E1E7263_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, trump kim meeting, trump kim meet, kim jong un, donald trump, usa, north korea, north korea travel, north korea plane, kim jong un plane, kim jong un train, koryo, dprk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3589688</guid>
      <title>Sweden debuts world's first electric road to charge moving vehicles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe world's first electrified road that recharges batteries of moving vehicles driving on it has opened in Sweden. Around 2 kms of electric rail has been embedded in a road close to Stockholm, according to the Guardian. The system transfers electricity from the installed underground rail to the vehicle above through a flexible arm that connects to the charging vehicle, according to Inhabitat. The electrified road is split up into 50m sections. Individual sections are only powered when a car or truck is overhead. The current is disconnected if a vehicle stops. When the vehicle drives off the electric rails, the system calculates the energy consumption and debits the driver. At a cost of around 1 million per kilometer, the cost to electrify roads is 50 times lower than required to build an urban tram line, according to the Guardian.  The Swedish government's road agency is planning for future national expansion. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Electric truck driving on electrified road2. Electricity is transferred through a flexible arm on charging vehicle3. The electrified road is split up into 50m sections, with individual sections powered when a car or truck is overhead4. The system calculates energy consumption and debits driversVOICEOVER (in English): "The world's first electrified road that recharges batteries of moving vehicles driving on it has opened in Sweden. Around 2 kilometers of electric rail has been embedded in a public road close to Stockholm.""The system transfers electricity from the installed underground rail to the vehicle above through a flexible arm that connects to the charging vehicle.""The electrified road is split up into 50-meter sections. Individual sections are only powered when a car or truck is overhead." "When the vehicle drives off the electric rails, the system calculates the energy consumption and debits the driver."SOURCES: The Guardian, Inhabitathttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/apr/12/worlds-first-electrified-road-for-charging-vehicles-opens-in-swedenhttps://inhabitat.com/worlds-first-electric-road-that-charges-moving-vehicles-debuts-in-sweden/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 11:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/13/3589688/3589688_8296A94729B8468BAF394535FD6128C0_180413_3589688_Sweden_debuts_world_s_first_electric_road_to_cha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C18/8F4/C188F4D026794764974BE15BFFB8A5BB_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, electrified roads, Sweden electrified road, Stockholm electrified road, electric vehicle charging, moving electric vehicle charging]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3589506</guid>
      <title>Healing after breast cancer surgery may trigger relapse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research suggests the healing process following breast cancer surgery may be triggering cancer in other parts of the body.According to MIT News, previous studies of breast cancer patients indicate they are prone to metastatic relapse 12 to 18 months after undergoing surgery for growth removal.It's been suggested that dormant cancer cells in other sites that were previously kept in check by the immune system are allowed to become active as the body focuses on healing its wound.Experiments on mice conducted by the Whitehead Institute found that while T-cells stalled the growth of injected cancer cells, simulated surgeries in areas far from the cancer resulted in increased tumor growth and incidence.Mice given anti-inflammatory drugs during or after surgery developed significantly smaller tumors, which often disappeared completely.Early research in humans shows the same strong association between anti-inflammatory drug use and a decline in metastasis, but more studies are needed.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Breast cancer patients prone to relapsing within 12 to 18 months of surgery2. Cancer cells in other sites allowed to spread during post-surgery wound healing3. Depiction of experiment on mice4. Anti-inflammatory drugs given after surgery prevented tumor growth and spreadVOICEOVER (in English): "Studies of breast cancer patients indicate that they are prone to metastatic relapse 12 to 18 months after surgical growth removal.""It's believed that dormant cancer cells in other sites previously kept in check by the immune system become active as the body focuses on healing its wound.""Experiments on mice found that while T-cells stalled the growth of injected cancer cells,  simulated surgeries in areas far from the cancer resulted in increased tumor growth and incidence.""Mice given anti-inflammatory drugs during or after surgery developed significantly smaller tumors, which often disappeared completely."SOURCES: MIT News, USA Todayhttp://news.mit.edu/2018/perioperative-nsaids-may-prevent-early-metastatic-relapse-in-post-surgical-breast-cancer-patients-0411https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/04/11/breast-cancer-surgery-healing-study/506525002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 08:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/13/3589506/3589506_8D9693A859844B78914D37E82A53548E_180413_3589506_Healing_after_breast_cancer_surgery_may_trigger__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/53B/263/53B26372B1224E1B843ED33FF8A3DE1C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, breast cancer, breast cancer surgery, tumor, cancer, cancer cells, cancer spread, NSAID, anti-inflammatory drugs, growth, relapse, dormant cancer cells, mastectomy, lumpectomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3591517</guid>
      <title>Rare minerals found in waters near Japanese island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA plethora of rare earth minerals have been discovered on a remote Japanese island, according to new research published in Scientific Reports.Researchers says that the seafloor surrounding Nishinoshima island is laden with 16 million tonnes of rare-earth oxides, the South China Morning Post reported, citing the study.On a global scale, the study estimates that the find could meet 62 years of yttrium demand, 47 years of europium, 32 years of Terbium, and 56 years of dysprosium needs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of findings2. Nishinoshima island3. What uses rare earth minerals4. How the discovery could meet demand for rare earth mineralsVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Nature, Financial Times, South China Morning Posthttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-23948-5https://www.ft.com/content/68245766-3d20-11e8-b7e0-52972418fec4http://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/2141445/discovery-rare-earth-minerals-japan-coast-secures-780-years***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 09:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/16/3591517/3591517_F2D853E4DE694CFCB5E033C915CED82E_180416_3591517_Rare_minerals_found_in_waters_near_Japanese_isla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CC3/2B8/CC32B8685FF446CC80F08B1DD612B4BF_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  rare earth minerals, new discovery, nishinoshima island, japan, earth minerals, europium, terbium, dysprosium, yttrium]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3591395</guid>
      <title>World's fastest Ironman planning to run Boston Marathon after broken neck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe world's fastest Ironman, who experienced a hangman's fracture in his neck just six months ago, is planning to compete in the Boston Marathon.  On October 11, 2017, triathlete and marathon runner Tim Don was involved in an accident when a vehicle turning into a gas station struck him in the side, according to the New York Times. Don experienced a hangman's fracture, a broken C2 vertebra. In order to keep competing, Don elected to have a halo put on. With a halo, titanium pins are screwed into the skull, two in front and two in back and then attached to metal bars, which are connected to a bust that must be worn for three months. Training in the halo has been extremely painful for Don. He's worked on strengthening his core and lower body. He was also able to train on an exercise bike as long as he did not lean forward to overload his neck.   Don says he expects to finish the marathon in around 2 hours and 50 minutes. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Don's hangman's fracture2. Halo being put on Don3. Don training with halo brace on4. Don running in Boston MarathonVOICEOVER (in English): "The world's fastest Ironman Tim Don was involved in an accident when a vehicle turning into a gas station and struck him in the side in October last year, according to the New York Times. Don experienced a hangman's fracture, a broken C2 vertebra."  "In order to keep competing, Don elected to have a halo put on. With a halo, titanium pins are screwed into the skull  two in front and two in back  and then attached to metal bars, which are connected to a bust that must be worn for three months." "Training in the halo has been extremely painful for Don. He's worked on strengthening his core and lower body. He was also able to train on an exercise bike as long as he did not lean forward to overload his neck."   "Don is now planning on competing in the Boston Marathon. He says he expects to finish in around 2 hours and 50 minutes." SOURCES: New York Times, The Telegraphhttps://mobile.nytimes.com/2018/04/12/sports/tim-don-boston-marathon-ironman.htmlhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/the-filter/tim-don-fastest-ever-ironman-shook-broken-neck-keep-running/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 06:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/16/3591395/3591395_BB8A908C5BD0404D98CC24892EF3EC74_180416_3591395_World_s_fastest_Ironman_planning_to_run_Boston_M_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E21/2F3/E212F3BEA78F4D008A9A5DE06666C298_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Tim Don, Ironman Tim Don, Tim Don broken neck, Tim Don Boston Marathon, Tim Don neck Boston Marathon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3591362</guid>
      <title>Gold-backed cryptocurrency used to attract Muslim investors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCryptocurrency traders are now turning to gold to draw investors from Muslim nations.Reuters reports that many Gulf states don't consider cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin or Ethereum as compliant with Sharia law, which emphasizes economic activity based on physical assets.To address this, Dubai startup OneGram has begun issuing a gold-backed cryptocurrency. Each unit has a corresponding gram of gold stored in a vault.The company obtained approval from an Islamic advisory firm, and has so far issued tens of millions of dollars worth of the currency. Only 60 percent of the planned amount of coins remains to be sold.A similar gold-backed crypto from HelloGold was released in Malaysia last October, after receiving permission from Islamic scholars in Kuala Lumpur.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Typical cryptocurrencies not compliant with Sharia principles2. Depiction of cryptocurrency backed by gold3. Tens of millions of dollars of OneGram cryptocurrency sold so farVOICEOVER (in English): "Many Gulf states don't consider cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin or Ethereum as compliant with Sharia law, which emphasizes economic activity based on physical assets.""To address this, Dubai startup OneGram has begun issuing a gold-backed cryptocurrency. Each unit has a corresponding gram of gold stored in a vault.""The company obtained approval from an Islamic advisory firm, and has so far issued tens of millions of dollars worth of the currency. Only 60 percent of the planned amount of coins remains to be sold."SOURCES: Reutershttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-crypto-currencies-islamic-finance-ins/cryptocurrency-traders-use-old-gold-in-drive-to-draw-islamic-investors-idUSKBN1HF076?il=0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 05:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/16/3591362/3591362_8BE0CA938D58454D8910C5662988B6AE_180416_3591362_Gold_backed_cryptocurrency_used_to_attract_Musli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0EE/FA3/0EEFA34E362E41429AEE2F17E47207A1_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, gold cryptocurrency, gold bar, Islamic cryptocurrency, Muslim cryptocurrency, onegram, middle east, gulf states, digital currency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592444</guid>
      <title>Plastic-eating enzyme could help in battling pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the U.S. and Britain say they have created a plastic-eating enzyme that could be used aide in the recovery and recycling of plastics. The enzyme is able to digest polyethylene terephthalate, or PET, plastic. PET plastics take hundreds of years to break down and have become an enormous source of pollution, according to Reuters.The findings were published on Monday in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences journal. Scientists from the U.S. Department of Energy's National Renewable Energy Laboratory and Britain's University of Portsmouth made the discovery while looking at the structure of a natural enzyme believed to have evolved in a recycling plant in Japan.Researchers added some amino acids to the enzyme which ended up speeding up its plastic-eating capabilities. The team will now work on improving the enzyme to see if it's capable to breaking down PET plastics on an industrial scale.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New enzyme breaking down PET plastic bottles2. PET plastics pollution3. Researchers created new enzyme by adding amino acids to natural plastic-eating enzyme from Japan4. Researchers will now see if the enzyme can be used on an industrial scaleVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the U.S. and Britain say they have created a plastic-eating enzyme that could be used aide in the recovery and recycling of plastics. The enzyme is able to digest polyethylene terephthalate, or PET, plastic.""PET plastics take hundreds of years to breakdown and have become an enormous source of global pollution on land and in the oceans.""Scientists made the discovery while looking at the structure of a natural plastic-eating enzyme believed to have evolved in a recycling plant in Japan. Researchers added some amino acids to the enzyme which ended up speeding up its plastic-eating capabilities." "The team will now work on improving the enzyme to see if it's capable to breaking down PET plastics on an industrial scale."  SOURCES: Reuters, The Independenthttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-plastic-enzyme/plastic-eating-enzyme-holds-promise-in-fighting-pollution-scientists-idUSKBN1HN2OZhttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/plastic-eating-enzyme-pollution-solution-waste-bottles-bacteria-portsmouth-a8307371.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 11:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/17/3592444/3592444_4F335F8151C542409F7526A87B3ECC5D_180417_3592444_Plastic_eating_enzyme_could_help_in_battling_pol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DEC/AAF/DECAAFD7CB67475A897F94B3214B8AB8_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, plastic-eating enzyme, plastics pollution, PET pollution, plastic digesting enzyme, plastics recycling, PET recycling]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592215</guid>
      <title>Trump's presidential state car is ready to roll this summer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new fleet of presidential limousines is set to debut this summer, with one of the Cadillacs already in the possession of the Secret Service, Fox News reported.Wrapped in black and white camouflage during its testing phase, the new presidential vehicle is expected to sport styling elements similar Cadillac's CT6 sedan. Known as "Cadillac One" or by the Secret Service as "The Beast," it will use a Kodiak medium-duty truck frame with custom-made body panels.The seven-seat interior is sealed to protect against a biological or chemical attack, with windows that can withstand armor-piercing bullets.The current edition of the Beast has 20-cm-thick heavy armor-plated doors and a reinforced steel plate running underneath the vehicle to protect it from roadside bombs.The presidential limousine has tear gas cannons and a night vision camera, as well as a pump-action shotgun. Extra weapons, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type are also on board. The fuel tank is armor-plated and encased in foam to prevent it from exploding. The kevlar-reinforced tires are puncture and shard-resistant, with steel rims that allow the car to continue driving if the tires are destroyed.Unlike the CT6, the Beast probably will not use the CT6's semi-autonomous drive system. Instead, it will always be driven by a highly trained agent who's skilled in defensive and evasive driving techniques.The vehicle bears the American flag and the Presidential Standard while traveling domestically. When abroad, the Presidential Standard is replaced by that country's flag.Cadillac has built every presidential vehicle since 1993. Cadillac President Johann de Nysschen told Fox News that the presidential vehicles have always been part of Cadillac's heritage and tradition. One they hope to carry on in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Donald Trump sits in "Cadillac One"2. Show the vehicle's armored bodywork and windows 3. The vehicle's interior is sealed to protect the president from biochemical attacks 4. The vehicle's armor-plated doors and reinforced steel plate in the undercarriage5. The vehicle is equipped with tear gas cannons, a night vision camera, a shotgun, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type6. The vehicle's armour-plated, foam-encased fuel tank7. The vehicle's tyres are puncture and shard-resistant with steel rims8. The vehicle probably will not use CT's semi-autonomous drive system9. The presidential state car displays the American flag and Presidential Standard. In a foreign country, that country's flag replaces the Presidential StandardVOICEOVER (in English): "Wrapped in black and white camouflage during its testing phase, the new presidential vehicle is expected to sport styling elements similar Cadillac's CT6 sedan. Known as 'Cadillac One' or by the Secret Service as 'The Beast,' it will use a Kodiak medium-duty truck frame with custom-made body panels.""The seven-seat interior is sealed to protect against a biological or chemical attack, with windows that can withstand armor-piercing bullets.""'The current edition of the Beast has 20-centimeter-thick heavy armor-plated doors and a reinforced steel plate running underneath the vehicle to protect it from roadside bombs.""The presidential limousine has tear gas cannons and a night vision camera, as well as a pump-action shotgun. Extra weapons, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type are also on board. The fuel tank is armor-plated and encased in foam to prevent it from exploding. The kevlar-reinforced tires are puncture and shard-resistant, with steel rims that allow the car to continue driving if the tires are destroyed.""Unlike the CT6, 'The Beast' probably will not use the CT6's semi-autonomous drive system. Instead, it will always be]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 07:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/17/3592215/3592215_30F7DC001FAE4B46BF237D35F331B000_180417_3592215_Trump_s_presidential_state_car_is_ready_to_roll__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/41B/4AE/41B4AEFB107F41139D7E66A40DB56CB2_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, trump limo, trump presidential limo, trump limousine, trump limo the beast, trump limousine video, the beast, gm limo, gm presidential limo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592200</guid>
      <title>Trump's presidential state car is ready to roll this summer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new fleet of presidential limousines is set to debut this summer, with one of the Cadillacs already in the possession of the Secret Service, Fox News reported.Wrapped in black and white camouflage during its testing phase, the new presidential vehicle is expected to sport styling elements similar Cadillac's CT6 sedan. Known as "Cadillac One" or by the Secret Service as "The Beast," it will use a Kodiak medium-duty truck frame with custom-made body panels.The seven-seat interior is sealed to protect against a biological or chemical attack, with windows that can withstand armor-piercing bullets.The current edition of the Beast has 20-cm-thick heavy armor-plated doors and a reinforced steel plate running underneath the vehicle to protect it from roadside bombs.The presidential limousine has tear gas cannons and a night vision camera, as well as a pump-action shotgun. Extra weapons, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type are also on board. The fuel tank is armor-plated and encased in foam to prevent it from exploding. The kevlar-reinforced tires are puncture and shard-resistant, with steel rims that allow the car to continue driving if the tires are destroyed.Unlike the CT6, the Beast probably will not use the CT6's semi-autonomous drive system. Instead, it will always be driven by a highly trained agent who's skilled in defensive and evasive driving techniques.The vehicle bears the American flag and the Presidential Standard while traveling domestically. When abroad, the Presidential Standard is replaced by that country's flag.Cadillac has built every presidential vehicle since 1993. Cadillac President Johann de Nysschen told Fox News that the presidential vehicles have always been part of Cadillac's heritage and tradition. One they hope to carry on in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Donald Trump sits in "Cadillac One"2. Show the vehicle's armored bodywork and windows 3. The vehicle's interior is sealed to protect the president from biochemical attacks 4. The vehicle's armor-plated doors and reinforced steel plate in the undercarriage5. The vehicle is equipped with tear gas cannons, a night vision camera, a shotgun, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type6. The vehicle's armour-plated, foam-encased fuel tank7. The vehicle's tyres are puncture and shard-resistant with steel rims8. The vehicle probably will not use CT's semi-autonomous drive system9. The presidential state car displays the American flag and Presidential Standard. In a foreign country, that country's flag replaces the Presidential StandardVOICEOVER (in English): "Wrapped in black and white camouflage during its testing phase, the new presidential vehicle is expected to sport styling elements similar Cadillac's CT6 sedan. Known as 'Cadillac One' or by the Secret Service as 'The Beast,' it will use a Kodiak medium-duty truck frame with custom-made body panels.""The seven-seat interior is sealed to protect against a biological or chemical attack, with windows that can withstand armor-piercing bullets.""'The current edition of the Beast has 20-centimeter-thick heavy armor-plated doors and a reinforced steel plate running underneath the vehicle to protect it from roadside bombs.""The presidential limousine has tear gas cannons and a night vision camera, as well as a pump-action shotgun. Extra weapons, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type are also on board. The fuel tank is armor-plated and encased in foam to prevent it from exploding. The kevlar-reinforced tires are puncture and shard-resistant, with steel rims that allow the car to continue driving if the tires are destroyed.""Unlike the CT6, 'The Beast' probably will not use the CT6's semi-autonomous drive system. Instead, it will always be]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 07:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/17/3592200/3592200_EFB4BE301CBC4058A85B8433893605ED_180417_3592200_Trump_s_presidential_state_car_is_ready_to_roll__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AED/AC2/AEDAC27EABE7447B8F788704058793B6_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, trump limo, trump presidential limo, trump limousine, trump limo the beast, trump limousine video, the beast, gm limo, gm presidential limo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592183</guid>
      <title>Sitting too much may affect brain and memory, study says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSitting too much is linked to changes in parts of the brain important for memory, according to a preliminary study by UCLA.Researchers wanted to look at the effects of sedentary behavior on brain health, particularly the sections of the brain critical to memory formation, UCLA reported, according to Science Daily. The UCLA team found 35 people ranging in age from 45 to 75 and asked their physical activity levels and the average number of hours per day spent sitting the week before. A high-resolution MRI scan was taken of each subject's medial temporal lobe, MTL. The MTL is the region of the brain involved when forming new memories. The scientists found that sedentary behavior is a significant predictor of thinning of the MTL and that physical activity is not enough to offset the harmful effects of prolonged periods of sitting. This is not to say that sitting too much causes thinner brain structures, but instead that extended periods seated are associated with thinner sections, the researchers said. According to the researchers, MTL thinning can be a precursor to cognitive decline and dementia in middle-aged and older adults. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People sitting for extended periods in different locations2. Subjects were asked about physical activity and average hours sitting3. MRI scans were taken of subject's MTL4. Office workers with affected MTLsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a preliminary UCLA study, sitting too much is linked to changes in parts of the brain important for memory. Researchers examined the effects of sedentary behavior on brain health, particularly the sections of the brain critical to memory formation.""The UCLA team found 35 people ranging in age from 45 to 75 and asked about their physical activity levels and the average number of hours per day spent sitting the week before. " "An MRI scan was taken of each subject's medial temporal lobe, or MTL. The MTL is the region of the brain involved when forming new memories." "The scientists found that sedentary behavior is a significant predictor of thinning of the MTL and that physical activity is not enough to offset the harmful effects of prolonged periods of sitting." SOURCES: Science Daily, The Bustlehttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/04/180412141014.htmhttps://www.bustle.com/p/sitting-too-much-can-change-your-brain-impact-your-memory-a-new-study-says-8791277***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 07:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/17/3592183/3592183_0F3D9C0BFAAA4ABD88B095D33D66CA91_180417_3592183_Sitting_too_much_may_affect_brain_and_memory__st_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1EA/675/1EA675170B0148638E43169D1B9308B1_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sitting too much, sitting brain memory, sedentary behavior, prolonged sitting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592065</guid>
      <title>NASA launch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's new planet-hunting satellite will seek out new Earth-like worlds over the next two years.Called the Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, the satellite searches for planets which transit in front of a star, causing a dip in its brightness. This pattern is akin to how Earth orbits the sun, and repeated brightness dips may indicate life.Planets orbiting other stars are termed exoplanets. This covers planets of all sizes from Earth and Mars, to Jupiter. TESS will search exoplanets outside our solar system.NASA says the TESS mission coverage will be 400 times greater than Kepler. Over 2 years it, it will look at 26 different sectors of space. According to NASA, TESS will observe stars up to 100 times brighter than previously covered. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of what an exoplanet is2. Depiction of how TESS will observe exoplanets and their dips in brightness3. Depiction of area covered by TESSVOICEOVER (in English): "Planets orbiting other stars are termed exoplanets. The term applies to planets of all sizes from Earth and Mars to Jupiter.""NASA's new spacecraft will search exoplanets outside our solar system.""Called the Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, the spacecraft will look for planets which transit in front of a star, causing a dip in its brightness.""Repeats of this pattern may indicate a habitable planet supporting life.""NASA says the mission will cover an area 400 times greater than observed by the Kepler space telescope.""TESS will look at 26 different sectors of space over a 2-year period."SOURCES: NASA https://www.nasa.gov/tess-transiting-exoplanet-survey-satellite***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 04:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/17/3592065/3592065_D65A98186D1A4F9FB502CB77650ACB37_180417_3592065_NASA_launch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4EE/A58/4EEA581CF668407C884F9682604D88FD_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, earth-like planets, kepler, tess, nasa, exoplanets, super earth, earth-like planets nasa, nasa exoplanets, nasa tess mission, james webb telescope, kepler mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3593211</guid>
      <title>SpaceX will build Mar spaceships at the Port of Los Angeles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLos Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti announced Monday that SpaceX will build Mars spaceships at a facility at the Port of L.A. "Today, I am pleased to officially announce that SpaceX will start production development of the Big Falcon Rocket in the Port of Los Angeles. This vehicle that holds the promise of taking humanity even deeper into the cosmos than ever before," Garcetti said during an annual speech, according to the Los Angeles Times.  The Big Falcon Rocket is a two-part launch vehicle designed to transport 100 people and 150 tons of cargo into space, according to Business Insider. When completed, it will be more than 348 feet tall.  The fully reusable rocket can be quickly refuelable and is designed to burn liquid methane, which can be manufactured on other planets and moons in the solar system, including Mars. According to public documents, SpaceX asked for permission to lease a 19-acre site called Berth 240 at the former Southwest Marine Shipyard. SpaceX wants to build a 200,000 square-foot rocketship factory on a historic site, so will now need to get approval from the port's Board of Harbor Commissioners. The initial 10-year lease, which contains two options for 10-year extensions, has a starting annual rent of around $1.38 million with annual adjustments based on the Consumer Price Index, according to the LA Times. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of proposed SpaceX BFR site in Port of Los Angeles. 2. Depiction of future BFR factory3. The two parts of the Big Falcon Rocket4. Depiction of BFR spaceship approaching MarsVOICEOVER (in English): "Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti announced Monday that SpaceX will build Mars spaceships at a facility at the Port of L.A. According to the LA Times, SpaceX asked for permission to lease a 19-acre site called Berth 240 at the former Southwest Marine Shipyard." "SpaceX will now need approval from the port's Board of Harbor Commissioners to construct a 200,000-square-foot rocketship factory for the Big Falcon Rocket on a historic site.""The initial 10-year lease, which contains two options for 10-year extensions, has a starting annual rent of around $1.38 million, with annual adjustments based on the Consumer Price Index.""Business Insider reports the Big Falcon Rocket is a two-part launch vehicle designed to transport 100 people and 150 tons of cargo into space. When complete, it will be more than 348 feet tall."SOURCES: Los Angeles Times, Business Insiderhttp://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-spacex-bfr-20180416-story.htmlhttp://www.businessinsider.com/spacex-mars-rocket-facility-approved-la-mayor-2018-4?utm_source=feedly&amp;utm_medium=referral***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/18/3593211/3593211_8B0A1614AD304F8980ABF4B577285520_180418_3593211_SpaceX_will_build_Mar_spaceships_at_the_Port_of__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D08/71F/D0871FEA25A14C8490DF8E10A6BE7BEE_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, SpaceX, SpaceX Big Falcon Rocket, SpaceX BFR Port of Los Angeles, SpaceX Port of Los Angeles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3593202</guid>
      <title>Australia's worsening Buruli ulcer epidemic has doctors baffled</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDoctors are scrambling to figure out how cases of a skin-eating disease are on the rise in Australia.Citing experts, the BBC reports Australian cases of Buruli ulcer have increased 400% since 2014. The disease can cut to the bone, spreading toxins that eradicate skin, blood vessels and fat This is what causes the ulcer to form.Mycobacterium ulcerans, the bacteria in the disease, is from the same family as leprosy and tuberculosis, according to the World Health Organization. Its origin is unknown, but doctors writing in the Medical Journal of Australia, speculate it may come from the environment, soil or could even be carried by mosquitoes.The WHO says early detection and antibiotic treatment are key to dealing with Buruli ulcer. The disease is commonly treated with a different combination of antibiotics, surgical techniques such as skin grafting as well as physiotherapy.The BBC reports health authorities have spent more than 750,000 USD combating the disease and raising awareness of it. However, doctors writing in the Aussie Medical journal are calling on Australia to do more, asking officials to immediately fund research into combating the disease.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of rise of disease2. Depiction of how disease spreads on skin3. Depiction of disease family4. Depiction of disease treatmentVOICEOVER (in English): "Citing experts, the BBC reports Australian cases of Buruli ulcer have increased 400% since 2014." "The disease can cut to the bone, spreading toxins that eradicate skin, blood vessels and fat." "This is what causes the ulcer to form.""Mycobacterium ulcerans, the bacteria in the disease, comes from the same family as leprosy and tuberculosis.""Its origin is unknown, but doctors writing in the Medical Journal of Australia, speculate  it may come from the environment, soil or could even be carried by mosquitoes." "The World Health organization says early detection and antibiotic treatment are key to dealing with Buruli ulcer.""The disease is commonly treated with a different combination of antibiotics, and where necessary, surgical techniques such as skin grafting."SOURCES: Medical Journal of Australia, World Health Organization, BBChttps://www.mja.com.au/journal/2018/208/7/tackling-worsening-epidemic-buruli-ulcer-australia-information-void-time-urgenthttp://www.who.int/mediacentre/factsheets/fs199/en/http://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-43779187***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/18/3593202/3593202_B7A59D05698A4DD980CC9164BE447CA3_180418_3593202_Australia_s_worsening_Buruli_ulcer_epidemic_has__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/26D/160/26D160F0DA824787B8BC985D53375DBC_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, myobacterium ulcerans, buruli ulcer, ulcer in australia, skin eating ulcer, buruli ulcer virus, what is the buruli ulcer, skin infection, skin disease]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592991</guid>
      <title>Passenger killed after engine explodes mid-flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA mid-flight engine explosion at 32,000 feet on Tuesday led to chaos over the skies of Philadelphia.According to the New York Times, Southwest Airlines flight 1380 was enroute to Dallas from New York when one of its two engines exploded mid-flight.According to NBC Philadelphia, the National Transportation and Safety Board are investigating the incident as "engine failure". The Boeing 737 aircraft was reportedly carrying 143 passengers and five crew at the time. It later emergency landed in Philadelphia. Shrapnel from the explosion shattered a plane window. NBC Philadelphia reports passenger Jennifer Riordan was partially pulled through the window.A passenger later told the New York Times Riordan was also hit by some shrapnel from the damaged plane engine. He explained passengers and crew dragged her back in, but she was unconscious when they did.Riordan later died despite attempts to revive her.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of plane engine explosion 2. Depiction of plane window shattering3. Depiction of Riordan being sucked from plane window4. Depiction of passengers and crew attempting to rescue RiordanVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: NBC Philadelphia, New York TImes, Dallas News, Chicago Tribune, Southwest Airlines, Albuquerque Journalhttps://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/Airplane-Makes-Emergency-Landing-at-Philadelphia-International-Airport-480008613.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/17/us/southwest-airlines-explosion.htmlhttps://www.dallasnews.com/business/southwest-airlines/2018/04/17/victim-southwest-airlines-flight-identified-new-mexico-bank-executive-motherhttp://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-southwest-airlines-emergency-landing-20180417-story.htmlhttps://www.southwestaircommunity.com/t5/Southwest-Stories/Southwest-Airlines-Confirms-Accident-Our-Hearts-Are-With-Those/ba-p/71993https://www.abqjournal.com/1160065/jet-with-engine-window-damage-makes-emergency-landing.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 08:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/18/3592991/3592991_3B9A0660A48C4FF2BDBA2879765846C4_180418_3592991_Passenger_killed_after_engine_explodes_mid_fligh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1F0/FB8/1F0FB81D8F9B4A46B845327511800E7B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News ,flight 1380, southwest airlines, jennifer riordan, gary kelly, boeing 737, CFM56, NTSB]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592765</guid>
      <title>Night owls risk earlier death, claims study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research suggests people who go to bed late were shown to have a 10 percent higher mortality rate than early risers.The study, published in Chronobiology International, observed 433,628 individuals for a 6-and-half-year period. Fifty-thousand late bedders of those sampled were more likely to die or suffer from diseases and mental health issues.This, co-lead author Kristin Knutson explained, may be due to stress, lack of exercise, alcohol, drug abuse or other unhealthy behaviors. Knutson suggests night owls could try to get to bed early more regularly and be exposed to light early in the morning.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of man going to bed late2. Depiction of health issues3. Depiction of man waking up earlyVOICEOVER (in English): "New research suggests people who go to bed late were shown to have a 10 percent higher mortality rate than early risers.""The study, published in Chronobiology International, observed 433,628 individuals for a 6-and-half-year period.""Fifty-thousand late bedders of those sampled were more likely to die or suffer diseases and mental health issues.""This, co-lead author Professor Kristin Knutson explained, may be due to stress, lack of exercise, alcohol, drug abuse or other unhealthy behaviors.""Knutson suggests night owls could try to get to bed early more regularly and get exposed to light early in the morning."SOURCES: Chronobiology International, Science Dailyhttps://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07420528.2018.1454458https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/04/180412085736.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 01:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/18/3592765/3592765_3C470F18E7EE49EABDF9D7C9139A8CD3_180418_3592765_Night_owls_risk_earlier_death__claims_study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F3E/17E/F3E17E43ABBD4CC39727EF10AD31EF49_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, going to bed late, sleep and health, night owls health, early risers, sleep problems, insomnia, healthy sleeping, unhealthy sleeping]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3592758</guid>
      <title>Study claims hand dryers blast fecal bacteria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANColonies of fecal bacteria have been found in air from restroom hand dryers and can spread throughout buildings, according to new research.The University of Connecticut study found bacteria blasted from hand dryers in 36 bathrooms within the institution's School of Medicine building. The research, published in Applied and Environmental Microbiology, found traces of the harmless lab-made PS533 and Staphylococcus aureus. The latter is associated with infections. The study's lead author told Newsweek the PS533 bacteria traveled from a lab through the air.Researchers also applied their test to restroom hand dryers with HEPA filters, but found that 25 percent of bacteria were still present.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of bacteria spreading throughout bathroom via toilet and dryer2. Depiction of bacteria from dryer3. Depiction of bacteria amount after HEPA filters are appliedVOICEOVER (in English): "A University of Connecticut study found bacteria blasted from hand dryers in 36 bathrooms within the institution's School of Medicine building.""The research, published in Applied and Environmental Microbiology, found traces of the harmless lab-made PS533 and Staphylococcus aureus. "The latter is associated with infections, while the former may have traveled from a lab through the air.""Researchers also applied their test to restroom hand dryers with HEPA filters, but found that 25 percent of bacteria were still present."SOURCES: Applied and Environmental Microbiology, Newsweek, Newserhttp://aem.asm.org/content/84/8/e00044-18.abstracthttp://www.newsweek.com/hand-dryer-bacteria-feces-hands-878925http://www.newser.com/story/257891/bathroom-hand-dryers-spew-fecal-matter.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 01:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/18/3592758/3592758_7A740B2B29A346F58173842D595B2F3D_180418_3592758_Study_claims_hand_dryers_blast_fecal_bacteria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A0F/C5B/A0FC5B9D436C4BE3A769AA0A32E878D3_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bacteria, hand dryers vs paper towels, hand dryers and germs, restroom hand dryer, bacteria in bathrooms, bathroom bacteria, bacteria from flushing toilet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3593903</guid>
      <title>How to properly wear an oxygen mask and hypoxia symptoms</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSouthwest Airlines Flight 1380 suffered a massive engine failure on Tuesday, which forced the pilot to make an emergency landing. When the left engine blew apart, it sent shrapnel through the plane, killing one passenger, and leaving a hole in the aircraft, according to CNN. The hole caused the cabin to depressurize, and the oxygen masks to drop down. One photo from passenger Marty Martinez shows several passengers wearing oxygen masks incorrectly. To properly use the mask, pull down on the mask until the plastic tubing is fully extended. Put the mask over you mouth and nose and breathe regularly. At altitudes over 15,000 feet, people struggle to breathe and keep their blood oxygenated. They can develop a condition called hypoxia and lose consciousness within minutes, according to Business Insider. According to the Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association, symptoms of hypoxia include, "nausea, apprehension, tunnel vision, headaches, fatigue, dizziness, blurred vision, tingling sensations, numbness and mental confusion."Flight 1380 engine failure occurred at 31,000 feet, according to passenger reports.The National Transportation Safety Board is currently investigating the incident. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Passengers wearing oxygen masks incorrectly2. Passenger correctly wearing oxygen mask3. People can develop hypoxia at altitudes over 15,000 feet4. Passengers using oxygen masksVOICEOVER (in English): "After Southwest Flight 1380 suffered massive engine failure and loss of cabin pressure, oxygen masks were deployed. One photo from passenger Marty Martinez shows several passengers wearing oxygen masks incorrectly." "To properly use the mask, pull down on the mask until the plastic tubing is fully extended. Put the mask over you mouth and nose and breathe regularly." "According to Business Insider, at altitudes over 15,000 feet, people struggle to breathe and keep their blood oxygenated. They can develop a condition called hypoxia and lose consciousness within minutes." "According to the Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association, symptoms of hypoxia include, 'nausea, apprehension, tunnel vision, headaches, fatigue, dizziness, blurred vision, tingling sensations, numbness and mental confusion.'"SOURCES: Business Insider, CNNhttp://www.businessinsider.com/southwest-emergency-landing-oxygen-masks-incorrectly-worn-1380-2018-4?utm_source=feedly&amp;utm_medium=referralhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/04/18/us/southwest-pilot-landing/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 10:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/19/3593903/3593903_A43E414365F24B7792C516BD8552EF96_180419_3593903_How_to_properly_wear_an_oxygen_mask_and_hypoxia__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6CB/CC0/6CBCC055BAF743CD967EF4317821BEF2_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, airplane oxygen masks, oxygen masks, how to wear oxygen masks, hypoxia, hypoxia symptoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3593847</guid>
      <title>&#x2018;Man with three faces&#x2019; suffers from rare genetic condition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[French man JÃ©rÃ´me Hamon has become the worldâ€™s first patient to undergo two face transplants. He suffers from neurofibromatosis type 1.According to the Mayo Clinic, Neurofibromatosis 1, or NF1, is a genetic condition that causes tumors to form along nervous tissue. These tumors are typically benign, but in some cases can become malignant and cancerous.Indicators of the condition include six or more flat, light-brown skin spots, small bumps on the iris, and bumps under the skin. The Mayo Clinic says signs typically appear around the age of 10. Other symptoms of NF1 are bone deformities, optic nerve tumors, affected individuals being below average height and perhaps having learning disabilities.According to the BBC, Hamonâ€™s NF1 causes severe tumors to form around his face. Hamon underwent his first face transplant in 2010 but had to go under the knife again in 2017 after medication for a cold caused his body to reject the transplant. That was removed last November, leaving Hamon unable to speak, hear or see for several months.Hamon remained like that in a Paris hospital until January when he received a second facial transplant, according to the BBC.  French media have called him the â€œman with three facesâ€. Despite all heâ€™s been through, he remains upbeat, telling French TV, â€œIâ€™m 43 and the donor was 22, so Iâ€™m 22 again.â€Information from the Britainâ€™s National Health Service says NF1 typically affects one in 3,000 people. Worldwide it affects 3 million people.A 2014 study by the Washington University in St. Louis found members of both sexes have almost equal chances of developing the condition, but it affects both differently. Females are at more risk for brain tumors and vision, while males may suffer more from learning disabilities.Thereâ€™s no cure for NF1, but treatment of the condition can involve pain medication, monitoring, and for cancerous tumors, chemotherapy and radiation therapy. Surgery is used on both cancerous and noncancerous tumors.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/19/3593847/3593847_4A73A8A0348A412A8BD13ADD53C977EB_180419_3593847____Man_with_three_faces____suffers_from_rare_gen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A38/C46/A38C46046F234A0EAE28D630859AE5FB_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,man with three faces,jerome hamon,neurofibromatosis,nf1,neurofibromatosis type 1,NF type 1,face transplant,second face transplant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3593513</guid>
      <title>Genes linked to fatal heart condition identified</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers say they have identified genes that are responsible for a fatal heart condition that can only be cured by heart and lung transplants.Pulmonary arterial hypertension, PAH, kills half of those with the condition within five years, but little was known about its cause, according to the BBC. Scientists say they have now discovered five genes that cause the illness. The results were published in the Journal Nature Communications. PAH causes the arteries carrying blood from the heart to the lungs to harden and thicken, eventually leading to heart failure.Researchers analyzed the genomes of more than 1,000 PAH patients and found that mutations in five genes were responsible for the disease. In people suffering from PAH, these five genes fail to produce the proteins that are needed for the structure, function and regulation of the body's tissues, according to the scientists.Now that the genes have been identified, the next step will be to develop new ways to treat the condition.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of PAH2. Depiction of PAH occuring in heart and lungs3. Researchers analyzing 1000+ patients, finding 5 genes responsible for PAH4. Depiction of PAH occuring in arteryVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers say they have identified genes that are responsible for a fatal heart condition that can only be cured by heart and lung transplants. Pulmonary arterial hypertension, PAH, kills half of those with the condition within five years." "PAH causes the arteries carrying blood from the heart to the lungs to harden and thicken, eventually leading to heart failure.""Researchers analyzed the genomes of more than 1,000 PAH patients and found that mutations in five genes were responsible for the disease." "In people suffering from PAH, these five genes fail to produce the proteins that are needed for the structure, function and regulation of the body's tissues."SOURCES: BBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/health-43727026***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/19/3593513/3593513_A85883F3F48C4DF08068CD465BFD0001_180419_3593513_Genes_linked_to_fatal_heart_condition_identified_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A73/7B2/A737B2636E4044BFB8465495D1EC1745_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Pulmonary arterial hypertension, PAH, PAH genes identified, pulmonary arterial hypertension genes, PAH treatments, PAH heart transplant, PAH lung transplant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3594669</guid>
      <title>Smartphones and polarized lenses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPolarized lenses can impact what you see on your smartphone.According to Allaboutvision.com, polarized light tends to reflect from flat surfaces and can create dangers such as glare and reduced visibility. Polarized lenses combat this with a filter that blocks this kind of light. When worn, polarized glasses can affect the viewing of GPS devices and cell phones. Allaboutvision.com notes boaters and pilots wearing them have reported visual issues with LCD panels on important systems.Popular Science writes that by rotating a smartphone 90 degrees in either direction, a user wearing polarized glasses can line up the glass and phone filters to make the screen viewable again.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of polarized light at the beach2. Depiction of man at beach putting on sunglasses with polarized lenses3. Depiction of pilot wearing polarized lenses and being unable to see important systems4. Depiction of man turning phone to line up polarized filters in phone and glassesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Allaboutvision.com, polarized light tends to reflect from flat surfaces and can create dangers such as glare and reduced visibility.""Polarized lenses combat this with a filter that blocks this kind of light.""When worn, polarized glasses can affect the viewing of GPS devices and cell phones." "Allaboutvision.com notes boaters and pilots wearing them have reported visual issues with LCD panels on important systems.""Popular Science writes that by rotating a smartphone 90 degrees in either direction, a user wearing polarized glasses can line up the glass and phone filters to make the screen viewable again."SOURCES: Popular Science, All About Vision, Randolph USAhttps://www.popsci.com/see-phone-screen-with-sunglasseshttp://www.allaboutvision.com/sunglasses/polarized.htmhttps://www.randolphusa.com/blog/can-pilots-wear-polarized-sunglasses/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 10:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/20/3594669/3594669_27416E3AC3CC4D8AB485BDCD04ED8B92_180420_3594669_Smartphones_and_polarized_lenses_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/480/D7A/480D7A1953E544DB8A7C8E7A5CC2CBE8_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, polarized sunglasses, sunglasses, smartphone, uv light, polarized lenses]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3594572</guid>
      <title>Materials recycled from old Tappan Zee Bridge will be used for artificial reefs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew York state recently announced a plan to use recycled sections of the demolished Tappan Zee Bridge to build new artificial reefs off Long Island's North Shore.New York state Governor Andrew Cuomo announced Tuesday that 43,200 cubic yards of the old Tappan Zee bridge will be dumped into coastal waters off of Long Island.In the first phase of the project, cleaned and recycled materials from the old bridge, steel pipe, and jetty rock will be submerged to build the artificial reefs. The artificial reefs will be expanded at six locations off of Long Island's North Shore. The artificial reefs will create an environment similar to a natural reef for fin fish, shellfish, and sea grass to regrow.Governor Cuomo said the project is the largest expansion of artificial reefs in state's history and will boost Long Island's recreational and sport fishing industries.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show the recycled sections of the bridge will be dumped into Long Island water.2. Cleaned and recycled materials and steel pipe and jetty rock will be used for the reefs.3. The six locations where the artificial reefs will be expanded at. 4. Artificial reefs can create an environment similar to natural reef for marine life.VOICEOVER (in English): "New York state Governor Andrew Cuomo announced Tuesday that 43,200 cubic yards of the old Tappan Zee bridge will be dumped into coastal waters off of Long Island.""In the first phase of the project, cleaned and recycled materials from the old bridge, steel pipe, and jetty rock will be submerged to build the artificial reefs.""The artificial reefs will be expanded at six locations off of Long Island's North Shore.""The artificial reefs will create an environment similar to a natural reef for fin fish, shellfish, and sea grass to regrow."SOURCES:https://patch.com/new-york/tarrytown/recycled-tzb-materials-become-artificial-reefshttp://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/04/18/new-yorks-tappan-zee-bridge-to-be-used-to-create-artificial-reefs.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 08:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/20/3594572/3594572_8B6300DF609A4A8F970DCFE3C9884385_180420_3594572_Materials_recycled_from_old_Tappan_Zee_Bridge_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C62/BC1/C62BC198F6EA458EA21D3799A0E7841F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, artificial reefs long island, tappan zee bridge demolition, tappan zee bridge new york, build artificial reefs, how to build artificial reefs, long island new york]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3596619</guid>
      <title>Facebook moves 1.5 billion users out of reach of new EU privacy law</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook has moved more than 1.5 billion users out of reach of a new European Union privacy law, Reuters reported. Users outside the United States and Canada are currently governed by terms of service agreed with the social network's international headquarters in Ireland. The European Union's General Data Protection Regulation, GDPR, is set to take effect May 25. The new law allows European regulators to fine companies for collecting or using personal data without users' consent.Facebook is liable under GDPR fines of up to 4 percent of its global revenue, around $1.6 billion, for any infractions, according to the Guardian.  Facebook user data from Asia, Africa and Latin America will be transferred from the Ireland headquarter offices to main offices in California.   The change affects more than 70 percent of the site's 2 billion-plus members. As of December, Facebook had 239 million users in the United States and Canada, 370 million in Europe and 1.52 billion users everywhere else.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Facebook moving users from Ireland to U.S.2. The GDPR takes effect May 25, gives EU regulators more authority3. How Facebook is affected by law, Facebook moving users data to U.S.4. Facebook global usersVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook has moved more than 1.5 billion users out of reach of a new European Union privacy law. Users outside the United States and Canada are currently governed by terms of service agreed with the social network's international headquarters in Ireland." "The European Union's General Data Protection Regulation, GDPR, is set to take effect May 25. The new law allows European regulators to fine companies for collecting or using personal data without users' consent.""Facebook is liable under GDPR fines of up to 4 percent of its global revenue, around $1.6 billion, for any infractions. Facebook user data from Asia, Africa and Latin America will be transferred from the Ireland headquarter offices to main offices in California."   "The change affects more than 70 percent of the site's 2 billion-plus members. As of December, Facebook had 239 million users in the United States and Canada, 370 million in Europe and 1.52 billion users everywhere else."  SOURCES: Reuters, Guardianhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-privacy-eu-exclusive/exclusive-facebook-to-put-1-5-billion-users-out-of-reach-of-new-eu-privacy-law-idUSKBN1HQ00Phttps://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/apr/19/facebook-moves-15bn-users-out-of-reach-of-new-european-privacy-law***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 10:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/23/3596619/3596619_533998B5220F41DA94A4D00643FEB3EC_180423_3596619_Facebook_moves_1_5_billion_users_out_of_reach_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/138/9FD/1389FD91595D4EE893CF882A20FEED98_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Facebook, EU privacy law, EU GDPR, General Data Protection Regulation, Facebook GDPR, Facebook user data]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3596596</guid>
      <title>Air India flight hits rough turbulence, injures 3 passengers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Air India flight from Amritsar to New Delhi last week experienced turbulence that left three passengers injured and caused a window panel to come loose. Air India Flight 462 was carrying over 240 passengers on April 19 for its 35 minutes flight to the nation's capital, the Hindu reported. Airline officials said the plane took off at 2:50 p.m. and hit rough turbulence soon after take-off around 15,000 feet due to bad weather. The turbulence lasted for around 10-12 minutes. Three passengers sustained minor injuries and were treated at the Delhi Airport.A window panel inside the aircraft also came loose during the turbulence, the officials said. India's aviation regulator, the Directorate General of Civil Aviation, and the Aircraft Accident Investigation Board are now investigating the incident.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flight path of AI Flight 4622. The flight was carrying over 240 passengers for the 35 minute flight3. Altitude of flight when it hit turbulence4. Flight attendant attempting to put window panel backVOICEOVER (in English): "An Air India flight from Amritsar to New Delhi last week experienced turbulence that left three passengers injured and caused a window panel to come loose." "According to the Hindu, Air India Flight 462 was carrying over 240 passengers on April 19 for the 35-minute flight.""Airline officials said the plane took off at 2:50 p.m. and hit rough turbulence soon after at around 15,000 feet, due to bad weather. "The turbulence lasted for around 10-12 minutes. Three passengers sustained minor injuries. A window panel inside the aircraft also came loose during the turbulence."SOURCES: The Hindu, India Todayhttp://www.thehindu.com/business/Industry/ai-flight-faces-turbulence-leaves-3-passengers-injured-window-panel-comes-off/article23637884.ecehttps://www.indiatoday.in/india/story/3-passengers-injured-as-amritsar-delhi-air-india-flight-hits-turbulence-mid-air-1217507-2018-04-22***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 09:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/23/3596596/3596596_636733D82EAF487C9570C716332F23F9_180423_3596596_Air_India_flight_hits_rough_turbulence__injures__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CE1/442/CE1442F13D864CE1A2DDEAB54AB8AB40_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Air India flight, Air India flight turbulence, Air India turbulence, flight turbulence, Air India window panel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3596560</guid>
      <title>Bill Gates, Airbus invest in real-time EarthNow satellite startup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new startup backed by Bill Gates plans on developing a 500-strong satellite constellation that will make all of Earth viewable.According to the Wall Street Journal, startup EarthNow plans to create a constellation of 500 half-ton satellites that will be launched in phases. Airbus, an investor in the company, will develop the satellites. EarthNow says these will use an upgraded version of the OneWeb microsatellite platform.A press release from the company says each satellite "unprecedented" levels of processing power and "more CPU" than other commercial satellites. EarthNow says the satellites use 'machine-learning' to adapt and interpret what they are observing in real-time.The company says the constellation will be used to monitor many areas, including: conflict zones, evolving storms, volcanic eruptions and illegal fishing. EarthNow also reckons the constellation could also be used to help media tell stories, for crop health evaluation, whale tracking and creating instant 3D models of towns or cities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of EarthNow's plans2. Depiction of EarthNow satellites around Earth3. Depiction of what satellites may observe4. Depiction of satellites using machine learning VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Wall Street Journal, startup EarthNow plans to create a constellation of 500 half-ton satellites that will be launched in phases.""Airbus, an investor in the company, will develop the satellites. EarthNow says these will use an upgraded version of the OneWeb microsatellite platform.""A press release says each satellite "unprecedented" levels of processing power and "more CPU" than other commercial satellites."The company says the constellation will be used to monitor many areas, including: conflict zones, evolving storms, volcanic eruptions and illegal fishing""EarthNow says the satellites use 'machine-learning' to adapt and interpret what they are observing in real-time."SOURCES: Earth Now, Wall Street Journal, TechCrunch, Geekwirehttps://EarthNow.comhttps://www.wsj.com/articles/satellite-project-draws-airbus-softbank-bill-gates-as-investors-1524043058https://techcrunch.com/2018/04/18/EarthNow-promises-real-time-views-of-the-whole-planet-from-a-new-satellite-constellation/https://www.geekwire.com/2018/EarthNow-satellite-video-bill-gates/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/23/3596560/3596560_1646BA7BEF0E49D69C8C08771573A944_180423_3596560_Bill_Gates__Airbus_invest_in_real_time_EarthNow__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/03A/3EF/03A3EF05B837415BAF303AB1B2EF817A_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, earthnow, bill gates, softbank, satellite constellation, satellite network, earth from space, machine learning, artificial intelligence, AI satellite, machine intelligence]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3596459</guid>
      <title>Keeping livers in warm storage improves transplant success, trial finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPreserving livers in warm storage similar to body temperature rather than cold storage improves transplant success a clinical trial has found. Transplant livers are normally kept prior to surgery, however many become damaged and unusable as a result, according to the BBC. The findings were published on April 18 in the journal Nature. For the study, researchers kept donated livers "alive" in a perfusion machine, pumping the organs with blood, nutrients and medicines. The trial involved 222 liver transplants at seven European medical centers. It looked at cold transplants versus warm livers connected to a perfusion machine. The participants were randomly picked to receive a liver warm liver or one preserved on ice. The scientists found 50 percent less tissue damage in the warm livers. They also found that warm livers had a higher transplant success compared to cold ones. Only 16 out of 137 warm livers had to be discarded, compared to 32 out of 133 cold ones.Researchers hope the study can help reduce the number of people that die waiting for transplants each year.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Perfusion machine and organ cold storage cooler2. The study looked at 222 liver transplants3. Liver transplant using warm liver4. Warm liver discards compared to cold liver discardsVOICEOVER (in English): "A clinical trial published in the journal Nature has found preserving livers in warm storage similar to body temperature rather than cold storage improves transplant success." "The trial involved 222 liver transplants at seven European medical centers. It looked at cold transplants versus warm livers connected to a perfusion machine. The participants were randomly picked to receive a liver warm liver or one preserved on ice." "According to the BBC, the scientists found 50 percent less tissue damage in the warm livers. They also found that warm livers had a higher transplant success compared to cold ones." "Only 16 out of 137 warm livers had to be discarded, compared to 32 out of 133 cold ones."SOURCES: BBC, Tech Timeshttp://www.bbc.com/news/health-43808461http://www.techtimes.com/articles/225660/20180419/warming-of-liver-similar-to-body-temperature-improves-organ-quality-for-transplant.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 07:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/23/3596459/3596459_20882C75C7174890A9AAFF924889A2FF_180423_3596459_Keeping_livers_in_warm_storage_improves_transpla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/83B/C64/83BC6434D33646DABA12FA6155EC5026_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, liver transplants, warm liver transplants, perfusion machine, liver perfusion machine, liver transplant success, liver transplant failure]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3596428</guid>
      <title>Human brain cells implanted into mice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have successfully implanted baby mice with human brain cells, according to new research.The findings were published in the journal Nature Biotechnology. The research could lead could potentially lead to new treatments for patients suffering from brain damage or brain disorders, according to the Salk Institute   where the research was carried out.Newsweek reports that researchers took brain cells from human fetuses, turned them fluorescent green and put them inside the brains of mice. Researchers also placed small plastic windows placed over animals' skulls to track how the human cells developed in their new environment. This was observed over a period of several months and human brain cells were observed to outnumber the mice brain cells in some areas, reports Newsweek.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of mouse, mouse brain and human brain2. Depiction of human brain cells and mouse3. Depiction of mouse skull window4. Depiction of how how mouse and human cells interactedVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Nature Biotechnology, Newsweek, https://www.nature.com/articles/nbt.4127.epdfhttp://www.newsweek.com/mouse-human-brains-brain-damage-organoids-893202https://www.salk.edu/news-release/grafted-brain-organoids-provide-insight-into-neurological-disorders/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 06:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/23/3596428/3596428_DCFF4434A06B4085AD3C556FB987C95E_180423_3596428_Human_brain_cells_implanted_into_mice_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2F8/99B/2F899B8EDAE34854A6BFEF09621FF3D6_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  human brain in animal, human brain mice, mouse brain human, weird science, salk institute]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3597271</guid>
      <title>New species of ant explodes to defend colony</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch published in the journal ZooKeys tells of a new species of exploding ant found in South East Asia's jungles.Called "Colobopsis explodens", the ant's body is filled with sacs of deadly toxic substance. They are minor workers in colonies.A lead researcher in the study told the Washington Post, that these ants attack threats to their nests by biting them, and then moving their posterior toward its body.The ants will flex their muscles so hard that their skin will burst and release the fluid all over the threat. Next, the threat would meet these massively insects. These are the colonies' major workers and act as the second line of defense.They remained unknown until now because scientists simply didn't know until recent years know how many types of exploding ants there are, according to the Post. Earlier research in ZooKeys reckons there maybe at least 15 kinds, including Colobopsis explodens.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of minor worker ant2. Depiction of min3. Depiction of ants exploding 4. Depiction of worker antVOICEOVER (in English): "Called 'Colobopsis explodens', the ant's body is filled with sacs of deadly toxic substance. They are minor workers in colonies.""A lead researcher in the study told the Washington Post, that these ants attack threats to their nests by biting them, and then moving their posterior toward its body." "The ants will flex their muscles so hard that their skin will burst and release the fluid all over the threat.""But in doing so, the ants also kill themselves.""Next, the threat would meet these massively insects. These are the colonies' major ant workers and act as the second line of defense."SOURCES: ZooKeys, Washington Post, National Geographichttps://zookeys.pensoft.net/article/22661/element/8/21233/https://blog.pensoft.net/2018/04/19/new-ant-species-from-borneo-explodes-to-defend-its-colony/https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/morning-mix/wp/2018/04/20/meet-the-exploding-ant-which-sacrifices-itself-for-its-colony/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.e33df5c5ba5ehttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/04/animals-ants-borneo-exploding-defense/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 07:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/24/3597271/3597271_F689A6EAE387440E8CF6AD85A25A5F3E_180424_3597271_New_species_of_ant_explodes_to_defend_colony_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E12/B57/E12B57612C39451FB408F3BDC22BB229_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, exploding ants,, ants, colobopsis explodens,, ant colony defense, major ant workers, minor ant workers, queen ant, ant nest, ant colony]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3597238</guid>
      <title>Giant plastics collector about to set sail for Great Pacific Garbage Patch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Ocean Cleanup is building a giant plastic-scooping system in Alameda, California and plans to set sail as early as this summer to begin cleaning up the Great Pacific Garbage Patch.  The Great Pacific Garbage Patch has an estimated 1.8 trillion pieces of plastics brought there by ocean currents and is roughly three times the size of France, according to an article published in Scientific Reports. The Ocean Cleanup, started by 23-year-old Boyan Slat, has designed a massive 2,000-foot long, floating tube that will serve as a barrier to trap plastic.It's made from HDPE plastic and is flexible enough to bend with the waves, but rigid enough to form a U-shaped barrier to trap floating plastics pollution, according to Fast Company. A nylon screen is attached underneath to catch plastics, but not be a threat to marine life. Large floating anchors, hundreds of feet below the surface, help steady the device so it moves slower in the current than the plastic, making it possible to pick up the garbage in front of the device. Ocean Cleanup spokesperson Joost Dubois said that when the final systems are sent out to the Pacific ocean, there will be 60 floating scoops in total. Boats will come every six to eight weeks to collect the plastics and take them to shore to be recycled.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The plastics collector being taken out to sea2. The plastics collector deployed at sea3. The anchoring system4. A boat coming to collect the plastics garbageVOICEOVER (in English): "The Ocean Cleanup is building a giant 2,000-foot-long plastic-scooping system in Alameda, California that will serve as a barrier to trap plastics floating in the Great Pacific Garbage Patch.""It's made from HDPE plastic and is flexible enough to bend with the waves, but rigid enough to form a U-shaped barrier to trap floating plastics pollution. A nylon screen underneath catches plastic without posing a threat to marine life." "Large floating anchors, hundreds of feet below the surface, help steady the device so it moves slower in the current than the plastic, making it possible to pick up the garbage in front of the device." "Boats will then come every six to eight weeks to collect the plastics and take them back to land to be recycled." SOURCES: Fast Company, ABC 7, Scientific Report, Inhabitathttps://www.fastcompany.com/40560810/the-revolutionary-giant-ocean-cleanup-machine-is-about-to-set-sailhttp://abc7news.com/society/the-ocean-cleanup-prepares-to-fight-plastic-with-plastic-in-alameda/3363441/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-22939-whttps://inhabitat.com/the-ocean-cleanup-is-about-to-send-a-giant-plastic-collector-to-the-great-pacific-garbage-patch/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 06:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/24/3597238/3597238_CB17CC0AE1A04656A24B7C4154E362A7_180424_3597238_Giant_plastics_collector_about_to_set_sail_for_G_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/88F/8D2/88F8D2CB97384A608D564E1E0C6B0374_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Ocean Cleanup, Great Pacific Garbage Patch, ocean plastics pollution, giant plastics collector, microplastics pollution, plastics cleanup]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3597990</guid>
      <title>New DNA structure found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have discovered a new type of DNA structure, according to research published in the journal Nature Chemistry.The Independent reports that the structure has been sighted previously, but this is the first time researchers have found it inside living cells.Normal DNA is made up of bases, coded as letters. These are adenine, thymine cytosine and guanine. Normally cytosine binds to guanine, and vice versa, but in the new structure cytosine was found to pair with cytosine.According to the Independent, scientists reckon the new structure may be partly responsible for reading DNA and turning them into useful substances. Gizmodo reports they may act as a sort of switch for controlling gene expression, but could mean nothing at all.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. DNA and the i-motif2. Bases in DNA3. Bases binding in the i-motif and double helix DNA4. The i-motif structureVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in the journal Nature Chemistry details a new type of DNA structure named the i-motif.""Normal DNA is made up of bases, coded as letters. These are adenine, thymine cytosine and guanine.""Normally cytosine binds to guanine, and vice versa, but in the new structure cytosine was found to pair with cytosine." "According to the Independent, scientists reckon the new structure may be partly responsible for reading DNA and turning them into useful substances."SOURCES: Nature Chemistry, Gizmodo, Independenthttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41557-018-0046-3https://gizmodo.com/forget-the-double-helix-scientists-discovered-a-new-dna-1825476635https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/dna-new-discovered-human-cells-living-imotif-australia-research-double-helix-knot-a8318116.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 06:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/25/3597990/3597990_44DF1A2899664B12AC89C25ECB20782D_180425_3597990_New_DNA_structure_found_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F32/22A/F3222A9E2CBE42009C896419C7C7782F_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, i-motif, genetics, dna research, dna structure, double helix, double helix structure, gene expression, dna binding]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3598960</guid>
      <title>North Korea's nuclear test site has collapsed, according to Chinese experts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANReports from two groups of Chinese geologists have found that North Korea's main nuclear testing site has collapsed, which could be the real reason Pyongyang is suspending its missile tests.The South China Sea Morning Post reports that North Korea's last six nuclear tests were all carried out at the Punggye-ri testing facility under Mount Mantap.During the latest test in September 2017, a bomb believed to have an explosive yield of 100 kilotonnes set off a powerful explosion. It caused an initial 6.3 magnitude tremor, and triggered several more earthquakes in the weeks that followed.Geologists from the University of Science and Technology of China analyzed the region's seismic data and found that the blast vaporized surrounding rock, creating a 200-meter hole as the area collapsed in on itself.A large section of the mountain ridge near the peak is also believed to have broken off as a result of shock waves.Researchers from the Jilin Earthquake agency reported similar findings, and added that the collapse created a chimney which could leak radioactive fallout into the air.Both studies concluded the testing site to be unstable and unusable.The area is located close to the Chinese border. But while authorities say no increase in radioactivity levels have been detected, they will continue monitoring the surrounding region.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of nuclear test sites at Mount Mantap2. Depiction of September 2017 nuclear test3. Depiction of earthquakes following September 2017 test4. Hole with 200-meter diameter created as mountain collapses in on itself5. Depiction of mountain ridge breaking off6. Depiction of chimney leaking radioactive particlesVOICEOVER (in English): "North Korea's last six nuclear tests were all carried out at the Punggye-ri testing facility under Mount Mantap.""During the latest test in September 2017, a bomb believed to have an explosive yield of 100 kilotonnes set off a powerful explosion."It caused an initial 6.3 magnitude tremor, and triggered several more earthquakes in the weeks that followed.""Geologists from the University of Science and Technology of China analyzed the region's seismic data and found that the blast vaporized surrounding rock, creating a 200-meter hole as the area collapsed in on itself.""A large section of the mountain ridge near the peak is also believed to have broken off as a result of shock waves.""Researchers from the Jilin Earthquake agency reported similar findings, and added that the collapse created a chimney which could leak radioactive fallout into the air."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, The Guardianhttp://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2143171/north-koreas-nuclear-test-site-has-collapsed-and-may-be-why-kim-jong-un?source=gmail&ust=1524793199971000&usg=AFQjCNEvAmvjwTlqwMOrH9EYexjneF0x5whttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/apr/26/north-korea-nuclear-test-site-collapse-may-be-out-of-action-china***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/26/3598960/3598960_49C29D9981BA4A39AD827398692B761B_180426_3598960_North_Korea_s_nuclear_test_site_has_collapsed__a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/353/6EF/3536EFE0900946C6BA7180927D1F167C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, north korea, nuclear test, nuclear test site, nuclear test site collapse, mountain collapse, mount mantap, mantapsan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3598847</guid>
      <title>How geoengineering technology could cool Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSolar geoengineering specialists reckon technology could cool the planet's temperature by using it to sulfur to the atmosphere.Volcanic eruptions can cool the earth. This is because they emit sulfur dioxide, a UV repellent gas, into the stratosphere.Earther reports that millions of high-altitude balloons carrying sulfur may also be an option. Another option, according to Earther, maybe to use aircraft such as the stratotanker to disperse the sulfur into the stratosphere, as the aircraft can already reach the required altitude. That altitude is around 6 miles from the earth's surface. Citing a leaked UN draft report on global warming, Reuters reports the organization's climate experts opined that solar geoengineering could be "economically, socially and institutionally infeasible." Harvard's solar engineering head Gert Wagner told Earther that deployment of solar radiation management tech would be "unambiguous proof of our miserable failure as a species to act as responsible planetary stewards." RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Earth and Sun2. Depiction of volcano, sulfur dioxide and artillery shells3. Depiction of high-altitude balloons4. Depiction of aircraft in stratosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "Solar geoengineering specialists reckon technology could cool the planet's temperature by using it to add sulfur to the atmosphere.""Volcanic eruptions can cool the earth. This is because they emit sulfur dioxide, a UV repellent gas, into the stratosphere.""Earther reports that millions of high-altitude balloons carrying sulfur may also be an option.""Another option, Earther reports, is to maybe use aircraft such as the stratotanker to disperse the sulfur into the stratosphere, as the aircraft can already reach that altitude."SOURCES: Earther, Reuters https://earther.com/the-machines-that-could-darken-the-sun-to-stop-climate-1825452265 https://uk.reuters.com/article/climatechange-geoengineering/developing-nations-to-study-ways-to-dim-sunshine-slow-warming-idUKL5N1RG47X***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 08:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/26/3598847/3598847_7EF01B0C5D6746FA8288155179375C69_180426_3598847_How_geoengineering_technology_could_cool_Earth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BC7/4E5/BC74E5062A1840A1891BB3DB62B57E12_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, solar geoengineering, srm, solar radiation management, sulfur in stratosphere, geoengineering, geoengineering and weather, stratosphere, stratotanker]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3598761</guid>
      <title>Security flaw allows all Nintendo Switch consoles to be hacked</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHackers have revealed how all Nintendo Switches can be made to run code through an exploit of an unpatchable flaw in the console's Nvidia Tegra X1 chip. The exploit is known as Fuse Gele and was talked about by developer Katherine Temkin from ReSwitched, according to TechCrunch. It makes use of a vulnerability at the silicon level of the Tegra X1 chip's USB recovery mode. The security flaw could allow for unwanted data to be exfiltrated, leading to Switch game piracy. The flaw is unpatchable as the issue is with the hardware on the Tegra X1 chips. This means that millions of Switches will be permanently open to attack. Only new consoles with the code fixed at the factory will be safe from the exploit, according to TechCrunch. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nintendo Switch being assembled2. Tegra X1 chip inside console3. Nintendo Switch being hacked4. The exploit is unpatchableVOICEOVER (in English): "Hackers have revealed how all Nintendo Switches can be made to run code through an exploit of an unpatchable flaw in the console's Nvidia Tegra X1 chip." "According to TechCrunch, the exploit is known as Fuse Gele and was talked about by developer Katherine Temkin from ReSwitched. It makes use of a vulnerability at the silicon level of the Tegra X1 chip's USB recovery mode." "The security flaw could allow for unwanted data to be exfiltrated, leading to Switch game piracy." "The flaw is unpatchable as the issue is with the hardware on the Tegra X1 chips." SOURCES: TechCrunch, The Inquirerhttps://techcrunch.com/2018/04/23/unstoppable-exploit-in-nintendo-switch-opens-door-to-homebrew-and-piracy/https://www.theinquirer.net/inquirer/news/3030823/nvidias-tegra-x1-flaw-allows-all-nintendo-switch-consoles-to-be-hacked***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 06:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/26/3598761/3598761_CE49720F7C564C8087375C31DE28CB43_180426_3598761_Security_flaw_allows_all_Nintendo_Switch_console_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D48/40F/D4840F4755F04116BB5C68A0E9B1D516_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Nintendo Switch, Nintendo Switch security flaw, Nintendo Switch FusÃ©e GelÃ©e, ReSwitched, Nintendo Switch hackers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3598580</guid>
      <title>How gut bacteria could affect the brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRecent studies have been looking at the link between the gut, specifically the microbiome, and its effects on the brain.A study at Kyushu University in Japan found that "germ-free" mice had more stress hormones than mice with healthy gut bacteria, according to BBC. This led researchers to look at treating depression and anxiety through alterations in the gut microbiome.How could gut microbes be affecting and reaching the brain? One possible route is through the vagus nerve, the connection between the brain and gut.Another possibility is that gut bacteria break down fiber into short-chain fatty acids that can have effects throughout the body. Brain disorders have been linked to the immune system, and with 70 to 80 percent of the immune system located in the gut, treating the microbiome could be vital to finding effective cures.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of gut and brain connection2. Vagus nerve connecting the gut and brain3. Gut bacteria4. Gut bacteria can affect brain disorders VOICEOVER (in English): "Recent studies have been looking at the link between the gut, specifically the microbiome, and its effects on the brain.""How could gut microbes be affecting and reaching the brain? One possible route is through the vagus nerve, the connection between the brain and gut.""Another possibility is that gut bacteria break down fiber into short-chain fatty acids that can have effects throughout the body." "Brain disorders have been linked to the immune system, and with 70 to 80 percent of the immune system located in the gut, treating the microbiome could be vital to finding effective cures." SOURCES: BBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/health-43815370?ocid=socialflow_facebook&ns_mchannel=social&ns_campaign=bbcnews&ns_source=facebook***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/26/3598580/3598580_C12D14B19A594D0292B94FBD599FD036_180426_3598580_How_gut_bacteria_could_affect_the_brain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3FC/AFD/3FCAFDDC0F5B4044960F790F83C6F067_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, gut bacteria, gut bacteria brain, gut bacteria mood, microbiome, immune system, gut health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3600017</guid>
      <title>Dark chocolate may have health benefits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDark chocolate may be giving your brain, immune system and eyes some benefits, according to three recently released small scale studies. According to ABC News, in one of the studies, subjects were told to eat 1.5 ounces of dark chocolate, and then their brain waves were analyzed on an EEG machine. Researchers found an increase in gamma waves 30 minutes after consuming the chocolate. According to principal researcher Dr. Lee Burk, "gamma frequency is associated with neurosynchronization, in other words neuroplasticity  It is the highest level of cognitive processing." In another study led by Dr. Burk, scientists look at the effect of dark chocolate on the immune system. Subjects were again given a dark chocolate bar the first week. The following week, they had their blood work analyzed. Researchers say they found an increase in anti-inflammatory markers and infection-fighting T-cells. Neither study was published, and both studies only had 10 participants. A third study published in the journal JAMA Ophthalmology investigated the link between chocolate and vision. In two separate tests, 30 subjects were given two chocolate bars, both dark and milk chocolate, and conducted vision tests roughly two hours later. Scientists found that after eating dark chocolate, participants had small vision improvements.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dark chocolate may affect brain, immune system and vision2. Participants given dark chocolate, then put on an E.E.G. machine3. Participants given dark chocolate, then blood analyzed to see immune system effects4. Participants having vision tested after eating different kinds of chocolate VOICEOVER (in English): "According to three studies, dark chocolate may be giving your brain, immune system and vision some small benefits." "To study dark chocolates effect on the brain, subjects were given 1.5 ounces then had their brain waves analyzed on an E.E.G. machine. Participants had an increase in gamma waves 30 minutes after eating the chocolate. Gamma waves are associated with high levels of cognitive processing.""In another study, scientists looked at the effect of dark chocolate on the immune system. Subjects were again given a dark chocolate bar the first week, and had the blood analyzed the following week. Participants had an increase in anti-inflammatory markers and infection-fighting T cells.""The third study looked at the link between dark chocolate and vision. In two separate tests, 30 subjects were given two chocolate bars, both dark and milk chocolate, and conducted vision tests roughly two hours later. Scientists found that after eating dark chocolate, participants had small vision improvements."  SOURCES: ABC Newshttp://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Wellness/dark-chocolate-give-brain-boost-studies-suggest/story?id=54720101***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 15:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/27/3600017/3600017_78337E10252F44539A7F859FFA1FA1A1_180427_3600017_Dark_chocolate_may_have_health_benefits_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/64E/176/64E17691514244559170BDB2AF7690B6_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dark chocolate, dark chocolate brain, dark chocolate immune system, dark chocolate vision, dark chocolate health benefits]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3599673</guid>
      <title>Geoengineering: cooling Earth with artillery shells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. researchers once devised a plan to cool the planet by firing artillery shells laced with alumina into the stratosphere.In 1992, researchers for the National Academy of Science published geoengineering options that included artillery shells containing UV-reflective alumina and 16-inch naval rifles.The plan would've seen these massive 1-ton shells half filled with alumina and half-filled with dispersal mechanisms and other materials. The scenario would see 40 10-barrel stations located on empty land areas or at sea due to noise, firing five shots per hour, for 24 hours a day for 250 days of the year.The scenario also envisaged the naval rifle firing a projectile containing alumina into the stratosphere. Once there it there it would disperse the substance. Alumina, like sulfur dioxide, can also reflect ultraviolet light.The academy's Committee on Science, Engineering and Public Policy drafted the plan in a 1992 publication titled 'Policy Implications of Greenhouse Warming: Mitigation, Adaptation, and the Science Base'.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of alumina, artillery shell and naval rifle2. Depiction of naval rifles3. Depiction of artillery shell being fired into atmosphere4. Depiction of artillery shell dispersing aluminaVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: National Academy of Sciences (PDF), Geophysical Research Letters,https://www.nap.edu/catalog/1605/policy-implications-of-greenhouse-warming-mitigation-adaptation-and-the-sciencehttps://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1029/2009GL039209***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 08:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/27/3599673/3599673_04836FD87B6E46A090AF4191883BA150_180427_3599673_Geoengineering__cooling_Earth_with_artillery_she_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0BA/9F1/0BA9F1DB073C4253A525F7CC45860A1C_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, geoengineering, solar geoengineering, artillery shells, alumina, aluminium oxide, climate change, solar radiation management, global warming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3599554</guid>
      <title>How hackers can break into your hotel room undetected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFinnish security researchers have found a way to gain access to entire buildings and hotel chains  all it takes is one keycard.According to a press release from data security firm F-Secure, two of the company's consultants discovered a software vulnerability in Vision by VingCard electronic lock systems, which is used in millions of hotel rooms worldwide.The pair wanted to find out if it's possible to open an electronically locked room without leaving a trace, and developed their own software to hack into the keycards.They found that information from a single keycard, even an expired and discarded one, can be scanned and copied using a small device.With custom software, it takes only a minute to decode the card and generate a master key, which can bypass any lock, allowing unrestricted access to any hotel or facility.The two consultants have since worked with lock manufacturer Assa Abloy to fix the software flaw with an update, which was made available to hotels last February.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Software vulnerability in Vision by VingCard electronic lock system2. Key card scanned by device3. Device generates master key4. Master key bypassing locks in hotelVOICEOVER (in English): "Consultants from data security firm F-Secure discovered a software vulnerability in Vision by VingCard electronic lock systems used in millions of hotel rooms worldwide.""They found that information from a single keycard, even an expired and discarded one, can be scanned and copied using a small device.""With custom software, it takes only a minute to decode the card and generate a master key.""The master key can bypass any lock, allowing unrestricted access to any hotel or facility."SOURCES: F-Secure, Reutershttps://press.f-secure.com/2018/04/25/f-secure-researchers-master-keys-to-hotels-can-be-created-out-of-thin-air/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cyber-keys/hotel-key-cards-even-invalid-ones-help-hackers-break-into-rooms-idUSKBN1HW1QB***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 07:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/27/3599554/3599554_1849D2CC8C704C5F9807DAEB5B314C5F_180427_3599554_How_hackers_can_break_into_your_hotel_room_undet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/75F/BDC/75FBDCA7F4A749409CA33977E6C96F0A_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, master key hack, hackers, keycard, key card, hotel security, hotel keycard, hotel key card, electronic lock, digital lock, rfid reader]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3599482</guid>
      <title>Mom warns about 'dry drowning' after daughter is left hospitalized</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFlorida mother Lacey Grace is sharing her daughter's story in the hopes it will save the life of another child from "dry drowning."Earlier this month, 4-year-old Elianna Grace was enjoying some swimming time at her grandparents' house in Sarasota, Florida.Elianna was playing with a pool noodle at the time, and reportedly put her mouth on the toy to blow when someone else simultaneously blew through the other end, causing water to shoot directly down her throat.The child immediately vomited, but 30 minutes after, she appeared normal again.Elianna later developed a fever that eventually subsided. However, a couple of days later, the fever returned.When Lacey took Elianna to the doctor, she was advised to take her daughter to the nearest emergency room immediately.Lacey said that Elianna's heart rate was running high, her oxygen level was low, and her skin was turning purple. A chest X-ray showed Elianna was suffering from inflammation and an infection from the chemicals in the swimming pool.Elianna was diagnosed with aspiration pneumonia, also known as "dry drowning," a condition that occurs when someone inhales water through the mouth or nose, causing water to enter the lungs.Lacey says she read an article a year earlier about a Texas boy  the same age as Elianna  who died from "dry drowning."An updated Facebook post from Lacey showed her daughter in her hospital bed smiling and showing a thumbs up sign. Elianna now recovering at home and is expected to be fine.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of how the girl swallowed pool water2. The girl's initial symptoms3. Dry drowning symptoms 4. Inflammation and infection in the girl's lungsVOICEOVER (in English): "Elianna put her mouth to blow out at the same time someone blew in the other end, causing the water to shoot directly down her throat.""On Monday, Elianna developed fever, which is normal for kids, however, a couple of days later, after Elianna's fever went down and then came back.""Lacey said that Elianna's heart rate was running high, oxygen level was low, and her skin was turning purple.""A chest X-ray showed inflammation and an infection from the chemicals in the swimming pool."SOURCES: http://fox8.com/2018/04/24/mom-warns-about-freak-accident-in-pool-that-left-daughter-hospitalized/https://www.gofundme.com/elianna039s-hospital-fund***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 05:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/27/3599482/3599482_ED917F18B637444CAC4EA5B613CE8811_180427_3599482_Mom_warns_about__dry_drowning__after_daughter_is_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/356/FE3/356FE3CB026D43BBA7DF9EE055520CEB_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dry drowning, dry drowning symptoms, dry drowning definition, dry drowning symptoms child, is my child dry drowning, dry drowning, dry drowning video, dry drowning definition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3600192</guid>
      <title>Researchers unearth evidence of ancient massacre in Sweden</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArchaeologists have discovered the site of a massacre that occurred in Sweden.  Research published in the journal Antiquity details a 1,500-year-old attack on the ringfort village of Sandby borg on the south-eastern Swedish island of Oland. To date, three of 53 houses have been excavated and the remains of 26 people have been found, including children. One of these contained nine bodies.Those remains included mostly male adults, three children and an infant were found inside.They were believed to have been slaughtered by raiders or a fire. Elsewhere on the site shows evidence of an elderly man who had fallen over a central fireplace. Researchers say he was unconscious or dead when he fell. The remains of various animals a horse, sheep, and a dog were also found on the site. Researchers found a plethora of weaponry including swords, spears and shields, as well as Roman currency and items. This part of Sweden was never part of the Roman empire, but was influenced by it. The study writes the massacre occurred during a period of great unrest and migration after the fall of the Roman Empire.  The study notes that those responsible for events at the site may have been trying to establish themselves as a new local ruling elite.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of ringfort dig area and structure2. Depiction of house where 9 bodies were found3. Depiction of house where man was found to have fallen4. Depiction of animals foundVOICEOVER (in English): "Research published in the journal Antiquity details a 1,500-year-old attack on the ringfort village of Sandby borg on the south-eastern Swedish island of Oland.""To date, three of 53 houses have been excavated and the remains of 26 people have been found, including children. One of these contained nine bodies.""Those remains included mostly male adults, three children and an infant were found inside.""They were believed to have been slaughtered by raiders or a fire.""Elsewhere on the site shows evidence of an elderly man who had fallen over a central fireplace."Researchers say he was unconscious or dead when he fell." "The remains of various animals a horse, sheep, and a dog were also found on the site.""Researchers say that those responsible for events at the site may have been trying to establish themselves as a new local ruling elite" SOURCES: Sandbyborg.se, Anitquity, BBC, The Guardianhttp://www.sandbyborg.sehttps://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/antiquity/article/moment-frozen-in-time-evidence-of-a-late-fifthcentury-massacre-at-sandby-borg/5C803B7E77A41439BC3B50D4BF96560E/core-readerwww.bbc.com/news/world-europe-43899393https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/apr/25/swedish-archaeologists-uncover-brutal-5th-century-massacre***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 01:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/04/28/3600192/3600192_4A9A7A77679A45F9978173F4FC85291B_180428_3600192_Researchers_unearth_evidence_of_ancient_massacre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/48B/03D/48B03D8C24444A9E9AFC447DACD3E840_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sweden, sandby borg, sandby borg oland sweden, sandby borg massacre]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3602311</guid>
      <title>Toxic caterpillar outbreak in London prompts health warning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDroves of white-haired caterpillars have invaded the British capital, with experts warning they can trigger allergic reactions in humans and pets.The BBC reports that UK officials have issued a health warning following an outbreak of toxic caterpillars of the oak processionary moth across London and southeast England.The species is a native of Southern Europe, but was accidentally introduced to Britain via imported live oaks in 2005.Each caterpillar contains 62,000 hairs, which are full of spines that can prick skin. They can be released from the body and stay active for up to five years.The hairs contain an irritating substance called thaumetopoein that can cause skin rashes, eye irritation, sore throats, and breathing difficulties.The British Forestry Commission has begun using biopesticides to help eliminate the caterpillars, and have cautioned residents against letting children or pets near affected areas.Traps will also be set for the invasive insects around the 150 hotspots identified by the commission.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Health warning issued over toxic caterpillar outbreak in London2. Caterpillar hairs contain spines, can be active for up to five years after release3. Substance in caterpillar hairs can irritate skin, eyes, respiratory system4. Oak trees treated with biopesticides to eliminate caterpillarsVOICEOVER (in English): "UK officials have issued a health warning following an outbreak of toxic caterpillars of the oak processionary moth across London and southeast England.""Each caterpillar contains 62,000 hairs, which are full of spines that can prick skin. They can be released from the body and stay active for up to five years.""The hairs contain an irritating substance called thaumetopoein that can cause skin rashes, eye irritation, sore throats, and breathing difficulties.""The British Forestry Commission has begun using biopesticides to help eliminate the caterpillars, and have cautioned residents against letting children or pets near affected areas."SOURCES: Forestry Commission, BBC, The Guardianhttps://www.forestry.gov.uk/oakprocessionarymothhttp://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-london-43930702https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/apr/28/processionary-moths-toxic-health-warning***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 09:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/01/3602311/3602311_005795B49F2A4EBA9387DB00F97FD5CC_180501_3602311_Toxic_caterpillar_outbreak_in_London_prompts_hea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CD0/439/CD04392768A6494CBA7BE7A5E544BC1D_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, toxic caterpillars, caterpillars, caterpillar outbreak, caterpillar infestation, oak processionary moth caterpillar, opm caterpillar, health warning, allergic reaction, rashes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3602232</guid>
      <title>GLN hopes to challenge Steam and Apple gaming by utilizing blockchain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGame Loot Network Holdings is planning to use blockchain technology to create an alternative gaming market and player reward system.According to Digital Trends, GLN has raised $2.5 million in presales, but will hold an initial coin offering on May 29. The company said during a test run, they saw $5 million in transactions and had 65,000 users.  The gaming company will use blockchain to handle transactions and its cryptocurrency, known as Loot, as part of its reward system. GLN will also offer a platform called Build to let independent game developers submit game ideas, story concepts and demos, which will also allow gamers to support developers using the Loot digital currency. GLN hopes that by using blockchain, it will help in competing with more established players in the PC and mobile-gaming market, like Steam and Apple.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. GLN using blockchain to compete against Steam and Apple2. GLN using blockchain to confirm transactions and cryptocurrency for rewards system3. GLN raising funds in Loot presales and ICO on May 294. Users using GLN during a test runVOICEOVER (in English): "Game Loot Network Holdings is planning to use blockchain technology to create an alternative gaming market and player reward system to challenge Steam and Apple in the PC and mobile gaming market.""GLN will use blockchain to handle transactions and its cryptocurrency Loot as part of its reward system.""According to Digital Trends, GLN has raised $2.5 million in presales, but will hold an initial coin offering on May 29." "The company said during a test run, they saw $5 million in transactions and had 65,000 users."  SOURCES: Digital Trendshttps://www.digitaltrends.com/computing/blockchain-based-game-platform/amp/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 07:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/01/3602232/3602232_8DAD8466C4524F0A9A5B8D82EE2F6B02_180501_3602232_GLN_hopes_to_challenge_Steam_and_Apple_gaming_by_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/46D/1CE/46D1CE93B04F4EBEAC81D2BBADCB29A6_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, blockchain, blockchain technology, Game Loot Network Holdings blockchain, pc gaming, mobile gaming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
