<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3603968</guid>
      <title>Russia launches its first floating nuclear power plant to the arctic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA massive floating nuclear power plant is now on its way to an Arctic port, after Russia's state nuclear corporation Rosatom launched the nuclear plant over the weekend.Russian officials say the Akademik Lomonosov is set to become the first series of floating nuclear power plants Russia plans to develop.The portable plant is not self-propelled and must be towed to the desired location. It is designed to provide energy to port cities and offshore gas and oil-extracting platforms.The floating nuclear power plant will be towed from St. Petersburg and around Norway to a Russian town called Murmansk to take on nuclear fuel. From Murmansk, the $232 million nuclear plant will head to the Arctic to power the oil-industry town of Pevek.With two nuclear reactors, the nuclear plant will produce up to 70 MW[a] of electricity, enough to power a city of 100,000 inhabitants.Rosatom says the nuclear plant is designed with the great margin of safety that exceeds all possible threats and makes nuclear reactors 'invincible' for tsunamis and other natural disasters.Rosatom also added that the floating nuclear plant meets all the requirements of the International Atomic Energy Agency and do not pose any threats to the environment.Despite such reassurances, Greenpeace nuclear expert Jan Haverkamp told Engadget that having nuclear reactors moving around the Arctic Ocean creates a obvious threat to a fragile environment which is already affected by climate change.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Akademik Lomonosov against a wireframe background2. Akademik Lomonosov docked3. The power plant towed by another ship4. The plant powering an oil drilling platform5. Show the power plant travelling from St. Petersburg to Murmansk to load nuclear fuel6. See the $233 million power plant head to the Arctic to power Pevek7. Representation of the plant powering a city with 200,000 inhabitants8. Show the power plant is disaster-proofed9. Show the power plant meets requirements from International Atomic Energy Agency and does not hurt the environment VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Russia officials, the Akademik Lomonosov is set to become the first series of floating nuclear power plants Russia plans to develop.""The portable plant is not self-propelled and must be towed to the desired location.""It is intended to provide energy energy to port cities and offshore gas and oil-extracting platforms.""The floating nuclear power plant will be towed from St. Petersburg and around Norway to a Russian town called Murmansk to take on nuclear fuel.""From Murmansk, the $232 million nuclear plant will head to the Arctic to power the oil-industry town of Pevek.""With two nuclear reactors, floating the nuclear plant will produce up to 70 MW[b] of electricity, enough to power a city with 100,000 inhabitants.""Rosatom says the nuclear plant is designed with the great margin of safety that exceeds all possible threats and makes nuclear reactors 'invincible' for tsunamis and other natural disasters.""Rosatom also added that the floating nuclear plant meets all the requirements of the International Atomic Energy Agency and do not pose any threats to the environment." SOURCES: ENDGADGET, ROSATOMhttps://www.engadget.com/amp/2018/04/30/russia-floating-nuclear-power-plant/http://www.rosatom.ru/en/press-centre/news/the-world-s-only-floating-power-unit-akademik-lomonosov-takes-the-sea/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 16:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/04/3603968/3603968_4817FF3382464083B8538441FC13A248_180504_3603968_Russia_launches_its_first_floating_nuclear_power_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BA4/298/BA429886A91C401BBFD445F7D7F10BD3_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, floating nuclear plant, floating nuclear power plant, russian floating nuclear plant, first floating nuclear plant, world's first floating nuclear power plant, akademik lomonosov nuclear, akademik lomonosov floating nuclear power plant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3603884</guid>
      <title>People with O blood type more likely to die from serious injury, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPeople who have O blood type may be at higher risk of dying from serious injury, according to a study published in Critical Care on Tuesday. Researchers in Japan looked at the medical records of 901 severe trauma patients who visited one of two emergency critical care centers in Japan from 2013 to 2016, according to the Telegraph. They found patients with type O blood had a death rate of 28 percent, while the death rate of patients from other blood groups combined was 11 percent. Lead researcher Dr. Waturu Takayama, from Tokyo Medical and Dental University Hospital, said "recent studies suggest that blood type O could be a potential risk factor for hemorrhage." People with blood type O have lower levels of the blood clotting protein known as von Willebrand Factor, vWF. "Therefore, a lower vWF level is a possible explanation for the increase in mortality in patients with blood type O, as observed in this study," researchers wrote. Since the study was conducted only in Japan, researchers suggested looking at results over different populations, as different countries tend to have different blood type distributions. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Study looked at 901 severe trauma patients from 2013 to 20162. O blood type patients had higher death rate3. O blood type patients could be at higher risk of hemorrhaging4. O blood type people have lower levels of vWF proteinVOICEOVER (in English): "People who have O blood type may be at higher risk of dying from serious injury. A study published in Critical Care looked at the medical records of 901 severe trauma patients who visited one of two emergency critical care centers in Japan from 2013 to 2016.""They found patients with type O blood had a death rate of 28 percent, while the death rate of patients from other blood groups combined was 11 percent." "The results suggest that blood type O could be a potential risk factor for hemorrhage." "People with blood type O have lower levels of the blood clotting protein known as von Willebrand Factor, vWF. According to the researchers, a lower vWF level is a possible explanation for the observed increase in mortality in patients with blood type O."SOURCES: Telegraph, Gizmodohttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/05/01/having-blood-type-o-almost-trebles-risk-dying-serious-injury/https://gizmodo.com/serious-injuries-are-more-likely-to-be-fatal-for-people-1825681748***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 13:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/03/3603884/3603884_8EBA8D108C824679A7C2A16BB368B862_180503_3603884_People_with_O_blood_type_more_likely_to_die_from_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CA9/F01/CA9F01D65957458A924ABC64A1CC6914_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, blood type, o blood type, o blood type serious injury, hemorrhage risk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3603844</guid>
      <title>Hawaii approves bill banning sunscreen with reef-killing chemicals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe same sunscreen that's protecting our skin is apparently harming the marine ecosystem.The Honolulu Star Advertiser reports that Hawaii lawmakers passed a bill on Tuesday prohibiting the sale and distribution of sunscreen that contains two chemicals known to damage coral reefs.Popular sunscreen brands like Coppertone, Banana Boat, and Hawaiian Tropic have been found to contain oxybenzone and octinoxate, which filter and absorb UV rays.A 2015 study led by the Haereticus Environmental Laboratory in Virginia looked at reefs in Hawaii, the U.S. Virgin Islands, and Israel, and found that the chemicals caused bleaching by eliminating algae and nutrients in the coral.According to NPR, just one drop of sunscreen is reportedly enough to damage delicate reef systems and disrupt the development of marine wildlife.Sunscreen manufacturers and retail and health reps who oppose the ban claim banning the chemicals could leave millions vulnerable to harmful sun exposure.The bill will need to be signed by the governor to pass into legislation. If it does, Hawaii will become the first U.S. state to enact a law of this kind, which will take effect on January 1, 2021.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hawaii to ban sale of sunscreens containing reef-killing chemicals2. Oxybenzone and octinoxate in sunscreen filter and absorb UV rays3. Chemicals eliminates algae, nutrients in coral, causing coral bleaching4. Chemicals disrupt development of other marine organismsVOICEOVER (in English): "Hawaii lawmakers have passed a bill prohibiting the sale and distribution of sunscreen that contains two chemicals known to damage coral reefs.""Several popular sunscreen brands have been found to contain oxybenzone and octinoxate, which filter and absorb UV rays.""A 2015 study of reefs in Hawaii, the U.S. Virgin Islands, and Israel found that the chemicals caused bleaching by eliminating algae and nutrients in the coral.""Just one drop of sunscreen is reportedly enough to damage delicate reef systems and disrupt the development of marine wildlife."SOURCES: Honolulu Star Advertiser, Washington Post, University of Central Florida, NPRhttp://www.staradvertiser.com/2018/05/01/breaking-news/bill-banning-chemicals-in-sunscreens-passes-in-state-legislature/https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/energy-environment/wp/2018/05/02/hawaii-might-be-about-to-ban-your-favorite-sunscreen-to-protect-its-coral-reefs/?utm_term=.43b4349da88bhttp://today.ucf.edu/lathering-up-with-sunscreen-may-protect-against-cancer-killing-coral-reefs-worldwide/https://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2018/05/02/607765760/hawaii-approves-bill-banning-sunscreen-believed-to-kill-coral-reefs***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 12:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/03/3603844/3603844_E6BA974AE5564F8A9878B4BD3BE50D97_180503_3603844_Hawaii_approves_bill_banning_sunscreen_with_reef_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A0/54E/1A054E21FCA745D59D89C0F081DCF7F6_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sunscreen ban, hawaii sunscreen ban, sunscreen, sunblock, coral bleaching, oxybenzone, octinoxate, reef killing chemicals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3603775</guid>
      <title>Southwest Airlines plane diverted after crack appears in window</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Southwest Airlines flight flying from Chicago to Newark on Wednesday morning diverted to Cleveland because of a window crack. "On my way to NJ for work and #Southwest957 gets a window crack," passenger Alejandro Aguina posted over Twitter, according to USA Today. The aircraft was carrying 73 passengers, and no injuries were reported, the airline said in a statement. The twin-engine Boeing 737 took off from Chicago's Midway International Airport at 9:53 a.m. and ascended to 33,000 feet over 20 minutes, according to Flightaware.com. According to passenger Linda Holley, a loud noise was then heard and a large crack appeared in a window. The plane then diverted to Cleveland Hopkins International Airport and landed at 10:46 a.m. There was no depressurization of the cabin, so oxygen masks were not deployed, according to FAA spokesman Greg Martin. The aircraft has been taken out of service as investigators try and figure out the cause of the incident. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Southwest 957 flight path2. Plane was carrying 73 passengers at 33,000 feet when crack occurred3. Cracked window in aircraft4. Plane landing at Cleveland airportVOICEOVER (in English): "A Southwest Airlines flight flying from Chicago to Newark on Wednesday morning diverted to Cleveland because of a window crack." "The twin-engine Boeing 737 carrying 73 passengers took off from Chicago's Midway International Airport at 9:53 a.m. and ascended to 33,000 feet over 20 minutes.""According to passenger Linda Holley, a loud noise was then heard and a large crack appeared in a window. There was no depressurization of the cabin, so oxygen masks were not deployed." "The plane then diverted to Cleveland Hopkins International Airport and landed at 10:46 a.m. The aircraft has been taken out of service as investigators try and figure out the cause of the incident." SOURCES: USA Today, CNN***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 10:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/03/3603775/3603775_ACBCAA74F4B04095834CFC9601C7EA89_180503_3603775_Southwest_Airlines_plane_diverted_after_crack_ap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/13C/1C1/13C1C1E640164A8E8AE49DD10361B9C2_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Southwest Airlines, Southwest plane window crack, Southwest window crack, Southwest Airlines cracked window, Southwest plane diverted]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3604784</guid>
      <title>Rhino bones excavated in Philippines suggest early human presence</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHumans weren't believed to be in the Philippines until 60,000 years ago, but new findings suggest they were there much much earlier.According to a study published in Nature, excavations in the Northern Philippine province of Kalinga have uncovered 57 stone tools and more than 400 animal bones from monitor lizards, deer, turtles, and the now-extinct stegodon.Researchers also found the mostly intact skeleton of an ancient rhino species. 13 of its bones displayed cut marks, indicating it had been butchered for food.CNN reports that the remains were dated to 709,000 years ago. Before this, the earliest indicator of human activity in the country was a 67,000-year-old foot bone uncovered at Callao Cave.The ancients who hunted the rhino were likely an archaic human species called homo erectus that may have arrived from China via Taiwan, or from Borneo via Palawan. Without solid evidence, however, researchers say the hobbit-like homo floresiensis from nearby Flores island may also be a suspect.They plan to continue excavating to hopefully find their culprit, and maybe even unlock more ancient human mysteries.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ancient tools and animal bones found in Kalinga, Philippines2. Depiction of rhinoceros skeleton discovery showing cut marks on bones3. Rhino skeleton dating back to 709,000 years ago 4. Possible origin of migrationVOICEOVER (in English): "Excavations in the Northern Philippine province of Kalinga have uncovered 57 stone tools and more than 400 animal bones from monitor lizards, deer, turtles, and the now-extinct stegodon.""Researchers also found the mostly intact skeleton of an ancient rhino species. 13 of its bones displayed cut marks, indicating it had been butchered for food.""The remains were dated to 709,000 years ago. Before this, the earliest indicator of human activity in the country was a 67,000-year-old foot bone uncovered at Callao Cave.""The ancients who hunted the rhino were likely an archaic human species called homo erectus that may have arrived from China via Taiwan, or from Borneo via Palawan. SOURCES: Nature, National Geographic, CNNhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-018-0072-8.epdfhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/05/stone-tools-rhinoceros-luzon-philippines-ancient-hominins-science/https://edition.cnn.com/2018/05/02/world/early-humans-philippine-islands/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 17:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/05/3604784/3604784_C9BDC9AFD3FE492ABE1E6954317DD17A_180505_3604784_Rhino_bones_excavated_in_Philippines_suggest_ear_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/69B/0F0/69B0F051462746A0B8657E28F5492EA0_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ancient rhino, rhino skeleton, rhino bones, homo erectus, ancient bones, earliest humans philippines, humans in philippines, early humans, kalinga excavation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3604763</guid>
      <title>Pentagon says China injured U.S. pilots in Djibouti with military lasers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. has filed a formal complaint with China after pilots in Africa were targeted by unauthorized Chinese laser activity.The Washington Post reports that the U.S. military's Camp Lemonnier base is located in Djibouti, just a few miles from China's first overseas naval base, which was opened last year.According to Pentagon spokeswoman Dana White, two pilots on a C-130 cargo plane were beamed with high-powered lasers while landing at the U.S. base, resulting in minor eye injuries.Similar incidents had also been reported in recent weeks. Citing intelligence sources, IHS Jane's Defence Weekly reports that the Chinese navy is suspected of using the laser weapons at their base or on a ship offshore.Reports from American pilots indicated that the lasers were of military grade, and originated from the Chinese base on at least three occasions.The U.S. has also requested an investigation on the incidents, though Beijing has yet to respond.Chinese military observers did tell the South China Morning Post it's possible the lasers were being used to scare off birds or spy drones, and may not have been targeting the pilots at all.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of US and China bases in Djibouti2. C-130 pilots injured by high-powered laser beam while landing plane3. Chinese military-grade lasers used on at least three occasions4. China suspected of using lasers from base or shipVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. military's Camp Lemonnier base is located in Djibouti, just a few miles from China's first overseas naval base, which was opened last year.""According to a Pentagon spokeswoman, two pilots on a C-130 cargo plane were beamed with high-powered lasers while landing at the U.S. base, resulting in minor eye injuries.""Similar incidents had also been reported in recent weeks. Citing intelligence sources, IHS Jane's Defence Weekly reports that the Chinese navy is suspected of using the laser weapons at their base or on a ship offshore.""Reports from American pilots indicated that the lasers were of military grade, and originated from the Chinese base on at least three occasions."SOURCES: Washington Post, South China Morning Post, IHS Jane's Defence Weeklyhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/checkpoint/wp/2018/05/03/u-s-accuses-china-of-directing-blinding-lasers-at-american-military-aircraft-in-djibouti/?utm_term=.eae72ddafaa0http://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2144603/true-threat-two-us-pilots-injured-chinese-militaryhttp://www.janes.com/article/79630/us-warns-pilots-of-laser-attacks-in-djibouti***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 17:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/05/3604763/3604763_B0D7D9F699D1495490B7F456687D94FA_180505_3604763_Pentagon_says_China_injured_U_S__pilots_in_Djibo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AFF/8B9/AFF8B9C641E342D5976620680AF09501_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, laser, chinese laser, chinese military lasers, djibouti, camp lemonnier, china naval base, china overseas base, laser eye injury, eye injury]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3604529</guid>
      <title>Tick and mosquito infections spreading rapidly, says CDC</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe number of Americans becoming sick from mosquito, tick and flea bites has more than tripled from 2004 through 2016, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said on Tuesday. The CDC said 96,075 diseases caused by mosquito, tick and flea bites were reported in 2016, up from 27,388 in 2004, according to Reuters.In 2016, infections were up 73 percent from 2015 due to the emergence of Zika, a mosquito transmitted illness that causes severe birth defects. Zika was the most common disease carried by ticks, mosquitoes and fleas reported in 2016, with 41,680 cases, followed by 36,429 cases of Lyme disease. The surge in infections may be the result of global warming, with warmer temperatures and shorter winters boosting mosquito, tick and flea populations. According to the CDC, the increases in cases are due to several factors, including growing insect populations that transmit the diseases and increased exposure to U.S. travelers abroad, who unknowingly transport the infections back into the country. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Number of illnesses from mosquito, tick and flea bites increasing2. Number of cases in 2016 compared to 2004, number of zika and lyme disease cases3. Warmer temperatures have increased vector populations4. Factors leading to surgeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the number of Americans becoming sick from mosquito, tick and flea bites has more than tripled from 2004 through 2016.""The CDC said 96,075 diseases caused by mosquito, tick and flea bites were reported in 2016, up from 27,388 in 2004. Zika was the most common disease carried by ticks, mosquitoes and fleas reported in 2016, with 41,680 cases, followed by 36,429 cases of Lyme disease.""The surge in infections may be the result of global warming, with warmer temperatures and shorter winters boosting mosquito, tick and flea populations." "According to the CDC, the increases in cases are due to several factors, including growing insect populations that transmit the diseases and increased exposure to U.S. travelers abroad, who unknowingly transport the infections back into the country." SOURCES: Reuters, New York Timeshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-health-insectillness/tick-mosquito-borne-infections-surge-in-united-states-cdc-idUSKBN1I2423https://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/01/health/ticks-mosquitoes-diseases.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 11:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/04/3604529/3604529_13743CC87B1D4809A3F242C0546ABBFB_180504_3604529_Tick_and_mosquito_infections_spreading_rapidly___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1BA/862/1BA8625933CB49F8AE14B7414EC64469_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mosquito infections, tick infections, mosquito tick bites, zika, lyme disease, flea bites]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3604426</guid>
      <title>India dust storms kill more than 110</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least 110 people have been killed after fierce dust storms struck the northern Indian states of Uttar Pradesh and Rajasthan late Wednesday.The storms have cut electricity, uprooted trees, destroyed houses and killed livestock, according to BBC. According to Uttar Pradesh's state disaster management authority commissioner Sanjay Kumar, the high casualty rate is due to people being trapped under falling debris caused from high-intensity winds, lightning strikes and fallen trees, according to CNN. The annual monsoon season in India is just starting, where afternoon storms and periods of torrential rainfall becomes prevalent. The powerful winds brought by the afternoon storms could be one of the factors causing so much sand and dust to be swept up into the air.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of dust storms2. Depiction of damage caused by dust storms3. Winds, lightning and fallen trees factors leading to increased casualties4. Depiction of dust stormVOICEOVER (in English): "At least 110 people have been killed after fierce dust storms struck the northern Indian states of Uttar Pradesh and Rajasthan late Wednesday.""According to BBC, the storms have cut electricity, uprooted trees, destroyed houses and killed livestock."  "According to Uttar Pradesh's state disaster management authority commissioner Sanjay Kumar, the high casualty rate is due to people being trapped under falling debris caused from high-intensity winds, lightning strikes and fallen trees.""The annual monsoon season in India is just starting, where afternoon storms and periods of torrential rainfall become prevalent. The powerful winds brought by the afternoon storms could be one of the factors creating so much dust."    SOURCES: Reuters, BBC, CNNhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-storm/storms-kill-at-least-78-in-western-and-northern-india-idUSKBN1I413Xhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-43987209https://edition.cnn.com/2018/05/03/asia/india-dust-storms-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 09:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/04/3604426/3604426_1F2E1EF9A7D2436592473A45228335FB_180504_3604426_India_dust_storms_kill_more_than_110_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A80/58D/A8058D4D5068486993569D77A3F37B8D_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, India dust storms, dust storms, strong winds, lightning strikes, sand storms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3604133</guid>
      <title>Millions die yearly because of air pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew information from the World Health Organization says that 7 million people die annually from exposure to polluted air. The organization says nine out of 10 people everywhere are exposed to dangerous pollutants. According to the WHO, 34% of all pollution-related deaths are due to heart disease and 20% are from stroke. The rest consist of various lung-related conditions including pneumonia, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and lung cancer.Around 3.6 million deaths were connected to exposure from indoor air pollutants such as fumes from cooking fires and stoves. The most vulnerable are children under 5 where pneumonia is the biggest risk to life, women working in smoky kitchens and people who work outside.According to the WHO, outdoor air pollution in cities and rural settings is caused by industry and energy supply, transportation, waste management, dust, farming practices, and household energy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of numbers in WHO report2. Depiction of medical conditions related to air pollution deaths3. Depiction of indoor pollution sources4. Depiction of outdoor pollution sourcesVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report from the World Health Organization says that 7 million people die annually from exposure to polluted air. "The organization says nine out of 10 people everywhere are exposed to dangerous pollutants.""The WHO says that 34% of all pollution related deaths are due to heart disease and 20% are from stroke."The rest consist of various lung-related conditions including pneumonia, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and lung cancer." "Around 3.6 million deaths were connected to exposure from indoor air pollutants such as fumes from cooking fires and stoves.""The WHO says outdoor air pollution in cities and rural settings is caused by industry and energy supply, transportation,SOURCES: World Health Organization, Bloomberghttp://www.who.int/news-room/air-pollutionhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-05-01/air-pollution-kills-7-million-people-a-year-who-reports***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 01:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/04/3604133/3604133_CDD8FED7108B4192BCE3CA5EC124A356_180504_3604133_Millions_die_yearly_because_of_air_pollution_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/989/B6C/989B6C166EF24E188E47C0432AAD75A7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, pollution, air pollution, indoor air pollution, household pollution, world health organization]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3606266</guid>
      <title>Goldman Sachs to begin operations to trade bitcoin futures contract</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWhile most banks shy away from cryptocurrency, one of the world's most well-known financial institutions is all set to bring it to Wall Street.The New York Times reports that Goldman Sachs will soon begin using its own money to trade Bitcoin futures contracts on behalf of its clients.Futures contracts are legal agreements to buy and sell a certain number of assets at a predetermined price, at a specified time in the future.The firm's executives are still somewhat skeptical of Bitcoin, concluding that while it isn't a fraud, it doesn't have the characteristics of a currency. Still, clients were interested, so the company hired its first digital assets trader to handle the crypto-trading operations.Goldman could buy and sell actual Bitcoin in the future, but will need to secure regulatory approval from the Federal Reserve to do so. They will also need to find a way to securely guard the bitcoin, to avoid it being stolen by hackers, as has been the fate of many digital currency exchanges.Experts have noted that the move will likely lend legitimacy to virtual currency, and are wondering whether it will prompt other financial institutions to follow suits.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Goldman Sachs trading bitcoin futures2. What a futures contract is3. Depiction of Goldman Sachs trading actual bitcoin4. Depiction of securely guarded bitcoinVOICEOVER (in English): "Goldman Sachs will soon begin using its own money to trade Bitcoin futures contracts on behalf of its clients.""Futures contracts are legal agreements to buy and sell a certain number of assets at a predetermined price, at a specified time in the future.""Goldman could buy and sell actual Bitcoin in the future, but will need to secure regulatory approval from the Federal Reserve to do so.""They will also need to find a way to securely guard the Bitcoin, to avoid it being stolen by hackers, as has been the fate of many digital currency exchanges."SOURCES: New York Timeshttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/02/technology/bitcoin-goldman-sachs.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 09:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/07/3606266/3606266_58EA0CDEEFC04783B977A9B4B92AD07C_180507_3606266_Goldman_Sachs_to_begin_operations_to_trade_bitco_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C96/666/C966665CD4274A37AD5093AA1DA9E76E_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, wall street, goldman sachs, bitcoin, virtual currency, bitcoin trading, cryptocurrency desk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3606833</guid>
      <title>The difference between lava flows and fissures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHawaii's Big Island continues to be plagued by volcanic eruptions, which have destroyed several homes and forced roughly 2,000 people to evacuate.Reuters reports that lava flows and fissures have caused a large part of the damage, though it's important to make a distinction between the two in order to better understand the situation.According to the U.S. Geological Survey, lava flows are streams of hot molten rock that pour out onto the earth during an effusive eruption.Lava flows come in different sizes and speeds depending on the viscosity of the lava. Its path is possible to predict since flows are confined by topography.Volcanic fissures meanwhile, are linear vents usually a few meters wide and several kilometers long through which lava spews out.Scientists may know the general direction of magma flow underground, but it's impossible to predict when and where fissures will appear.Seismic activity and cracks on the ground may indicate that a fissure will soon appear, but the unpredictability of this force of nature definitely makes the situation in Hawaii even more dangerous.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of magma rising and erupting from a volcano2. Depiction of a lava flow3. Depiction of volcanic fissures4. Depiction of underground magma flowVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the U.S. Geological Survey, lava flows are streams of hot molten rock that pour out onto the earth during an effusive eruption.""Lava flows come in different sizes and speeds depending on the viscosity of the lava. Its path is possible to predict since flows are confined by topography.""Volcanic fissures meanwhile, are linear vents usually a few meters wide and several kilometers long through which lava spews out.""Scientists may know the general direction of magma flow underground, but it's impossible to predict when and where fissures will appear."SOURCES: U.S. Geological Survey, Hawaii News Now, Reutershttps://volcanoes.usgs.gov/vsc/glossary/http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/story/38122335/lava-flows-vs-fissures-whats-the-differencehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-hawaii-volcano/hawaiis-big-island-on-high-alert-after-earthquakes-lava-fissures-idUSKBN1I608N***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 06:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/08/3606833/3606833_89813ACDA70340F98FB4D40419C2CFA7_180508_3606833_The_difference_between_lava_flows_and_fissures_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5A2/32F/5A232F8D071B45CFA6D69EDC937988EC_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hawaii, hawaii volcano, volcanic eruption, lava flow, fissure, volcanic fissure, fissure vent, magma, lava, Kilauea, volcano]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3607377</guid>
      <title>The difference between lava flows and fissures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHawaii's Big Island continues to be plagued by volcanic eruptions, which have destroyed several homes and forced roughly 2,000 people to evacuate.Reuters reports that lava flows and fissures have caused a large part of the damage, though it's important to make a distinction between the two in order to better understand the situation.According to the U.S. Geological Survey, lava flows are streams of hot molten rock that pour out onto the earth during an effusive eruption.Lava flows come in different sizes and speeds depending on the viscosity of the lava. Its path is possible to predict since flows are confined by topography.Volcanic fissures meanwhile, are linear vents usually a few meters wide and several kilometers long through which lava spews out.Scientists may know the general direction of magma flow underground, but it's impossible to predict when and where fissures will appear.Seismic activity and cracks on the ground may indicate that a fissure will soon appear, but the unpredictability of this force of nature definitely makes the situation in Hawaii even more dangerous.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of magma rising and erupting from a volcano2. Depiction of a lava flow3. Depiction of volcanic fissures4. Depiction of underground magma flowVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the U.S. Geological Survey, lava flows are streams of hot molten rock that pour out onto the earth during an effusive eruption.""Lava flows come in different sizes and speeds depending on the viscosity of the lava. Its path is possible to predict since flows are confined by topography.""Volcanic fissures meanwhile, are linear vents usually a few meters wide and several kilometers long through which lava spews out.""Scientists may know the general direction of magma flow underground, but it's impossible to predict when and where fissures will appear."SOURCES: U.S. Geological Survey, Hawaii News Now, Reutershttps://volcanoes.usgs.gov/vsc/glossary/http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/story/38122335/lava-flows-vs-fissures-whats-the-differencehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-hawaii-volcano/hawaiis-big-island-on-high-alert-after-earthquakes-lava-fissures-idUSKBN1I608N***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/09/3607377/3607377_DC33DEE07B354117BD2338F092D373F1_180509_3607377_The_difference_between_lava_flows_and_fissures_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/845/E68/845E687E27BA40B3A4537ACD8EF3C832_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hawaii, hawaii volcano, volcanic eruption, lava flow, fissure, volcanic fissure, fissure vent, magma, lava, Kilauea, volcano]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3607371</guid>
      <title>European Union rolls out tough new privacy legislation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBusinesses operating in the European Union could be fined $20 million Euros or 4% of their global turnover for violating new privacy laws. The fine amount is determined by whichever figure is larger. According to the New York TImes, 4% of Facebook's global turnover would be around $1.6 billion.According to Reuters, the law will apply to social media companies, banks, insurance firms, technology businesses and any enterprise which collects consumer data en-masse.The new law means thats companies need to be more transparent about how they handle user data, get permission for it and gives users power to request for it to be deleted, or moved elsewhere.U.S. Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen warned the law may give rise to more cyber threats. According to Reuters, she said users opting not to give information may hamper internet security research which relies on trends in this data.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of EU data law2. Depiction of companies taking consumer data on board3. Depiction of user requesting, then deleting data4. Depiction of potential cyber security threatVOICEOVER (in English): "From May 2018, businesses operating in the European Union could be fined 20 million euros or 4% of their global turnover for violating new privacy legislation.""The fine amount is determined by whichever figure is larger.""According to Reuters, the law will apply to social media companies, banks, insurance firms, technology businesses and any enterprise which collects consumer data en-masse.""The new law means thats companies need to be more transparent about how they handle user data, get permission for it and gives users power to request for it to be deleted, or moved elsewhere.""U.S. Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen warned the law may give rise to more cyber threats. "She said users opting not to give information may hamper internet security research which relies on trends in this data."SOURCES: New York Times, Reutershttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/06/technology/gdpr-european-privacy-law.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-sandberg-privacy/facebook-to-hand-privacy-controls-to-users-ahead-of-eu-law-idUSKBN1FC1Q6https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-cyber-nielsen/u-s-official-warns-of-unintended-consequences-of-european-data-privacy-law-idUSKBN1HO36J***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/09/3607371/3607371_3A1EC29A4CDA49A8B32B5319194033BC_180509_3607371_European_Union_rolls_out_tough_new_privacy_legis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8ED/5FE/8ED5FEAB9E474F5B884C12C17401BB97_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, privacy, internet privacy, gdpr, digital rights, european union, eu, eu privacy law, eu gdpr law, internet freedoms, malware, cyber security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3607362</guid>
      <title>UK to eliminate wet wipes in battle against plastic pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.K. government announced it will ban wet wipes as part of its 25-year environmental plan to battle plastics pollution. The Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs now classes wet wipes as a serious environmental hazard, along with plastic bags, according to the Sun. Wet wipes are made from polyester and are non-biodegradable. Makers of wet wipes say their products can be flushed, but they do not disintegrate in the sewers like toilet paper, which lead to sewer blockages.A study from Water UK found that wet wipes are responsible for 93 percent of the material causing sewer blockages in the country, according to the Guardian.   An official from the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs said, "we have pledged to eliminate all avoidable plastic waste, and that includes single-use products that include plastic such as wet wipes." RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. UK planning to ban wet wipes2. Depictions of people using wet wipes3. Person flushing wet wipe down toilet4. Fatbergs are made up mostly of wet wipesVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.K. government announced it will ban wet wipes as part of its 25-year environmental plan to battle plastics pollution." "According to the Sun, the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs now classes wet wipes as a serious environmental hazard, along with plastic bags." "Wet wipes are made from polyester and are non-biodegradable. Makers of wet wipes say their products can be flushed, but they do not disintegrate in the sewers like toilet paper, which lead to sewer blockages.""According to the Guardian, a study from Water UK found that wet wipes are responsible for 93 percent of the material causing sewer blockages in the country."SOURCES: The Sun, Guardianhttps://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6226131/wet-wipes-uk-britain-eliminated-plastic-pollution/https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/dec/12/baby-wipes-93-percent-matter-causing-uk-sewer-blockages***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 01:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/09/3607362/3607362_B990252090CA4A1B9FD52EED8C713D10_180509_3607362_UK_to_eliminate_wet_wipes_in_battle_against_plas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0EE/18B/0EE18B9A9E1D478D882FA96428E54521_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, baby wipes ban, wet wipes ban, plastics pollution, single use plastics, wet wipes sewer blockages]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3608131</guid>
      <title>Massive six story deep sinkhole opens up in New Zealand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA massive sinkhole has opened up on a dairy farm in New Zealand, exposing 60,000-year-old volcanic rock deposits.   The sinkhole appeared after several days of heavy rainfall on a farm near the North Island town of Rotorua, according to CBS News. Experts say rains dissolved underground limestone over thousands of years, which eventually caused the ground to collapse and form the canyon. The sinkhole is 20 meters deep, roughly six stories, and around 220 meters long, about the length of two soccer fields.  Volcanologist Brad Scott told TVNZ that the fissure appeared on the crater of a long-dormant volcano. Scott said the deposits at the bottom of the sinkhole were the original 60,000-year-old volcanic deposits that came out of the crater.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of sinkhole2. The sinkhole3. The sinkhole is 6 stories deep and the length of 2 soccer fields4. The sinkholeVOICEOVER (in English): "A massive sinkhole has opened up on a dairy farm in New Zealand, exposing 60,000-year-old volcanic rock deposits. According to CBS News, the sinkhole appeared after several days of heavy rainfall on a farm near the North Island town of Rotorua.""Experts say rains dissolved underground limestone over thousands of years, which eventually caused the ground to collapse and form the canyon." "The sinkhole is 20 meters deep, roughly six stories, and around 220 meters long, about the length of two soccer fields."  "Volcanologist Brad Scott told TVNZ that the fissure appeared on the crater of a long-dormant volcano. Scott said the deposits at the bottom of the sinkhole were the original 60,000-year-old volcanic deposits that came out of the crater."SOURCES: CBS News, Sky News, ScienceAlerthttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-zealand-sinkhole-on-dairy-farm-near-north-island-town-of-rotorua/https://news.sky.com/story/giant-sinkhole-opens-into-60000-year-old-volcano-in-new-zealand-11362925https://www.sciencealert.com/biggest-ever-sinkhole-in-new-zealand-rips-gaping-chasm-two-football-fields-long-rotorua-north-island***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 04:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/10/3608131/3608131_64BB715B1C6140C492D3A8B757FE5346_180510_3608131_Massive_six_story_deep_sinkhole_opens_up_in_New__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/18A/50E/18A50EBB7AF7455989588510ACCBCE56_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sinkhole, New Zealand sinkhole, New Zealand North Island sinkhole, volcanic deposits]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3609370</guid>
      <title>Third-hand smoke can contaminate non-smoking areas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found that chemicals from tobacco smoke can contaminate indoor areas where no one has smoked for decades.The Washington Post reports that Drexel University researchers analyzing air in a non-smoking classroom found that chemicals from third-hand smoke made up 29% of the air mass.When they filled a glass container with cigarette smoke and then treated it with outdoor air, the team found that third-hand smoke chemicals in the air increased by 13% after contact with the container.Experiments show that third-hand smoke residue on surfaces can be redistributed into the air when exposed to chemicals like ammonia, and attach to aerosol particles that enter via the HVAC system.The same system allows the particles to be carried to different rooms throughout a building, exposing people to the potentially hazardous chemicals.Current studies on third-hand smoke indicate it has harmful effects, with one UK study suggesting every 1 in 1,000 of those exposed face an increased risk of cancer.But scientists believe more research is needed not only on the health implications, but also on whether chemicals in increasingly popular e-cigarettes will have a similar effect.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tobacco smoke chemicals found in non-smoking areas2. Depiction of third-hand smoke laboratory experiment 3. Depiction of third-hand smoke chemicals attaching to aerosol particles4. Third-hand smoke chemicals carried to different rooms via air distribution systemVOICEOVER (in English): "Drexel University researchers analyzing air in a non-smoking classroom found that chemicals from third-hand smoke made up 29% of the air mass.""When they filled a glass container with cigarette smoke and then treated it with outdoor air, the team found that third-hand smoke chemicals in the air increased by 13% after contact with the container.""Experiments show that third-hand smoke residue on surfaces can be redistributed into the air when exposed to chemicals like ammonia, and attach to aerosol particles that enter via the HVAC system.""The same system allows the particles to be carried to different rooms throughout a building, exposing people to the potentially hazardous chemicals."SOURCES: Science Advances, Washington Post, Newsweekhttp://advances.sciencemag.org/content/4/5/eaap8368.fullhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2018/05/09/third-hand-smoke-is-widespread-and-may-be-dangerous-mounting-evidence-shows/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.34872f5e3e6fhttp://www.newsweek.com/thirdhand-smoke-scientists-warn-exposure-cigarette-chemicals-where-no-one-has-918694***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/11/3609370/3609370_641C05FC50E941E090C4ABB79DF46646_180511_3609370_Third_hand_smoke_can_contaminate_non_smoking_are_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5FF/1FE/5FF1FE627E3B4B7296E1DF56BB563774_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, third hand smoke, smoking, cigarette smoke, tobacco smoke, effects of smoking, third hand smoke dangers, HVAC, ventilation, air distribution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3609339</guid>
      <title>Over 100 new marine species found around Bermuda</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMarine scientists have discovered over 100 new species in waters surrounding Bermuda. The Nekton project team used special equipment including submersibles, as well as technical divers and remotely operated vehicles. The depth region they looked at is known as the raritrophic zone. Only low amounts of sunlight reach this deep. Some media have dubbed it Bermuda's "twilight zone".Last year researchers sighted a lionfish at a depth of 302m. That's said to be the deepest observed. In another study scientists also detailed a new kind of black coral fauna called Stichopathes poutalesi. This tree-like coral was sighted at 300m deep.Oxford University Biology Professor and Director of the Nekton project Alex Rogers said the discoveries are, "evidence of how little we know and how important it is to document this unknown frontier to ensure that its future is protected."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Structure of volcano beneath Bermuda2. Depiction of different subsea zones3. Depiction of lionfish4. Depiction of black coralVOICEOVER (in English):  "Scientists researching waters around Bermuda and its subsea volcanic seamount have found new species of marine life." "The depth region they looked at is known as the raritrophic zone.""Only low amounts of sunlight reach this deep.""Last year researchers sighted a lionfish at a depth of 302 meters. That's said to be the deepest observed.""In another study scientists also detailed a new kind of black coral fauna called Stichopathes poutalesi.""This tree-like coral was sighted at 300 meters deep."SOURCES: Nekton Mission, Peerj, Biotaxahttps://nektonmission.orghttps://peerj.com/articles/3683/https://biotaxa.org/Zootaxa/article/view/zootaxa.4344.2.11/30295***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 11:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/11/3609339/3609339_6E7E14B93A2C41EB9C7BCB00CEBB0D99_180511_3609339_Over_100_new_marine_species_found_around_Bermuda_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/548/78C/54878CB2A4CB4560A19B67352D91CF61_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, marine life, bermuda volcano, nekton mission, new species found, scientific discovery, sticopathes poutalesi, nekton, submarine, subermisble, deep sea twilight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3609230</guid>
      <title>Researchers say large predators moving into expected areas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study says large predators are moving into unexpected areas in order to recolonize former hunting grounds taken over by humans. According to Duke University researchers in a press release, large predator sightings such as alligators on the beach, killer whales in rivers and mountain lions in open fields are a sign that local populations have rebounded thanks to conservation efforts. The study, published in the journal Current Biology, found that alligators and sea otters were actually re-colonizing ecosystems that had been prime hunting grounds before humans decimated their populations. By collating data from other studies and government reports, Duke researchers found alligators, see otters, river otters, gray whales, gray wolves, mountain lions, orangutans and bald eagles populations were either as abundant or more abundant in "novel" habitats than in traditional ones. Rebounding numbers have shown that several large predators once thought to be highly habitat specific, are actually quite adaptable. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Alligator on beach, killer whale in river, and mountain lion in open field2. Alligator and sea otter feeding3. Populations of large predators that have increasedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Duke University researchers in a press release, large predator sightings such as alligators on the beach, killer whales in rivers and mountain lions in open fields are a sign that local populations have rebounded thanks to conservation efforts." "The study, published in the journal Current Biology, found that alligators and sea otters were actually re-colonizing ecosystems that had been prime hunting grounds before humans decimated their populations." "Duke scientists alligators, see otters, river otters, gray whales, gray wolves, mountain lions, orangutans and bald eagles populations were either as abundant or more abundant in "novel" habitats than in traditional ones." SOURCES: CBS Denver, Duke Universityhttp://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/05/08/animals-predators-odd-places/https://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2018-05/du-aot050718.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 10:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/11/3609230/3609230_CF16222E50EE42E5B1B90E1CD0F7CC26_180511_3609230_Researchers_say_large_predators_moving_into_expe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/972/979/97297918CF4540D08CE3FCBFC4C0975D_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, large predators, large predators recolonization, large predator conservation efforts, large predator sightings, animal sightings]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3610944</guid>
      <title>Paris knifeman was flagged as a possible threat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Paris knifeman, who killed one person and wounded four others in an attack on Saturday evening, had previously been flagged as a potential security risk by authorities. Police have identified the attacker as 20-year-old Khamzat Azimov. Azimov shouted "Allahu akbar" in the busy Opera district around 9 p.m. Saturday night as he began his attack. According to the BBC, eyewitnesses said Azimov was dressed in a black tracksuit and had a beard. Azimov attempted to enter several restaurants and bars, but was blocked by people inside. Authorities arrived on the scene in minutes. Police first attempted to stop Azimov with a stun-gun, but when that failed, they shot him dead.  The man killed was a 29-year-old from Luxembourg, while the four wounded included two men in their 30s, one 26-year-old woman and one 54-year-old woman. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of the knife attack2. Knifeman beginning his knife attack3. Knifeman attempting to enter a restaurant4. Knifeman lying on street after being shot by policeVOICEOVER (in English): "The Paris knifeman, who killed one person and wounded four others in an attack on Saturday evening, had previously been flagged as a potential security risk by French authorities." "Police have identified the attacker as 20-year-old Khamzat Azimov. Azimov shouted 'Allahu akbar' in the busy Opera district around 9 p.m. Saturday night as he began his attack." "Azimov attempted to enter several restaurants and bars, but was blocked by people inside." "Authorities arrived on the scene in minutes. Police first attempted to stop Azimov with a stun-gun, but when that failed, they shot him dead."  SOURCES: REUTERS, BBC, NEW YORK POSThttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-security-attacker/paris-knife-attacker-was-french-citizen-born-in-chechnya-idUSKCN1IE07Ahttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-44096595https://nypost.com/2018/05/13/knifeman-in-paris-terror-attack-was-flagged-as-potential-threat/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 08:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/14/3610944/3610944_E79C3E88CDB04582B6E6DB89E7B3F5F4_180514_3610944_Paris_knifeman_was_flagged_as_a_possible_threat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/108/613/1086138A84E54BFE8AB258DAA5C78182_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Paris knife attack, Paris knifeman, Paris knife attack Opera district, France knife attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3610917</guid>
      <title>Massive wave is largest ever recorded in southern hemisphere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew Zealand scientists claim a monster wave detected during a storm is the largest ever recorded in the southern hemisphere.The BBC reports that according to the Meteorological Service of New Zealand, a solitary buoy measured a 78-foot wave in the Southern Ocean off Campbell Island on the night of May 9.The massive wave is roughly the same height as an seven-storey building, and just a bit taller than five double decker buses stacked on top of each other.It beat out the previous record holder  a 72-foot swell recorded in Tasmania in 2012.The wave formed during a storm, in which the significant wave height or the average of the top third of waves measured from crest to trough reached over 48 feet.Though a record for the Southern Ocean, larger wave heights have been identified in the northern hemisphere.Scientists say it's possible the storm generated even bigger waves that weren't recorded by the buoy, which operates for only 20 minutes every three hours.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 23.8-meter-tall wave recorded by buoy in Southern Ocean2. Wave is as tall as an 7-storey building or five stacked double decker buses 3. Significant wave height measuring 14.9 meters4. Buoy records for only 20 minutes every three hoursVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Meteorological Service of New Zealand, a solitary buoy measured a 78-foot wave in the Southern Ocean off Campbell Island on the night of May 9.""The massive wave is roughly the same height as a 7-storey building, and just a bit taller than five double decker buses stacked on top of each other.""The wave formed during a storm, in which the significant wave height or the average of the top third of waves measured from crest to trough reached over 48 feet.""Scientists say it's possible the storm generated even bigger waves that weren't recorded by the buoy, which operates for only 20 minutes every three hours."SOURCES: BBC, Sydney Morning Herald, ABC Newshttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-44078255https://www.smh.com.au/environment/weather/surf-s-really-up-largest-wave-ever-recorded-in-southern-ocean-20180510-p4zej6.htmlhttp://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-11/largest-wave-ever-recorded-in-southern-ocean/9751680***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 07:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/14/3610917/3610917_CEB4F2BCA213402EB68647075AA77325_180514_3610917_Massive_wave_is_largest_ever_recorded_in_souther_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/03D/69D/03D69DD88D9543638864FEAB3D57AAE3_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, massive wave, largest wave, monster wave, southern hemisphere, southern ocean, wave height, significant wave height, buoy, storm, stormy, new zealand, campbell island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3610850</guid>
      <title>Study posits sun will form nebula on death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research published in Nature Astronomy suggests the sun will become a planetary nebula. These are formed by a collapsed star's core lighting up surrounding gas and dust it ejected during the final stages of stellar death. This can last for around 10,000 years, reports the Smithsonian.The Smithsonian adds that previous research posited that the sun's dying core wouldn't warm up quick enough to do this, but the new study demonstrates it could actually heat at triple this speed.That means it has the potential to form a faint planetary nebula. A researcher on the study to the Guardian that the nebula would be viewable from the Andromeda galaxy 2 million light years away.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the sun becoming a red giant and consuming planets2. Depiction of a white dwarf becoming a nebula3. Depiction of the sun heating three times as fast in new theory4. Depiction of sun's post-death nebula from exoplanet in Andromeda galaxyVOICEOVER (in English): "When the sun comes to the end of its life cycle, it'll become a red giant and expand so much it may consume some planets like Mercury and Venus." "After this it is believed to become a white dwarf and eventually die.""New research published in Nature Astronomy suggests the sun will become a planetary nebula." "These are formed by a collapsed star's core lighting up surrounding gas and dust it ejects during the final stages of stellar death. This can last for around 10,000 years.""Previous research posited that the sun's dying core wouldn't warm up quick enough to do this, but the new study demonstrates it could actually heat at triple the original believed speed.""That means it has the potential to form a faint planetary nebula.""A researcher on the study told the Guardian the nebula would be viewable from the andromeda galaxy 2 million light years away."SOURCES: Nature Astronomy, The Guardian, Smithsonian, Phys.org (Press Release)https://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-018-0453-9.epdfhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/may/07/sun-will-flare-into-massive-planetary-nebula-when-it-dieshttps://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/sun-will-produce-beautiful-planetary-nebula-when-it-dies-180969028/https://phys.org/news/2018-05-sun-dies.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 05:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/14/3610850/3610850_433CB5854F79456BAAD91AF53C0481A9_180514_3610850_Study_posits_sun_will_form_nebula_on_death_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/852/E5A/852E5AFF76884F4888D32021070906A8_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sun, planetary nebula, sun becomes nebula, what happens when the sun burns out, astronomy, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3611857</guid>
      <title>Melania Trump treated for benign kidney condition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFirst lady Melania Trump underwent an "embolization procedure" to treat a benign kidney condition at Walter Reed National Military Medical Center, the White House said on Monday.The White House said the surgery was successful with no complications, and that the first lady would most likely remain in the hospital for the duration of the week, according to CNN. During an embolization procedure, blood supply is cut to a certain part of the body, in order to stop oxygen flow to the affected area.One instance where a benign kidney growth would require an embolization procedure is with an angiomyolipoma, a benign collection of fat and muscle .  According to CBS News, embolizations can also be used to treat aneurysms, or artery bulges, and arteriovenous malformation, or abnormal artery and vein connections. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of the procedure2. Depiction of an embolization3. Angiomyolipoma on kidney4. Embolizations can also be used to treat aneurysms and arteriovenous malformationVOICEOVER (in English): "First lady Melania Trump underwent an 'embolization procedure' to treat a benign kidney condition at Walter Reed National Military Medical Center on Monday morning."The White House said the surgery was successful with no complications, and that the first lady would most likely remain in the hospital for the duration of the week." "During an embolization procedure, blood supply is cut to a certain part of the body, in order to stop oxygen flow to the affected area.""One instance where a benign kidney growth would require an embolization procedure is with an angiomyolipoma, a benign collection of fat and muscle.""According to CBS News, embolizations can also be used to treat aneurysms, or artery bulges, and arteriovenous malformation, or abnormal artery and vein connections." SOURCES: CNN, CBS Newshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/05/14/health/melania-trumps-kidney-procedure-explained/index.html?no-st=1526341230https://www.cbsnews.com/news/first-lady-melania-trump-hospitalized-for-embolization-procedure-to-treat-kidney-condition-today-2018-05-14/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 12:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/15/3611857/3611857_177D9D511B8046DE8E61B2D529D65635_180515_3611857_Melania_Trump_treated_for_benign_kidney_conditio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8BA/42C/8BA42C66B5994747A0141796D8C40F12_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kidney embolization, kidney embolization procedure, Melania Trump kidney embolization, Melania Trump benign kidney condition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3611810</guid>
      <title>'Explosive eruptions' possible in Hawaii</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGeologists have warned an explosive eruption is possible at Hawaii's Kilauea volcano.Writing last Wednesday, the United States Geological Survey said if lava at the Kilauea volcano summit drops beneath groundwater levels, the inflow of water could result in steam-driven explosions.The USGS warns that steam-driven ballistic projectiles  blocks measuring 2 meters across and weighing up to several tons  could be sent flying 1 kilometer from the summit. Smaller blocks may travel farther.Citing geologists, Reuters reports an explosive eruption could send ash plumes as high as 6,000 meters. Ash clouds and other, even smaller debris from such an even could spread up to 19.2 kilometers from the Kilauea summit.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Kilauea lava lake2. Depiction of ballistic projectiles3. Depiction of gas plume heightVOICEOVER (in English): "The United States Geological Survey said if lava in the Kilauea volcano summit drops beneath groundwater levels, the inflow of water could result in steam-driven explosions.""The USGS warns that steam-driven ballistic projectiles, blocks measuring 2 meters across and weighing up to several tons, could be sent flying 1 kilometer from the summit.""Smaller blocks may travel further.""Citing geologists, Reuters reports an explosive eruption could send ash plumes as high as 6,000 meters."SOURCES: USGS, Reutershttps://volcanoes.usgs.gov/observatories/hvo/https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-hawaii-volcano/cracks-in-hawaii-volcano-roar-amid-warnings-of-more-idUKKCN1IF02V***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 11:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/15/3611810/3611810_55914243CA60461FB0EA6C403EC18CE3_180515_3611810__Explosive_eruptions__possible_in_Hawaii_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/817/A9E/817A9E5405F74494A9AB324E94BFA772_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kilauea, volcano, hawaii eruption 2018, kilauea eruption, explosive eruption, natural disasters]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3612343</guid>
      <title>Sichuan Airlines co-pilot sucked halfway out of cockpit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Sichuan Airlines co-pilot was sucked halfway out of an aircraft cockpit when it windshield shattered mid-flight, according to Chinese state media. Flight 3U8633 was flying from Chongqing to Lhasa. The Airbus A319 aircraft was carrying 119 passengers. Captain Liu Chuanjian told the Chengdu Economic Daily, the aircraft was cruising mid-flight when the windshield suddenly cracked and made a loud bang. The co-pilot was sucked halfway out of the cockpit window, but he was wearing his seatbelt. He was dragged back into the cockpit. The plane was then forced to make an emergency landing. None of the passengers were harmed. The co-pilot suffered scratches and a sprained wrist. An investigation has started into the incident. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The aircraft was carrying 119 passengers2. The windshield cracking mid-flight3. The co-pilot sucked halfway out of cockpit window4. The plane landingVOICEOVER (in English): "Sichuan Airlines Flight 3U8633 was flying from Chongqing to Lhasa carrying 119 passengers.""Captain Liu Chuanjian told the Chengdu Economic Daily, the aircraft was cruising mid-flight when the windshield suddenly cracked and made a loud bang.""The co-pilot was sucked halfway out of the cockpit window, but he was wearing his seatbelt. He was dragged back into the cockpit." "The plane was then forced to make an emergency landing. None of the passengers were harmed. The co-pilot suffered scratches and a sprained wrist." SOURCES: BBC, CNNhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-44121377?ocid=socialflow_facebook&ns_mchannel=social&ns_campaign=bbcnews&ns_source=facebookhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/05/15/asia/chinese-airline-accident-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 08:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/16/3612343/3612343_0DAFE397D1D2425EBB6389DB15F32EE6_180516_3612343_Sichuan_Airlines_co_pilot_sucked_halfway_out_of__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ACC/A88/ACCA8822E1324191BF725993964962EF_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, co-pilot sucked out, co-pilot almost sucked out, Sichuan Airlines co-pilot halfway sucked out, sucked out of plane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3612264</guid>
      <title>What the symptoms of necrotizing fasciitis?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Indianapolis woman died two months after contracting necrotizing fasciitis, commonly known as flesh-eating bacteria, while on vacation in Florida. According to Tech Times, 50-year-old Carol Martin was misdiagnosed by doctors twice. It wasn't until her third visit to the hospital, after her condition had become serious, did physicians realize it was flesh-eating bacteria. According the Centers for Disease and Control and Prevention, necrotizing fasciitis is a serious bacterial infection that spreads quickly and kills the body's soft tissue. People with flesh-eating bacteria usually begin to display symptoms within a couple of hours after an injury. Symptoms may seem like another injury or illness. Some people complain of a pulled muscle like pain or soreness. The skin may also get warm and form red or purplish areas of inflammation that rapidly spread. Later symptoms can include fever, chills, fatigue and vomiting. If you're experiencing any of these symptoms, seek immediate medical attention.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bacteria killing soft tissue2. Flesh-eating bacteria symptoms normally appear within hours3. Flesh-eating bacteria affecting skin cross section4. Later symptoms can include fever, chills, fatigue and vomitingVOICEOVER (in English): "According the Centers for Disease and Control and Prevention, necrotizing fasciitis is a serious bacterial infection that spreads quickly and kills the body's soft tissue." "People with flesh-eating bacteria usually begin to display symptoms within a couple of hours after an injury. Symptoms may seem like another injury or illness. Some people complain of a pulled muscle like pain or soreness." "The skin may also get warm and form red or purplish areas of inflammation that rapidly spread." "Later symptoms can include fever, chills, fatigue and vomiting." SOURCES: Tech Times, CDChttp://www.techtimes.com/articles/227639/20180513/indianapolis-woman-dies-from-misdiagnosed-necrotizing-fasciitis-what-are-the-symptoms-of-flesh-eating-disease.htmhttps://www.cdc.gov/features/necrotizingfasciitis/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 06:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/16/3612264/3612264_14447309BDDA432A95A9DA1B543727C4_180516_3612264_What_the_symptoms_of_necrotizing_fasciitis__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3D7/6DD/3D76DDAC0E7E43DBA9D8977D0C32D22A_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, necrotizing fasciitis, flesh-eating bacteria, flesh eating bacteria symptoms, necrotizing fasciitis symptoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3612246</guid>
      <title>MH370 deliberately crashed by captain, suggest aviation experts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA panel of aviation experts have suggested that Malaysian Airlines flight MH370 was deliberately flown off-course and crashed.CBS reports that the experts put together by 60 Minutes Australia believe the captain masterminded the plane's disappearance, in what is possibly an intricately planned mass murder-suicide.According to Boeing 777 pilot and instructor Simon Hardy, the aircraft flew along the Thai-Malaysian border, criss-crossing into both countries' airspace to avoid detection.Captain Zaharie Ahmad Shah dipped the plane's wings left over his hometown of Penang, leading Hardy to suspect he looked out the window in an emotional goodbye. The plane then turned northwest before dropping off the range of military radar.Crash investigator Larry Vance believes the captain depressurized the cabin at some point to disable passengers, which could explain the lack of any texts or emergency calls.Satellite data had picked up faint signals from the plane's engines, showing it could have flown either north toward Kazakhstan, or south to the Indian Ocean. Calculations indicated the latter.In searching for the missing plane, the Australian Transport and Safety Bureau worked under the assumption that it crashed into the ocean following an uncontrolled dive.Hardy believes the pilot was controlling the aircraft until the end. He would have easily pulled out of the death dive and flown longer before impact, which would put the crash site outside the current search area.While the experts present some compelling theories, the fact remains that four years on, the plane has yet to be found.Without solid evidence from the wreckage, there's no way to definitively unravel the mysteries surrounding MH370.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Malaysian Airlines flight MH370 flying over Thai-Malaysian border2. MH370 captain dipping left wing to look out at Penang3. Depiction of cabin depressurization incapacitating passengers4. Satellite data indicating plane's possible endpoint5. Depiction of death dive scenario6. Depiction of death dive counter-scenarioVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Boeing 777 pilot and instructor Simon Hardy, the aircraft flew along the Thai-Malaysian border, criss-crossing into both countries' airspace to avoid detection.""Captain Zaharie Ahmad Shah dipped the plane's wings left over his hometown of Penang, leading Hardy to suspect he looked out the window in an emotional goodbye. The plane then turned northwest before dropping off the range of military radar.""Crash investigator Larry Vance believes the captain depressurized the cabin at some point to disable passengers, which could explain the lack of any texts or emergency calls.""Satellite data had picked up faint signals from the plane's engines, showing it could have flown either north toward Kazakhstan, or south to the Indian Ocean. Calculations indicated the latter.""In searching for the missing plane, the Australian Transport and Safety Bureau worked under the assumption that it crashed into the ocean following an uncontrolled dive.""Hardy believes the pilot was controlling the aircraft until the end. He would have easily pulled out of the death dive and flown longer before impact, which would put the crash site outside the current search area."SOURCES: 60 Minutes Australia, CBS, Washington Posthttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cm1j1fpldkchttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/malaysia-airlines-flight-370-crash-deliberate-panel-of-aviation-experts/https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2018/05/14/mh370-experts-think-theyve-finally-solved-the-mystery-of-the-doomed-malaysia-airlines-flight/?utm_term=.5e81d77ffb91***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 06:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/16/3612246/3612246_71DA4A88254441989AF71ACDA8D460B6_180516_3612246_MH370_deliberately_crashed_by_captain__suggest_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B82/DC8/B82DC833FDF1491BB4CBFE331AF4E324_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mh370 mystery, malaysian airlines, malaysia airlines, malaysian airlines disappearance, mh370 disappearance, plane crash, missing plane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3613091</guid>
      <title>Dark energy may not impact planet formation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research simulating the effects of dark energy on star formation speculates that alien life may exist in another universe.Star formation, according to Durham Cosmology Professor Richard Bower, is the battle between the attraction of gravity and repulsion of dark energy. Our universe is believed to host very little of the substance. Scientists speculate large amounts of the theoretical substance creates dead universes.Researchers simulated the impact of several hundred times more dark energy and found it had only a modest impact on star and planet formation. The small amount of dark energy in our own universe, according to the researchers, may be due to an undiscovered law of nature.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of dark energy2. Depiction of star formation3. Depiction of a universe forming with dark energy4. Depiction of the solar system with dark energyVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Durham University, Fox Newshttps://www.dur.ac.uk/news/newsitem/?itemno=34583http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/05/15/scientists-believe-alien-life-may-exist-in-other-universes-after-discovering-mysterious-force.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 07:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/17/3613091/3613091_F30AD1FFAD3A4FAAA58C380955C4C1DD_180517_3613091_Dark_energy_may_not_impact_planet_formation_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/028/9DC/0289DCAD7766439AA41F6513F0A422B7_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dark energy, dark energy aliens, multiverse, dark energy, gravity, star formation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3613081</guid>
      <title>Massive security operation deployed for royal wedding</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn preparation for Prince Harry and Meghan Markle's May 19 royal wedding, a massive security operation has been deployed throughout Windsor. More than 100,000 expected visitors will have to pass through tight security measures to get into the small town, according to Reuters.   Around 3,000 police officers are also expected to be on hand. In addition to road closures which will seal off the town and police patrols, visitors will have to pass through airport-style scanning checks before they can reach the street surrounding the castle, Reuters reported. Automatic license plate recognition technology has been checking vehicles entering town, while authorities have been conducting random stops, according to NBC News. Large steel and concrete barriers have been erected in and around Windsor to prevent vehicle attacks.  Police have been searching through garbage bins, searching drain and manhole covers and using sniffer dogs to search mailboxes. According the Thames Valley Police, counter-drone systems may also be used as part of the security operation.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The town will close roads, have police patrols and airport-style scanning checks2. A road security stop and anti-vehicle barriers3. Police searching bins, drains and mailboxes4. Counter-drone systemVOICEOVER (in English): "More than 100,000 expected visitors will face tight security measures in Windsor for the May 19 royal wedding. In addition to road closures which will seal the town off and police patrols, visitors will have to pass airport-style scanning checks to reach the street surrounding the castle.""Automatic license plate recognition technology has been checking vehicles entering town, while authorities have been conducting random stops. Large steel and concrete barriers have been erected in and around Windsor to prevent vehicle attacks.""Police have been searching through garbage bins, searching drain and manhole covers and using sniffer dogs to search mailboxes."   "According the Thames Valley Police, counter-drone systems may also be used as part of the security operation."  SOURCES: BBC, Reuters, NBC Newshttp://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-berkshire-43839855https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-royals-security/no-threat-but-uk-royal-wedding-fans-in-windsor-face-tight-security-idUSKCN1IH22Bhttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/huge-security-operation-descend-prince-harry-meghan-markle-wedding-n872281***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 07:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/17/3613081/3613081_4EB3692FB9734E13B5FEEC9715E171A1_180517_3613081_Massive_security_operation_deployed_for_royal_we_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6AC/BCF/6ACBCF69E4ED4247811661FD78A4948F_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, royal wedding security, UK royal wedding, royal wedding security measures, Prince Harry, Meghan Markle, royal wedding tight security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3613022</guid>
      <title>Chimpanzees have cleaner beds than humans, study says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChimpanzees maintain cleaner beds compared to humans because they in essence change their sheets every night, according to a new study. Researchers from North Carolina State University published their findings in the Royal Society Open Science journal on Tuesday.  Scientists swabbed chimpanzee nests in the Issa Valley in Tanzania and discovered only 3.5 percent of the bacteria found originated from the chimps' own skin, saliva or feces, the National Geographic reported.According to a previous North Carolina study, human beds in comparison had bacteria levels around 35 percent. The team also found that chimpanzee nests had few ticks and fleas. One explanation for the difference in levels of bacteria, is that chimps build a new nest each night, while humans sleep typically sleep in the same room.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chimps have cleaner beds than humans2. Chimp nests had bacteria levels of 3.5%3. Human beds had bacteria levels of 35%4. Chimp building a nestVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the journal the Royal Society Open Science, chimpanzees maintain cleaner beds compared to humans because they in essence change their sheets every night." "According to National Geographic, scientists from North Carolina State University swabbed chimpanzee nests in the Issa Valley in Tanzania and discovered only 3.5 percent of the bacteria found originated from the chimps' own skin, saliva or feces." "This is in comparison to a previous North Carolina study that found human beds with bacteria levels around 35 percent." "One explanation for the difference in levels of bacteria, is that chimps build a new nest each night, while humans typically sleep in the same room."  SOURCES: National Geographic, The Telegraphhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/05/chimpanzee-animals-beds-health/https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/05/15/chimpanzees-have-cleaner-beds-humans-say-scientists/amp/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 06:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/17/3613022/3613022_8AAB1CAD12C14855A18AB9194562E3DA_180517_3613022_Chimpanzees_have_cleaner_beds_than_humans__study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/66A/4A4/66A4A400C5E34208A743E48B802DD964_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, chimpanzee, chimps, chimpanzee beds cleaner human beds, chimps cleaner humans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3612994</guid>
      <title>Poor sleep patterns linked to mood disorders</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have connected irregular sleep patterns with mood disorders and depression.Disrupting the body's circadian rhythm by going to bed late and using smartphones late at night maybe impacting people's mental health.Research published in the Lancet suggests people more active at night than in the day are up to 10% more likely to be found to have a mood disorder.The study found higher rates of depression, unhappiness, bipolar disorder, loneliness, mood instability and poor reaction-times in individuals with disrupted body clocks, the BBC reported.Speaking in the Guardian, a researcher recommended not using mobile phones, or getting drinks late at night, and avoiding other activities at night.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of man using phone late at night 2. Depiction of man waking late in day and feeling low 3. Depiction of habits recommended to avoidVOICEOVER (in English):  "Disrupting the body's circadian rhythm by going to bed late and using smartphones late at night maybe impacting people's mental health.""Research published in the Lancet suggests people more active at night than in the day are up to 10% more likely to be found to have a mood disorder.""Speaking in the Guardian, a researcher recommended not using mobile phones, or getting drinks late at night, and avoiding other activities at night."SOURCES: The Guardian, BBChttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/may/15/disruption-of-daily-rhythms-linked-to-mental-health-problemshttp://www.bbc.com/news/health-44113414***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 05:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/17/3612994/3612994_E2836BCFCAAC42EC98A94D6620883BC0_180517_3612994_Poor_sleep_patterns_linked_to_mood_disorders_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AFB/24A/AFB24A9BCB29416890059A5040730AB8_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sleep, sleep research, science, sleep and mental health, smartphone and sleep]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3612990</guid>
      <title>UK police face recognition tech wrong in 98% of cases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFace recognition technology used by British police is inaccurate in many cases according to new findings.New findings by British newspaper the Independent say that facial recognition technology employed by the UK's Metropolitan Police force is wrong 98% of the time.The newspaper reports that of 104 alerts created by the force's face recognition system, only two were correct.Elsewhere, the Independent also found that facial recognition used by police in Wales has been wrong 2,400 times since last June.The newspaper reports that most of this happened last summer in Cardiff when the city was hosting UEFA Champions League final. Less than 10 percent were accurate matches.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of cameras watching a busy UK street2. Depiction of Metropolitan police facial recognition accuracy statistics 3. Depiction of camera scanning faces of people4. Depiction of camera scanning busy crowdVOICEOVER (in English): "New findings by British newspaper the Independent say that facial recognition technology employed by the UK's Metropolitan Police force is wrong 98% of the time.""The newspaper reports that of 104 alerts created by the force's face recognition system, only two were correct.""Elsewhere, the Independent also found that facial recognition used by police in Wales has been wrong 2,400 times since last June.""The newspaper reports that most of this happened last summer in Cardiff when the city was hosting UEFA Champions League final.""Less than 10 percent were accurate matches."SOURCES: Independent, CNET, BBC https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/met-police-facial-recognition-success-south-wales-trial-home-office-false-positive-a8345036.htmlhttps://www.cnet.com/news/facial-recognition-software-inaccurate-in-98-of-metropolitan-police-cases-reports/http://www.bbc.com/news/technology-44089161***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 05:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/17/3612990/3612990_7499A8B8CDD4490D86F1CDEA04A27EAA_180517_3612990_UK_police_face_recognition_tech_wrong_in_98__of__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/68E/68F/68E68F9DC8B044148D17D5620714566B_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, British surveillance, facial recognition systems, face recognition technology, face recognition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3614088</guid>
      <title>Teen develops 'wet lung' after vaping for three weeks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn a study published in the journal Pediatrics, a Pennsylvania woman developed hypersensitivity pneumonitis, otherwise known as "wet lung", after using e-cigarettes.E-cigarettes work by heating liquid that turns into vapor, which the user then inhales and exhales, much like when one smokes a cigarette. The liquids usually contain flavorings, propylene glycol, glycerin and often nicotine. An 18-year-old Pennsylvania woman had only been vaping for three weeks when she developed symptoms so severe that she was sent to the emergency room of the University of Pittsburgh Medical Center, CNN reports.Dr. Casey Sommerfeld of Children's Healthcare of Atlanta, who was part of the study, says chemicals in an e-cigarette may have triggered a patient's body to create an immune response, leading to lung damage and inflammation.Sommerfeld said the immune response in the patient led to increased inflammation and "leaky" blood vessels, which in turn can lead to fluid accumulation in the lungs.The teenager exhibited symptoms of coughing, difficulty breathing that was quickly getting worse, and sudden stabbing pains in her chest every time she inhaled or exhaled.When her condition worsened and she went into respiratory failure, she required a mechanical ventilator to breathe for her, and required tubes inserted on both sides of her chest to drain fluid from her lungs.The woman's condition was diagnosed as hypersensitivity pneumonitis, sometimes called "wet lung", which is an inflammation of the lungs due to an allergic reaction to chemicals or dust."After being treated with methylprednisolone, a drug used to treat severe allergic reactions, the woman's condition improved and she was taken off the mechanical support system five days after being admitted to the hospital, CNN reported.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of vaping causing lung inflammation2. Leaky blood vessel and fluid in lungs3. Coughing, breathing difficulty and chest pain symptoms4. Woman attached to ventilator machine and tubes in her chestVOICEOVER (in English): "In a study published in the journal Pediatrics, Dr. Casey Sommerfeld of Children's Healthcare of Atlanta says chemicals in an e-cigarette may have triggered a patient's body to create an immune response, leading to lung damage and inflammation.""Sommerfeld said the immune response in the patient led to increased inflammation and 'leaky' blood vessels, which in turn can lead to fluid accumulation in the lungs.""The teenager exhibited symptoms of coughing, difficulty breathing that was quickly getting worse, and sudden stabbing pains in her chest every time she inhaled or exhaled.""When her condition worsened and she went into respiratory failure, she required a mechanical ventilator to breathe for her, and required tubes inserted on both sides of her chest to drain fluid from her lungs."SOURCES: Pediatrics, CNN, Buzzfeedhttp://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/early/2018/05/15/peds.2016-3927?sso=1&sso_redirect_count=1&nfstatus=401&nftoken=00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000&nfstatusdescription=ERROR%3a+No+local+tokenhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/05/17/health/case-study-teen-vaping-wet-lung/index.htmlhttps://www.buzzfeed.com/laurenstrapagiel/teen-girl-wet-lung-vaping-ecigarette?utm_term=.jmjbaMm9D#.my3OoM086***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 11:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/18/3614088/3614088_26455C1581474EFC9BB43D8F3E340BAF_180518_3614088_Teen_develops__wet_lung__after_vaping_for_three__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B85/5E3/B855E3BBC2D5482DBF7E41E1238462B9_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hypersensitivity pneumonitis, wet lung, e-cigarettes, vaping, vape, smoking, teenage smoking, lung inflammation, lung damage, coughing, trouble breathing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3613997</guid>
      <title>Why people are hearing different things in 'Yanny' v 'Laurel' viral clip</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn audio clip saying either the word "yanny" or "laurel" has gone viral over social media.   The short audio clip originated on Vocabulary.com under the word "laurel," and was traced back to a Flowery Branch High School freshman in Georgia on May 11, who posted the audio clip to her Instagram story, Wired reported.The sound clip was then posted by YouTuber Cloe Feldman onto Twitter where it took off.A possible explanation why people are hearing different words is because the file is "acoustically ambiguous" or very poor-quality, according to Northwestern University neurobiology professor Nina Kraus. The clip that went viral had already been re-recorded several times, meaning there were multiple steps that degraded the quality of the audio.   According to Brad Story, professor of speech, language and hearing sciences at the University of Arizona, the two words also have similar sound patterns. This combined with the low quality of the sound file could account for the different things people hear. The pitch of the clip can also affect what is heard. In general, people heard "yanny" more consistently when the pitch was lower and "laurel" when the pitch was higher.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. An audio clip saying either 'yanny' or 'laurel' 2. The audio clip being re-recorded and passed around3. People listening to the same audio clip but hearing different things4. Pitch of audio clip also affects what word is heardVOICEOVER (in English): "An audio clip saying either the word 'yanny' or 'laurel' has gone viral over social media. According to Northwestern University neurobiology professor Nina Kraus, a possible explanation why people are hearing different words is because the file is "acoustically ambiguous" or very poor-quality." "The clip that went viral had already been re-recorded several times, meaning there were multiple steps that degraded the quality of the audio. According to Brad Story, professor of speech, language and hearing sciences at the University of Arizona, the two words also have similar sound patterns." "This combined with the low quality of the sound file could account for the different things people hear." "The pitch of the clip can also affect what is heard. In general, people heard 'yanny' more consistently when the pitch was lower and 'laurel' when the pitch was higher."  SOURCES: NPR, Wired, The Atlantichttps://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2018/05/16/611701171/yanny-or-laurel-why-people-hear-different-things-in-that-viral-clip?utm_campaign=storyshare&utm_source=twitter.com&utm_medium=socialhttps://www.wired.com/story/yanny-and-laurel-true-history/https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2018/05/dont-rest-on-your-laurels/560483/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 10:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/18/3613997/3613997_F24A9EF9528D4D4FB3B002970FACBB2E_180518_3613997_Why_people_are_hearing_different_things_in__Yann_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/99B/F5F/99BF5F827BA44729913A231D7E725AC9_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, laurel or yanny, yanny or laurel, viral audio clip, sound file, pitch, acoustically ambiguous]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3613789</guid>
      <title>Rise in banned chemical use hurting ozone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research published in the journal Nature details findings that posit something or someone in East Asia is producing a banned ozone-depleting chemical. According to the BBC, CFC-11 was used in the 1930s as a refrigerant. It could also be found in solvents and aerosols. Scientists say the continued production of the chemical may slow the recovery of the Ozone.Speaking to Time, university of Maryland expert Ross Salawitch said the "rogue production" of CFC-11 could hurt the ozone recovery.Researchers considered several factors to explain the continued presence of CFC-11, but concluded that unreported new production is behind it.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of East Asia and chemical2. Depiction of where chemical was used3. Depiction of how chemical hurts the ozone4. Depiction of unreported productionVOICEOVER (in English): "New research published in the journal Nature details findings that posit somewhere in East Asia is producing the banned ozone-depleting chemical CFC-11.""According to the BBC, CFC-11 was used in the 1930s as a refrigerant. It could also be found in solvents and aerosols.""Scientists say the continued production of the chemical may slow the recovery of the ozone.""Researchers considered several factors to explain the continued presence of CFC-11, but concluded that unreported new production is behind it."SOURCES: Nature, BBC, Time, Washington Posthttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-018-0106-2http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-44138984http://time.com/5279650/ozone-eating-cfcs-rising-again/https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/energy-environment/wp/2018/05/16/someone-somewhere-is-making-a-banned-chemical-that-destroys-the-ozone-layer-scientists-suspect/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 06:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/18/3613789/3613789_1F87AB26CDEC498BA83D8FD6DD1E1055_180518_3613789_Rise_in_banned_chemical_use_hurting_ozone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/59B/75A/59B75A3A96B44C419CA3F029369974B5_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ozone, ozone layer, montreal protocol, cfc-11, cfc11, hole in the ozone layer, ozone hole, antarctica]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3615768</guid>
      <title>Hawaiian local seriously injured by lava bomb</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHawaii's Kilauea volcano claimed its first serious injury after a local was lava-bombed while on his home's balcony.The Honolulu Star Advertiser reports that according to Hawaii County Fire Department officials, the homeowner had been standing on his 3rd floor balcony when a lava bomb struck his leg, shattering it from shin to foot. He's alive but currently in the hospital, reports ABC 13.Lava bombs are masses of molten rock that are hurled hundreds of feet into the air during an eruption, and which solidify before hitting the ground.According to officials, these lava spatters can be as large as a cow and weigh as much as a refrigerator. Even small pieces can be deadly.Scientists believe the spatter as well as a recent change in lava flow may be due to old and new magma mixing in the ground, creating hotter and higher lava fountains.Elsewhere on Big Island, quick-flowing lava from two fissures has reportedly merged and cut through a highway towards the ocean. This latest development has prompted evacuations and health hazard warnings due to increased sulfur dioxide emissions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of lava bombs2. Depiction of lava bomb size and weight3. Depiction of lava bomb injuring a Hawaii man4. Depiction of a lava fountain and hotter, more fluid lava flowsVOICEOVER (in English): "Lava bombs are masses of molten rock that are hurled hundreds of feet into the air during an eruption, and which solidify before hitting the ground.""According to officials, these lava spatters can be as large as a cow and weigh as much as a refrigerator. Even small pieces can be deadly.""A lava bomb reportedly struck a Hawaii homeowner who was standing on his 3rd floor balcony, shattering his leg from shin to foot.""Scientists believe the spatter as well as a recent change in lava flow may be due to old and new magma mixing in the ground, creating hotter and higher lava fountains."SOURCES: Honolulu star Advertiser, ABC 13, News.com.auhttp://www.staradvertiser.com/2018/05/19/breaking-news/small-explosive-event-creates-light-ash-concerns-for-pahala/http://abc13.com/first-injury-reported-due-to-hawaiis-kilauea-volcano/3499247/http://www.news.com.au/technology/environment/natural-wonders/hawaiian-local-suffers-serious-leg-injury-being-lavabombed-while-sitting-on-porch/news-story/95fcb321ffb10bc155e301cde42700b0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 11:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/21/3615768/3615768_F777C7B5B2CF4915BB9D85F964B5E2BC_180521_3615768_Hawaiian_local_seriously_injured_by_lava_bomb_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/427/185/427185E58B304B0695A3F8D336A1A2B7_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, lava bomb, lava spatter, lava splatter, lava flow, Hawaii volcano, volcanic eruption, fissures, lava, magma, man lava bombed, leg injury, Kilauea, molten rock]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3615705</guid>
      <title>China lands bomber on South China Sea man-made islands for first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has landed a bomber on its man-made islands in the heavily disputed territory of the South China Sea for the first time.According to Chinese state media, a long-range H-6K bomber was used in landing and take off drills. Beijing's defense ministry did not say where the bomber landed, but added the drills included simulated strikes against sea targets. According to the Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, using Chinese social media posts, identified the location as Woody Island. The H-6K has a combat radius of almost 1,900 nautical miles (3,520 km), meaning all of Southeast Asia would be in range from Woody Island, according to the Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative.   The South China Sea is a vital global trade route subject to overlapping claims by six countries. Analysts say China will soon land bombers even farther south in the Spratly Islands, where runways and hangars have also been built on reefs. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woody Island and a China H-6K bomber2. H-6K bomber landing and taking off from Woody Island runway3. H-6K bomber flying away from Woody Island 4. H-6K bomber combat radiusVOICEOVER (in English): "China for the first time has landed a bomber on one of its man-made islands in the disputed territory of the South China Sea." "According to Chinese state media, a long-range H-6K bomber was used in landing and take off drills. Beijing's defense ministry did not say where the bomber landed, but added the drills included simulated strikes against sea targets." "According to the Washington-based Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, using Chinese social media posts, identified the location as Woody Island, in the Paracel Islands." "The H-6K has a combat radius of almost 1,900 nautical miles (3,520 km), meaning all of Southeast Asia would be in range from Woody Island."SOURCES: BBC, CNBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-44180773https://www.cnbc.com/2018/05/19/china-lands-bomber-on-south-china-sea-island-for-first-time.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 10:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/21/3615705/3615705_921B7F33375A47CC849DF3E528E61967_180521_3615705_China_lands_bomber_on_South_China_Sea_man_made_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B29/147/B29147E301B445BCB93F1766899D9F67_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, South China Sea, China HK-6 bomber, China HK-6 bomber Woody Island, China man-made islands, China fake islands]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3615689</guid>
      <title>Hotel pools and hot tubs linked to a third of swimming-related disease outbreaks, CDC says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHotel pools and hot tubs were linked to a third of all swimming-related disease outbreaks between 2000 to 2014, a new CDC report finds. During that stretch, a total of 493 outbreaks linked to chlorinated or treated water were reported in 46 states and Puerto Rico, the report said. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention released the results on Thursday in its Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report. In total, the outbreaks led to at least 27,219 illnesses and eight deaths, according to the report.Cryptosporidium (also known as Crypto), Pseudomonas, and Legionella were responsible for many of the outbreaks at swimming venues during that 15-year period.Crypto is a parasite that can survive even in properly maintained pools. Pseudomonas and Legionella are bacteria that can survive disinfectants in slimy areas of hot tubs, pools and water parks. The CDC report also outlined tips on how to protect from germs while at public swimming areas.      RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hotel pools and hot tubs linked to swimming-related disease outbreaks2. Crypto, Pseudomonas, and Legionella responsible for many of the outbreaks3. Depiction of hotel pool with crypto4. Pseudomonas and Legionella can survive disinfectants at public swimming venuesVOICEOVER (in English): "According the CDC's Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, hotels pools and hot tubs were linked to a third of all swimming-related disease outbreaks between 2000 to 2014. During that time, a total of 493 outbreaks linked to chlorinated or treated water were reported in 46 states and Puerto Rico.""In total, the outbreaks led to over 27,000 illnesses and eight deaths. Cryptosporidium, also known as Crypto, Pseudomonas, and Legionella were responsible for many of the outbreaks.""Crypto is a parasite that can survive even in properly maintained pools." "Pseudomonas and Legionella are bacteria that can survive disinfectants in slimy areas of hot tubs, pools and water parks." SOURCES: CDC, CNNhttps://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2018/p0517-swimming-related-diseases.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/05/17/health/crypto-bacteria-swimming-pools-hot-tubs-cdc/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/21/3615689/3615689_5A218AFB7B79470FBE74421263E0DF36_180521_3615689_Hotel_pools_and_hot_tubs_linked_to_a_third_of_sw_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7DD/144/7DD1446B956941F6A80CAF895188232B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hotel pools, hotel hot tubs, swimming-related diseases, crypto outbreak, legionella, pseudomonas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3615631</guid>
      <title>Third of Irish bees face extinction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA large segment Ireland's bumble bee species is facing extinction.According to the Irish Times, one third of Ireland's 98 bumble bee species are facing extinction. The Irish Mirror reports that 21 species of bees are crucial to the environment as they provide pollination for crops and flowers.An ecologist told the Irish Mirror that prior to 1960, rare species like the great yellow bumble bee, red-shanked carder bee and shrill carder bee used to be present across Ireland.Reasons for the dwindling bee population, according to the Irish Mirror, are habitat loss, pesticides, climate change and starvation brought about by a decline in wildflowers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of declining bee species in Ireland2. Depiction of bee pollinating flower3. Depiction of reasons behind declining bee population4. Depiction of rare species moving to Irish west coastVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Irish Times, one third of Ireland's 98 bumble bee species are facing extinction.""The Irish Mirror reports that 21 species of bees are crucial to the environment as they provide pollination for crops and flowers.""Reasons for the dwindling bee population, according to the Irish Mirror, are habitat loss, pesticides, climate change and starvation brought about by a decline in wildflowers.""An ecologist told the Irish Mirror that prior to 1960, rare species like the great yellow bumble bee, red-shanked carder bee and shrill carder bee used to be present across Ireland."SOURCES: Biodiversity Ireland, Irish Times, Irish Mirrorhttp://www.biodiversityireland.ie/projects/irish-pollinator-initiative/bees/declines-in-irish-bees/https://www.irishtimes.com/news/environment/irish-bumblebee-population-in-decline-1.3495040https://www.irishmirror.ie/news/irish-news/ireland-bumblebee-population-extinction-fears-12540940***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 08:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/21/3615631/3615631_D1DABECAA1504FEF99E915ED6483514D_180521_3615631_Third_of_Irish_bees_face_extinction_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DEC/D1E/DECD1E47B35C4F5AAB2C2587700F803D_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bumble bee, ireland, bumble bee extinction, bee habitat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3615536</guid>
      <title>Bitcoin mining usage may consume 0.5% of world's electricity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research posits that Bitcoin mining will consume half a percent of the world's total electricity by the end of 2018, then 5 percent in a few years.According to research published in the journal Joule, the same amount of electricity used in one Bitcoin transaction could power the average Dutch household for a month.The study says the Bitcoin network currently consumes 2.55 gigawatts of electricity, nearly the same as Ireland. By the end of 2018, the study predicts predicts that number rise to 7.8 gigawatts.Bitcoin transactions require massive computational power, and thereby large amounts of electricity to function. Computers in the decentralized Bitcoin network calculating transactions compete every 10 minutes to create the next block of transactions in the chain. Known as Bitcoin mining, this process sees the winning hardware get 12.5 bitcoins, or around $100,000. However, as Bitcoin calculations become more difficult to solve people employing more computational power have a higher chance of winning. The problem with this, study author Alex Devries explained to Gizmodo, is that the process motivates participants in the network to use more hardware, and as a result more power.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Bitcoin power statistics2. Depiction of Bitcoin power requirements 3. Depiction of Bitcoin mining4. Depiction of increased power consumption by more hardwareVOICEOVER (in English): "According to research published in the journal Joule, Bitcoin's electricity needs may reach as high as 0.5% of the world's total by the end of 2018, and 5 percent within a few years.""The same amount of electricity used in one Bitcoin transaction could power the average Dutch household for a month.""The study says the Bitcoin network currently consumes 2.55 gigawatts of electricity, nearly the same as Ireland.""By the end of 2018, the study predicts that number rise to 7.8 gigawatts.""Computers in the decentralized Bitcoin network calculating transactions compete every 10 minutes to create the next block of transactions in the chain. "Known as Bitcoin mining, this process sees the winning hardware get 12.5 Bitcoins, or around $100,000. ""However, as Bitcoin calculations become more difficult to solve people employing more computational power have a higher chance of winning.""The problem with this, study author Alex Devries explained to Gizmodo, is that the process motivates participants in the network to use more hardware, and as a result more power."SOURCES: Eurekalert (Press Release), Joule, Gizmodo, Popular Mechanics, https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2018-05/cp-bet051018.phphttps://www.cell.com/joule/fulltext/S2542-4351(18)30177-6https://gizmodo.com/alarming-study-suggests-bitcoin-consumes-an-astonishing-1826075745https://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/security/a27241/how-bitcoin-cryptocurrencies-work/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 06:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/21/3615536/3615536_6BC159E14D9946F0845C93EC24B8239C_180521_3615536_Bitcoin_mining_usage_may_consume_0_5__of_world_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/744/079/744079ED300E4A10866B4111D67CB5EF_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bitcoin, bitcoin mining, cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency power, blockchain, bitcoin power consumption, bitcoin mining hardware]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3616478</guid>
      <title>Hawaii volcano spews toxic gas and glass into the air</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPeople in Hawaii are now being warned of white plumes of toxic air and extremely fine glass particles as lava continues to pour out from the Kilauea volcano.Officials warned the public on Sunday to avoid the cloud formed by the chemical reaction when lava meets seawater, according to CBS News. According to officials, two lava flows have reached the Pacific, creating thick steam clouds known as "laze." Laze clouds are laced with hydrochloric acid and fine glass shards that can irritate skin and eyes and affect breathing. The laze cloud from the plume spread as far as 15 miles west of location the lava entered the Pacific on the Big Island's southern coast, according to CBS News. The Coast Guard is currently enforcing a 984-foot (330 metres) safety zone around the ocean point of entry. Kilauea has burned down 40 structures, including 25 homes since it starting erupting on May 3. Around 2,000 people have had to evacuate their homes. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of the two lava flows reaching the Pacific2. Laze clouds are laced with hydro3. Lava flowing into ocean forming laze cloud4. Size of safety zoneVOICEOVER (in English): "People in Hawaii are being warned of white plumes of toxic air and extremely fine glass particles as lava continues to pour out from the Kilauea volcano. Officials say two lava flows have reached the Pacific, creating thick steam clouds known as 'laze.'""Laze clouds are laced with hydrochloric acid and fine glass shards that can irritate skin and eyes and affect breathing." "The laze cloud from the plume spread as far as 15 miles west of location the lava entered the Pacific on the Big Island's southern coast.""The Coast Guard is currently enforcing a 984-foot safety zone around the ocean point of entry." SOURCES: BBC, CBS News, NPRhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-44195898http://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/05/21/hawaii-volcano-lava-eruption/https://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2018/05/21/612969472/hawaii-volcanos-lava-spews-laze-of-toxic-gas-and-glass-into-the-air***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 12:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/22/3616478/3616478_CC695E1E2EE846099E68D43B0F7F7B85_180522_3616478_Hawaii_volcano_spews_toxic_gas_and_glass_into_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/454/C73/454C735CD0C74B149AC102667C8B928F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Hawaii volcano, Kilauea eruption, Kilauea toxic laze clouds, Kilauea toxic clouds, Mount Kilauea eruption 2018]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3616400</guid>
      <title>China launches relay satellite to the far side of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has deployed a relay satellite that's meant to bridge communication between Earth and a planned exploration on the far side of the moon, Xinhua News Agency reports.Queqiao, or "Magpie Bridge", is named after a Chinese folklore in which magpies form a bridge to enable two star-crossed lovers to meet for one day.The Queqiao satellite features a dish antenna and two solar arrays, and was launched atop a Long March 4C rocket from southwest China on Sunday morning.Queqiao is expected to enter a halo orbit around the second Lagrangian Point, and would be the world's first communication satellite operating in that orbit.Its main purpose is to establish a communication link between Chinese Mission control and the Chang'e 4 lunar probe, which will explore the moon's dark side. It's currently scheduled for a December 2018 launch.Queqiao is also equipped with the Netherlands-China Low-Frequency Explorer, a radio scanner that will search for ancient radio signals dating back to the formation of the early universe.The reason the satellite is able to do this is because it would be in the "shadow" of the moon, completely unaffected by Earth's interference.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Queqiang relay satellite launched into space atop Long March 4C rocket2. Depiction of Queqiang orbiting second Lagrange Point 3. Queqiang to transmit signals from Earth to Chang'e lunar probe's future location on the dark side of the moon4. Depiction of Queqiang radio scanner searching for ancient radio signalsVOICEOVER (in English): "The Queqiao satellite features a dish antenna and two solar arrays, and was launched atop a Long March 4C rocket from southwest China on Sunday morning.""Queqiao is expected to enter a halo orbit around the second Lagrangian Point, and would be the world's first communication satellite operating in that orbit.""Its main purpose is to establish a communication link between Chinese Mission control and the yet-to-be-launched Chang'e 4 mission that will explore the moon's dark side.""Queqiao is also equipped with the Netherlands-China Low-Frequency Explorer, a radio scanner that will search for ancient radio signals dating back to the early universe."SOURCES: Xinhua News Agencyhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-05/21/c_137194788.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 10:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/22/3616400/3616400_7CCEF240B12143AABD6A75B8A6DA469C_180522_3616400_China_launches_relay_satellite_to_the_far_side_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/526/EB3/526EB3BE400147A98EA86224FF3E919F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China, Magpie Bridge, moon dark side, moon far side, relay satellite, satellite communications, lunar mission, lunar probe, chang'e, Space, Space satellite, Space rocket, Moon, Dark side of Moon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3616183</guid>
      <title>Bug in cell phone tracking firm's website exposed locations of American users in real-time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA company that collects real-time location data of millions of cell phone users throughout North America had a bug on its website that let anyone see where a person was located without having to obtain consent. LocationSmart is a data aggregator and says it has "direct connections" to cell carriers to obtain location information from nearby cell towers, according to ZDNet.The website has a trial-page that allows interested customers to test the accuracy of the system. The page requires explicit consent from the user before location data can be collected by sending a one-time text message.  However, a bug on the website discovered by Carnegie Mellon University researcher Robert Xiao, allowed anyone to track someone's location without their consent. Xiao told ZDNet, a simple bug allowed a person to skip the consent section and jump straight to the location. In a statement from spokesperson Brenda Schafer, LocationSmart "confirmed that the vulnerability was not exploited prior to May 16, and did not result in any customer information being obtained without their permission."Xiao said the bug may have exposed almost every cell phone user in North America, around 200 million customers, ZDNet reported. According to a LocationSmart statement, the bug has been resolved and the demo has been disabled. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. LocationSmart claims it can obtain location data from cell carrier towers2. Cell phone users being tracked without their consent3. Depiction of cell tower triangulation to locate users4. Bug exposing cell phone data for 200 million customersVOICEOVER (in English): "LocationSmart is a data aggregator and claims it has 'direct connections' to cell carriers to obtain location information from nearby cell towers throughout North America. A bug on its website lets anyone see where a person was located without having to obtain consent." "According to ZDNet, the website has a trial-page that allows customers to test the accuracy of the system.The page requires explicit consent from the user before location data can be collected by sending a one-time text message." "Carnegie Mellon University researcher Robert Xiao found a bug that allowed a person to skip the consent section and jump straight to the location." "Xiao said the bug may have exposed almost every cell phone user in North America, around 200 million customers."SOURCES: ZDNet, LocationSmarthttps://www.zdnet.com/article/cell-phone-tracking-firm-exposed-millions-of-americans-real-time-locations/https://www.zdnet.com/article/us-cell-carriers-selling-access-to-real-time-location-data/https://www.locationsmart.com/company/news/statement-regarding-recently-reported-security-incident***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 06:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/22/3616183/3616183_022D636D589D4BEDA8D248FDBBDD1271_180522_3616183_Bug_in_cell_phone_tracking_firm_s_website_expose_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/45A/D4C/45AD4C5ECA4D499286553E8CF180EB10_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, LocationSmart, LocationSmart data aggregator, cell phone tracking, smartphone tracking, LocationSmart website bug]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3616961</guid>
      <title>Fukushima's nuclear storage tanks are almost full</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWater containing radioactive byproducts have almost filled up the storage tanks at the the Fukushima No. 1 nuclear power plant in Japan.According to Japan's Yomiuri Shimbun, the Fukushima No. 1 nuclear plant reactor that suffered meltdowns during the 2011 earthquake and tsunami may end up contaminating groundwater. The reactor produces about 160 tons of radioactive water per day. The filters that remove radioactive elements from water are not able to remove an element called tritium, thus resulting in the amount of water containing only tritium to steadily increase.The storage tanks at Fukushima have a capacity of about 1.13 million tons, with about 1.07 million tons of that capacity already filled. Of the space used, 80 percent is occupied by treated water containing tritium.The area the tanks occupy totals about 230,000 square meters, which is the equivalent of about 32 soccer fields, and there is almost no more expansion space left to allow for more storage.Officials reportedly have been trying to increase storage capacity by building bigger tanks when it's time to replace the current ones. However, a senior official of Japan's' Economy, Trade and Industry Ministry said this storage method is already close to capacity. Tokyo Electric Power Company is planning to secure 1.37 million tons of storage capacity by the end of 2020, but has yet to decide on what to do after 2021. Regarding the treated water, TEPCO's chief decommissioning officer Akira Ono said that it is impossible to keep storing it forever. The Japan News reports that tritium is produced during regular nuclear plant operations, but also exists in nature. An average of 380 trillion becquerels of treated water containing tritium was released annually into the ocean in the five years before the nuclear plant disaster.Yomiuri Shimbun reports that the treated water containing tritium at Fukushima measures up to more than 1 million becquerels per liter. This is more than 10 times the national standard allowed for release into the ocean, which is 60,000 becquerels per liter. However, if the water is diluted, it can be released into the sea.The Japan News reports that a 2016 report by the industry ministry's working group said there are five ways to deal with treated water: releasing it into the sea, evaporation, releasing it after electrolysis, underground burial, or injection into geological layers. Out the five options, releasing it into the sea was seemed as the cheapest and the quickest way to dispose of the water.An expert committee organized by the ministry says it plans to to hold a public hearing in Fukushima Prefecture and other places to allow local residents to voice their opinions on what to do with the radioactive water.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show tanks capacity and most of them are occupied by treated water contained tritium.2. Show how much area the tanks have occupied and there is very little space left for expansion.3. Show Tokyo Electric Power Company plans to secure more storage capacity by the end of 2020.4. Show water contained tritium was released annually into the ocean.VOICEOVER (in English): "The storage tanks at Fukushima have a capacity of about 1.13 million tons, with about 1.07 million tons of that capacity already filled. Of the space used, 80 percent of that is occupied by treated water containing tritium.""The area the tanks occupy totals about 230,000 square meters, which is the equivalent of about 32 soccer fields, and there is almost no more expansion space left to allow for more storage.""Tokyo Electric Power Company is planning to secure 1.37 million tons of storage capacity by the end of 2020, but has yet to decide on what to do after 2021.""The Japan News reports that tritium is produced during regular nuclear plan]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 07:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/23/3616961/3616961_F473813C5D134DDA8504870C725F1589_180523_3616961_Fukushima_s_nuclear_storage_tanks_are_almost_ful_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3F9/E32/3F9E32F6CBC84A8398B1FE797037BD39_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, News, fukushima nuclear plant, fukushima nuclear plant today, fukushima nuclear plant 2018, fukushima, fukushima 2018, fukushima nuclear disaster 2017, fukushima radiation, fukushima water storage tanks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3617559</guid>
      <title>Blood type A people may be more likely to get traveler's diarrhea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found that a certain strain of E. coli is more likely to cause traveler's diarrhea in people with blood type A. According to the study published on May 17 in the Journal of Clinical Investigation, the diarrhea-causing strain of E. coli secretes a protein that attaches to sugar molecules on type A blood cells, but not type B or O cells. According to Science News, researchers from Washington University School of Medicine and Johns Hopkins University also found these sugar molecules are also present in the gut linings of people with blood type A. Scientists had 106 healthy volunteers drink water laced with a strain of E. coli extracted from a person in Bangladesh with severe diarrhea. After five days, 81 percent of the type A or AB volunteers developed moderate to severe diarrhea compared to about half with blood types O or B. The results could mean that a vaccine targeting the bacterial protein could be effective. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Blood type A person being infected by E. coli strain2. E. coli strain attracted to A blood type, but not type B or O cells3. Volunteer drinking water laced with E. coli4. 81 percent of A or AB volunteers developed moderate to severe diarrhea after five daysVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the study published in the Journal of Clinical Investigation, a certain strain of E. coli is more likely to cause traveler's diarrhea in people with blood type A.""Researchers from Washington University School of Medicine and Johns Hopkins University found that the diarrhea-causing strain of E. coli secretes a protein which attaches to sugar molecules on type A blood cells, but not type B or O cells. Scientists also found these sugar molecules present in the gut linings of people with blood type A." "Scientists had 106 healthy volunteers drink water laced with a strain of E. coli extracted from a person in Bangladesh with severe diarrhea." "After five days, 81 percent of the type A or AB volunteers developed moderate to severe diarrhea compared to about half with blood types O or B." SOURCES: Science Newshttps://www.sciencenews.org/article/your-blood-type-might-make-you-more-likely-get-travelers-diarrhea***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 05:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/24/3617559/3617559_718B3AA344E34068A9FC11006B9DFE66_180524_3617559_Blood_type_A_people_may_be_more_likely_to_get_tr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F1B/E1B/F1BE1B88696241DE9CD5A2484479E0FD_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, traveler's diarrhea, e coli, e coli proteins, e coli diarrhea, e coli vaccines, blood type a, blood type traveler's diarrhea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3617545</guid>
      <title>VAR cameras fail at major soccer final ahead of World Cup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAustralia's Football Federation admitted that the Video Assistant Referee technology (VAR) they used encountered a technical failure that led to a controversial goal. According to the federation, the incident took place at the grand final of Australia's A league between Melbourne Victory and Newcastle Jets earlier this month. When Victory was delivering the ball from a free-kick play, the software that VAR system provider Hawk-eye uses crashed, causing the cameras to partially lose 30 seconds of footage.During the glitch, three players in the Victory's outfit were already standing in offside position, and the referees did not signal offside either. This failure allowed Victory's players to take the chance at controlling the ball, which later led to the controversial goal that helped the team clinch the league title.Greg O'Rourke, the head of Australia's A-League said the technology failed on this occasion and the broadcast angles required were unavailable. They are working with Hawk-Eye's UK head office to prevent this from happening again.Hawk-Eye's Australian branch declined to comment on the glitch, the Sydney Morning Herald reported.VAR was introduced as a technology-based solution to correct human referees' errors when they need to make a decision in just split seconds.Last month, FIFA announced that Hawk-Eye will be the VAR system provider and will feature its camera prominently in all the FIFA World Cup fixtures in Russia this summer. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show Australia A league's grand final and the VAR cameras installed in the stadium.2. Show the controversial incident and the cameras' malfunction.3. Show the three players are already on the offside position.4. Show the controversial goal being scored.VOICEOVER (in English): According to the federation, the incident took place at the grand final of Australia's A league between Melbourne Victory and Newcastle Jets earlier this month. When Victory was delivering the ball from a free-kick play, the software that VAR system provider Hawk-eye uses crashed, resulting in the cameras partially losing 30 seconds of footage.During the glitch, three players in the Victory's outfit were already standing in offside position, the referees did not signal offside either. This failure allowed Victory's players to take the chance at controlling the ball, which later led to the controversial goal that helped the team clinch the league title.SOURCES: https://www.telesurtv.net/english/news/Soccer-VAR-Technology-Fails-in-Major-Final-Ahead-of-World-Cup-20180506-0004.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 05:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/24/3617545/3617545_4B7390091CA74ED8B737DCE951F474AB_180524_3617545_VAR_cameras_fail_at_major_soccer_final_ahead_of__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CFB/5BF/CFB5BF222C7849FDB1670F49E8B9A9FE_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, var technology in football, vartech systems, var controversy, var australia, video assistant referees will be used at 2018 world cup in russia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3617446</guid>
      <title>Floating nation with its own government and cryptocurrency to launch by 2022</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA floating nation with its own government and virtual currency could become a reality in just a few years.CNBC reports that nonprofit organization Blue Frontiers is heading the Floating Island Project, which seeks to build up to 300 homes on a manmade island off the coast of Tahiti.Despite partnering with and being located in French Polynesia, the floating community will be self-governed and have its own cryptocurrency called Varyon.The Varyon payment token can be exchanged for goods and services in the Blue Frontiers ecosystem, in other island systems, or between token holders.Houses on the island are movable, so residents can easily float away to another seastead if they don't want to live under a particular government.Since land in this region will likely disappear with rising sea levels, organizers say the new island could provide housing for the displaced. The community would also function as a business center, one that's stable and free from government regulation.Blue Frontier's pilot island is expected to cost up to $50 million, and be up and running by 2022.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Floating Island Project2. Floating Island will have its own government and cryptocurrency3. Depiction of Varyon payment token4. Depiction of movable houses5. Floating Island Project as housing for displaced residents of sunken islandsVOICEOVER (in English): "Nonprofit organization Blue Frontiers is heading the Floating Island Project, which seeks to build up to 300 homes on a manmade island off the coast of Tahiti.""Despite partnering with and being located in French Polynesia, the floating community will be self-governed and have its own cryptocurrency called Varyon.""The Varyon payment token can be exchanged for goods and services in the Blue Frontiers ecosystem, in other island systems, or between token holders.""Houses on the island are movable, so residents can easily float away to another seastead if they don't want to live under a particular government."SOURCES: CNBC, Blue Frontiershttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/05/18/floating-island-is-planned-with-government-cryptocurrency-and-houses.htmlhttps://www.blue-frontiers.com***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 02:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/24/3617446/3617446_0202BE6561404B96B50C4C3388EFE0B8_180524_3617446_Floating_nation_with_its_own_government_and_cryp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/34C/80C/34C80CC29B1B43E692FC844F0F53070F_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, floating island, cryptocurrency, seastead, first floating nation, floating community, floating nation, floating island project, autonomous, french polynesia, blue frontiers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3617438</guid>
      <title>Adaptive battery can charge in seconds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new battery design from Cornell University could charge devices in seconds.Typical battery design usually consists of a structure with cathode and anode on the ends and electrolyte in between.Electricity flows to out the anode toward whatever its powering, then back through the battery cathode creating a circuit.New research from Cornell University details a battery design where all the parts intertwine in a 3D structure, surrounded by thousands of energy-storing nano pores. The twisting, self-assembling gyrodial is dense with power and eliminates a lot of the weight in traditional batteries and allows for much quicker energy transfer. Speaking in a Cornell news release, lead researcher Dr. Ulrich Wiesner said the nanoscale design could see batteries being charged in seconds, or even faster.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of how current battery design powers devices2. Depiction of new battery design's structure3. Depiction of current battery becoming new battery4. Depiction of battery inside a phone and being chargedVOICEOVER (in English): "Typical battery design usually consists of a structure with cathode and anode on the ends and electrolyte in between.""Electricity flows to out the anode toward whatever its powering, then back through the battery cathode, creating a circuit." "New research from Cornell University details a battery design where all the parts intertwine in a 3D structure, surrounded by thousands of energy-storing nano pores." "The twisting, self-assembling gyrodial is dense with power and eliminates a lot of the weight in traditional batteries and allows for much quicker energy transfer." "Speaking in a Cornell news release, lead researcher Dr. Ulrich Weisner said the nanoscale design could see batteries being charged in seconds, or even faster."SOURCES:  Cornell University, Energy and Environmental Science, New Atlashttp://news.cornell.edu/stories/2018/05/self-assembling-3d-battery-would-charge-secondshttp://pubs.rsc.org/en/content/articlelanding/2018/ee/c7ee03571c#!divAbstracthttps://newatlas.com/gyroid-self-assembling-3d-battery/54693/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 02:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/24/3617438/3617438_00396E558420406D8D291BFBEF58BC90_180524_3617438_Adaptive_battery_can_charge_in_seconds_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0FE/94E/0FE94EFEBABA4DDFB3DE2CEC55DF9FA4_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, instant battery charger, battery charging, charger, battery, iphone, smartphone, android, mobile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3618501</guid>
      <title>Lawsuit alleges Facebook did mass surveillance of its users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA lawsuit filed in California alleges that Facebook acquired masses of data from users via its apps.   Former startup Six4Three claims that Facebook used its apps for mass surveillance on users by assembling data from their texts and photos. Six4Three also alleges Facebook used its software to listen to users and remotely powered their Bluetooth to pinpoint locations, sometimes without consent.Citing the lawsuit, the Guardian reports that Facebook could gather metadata from Android phone texts messages. Six4Three claims that the company could access nearly all photos on iPhones, as well as those not uploaded to Facebook."The lawsuit also alleges that Facebook also acquired some people's data without their consent.  According to the Guardian, the company allegedly gathered information sent by users not on the platform to people with Facebook apps on their phone." Citing the lawsuit, the Huffington post reports Facebook allegedly used information from Onavo, an app it owns, to observe what people used their phones for beyond Facebook.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of case2. Depiction of iPhone and Android phone3. Depiction of Facebook taking information without consent4. Depiction of man in apartment on phoneVOICEOVER (in English): "Former startup Six4Three claims that Facebook used its apps for mass surveillance on users by assembling data from their texts and photos "...  listening to their microphones and using Bluetooth to pinpoint locations, sometimes without consent.""Citing the lawsuit, the Guardian reports that Facebook could gather metadata from Android phone texts messages.""Six4Three claims that the company could access nearly all photos on iPhones, as well as those not uploaded to Facebook.""The lawsuit also alleges that Facebook also acquired some people's data without their consent. "According to the Guardian, the company allegedly gathered information sent by users not on the platform to people with Facebook apps on their phone." "Citing the lawsuit, the Huffington post reports Facebook allegedly used information from Onavo, an app it owns, to observe what people used their phones for beyond Facebook."SOURCES: The Guardian, Huffington Posthttps://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/may/24/facebook-accused-of-conducting-mass-surveillance-through-its-appshttps://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/facebook-allegations-reading-texts-accessing-microphones_us_5b06c226e4b07c4ea105b154***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 09:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/25/3618501/3618501_0665106AD39C43A98FBADD4A0515B115_180525_3618501_Lawsuit_alleges_Facebook_did_mass_surveillance_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F0D/B42/F0DB42A0AAF7443988A74B3824D0232D_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, facebook, mark zuckerberg, facebook mass surveillance, facebook privacy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3618399</guid>
      <title>Giant hammerhead flatworms are invading France</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have discovered that an invasive species of flatworms have been quietly occupying French soil for the past two decades.The Washington Post reports that they would have gone unnoticed if not for amateur naturalist Pierre Gros, who spotted the strange critters in his garden, and Jean-Lou Justine, a zoologist at France's Museum of Natural History who later identified them as hammerhead flatworms.According to the journal PeerJ, hammerheads are a giant species of flatworms with shovel-like heads that are native to Asia. They can grow up to a meter long and appear to reproduce asexually.Citizen sightings indicate that at least three hammerhead species have been in metropolitan France as early as 1999, with two others reported in overseas territories.The invasive species feed on earthworms in the soil, which they immobilize by secreting small amounts of the paralytic poison tetrodotoxin   the same neurotoxin found in the potentially lethal Japanese delicacy fugu or puffer fish.Since earthworms help aerate soil and keep it fertile, scientists worry that the presence of predatory flatworms may threaten biodiversity and drastically affect the ecosystem.They believe the worms were likely transported to Europe via tropical plants, but remain baffled by how they went undetected for almost 20 years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of hammerhead flatworms' size, origin, reproduction2. Depiction of hammerhead flatworms in France3. Depiction of a hammerhead flatworm preying on an earthworm4. Depiction of hammerhead flatworms threatening ecosystemVOICEOVER (in English): "Hammerheads are a giant species of flatworms with shovel-like heads that are native to Asia. They can grow up to a meter long and appear to reproduce asexually.""Citizen sightings indicate that at least three hammerhead species have been in metropolitan France as early as 1999, with two others reported in overseas territories.""The invasive species feed on earthworms in the soil, secreting small amounts of the paralytic poison tetrodotoxin to immobilize their prey.""Since earthworms help aerate soil and keep it fertile, the presence of predatory flatworms may threaten biodiversity and drastically affect the ecosystem."SOURCES: PeerJ, Washington Posthttps://peerj.com/articles/4672/https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/speaking-of-science/wp/2018/05/22/giant-predatory-worms-invaded-france-but-scientists-just-noticed-them/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 07:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/25/3618399/3618399_EA2574AEC65B4F16920E58ACB9F2F2D9_180525_3618399_Giant_hammerhead_flatworms_are_invading_France_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CB9/544/CB9544B906E9428087774E10E5F3660A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hammerhead flatworms, flatworms, worms, giant worms, invasive species, France, carnivorous worms, predatory worms, earthworms, tetrodotoxin, neurotoxin, paralysis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3620367</guid>
      <title>U.S. warships sail to South China Sea, angers China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo U.S. Navy warships sailed near the South China Sea islands on Sunday while carrying out "freedom of navigation operations," two American officials told Reuters.The USS Antietam, a guided missile cruiser, and the USS Higgins, a guided-missile destroyer came within 12 nautical miles of the Paracel Islands. The American vessels carried out maneuvering operations close too Tree, Lincoln, Triton and Woody islands in the Paracels, one of the officials told Reuters. China said in a statement from the Ministry of National Defense on its website that it confronted the U.S. ships and warned them to leave. The chief spokesman for China's Ministry of National Defense, Senior Col. Wu Qian, said that the U.S. "gravely violated Chinese sovereignty," according to the New York Times. Tensions have been on the rise in the area after China for the first time landed one of its long-range H-6K strategic bombers on one of its man-made island in the Paracels, Woody Island.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location where US vessels entered South China Sea2. USS Antietam and USS Higgins sailing within 12 nautical miles of Paracels 3. US vessels carrying out operations on Tree, Lincoln, Trinton and Woody Islands4. China H-6K bomber taking off from Woody IslandVOICEOVER (in English): "According to two American officials, two U.S. Navy warships sailed near the South China Sea islands on Sunday while carrying out 'freedom of navigation operations.'""The USS Antietam, a guided missile cruiser, and the USS Higgins, a guided-missile destroyer came within 12 nautical miles of the Paracel Islands.""One of the U.S. officials told Reuters, that the American vessels carried out maneuvering operations close too Tree, Lincoln, Triton and Woody islands in the Paracels." "Tensions have been on the rise in the area after China for the first time landed one of its long-range H-6K strategic bombers on one of its man-made island in the Paracels, Woody Island."  SOURCES: Reuters, New York Timeshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-military-exclusive/exclusive-us-warships-sail-near-south-china-sea-islands-claimed-by-beijing-idUSKCN1IS07Whttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/27/world/asia/china-us-navy-paracel-islands.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/28/3620367/3620367_14BF2F79F7EC404BBA434B6D6C67D04E_180528_3620367_U_S__warships_sail_to_South_China_Sea__angers_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DF0/50C/DF050CE4DB6F4D59AA1B32600EB3E7CA_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, South China Sea, US warships South China Sea, USS Antietam, USS Higgins, freedom of navigation, West Philippine Sea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3620120</guid>
      <title>California senators call for nationwide drift net ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDisturbing footage of a shark being bludgeoned by a fisherman has led to increased calls for a ban on drift gill nets in commercial fishery.The Mercury News reports that the video was taken by an undercover activist and posted online by Mercy for Animals, and comes as two California senators introduced a bill to ban the nets nationwide.Drift gill nets are long walls of meshed synthetic netting held vertically in the water by floats along the top and weights on the bottom.According to the United Nations Food and Agriculture Organization, fish are caught when their gills get stuck in the mesh openings, the sizes of which vary depending on the type of fish being targeted.But non-target animals, called bycatch, are also captured. Sharks, dolphins, and sea lions often get tangled in the net and are unable to free themselves, leading to death or serious injury.Drift net fishermen claim the industry has implemented measures to reduce bycatch, including using nets with larger openings and electronic devices to scare off dolphins.Still, opponents say the casualties are unnecessary and unacceptable, believing that phasing them out is the best way to stop the horror.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of drift gill nets in the sea2. Depiction of how drift gill nets catch fish3. Depiction of marine animal bycatch entangled by the net4. Depiction of improvements to drift netsVOICEOVER (in English): "Drift gill nets are long walls of meshed synthetic netting held vertically in the water by floats along the top and weights on the bottom.""Fish are caught when their gills get stuck in the mesh openings, the sizes of which vary depending on the type of fish being targeted.""But non-target animals, called bycatch, are also captured. Sharks, dolphins, and sea lions often get tangled in the net and are unable to free themselves, leading to death or serious injury.""Drift net fishermen claim the industry has implemented measures to reduce bycatch, including using nets with larger openings and electronic devices to scare off dolphins."SOURCES: The Mercury News, Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, Mercy for Animalshttps://www.mercurynews.com/2018/05/24/brutal-video-shows-california-fisherman-beating-shark-with-baseball-bat-increases-call-for-ban-on-gill-nets/http://www.fao.org/docrep/003/t0502e/t0502e01.htmhttp://www.mercyforanimals.org/home2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 06:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/28/3620120/3620120_286CD412A8CC45B5A6786624B7247135_180528_3620120_California_senators_call_for_nationwide_drift_ne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4BC/461/4BC4614642334FA9B66242FA7CF90A0F_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, drift nets, gill nets, drift gill nets, mercy for animals, bycatch, drift net fishing, gill net fishing, deadly catch, commercial fishing, death net, ban the net]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3620115</guid>
      <title>Coral bleaching has left only 1% of Japan's biggest reef healthy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRising sea temperatures have impacted the ability of Japan's biggest coral reef to recover from bleaching, resulting in only one percent of the reef being in good health, according to a new study. Bleaching can occur due to changing environmental conditions such as rising sea temperatures and causes coral to expel tiny photosynthetic algae which drains them of their color. Since the 1980s, the volume of coral in Sekisei Lagoon near Okinawa has plummeted by nearly 80 percent. The coral has been damaged by starfish eating coral and rising ocean temperatures, according to Japan Today.The latest study shows that the corals haven't recovered much since 2008 due to the 1998, 2001, 2007, and 2016 bleaching events. The lagoon itself is around 67.89 square kilometers with only around 1.4% of its corals still healthy. Coral reefs are home to 25% of marine life even though they only make up one percent of the marine environment.The only way the corals would be able to recover is if the temperature in the ocean drops and algaes are able to colonise them again, reports AFP.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Coral bleaching2. Coral bleaching events in lagoon3. Size of lagoon and bleached corals in lagoon4. Depiction of coral reef improving due to decreasing temperaturesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a government study, rising sea temperatures have impacted the ability of Japan's biggest coral reef to recover from bleaching, as a result, only one percent of the reef is in good health.""Due to rising sea temperature, the reef has suffered bleaching events in 1998, 2001, 2007 and 2016 leading to a decrease in the overall coral volume by nearly 80 percent in Sekisei Lagoon.""The lagoon is approximately 67.89 square kilometers with only around 1.4 percent of its corals healthy.""Coral reefs are home to 25 percent of sea life, even though they only make up one percent of marine environment. The only way for the coral to recover is if sea temperatures drop and algae are able to recolonize them again."SOURCES: EcoWatch, AFP, Japan Todayhttps://www.ecowatch.com/japan-coral-reef-bleaching-2570800547.htmlhttps://www.afp.com/en/news/2265/only-1-pct-japans-biggest-coral-reef-healthy-survey-doc-1539nj2https://japantoday.com/category/national/only-1-pct-of-japan's-biggest-coral-reef-healthy-survey***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 06:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/28/3620115/3620115_325D6D5F3FED4A629BD43ECF997DE7AC_180528_3620115_Coral_bleaching_has_left_only_1__of_Japan_s_bigg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C28/61A/C2861A5DDFF74D1EB46B79C9CD22738E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Japan, Coral Reefs, Marine Biodiversity, Mass coral mortality, Climate Change, coral reefs bleaching, global warming, rising sea temperatures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622537</guid>
      <title>What is Manhattanhenge?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew York City residents can witness a unique urban phenomenon known as Manhattanhenge, but what exactly is it?CBS reports that the term, coined by astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson, is a callback to Stonehenge, where the sun rises in perfect alignment with the stones during summer solstice.Manhattanhenge occurs around the dates framing the summer solstice, and is contingent on the exact position of the Earth on its orbital path around the sun.Manhattan's city grid is tilted 29 degrees east, with streets set at 90 degree angles. When the sun's path is at 29 degrees north of due west, it aligns with streets on the grid.The setting sun can be seen simultaneously on all streets heading east and west. It's an unusual event that happens four times a year in May and July, twice with a half sun and twice with the entire disk visible.This year, Manhattanhenge went down around Memorial day, on May 29 and 30, and will be seen again on July 12 and 13.Experts say the sunset alignment isn't just limited to NYC. Gridded cities like Chicago or Toronto experience similar phenomena, just on different dates.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Earth's position relative to the sun2. Depiction of sun lining up directly with the Manhattan city grid 3. Depiction of Manhattanhenge and approximate dates each yearVOICEOVER (in English): "Manhattanhenge occurs around the dates framing the summer solstice, and is contingent on the exact position of the Earth on its orbital path around the sun.""Manhattan's city grid is tilted 29 degrees east, with streets set at 90 degree angles. When the sun's path is at 29 degrees north of due west, it aligns with streets on the grid.""The setting sun can be seen simultaneously on all streets heading east and west. It's an unusual event that happens four times a year in May and July, twice with a half sun and twice with the entire disk visible."SOURCES: Space.com, CBShttps://www.space.com/40639-the-story-of-manhattanhenge.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/what-is-manhattanhenge-sunset-new-york-city-today-what-time-best-place-2018-05-30/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 12:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/31/3622537/3622537_0BB2006002204B13BB5B9BB1077A0760_180531_3622537_What_is_Manhattanhenge__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F6B/E16/F6BE161521A44C0899797DA94D79504B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, manhattanhenge, manhattan solstice, sunset, manhattan sunset, what is manhattanhenge, new york sunset, city grid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622319</guid>
      <title>Archaeologists uncover skeleton of man crushed while fleeing Pompeii</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArchaeologists have unearthed the skeleton of a Pompeii resident who managed to survive an initial volcanic blast, only to end up getting crushed by a rock.The skeleton had been pinned underneath a 300-kilogram block of stone during the eruption of Mount Vesuvius in A.D. 79, according to a Facebook post by the Pompeii Parco Archeologico.The decapitated remains are believed to be that of a 30-year-old male. Lesions on the tibia suggest a bone infection, which would have hampered the man's ability to flee.The bones were found on the first storey level, over a thick layer of volcanic fragments called lapilli. This suggests he survived the first phase of the eruption.Scientists think the man had been hit by hot pyroclastic flows while fleeing. A massive rock thrown by the volcanic cloud then collided with his upper body, crushing his head and thorax.The unfortunate man's skeleton is the latest discovery out of Pompeii. Excavations in the past few months have unearthed the remains of a horse and a young child.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of skeleton pinned under block of stone2. Depiction of 30-year-old male victim with lesions on leg3. Remains found over a layer of volcanic fragments4. Depiction of pyroclastic flow, collision with stone blockVOICEOVER (in English): "Archaeologists in Pompeii have unearthed a skeleton that had been pinned underneath a 300-kilogram block of stone during the eruption of Mount Vesuvius in A.D. 79.""The decapitated remains are believed to be that of a 30-year-old male. Lesions on the tibia suggest a bone infection, which would have hampered the man's ability to flee.""The bones were found on the first storey level, over a thick layer of volcanic fragments called lapilli. This suggests he survived the first phase of the eruption.""Scientists think the man had been hit by hot pyroclastic flows while fleeing. A massive rock thrown by the volcanic cloud then collided with his upper body, crushing his head and thorax."SOURCES: Pompeii Parco Archeologico, CNNhttps://www.facebook.com/pompeiisoprintendenza/posts/1813608315613045https://edition.cnn.com/2018/05/29/health/pompeii-victim-crushed-rock-eruption-intl-trnd/index.html?no-st=1527659706***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 08:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/31/3622319/3622319_DDC17F75657841E586F1F8BEC12DD87B_180531_3622319_Archaeologists_uncover_skeleton_of_man_crushed_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/321/FBE/321FBE54CF8641C587B3E26B6BA7BBA1_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, pompeii, skeleton, mount vesuvius, excavation, volcanic eruption, stone block, man crushed by rock, ancient rome, pyroclastic flow, volcanic blast, lapilli]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622093</guid>
      <title>Cockroach milk is nutrient-rich and could be the next superfood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that cockroach milk is highly nutritious, and could even feed future generations.The Washington Post reports that unlike most insect species, the Pacific beetle cockroach is viviparous. This means it gives birth to live offspring instead of eggs,which it nourishes with a yellow, liquid substance from her brood sac.Instead of simply being digested, the liquid milk is deposited in the embryo's midguts and forms into tiny crystals. Analyses revealed the crystalline milk is a complete food containing proteins, lipids, and carbohydrates, and with three times more energy than buffalo milk.But despite being touted as one of the most nutritious substances on the planet, it's unclear whether no telling roach milk is safe for human consumption. To work around this, scientists are now reverse bioengineering the milk and working on using yeast to produce the beetle roach crystals in larger quantities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of pacific beetle cockroaches providing milk to live embryos2. Depiction of crystallized milk stored in embryos' midgut3. Depiction of nutrient-rich crystals as having more energy than buffalo milk4. Depiction of scientists reverse bioengineering cockroach milkVOICEOVER (in English): "Unlike most insect species, the Pacific beetle cockroach gives birth to live offspring, feeding them a yellow, liquid substance from her brood sac.""Instead of simply being digested, the liquid milk is deposited in the embryo's midguts and forms into tiny crystals.""Analyses revealed the crystalline milk is a complete food containing proteins, lipids, and carbohydrates, and with three times more energy than buffalo milk.""Scientists are now reverse bioengineering the milk and working on using yeast to produce the beetle roach crystals in larger quantities."SOURCES: International Union of Crystallography Journal, NPR, Washington Posthttp://journals.iucr.org/m/issues/2016/04/00/jt5013/https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2016/08/06/488861223/cockroach-milk-yes-you-read-that-righthttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/morning-mix/wp/2016/07/26/the-case-for-cockroach-milk-its-the-most-caloric-protein-on-earth-scientists-say/?utm_term=.4007f2a638b5***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 02:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/05/31/3622093/3622093_EA9097728C854EBEA44DCD5F932FC38E_180531_3622093_Cockroach_milk_is_nutrient_rich_and_could_be_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/250/734/2507349E6DDB4CF59D9B341BE42F7E2B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cockroach milk, superfood, cockroach, pacific beetle cockroach, roach, baby roach, lili mip, superfood trend, milk, non dairy milk, milk alternatives, dairy alternatives, crystal protein]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
