<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3497554</guid>
      <title>Boring Company bids to build express travel pods in Chicago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEElon Musk's Boring Company has put in a bid to build an express transit link between O'Hare airport and downtown Chicago. Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel announced the city would be accepting proposals to build an express service from the airport to downtown last Wednesday, according to Newsweek.  Soon after Musk tweeted, "The Boring Company will compete to fund, build and operate a high-speed Loop connecting Chicago O'Hare Airport to downtown." The loop would be a system of tunnels underneath the city that would use electric pods rather than a vacuum tube like the hyperloop concept. The proposed route would be less than 20 miles and would need to take less than 20 minutes, according to Mayor Emanuel. The Boring Company will need  to present plans on design, finance, construction, operation and maintenance of the Loop system. No taxpayer funding will be made available for the transit project.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tunnel boring machine digging a tunnel2. Travel pods traveling through tunnel3. Electric travel pod4. The route will need to take less than 20 minutesVOICEOVER (in English): "Elon Musk's Boring Company has put in a bid to build an express transit link between O'Hare airport and downtown Chicago." "Musk tweeted the announcement saying, 'The Boring Company will compete to fund, build and operate a high-speed Loop connecting Chicago O'Hare Airport to downtown.'" "The loop would be a system of tunnels underneath the city that would use electric pods rather than a vacuum tube like the hyperloop concept." "The proposed route would be less than 20 miles and would need to take less than 20 minutes."SOURCES: Newsweek, BBC, Futurism, Engadgethttp://www.newsweek.com/elon-musks-boring-company-bids-dig-tunnel-under-chicago-electric-pods-726690http://www.bbc.com/news/technology-42181133https://futurism.com/elon-musk-compete-build-new-chicago-transportation-system/https://www.engadget.com/2017/11/30/elon-musk-boring-company-chicago-airport-transit/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 10:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/04/3497554/3497554_888CDCE1C095418BA1B4959E9D30838E_171204_3497554_Boring_Company_bids_to_build_express_travel_pods_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2A1/484/2A14845A012A414E8D659D553A96094F_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Boring Company, Elon Musk Boring Company, Chicago O'hare electric pod transit, Chicago travel pods, Chicago airport transit system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3497402</guid>
      <title>Boring Company bids to build express travel pods in Chicago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEElon Musk's Boring Company has put in a bid to build an express transit link between O'Hare airport and downtown Chicago. Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel announced the city would be accepting proposals to build an express service from the airport to downtown last Wednesday, according to Newsweek.  Soon after Musk tweeted, "The Boring Company will compete to fund, build and operate a high-speed Loop connecting Chicago O'Hare Airport to downtown." The loop would be a system of tunnels underneath the city that would use electric pods rather than a vacuum tube like the hyperloop concept. The proposed route would be less than 20 miles and would need to take less than 20 minutes, according to Mayor Emanuel. The Boring Company will need  to present plans on design, finance, construction, operation and maintenance of the Loop system. No taxpayer funding will be made available for the transit project.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tunnel boring machine digging a tunnel2. Travel pods traveling through tunnel3. Electric travel pod4. The route will need to take less than 20 minutesVOICEOVER (in English): "Elon Musk's Boring Company has put in a bid to build an express transit link between O'Hare airport and downtown Chicago." "Musk tweeted the announcement saying, 'The Boring Company will compete to fund, build and operate a high-speed Loop connecting Chicago O'Hare Airport to downtown.'" "The loop would be a system of tunnels underneath the city that would use electric pods rather than a vacuum tube like the hyperloop concept." "The proposed route would be less than 20 miles and would need to take less than 20 minutes."SOURCES: Newsweek, BBC, Futurism, Engadgethttp://www.newsweek.com/elon-musks-boring-company-bids-dig-tunnel-under-chicago-electric-pods-726690http://www.bbc.com/news/technology-42181133https://futurism.com/elon-musk-compete-build-new-chicago-transportation-system/https://www.engadget.com/2017/11/30/elon-musk-boring-company-chicago-airport-transit/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 08:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/04/3497402/3497402_E86FFB6E5B7D41FAB01D8899327718C1_171204_3497402_Boring_Company_bids_to_build_express_travel_pods_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/979/3D1/9793D13B761B4F2983AE242B21A30B51_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Boring Company, Elon Musk Boring Company, Chicago O'hare electric pod transit, Chicago travel pods, Chicago airport transit system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3499019</guid>
      <title>Massive bubble of hot rock detected beneath New England</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new study has found that the idyllic New England region could eventually become a hotbed of volcanic activity.Using data from earthquake measurement devices, Rutgers University researchers analyzed the speed and direction of seismic waves to visualize subsurface conditions.According to a university press release, they detected a massive upwelling of hot rock under Vermont, New Hampshire, and Massachusetts, after noticing the area was noticeably hotter than neighboring regions.Though the hot mass is slowly and steadily rising, it will take millions of years before it reaches the surface and reshapes the area's geography or create a volcano.Scientists say what's happening in New England may be similar to the onset of the Yellowstone supervolcano.It emphasizes how intricate and dynamic the Earth's subsurface features are, and definitely warrants further study.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Researchers analyzed seismic waves to visualize subsurface conditions2. Mass of hot rock detected under Vermont, New Hampshire, and Massachusetts3. Hot rock rising slowly, could eventually lead to region becoming volcanically active 4. Potential volcanic eruptions possible, but won't be for millions of yearsVOICEOVER (in English): "Using data from earthquake measurement devices, Rutgers University researchers analyzed the speed and direction of seismic waves to visualize subsurface conditions.""They detected a massive upwelling of hot rock under Vermont, New Hampshire, and Massachusetts, after noticing the area was noticeably hotter than neighboring regions.""Though the hot mass is slowly and steadily rising, it will take millions of years before it reaches the surface and reshapes the area's geography or create a volcano."SOURCES: Rutgers University, National Geographic, Forbeshttps://news.rutgers.edu/research-news/mass-warm-rock-rising-beneath-new-england-rutgers-study-suggests/20171121#.WidNtoiGOUlhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/12/magma-bubble-rising-under-new-england-volcanoes-science/https://www.forbes.com/sites/trevornace/2017/12/05/enormous-pool-of-molten-rock-found-rising-beneath-new-england/#6bc482b6273e***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 09:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/06/3499019/3499019_3C264C2495B543D885161F180F469BC0_171206_3499019_Massive_bubble_of_hot_rock_detected_beneath_New__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7F3/F79/7F3F795ECC254B4D9FD3248805C2E56F_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hot rock, magma, new england, magma rising, molten rock, volcanoes, volcanic activity, seismic waves, seismic measurement, geology, EarthScope, Rutgers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3498957</guid>
      <title>How flu vaccines work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe flu has arrived early in North America, as officials worry this season's outbreak could be severe. According to the Center for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), the percentage of patients reporting flu-like symptoms reached the 2.2 percent threshold by late November, indicating flu season had begun, USA Today reported.Experts believe the U.S. could be hit hard by the H3N2 strain, the same strain behind Australia's especially bad flu season. The flu vaccine has been shown to be 10 percent against H3N2, according to a research paper in Eurosurveillance.  Flu vaccines cause antibodies to develop in the body around two weeks after vaccination, according the the CDC. These antibodies then help the body fight against virus infections that are in the vaccine. The seasonal flu vaccine is designed to protect against influenza viruses researchers predict will be the most common during the upcoming season, the CDC reported.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman with flu symptoms talking to doctor2. Experts believe the H3N2 strain could be prevalent this year3. Flu shots cause the body to develop antibodies in about two weeks4. Antibodies attacking a virusVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the CDC, the percentage of patients reporting flu-like symptoms reached the 2.2 percent threshold by late November, indicating flu season has begun." "Experts believe the U.S. could be hit hard by the H3N2 strain this year, which the flu vaccine was found to be only 10 percent effective against." "Flu vaccinations cause the body to develop antibodies in about two weeks. These antibodies then help fight against viruses in the vaccine.""The seasonal flu vaccine is designed to protect against influenza strains researchers predict will be the most common during the upcoming season."SOURCES: USA Today, CDChttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2017/12/05/flu-season-has-arrived-and-could-bad-one/925193001/https://www.cdc.gov/flu/protect/keyfacts.htm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 08:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/06/3498957/3498957_608B5C5933E34C9EB10B8F9B4A696980_171206_3498957_How_flu_vaccines_work_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5D4/360/5D43606E399541259411FAE165E3A3F1_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, flu season, flu shots, flu vaccinations, H3N2 influenza strain, H3N2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3498853</guid>
      <title>Amazon patents self-destructing delivery drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAmazon has been granted a patent for self-destructing delivery drones in case of mid-air emergencies.The company filed the patent last year, according to New Atlas. In addition to a person controlling the drone's flightpath, the drone would also have a "fragmentation controller" responsible for breaking the drone apart if needed. The fragmentation controller would detect any drone error and come up with a "fragmentation sequence" in order to determine which parts should be broken off the machine. The controller would need to be able to track the flight path, weather conditions and topography to determine what parts can be released.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Amazon delivery drone delivering a package2. Drone operator controlling the delivery drone3. Amazon drone falling apart during a fragmentation sequence4. Drone fragmentation controller has the ability to track flight path, weather and topographyVOICEOVER (in English): "Amazon has been granted a patent for self-destructing delivery drones in case of mid-air emergencies." "In addition to a person controlling the drone's flightpath, the drone would also have a 'fragmentation controller' responsible for breaking the drone apart if needed." "The fragmentation controller would detect any drone error and come up with a 'fragmentation sequence' in order to determine which parts should be broken off the machine." "The controller would need to be able to track the flight path, weather conditions and topography to determine what parts can be released." SOURCES: New Atlas, NBC Newshttps://newatlas.com/amazon-delivery-drones-self-destuct/52456/https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/amazon-drone-designed-self-destruct-emergencies-here-s-why-ncna826246***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 07:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/06/3498853/3498853_86C524F440284C4C9C89710B517CE75A_171206_3498853_Amazon_patents_self_destructing_delivery_drones_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6D5/DF8/6D5DF82955544310AAEFE5098933446B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Amazon delivery drone, Amazon drone, Amazon self-destruct drone, Amazon patents self destruct drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3498834</guid>
      <title>Scientists call for ban on glitter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEEnvironmental experts are calling for a worldwide ban on glitter amidst concerns that it is hazardous to the environment.Fortune reports that glitter is made from millimeter-sized bits of a polymer called polyethylene terephthalate or PET, or sometimes known as mylar. Scientists consider it a microplastic, and say it should be banned.Glitter filters into the oceans, where it gets mistaken for food by fish and other sea creatures, and can leach out harmful chemicals into the marine environment.A 2014 study estimated that the world's seas contain roughly 5.25 trillion pieces of plastic trash, with microplastics accounting for 92.4%.The UK is set to officially ban items that contain tiny plastics called microbeads by 2018, with other countries also following suit.Some British nurseries have already taken up the call to give up glitter, and banned the use of the product in their facilities. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Glitter is a microplastic, made from polymer called mylar2. Glitter filters into oceans, can cause harm to marine life3. Microplastics make up 92.4% of the trillions of plastic trash polluting the oceans4. UK to officially ban items that contain microbeads in 2018VOICEOVER (in English): "Glitter is made from millimeter-sized bits of a polymer known as PET, or mylar. Scientists consider it a microplastic, and argue that it should be banned.""Glitter filters into the oceans, where it gets mistaken for food by fish and other sea creatures, and can leach out harmful chemicals into the marine environment.""A 2014 study estimated that the world's seas contain roughly 5.25 trillion pieces of plastic trash, with microplastics accounting for 92.4%""The UK is set to officially ban items that contain tiny plastics called microbeads by 2018, with other countries also following suit."SOURCES: Fortune, New York Times, U.S. National Library of Medicinehttp://fortune.com/2017/11/30/banning-glitter/https://www.nytimes.com/2017/11/30/style/glitter-ban.htmlhttps://toxtown.nlm.nih.gov/text_version/chemicals.php?id=96***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 06:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/06/3498834/3498834_D1FA3ABC772A44FDAB730430C2DEB300_171206_3498834_Scientists_call_for_ban_on_glitter_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/91D/7F0/91D7F09F082F4C56B975B2BA3A6FD1AA_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, glitter, microplastics, plastic pollution, plastic trash, ocean pollution, microbeads, glitter ban, glitter hazard]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3500052</guid>
      <title>MIT engineers create living tattoo using live bacteria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA team at MIT have successfully created the world's first living tattoo, using ink made from live bacteria.According to MIT News, engineers programmed bacterial cells to light up in response to different chemicals, then mixed them with hydrogel and cell-feeding nutrients to form a bio ink.A custom 3D printer was used to print out layers of ink on a transparent elastomer patch, creating a tattoo in the shape of a tree.When the patch is placed over skin that had been exposed to the chemical stimuli, the bacteria sensed the chemicals and caused branches of the tree tattoo to light up.The living tattoo has numerous applications, and can be used to sense pollutants in the environment, or detect changes in body temperature and pH.In the future, the team says their creation can be used to create drug capsules that produce and release compounds such as glucose therapeutically, over time. It may even be used to create living computers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bacteria programmed to respond to stimuli, combined with hydrogel to make ink2. 3D printer used to print living tattoo in the shape of a tree3. Tattoo lights up when bacteria senses the chemical compound on the skin4. Tattoo can be engineered to detect pollutants, or changes in temperature or pHVOICEOVER (in English): "Engineers programmed bacterial cells to light up in response to different chemicals, then mixed them with hydrogel and cell-feeding nutrients to form a bio ink.""A custom 3D printer was used to print out layers of ink on a transparent elastomer patch, creating a tattoo in the shape of a tree.""When the patch is placed over skin that had been exposed to the chemical stimuli, the bacteria sensed the chemicals and caused branches of the tree tattoo to light up.""The living tattoo has numerous applications, and can be used to sense pollutants in the environment, or detect changes in body temperature and pH."SOURCES: Massachusetts Institute of Technologyhttp://news.mit.edu/2017/engineers-3-d-print-living-tattoo-1205***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 15:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/07/3500052/3500052_096E7D8B925C418583318105619AEA48_171207_3500052_MIT_engineers_create_living_tattoo_using_live_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D1E/D51/D1ED51C299724D239E43385C16330D6B_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, living tattoo, live bacteria, bacteria, 3D tattoo, 3D printed tattoo, bacteria tattoo, sensor, chemical stimuli, hydrogel, bio ink]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3499895</guid>
      <title>Norway developing world's first all-electric autonomous shipping container</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETwo Norwegian companies have teamed up to build the world's first all-electric, autonomous container ship. Norwegian company Yara and maritime technology company Kongsberg have said the vessel will be ready by late 2018, according the New Atlas. The state-of-the-art ship will transport chemicals and fertilizers from a Yara production plant to nearby towns. The plan is for the boat to first be operated by a crew in 2018, before transitioning into remote operations in 2019 and then fully autonomous by 2020. By transitioning to an all-electric shipping pathway, Yara can cut down 40,000 truck deliveries a year, which translates into reductions in nitrogen oxide and carbon dioxide emissions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The all-electric, autonomous container ship2. Containers being loaded onto the shipping vessel3. Vessel using automatic mooring to leave the shipping yard4. Container ship sailing through the waterVOICEOVER (in English): "Norwegian company Yara and maritime technology firm Kongsberg are teaming up to build the world's first all-electric, autonomous container ship." "The state-of-the-art ship will transport chemicals and fertilizers from a Yara production plant to nearby towns." "The plan is for the boat to first be operated by a crew in 2018, before transitioning into remote operations in 2019 and then fully autonomous by 2020." "By transitioning to an all-electric shipping pathway, Yara can cut down 40,000 truck deliveries a year, which translates into reductions in nitrogen oxide and carbon dioxide emissions."SOURCES: New Atlashttps://newatlas.com/autonomous-electric-shipping-container-vessel/49477/#p463526***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 11:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/07/3499895/3499895_D58129A542F64A829603952478E26A21_171207_3499895_Norway_developing_world_s_first_all_electric_aut_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3F0/DDD/3F0DDD711295452598B00FFFA8BD4920_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, container ship, all-electric container ship, autonomous container ship, autonomous vessels, shipping vessel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3500832</guid>
      <title>Air Force developing non-lethal cruise missile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. Air Force is developing a new, non-lethal cruise missile which officials say could knock out North Korean missiles. The system is called the CHAMP, which stands for Counter-electronics High Power Microwave Advanced Missile Project. It's a high-powered microwave weapon that can be delivered on an air-launched cruise missile from an American bomber, according to CNN. The Champ system is designed to fly at low altitudes into enemy airspace and send out strong electromagnetic impulses in order to jam enemy control-and-command systems. Cruise missiles fired by the enemy would then splash down in the ocean. The system is still in the development phase and also has drawbacks. Although non-lethal, the missile looks similar to the nuclear-capable variant and could be mistaken as an act of war if spotted by other countries. Another obstacle for the CHAMP system is that military equipment often has redundant wiring and insulation to protect from electronic attacks. The system would need to be able to disable all those electronics in order to successfully bring missiles down out of the sky. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. CHAMP missile sending out electromagnetic impulses2. B52 launching a CHAMP missile3. CHAMP missile disabling a mobile command and control system 4. An enemy cruise missile splashing down in the oceanVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Air Force is developing a new, non-lethal cruise missile which officials say could knock out North Korean missiles." "The CHAMP system is a high-powered microwave weapon that can be delivered on an air-launched cruise missile from an American bomber.""The CHAMP missiles are designed to fly at low altitudes into enemy airspace and send out strong electromagnetic impulses in order to jam enemy control-and-command systems." "Cruise missiles fired by the enemy would then splash down in the ocean." SOURCES: CNN, Business Insider***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 15:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/08/3500832/3500832_F2F3554ABAE141469F4618ECE0DB09AE_171208_3500832_Air_Force_developing_non_lethal_cruise_missile_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/207/A54/207A54EB08A249C9A92F0490B20CE23C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, CHAMP missile, CHAMP missile system, EMP weapons, CHAMP cruise missiles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3500415</guid>
      <title>ITER nuclear fusion project reaches 50 percent completion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEConstruction on the International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor (ITER) in southern France has reached the important halfway milestone.The ITER project consists of 35 nations working on the most complex reactor ever built, consisting of over one million different components, Newsweek reported.Fusion energy looks to replicate the same process that powers the sun by converting hydrogen atoms into helium through a process that occurs at extreme temperatures, the Guardian reported.The ITER hopes to use hydrogen fusion controlled by massive superconducting magnets to create heat energy that can drive turbines to produce electricity. The energy produced would have zero carbon emissions, and could potentially be done at low cost if the production scale is large enough.The reactor will have to be able to sustain temperatures 150 million degrees celsius  10 times hotter than the sun's core. The massive donut-shaped tokamak reactor will be surrounded by giant magnets that take superheated plasma away from the metal walls of the container. This requires the magnets to be cooled to -269 degrees celsius. The next milestone for the project will be to get to "first plasma" by December 2025 in order to prove the concept is viable.      RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The ITER site2. A nuclear fusion reaction3. The tokamak reactor4. A close up cross section of the tokamak reactorVOICEOVER (in English): "Construction on the International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor in southern France has reached the important halfway milestone.""Fusion energy looks to replicate the same process that powers the sun by converting hydrogen atoms into helium through a process that occurs at extreme temperatures.""The reactor will have to be able to sustain temperatures 150 million degrees celsius  10 times hotter than the sun's core." "The massive donut-shaped tokamak reactor will be surrounded by giant magnets that take superheated plasma away from the metal walls of the container. This requires the magnets to be cooled to -269 degrees celsius." SOURCES: Newsweek, Guardianhttp://www.newsweek.com/fusion-energy-iter-reactor-50-percent-complete-735266https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/dec/06/iter-nuclear-fusion-project-reaches-key-halfway-milestone***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 07:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/08/3500415/3500415_FA158BB3F9234E18B41F548430CD89FF_171208_3500415_ITER_nuclear_fusion_project_reaches_50_percent_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EC3/DCE/EC3DCEBF7D344ECDBEBE9B40653E35A5_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nuclear fusion, ITER, ITER fusion project, International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor, nuclear fusion energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3502624</guid>
      <title>Electron rocket prepares second launch from New Zealand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONERocket Lab has had to repeatedly postpone the test flight of their second Electron vehicle to Tuesday afternoon, after weather conditions and orbital traffic proved less than ideal on Monday.The New Zealand Herald reports that the electron rocket known as 'Still Testing' is currently at a launch site in New Zealand.  It's 17 meters long and can carry a 150-kilogram payload into orbit.The rocket will be launched into space from the Mahia Peninsula, with the first stage scheduled to separate and fall into the Pacific two and a half minutes into the flight.Three shoebox-sized satellites will then be released at 8 minutes, 31 seconds.The single Dove Pioneer CubeSat is an Earth-imaging satellite, while the two Lemur-2 satellites are used for weather mapping and ship traffic tracking.Rocket Labs successfully launched its first Electron rocket in May 2017, though it failed to reach orbit.The company originally planned three test flights, and will run a third test launch if needed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Electron rocket is 17m long, can carry 150kg payload into orbit2. Rocket set for second launch attempt from Mahia Peninsula 3. Rocket will release three shoebox-sized satellites into space4. Satellites will be used for Earth imaging, weather mapping, and ship traffic trackingVOICEOVER (in English): "The Electron rocket known as 'Still Testing' is currently at a launch site in New Zealand.  It's 17 meters long and can carry a 150-kilogram payload into orbit.""The rocket will be launched into space from the Mahia Peninsula, with the first stage scheduled to separate and fall into the Pacific two and a half minutes into the flight.""Three shoebox-sized satellites will then be released at 8 minutes, 31 seconds.""The single Dove Pioneer CubeSat is an Earth-imaging satellite, while the two Lemur-2 satellites are used for weather mapping and ship traffic tracking."SOURCES: New Zealand Herald, Spaceflight Nowhttp://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&objectid=11957268https://spaceflightnow.com/2017/12/07/rocket-lab-pushes-back-second-electron-launch-by-one-day/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 14:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/11/3502624/3502624_26B8A790980649538C51FF8CEEC7918D_171211_3502624_Electron_rocket_prepares_second_launch_from_New__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/909/C61/909C611AA617487FADE4D603A12890F3_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, electron rocket, electron launch, rocket launch, new zealand rocket launch, rocket labs, still testing, dove pioneer, lemur-2, cubesats, satellites, payload, rocket]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3503117</guid>
      <title>Bomber arrived in U.S. via "chain migration"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe man responsible for the attempted suicide bombing on the Big Apple's Port Authority tunnel came to the U.S. 6 years ago via so-called "chain migration."According to the New York Times, Akayed Ullah came to the U.S. in February 2011 from Bangladesh via, what officials call, "extended family chain migration." He is the nephew of a American citizen.Ullah is said to have lived in Brooklyn as a legal permanent resident with his parents, brother and brother's wife. His father died some time ago, reported NBC New York, citing a witness talking to News 4.The 27-year-old also stayed at an apartment building on Ocean Parkway in Kensington. It's here he's believed to have assembled the explosive, reported NBC New York.From March 2012 to March 2015, Ullah held license to operate as a for-hire driver but not as a yellow taxi driver, Taxi and Limousine Commission spokesperson told ABC 7 New York. Prior to the attack, he worked as a electrician at a building site in Manhattan, reported the New York Times.Ullah told investigators his attack was inspired by Islamic State. He claimed to have watched IS propaganda videos, read extremist literature and learned how to make explosives online, NBC New York reported, citing law enforcement officialsU.S. President Donald Trump blamed lax immigration for the attack. According to the New York Post, he said chain migration was incompatible with national security and called on congress to end it.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of bomber travelling to US via extended family chain migration2. Depiction of bomber's family and residences3. Depiction of bomber's reported driver license and role as electrician4. Depiction of bomber watching material on internetVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the New York Times, Akayed Ullah came to the U.S. in February 2011 from Bangladesh via, what officials call, "extended family chain migration".""He is the nephew of an American citizen.""Ullah is said to have lived in Brooklyn as a legal permanent resident with his parents, brother and brother's wife. His father died some time ago.""The 27-year-old also stayed at an apartment building on Ocean Parkway in Kensington. It's here he's believed to have assembled the explosive.""From March 2012 to March 2015, Ullah had a license to operate as a for-hire driver, but not as a yellow taxi driver.""Prior to the attack, he worked as a electrician at a construction site in Manhattan""Ullah told investigators his attack was inspired by Islamic State."  "He claimed to have watched their propaganda videos, read extremist literature and learned how to make bombs at his apartment in Kensington."SOURCES: New York Times, New York Post, CBS New York, ABC 7 New York, NBC New York, https://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/11/nyregion/akayed-ullah-port-authority-bombing-suspect.html?rref=nyregionhttps://nypost.com/2017/12/11/suicide-bombing-suspect-was-a-cab-driver-bent-on-revenge-cops/http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2017/12/11/port-authority-terror-suspect/http://abc7ny.com/nyc-terror-attack-what-we-know-about-the-suspect/2768447/https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Port-Authority-Explosion-Who-Is-Suspect-New-York-City-463387393.htmlhttps://nypost.com/2017/12/11/trump-blames-lax-immigration-system-for-nyc-terror-attack/ ***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 08:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/12/3503117/3503117_383CC7292D5546AD85D7CD72AA6821CF_171212_3503117_Bomber_arrived_in_U_S__via__chain_migration__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F4B/063/F4B063CC535D4163A0F356EDF0B92D33_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, new york port authority attack, port authority bombing, akayed ullah, who is akayed ullah, port authority bomber background, new york attack 2017, bangladesh bomber new york]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3503073</guid>
      <title>China to have 626 million surveillance cameras by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina is building its surveillance network, and could soon be keeping a close eye on each and every one of their 1.3 billion citizens.The Straits Times reports that roughly 176 million AI-equipped surveillance cameras are currently installed across China, with the number set to increase to 626 million by 2020.Citizens' ID profiles, social media photos, and other personal details are being filed in a database and connected to security cameras nationwide.The advanced surveillance system uses facial recognition technology to instantly identify the name, gender, and age of any pedestrian, and the type and color of any vehicle.The same technology is being used by commercial and private institutions for financial dealings, keyless entry, and even to thwart toilet paper theft.The system can also scan faces and compare them with the police database, allowing authorities to locate and apprehend criminals at large.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Surveillance cameras in China to number 626 million by 20202. Database containing citizens' ID profiles, social media photos to be connected to surveillance camera network 3. AI can identify pedestrians and vehicles captured on CCTV footage4. System can be used to identify and arrest criminals VOICEOVER (in English): "Roughly 176 million AI-equipped surveillance cameras are currently installed across China, with the number set to increase to 626 million by 2020.""Citizens' ID profiles, social media photos, and other personal details are being filed in a database and connected to security cameras nationwide.""The advanced surveillance system uses facial recognition technology to instantly identify the name, gender, and age of any pedestrian, and the type and color of any vehicle.""The system can also scan faces and compare them with the police database, allowing authorities to locate and apprehend criminals at large."SOURCES: Straits Times, Global Times, South China Morning Post, BBChttp://www.straitstimes.com/opinion/chinas-all-seeing-surveillance-state-is-reading-its-citizens-faceshttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1070546.shtmlhttp://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2115094/china-build-giant-facial-recognition-database-identify-anyhttp://www.bbc.com/news/av/world-asia-china-42248056/in-your-face-china-s-all-seeing-state***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 08:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/12/3503073/3503073_6D1C90D2CD87413780C423086677C55A_171212_3503073_China_to_have_626_million_surveillance_cameras_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B79/832/B798325B719F423FB94F612EFDFFE601_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, china surveillance, mass surveillance, surveillance state, police state, big brother, skynet, cctv, surveillance, surveillance network, big brother is watching]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3503038</guid>
      <title>Suspect held after attempted suicide attack in New York</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA Bangladeshi man set off a homemade explosive device in one of Manhattan's busiest transit hubs, in what authorities are calling a terrorist attack.According to the New York Times,the incident occurred in the underground passageway between the Port Authority Times Square subway stations.27-year-old suspect Akayed Ullah had strapped a pipe bomb to his body using velcro and zip ties, and detonated the device around 7:20 a.m.The powder-filled pipe was ignited using a Christmas light bulb, matches, and a 9-volt battery, but failed to detonate properly. One cap was blown off, but the rest of the pipe remained intact.Ullah sustained burns and lacerations to his hands and abdomen, and was taken to the hospital after being subdued by police. Several others received minor injuries.The suspect claimed the bombing was done in retaliation to U.S. airstrikes on the Islamic State in Syria, and says he took inspiration from similar Christmas attacks in Europe.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of bombing2. Pipe bomb attached to suspect with velcro and zip ties, detonated at 7:20 a.m.3. Pipe bomb ignited using christmas light bulb, matches, 9 volt battery, did not detonate properly4. Suspect, others injuredVOICEOVER (in English): "The incident occurred in the underground passageway between the Port Authority Times Square subway stations.""27-year-old suspect Akayed Ullah had strapped a pipe bomb to his body using velcro and zip ties, and detonated the device around 7:20 a.m.""The powder-filled pipe was ignited using a Christmas light bulb, matches, and a 9-volt battery, but failed to detonate properly. One cap was blown off, but the rest of the pipe remained intact.""Ullah sustained burns and lacerations to his hands and abdomen, while several others received minor injuries."SOURCES: New York Times, Reuters, The Telegraphhttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/12/11/nyregion/port-authority-explosion-bombing.html?action=click&module=TopStories&pgtype=Homepagehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-newyork-incident/subway-bomber-wounds-self-three-victims-in-new-york-idUSKBN1E51E9http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/11/new-york-police-respond-reports-explosion-inmanhattan/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 07:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/12/3503038/3503038_32D33202F86D44EF9CDECBF9AED9E3CF_171212_3503038_Suspect_held_after_attempted_suicide_attack_in_N_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4E7/FFC/4E7FFCAD78CE40AF91A3156ED39C3D6F_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, new york bombing, port authority bombing, new york attack, ny bombing, new york subway bomb, pipe bomb, explosive, new york subway, akayed ullah]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3503903</guid>
      <title>Bitcoin marches towards $20,000, as Litecoin and Ethereum hit record highs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEVirtual currencies continue to gain in value as Bitcoin hit another all-time high on Tuesday, as investors now hope to break the $20,000-mark. The interest in Bitcoin has also helped other cryptocurrencies hit record highs as well, Business Insider reported.Both Litecoin and Ethereum hit all-time highs Tuesday morning. Ether reached $600 a token, while Litecoin gained more than 40 percent to $312. Due to the huge surge in traffic, cryptocurrency trading platform Coinbase had to temporarily halt trading on litecoin and ethereum. Coinbase's status page showed both cryptocurrencies were experiencing major outages.  The 10 largest cryptocurrencies were all trading in the green on Tuesday, CoinMarketCap reported. But as digital currencies continues to set new records, many analysts are concerned that the speculative bubble will eventually burst. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bitcoin price going up2. Litecoin and Ethereum prices hitting all-time highs 3. Coinbase website experiencing surge in traffic4. Coinbase halting Litecoin and Ethereum trading do to website outages5. Analysts warn the digital currency speculative bubble will eventually burstVOICEOVER (in English): "Virtual currencies continue to gain in value as Bitcoin hit another all-time high on Tuesday, as investors now hope to break the $20,000-mark." "The interest in Bitcoin also helped Litecoin and Ethereum break new marks. Litecoin gained more than 40 percent to $312, while Ethereum hit $600 a token.""Due to the huge surge in traffic, cryptocurrency trading platform Coinbase had to temporarily halt trading on Litecoin and Ethereum." "Coinbase's status page showed both cryptocurrencies were experiencing major outages."  "But as digital currencies continues to set new records, many analysts are concerned that the speculative bubble will eventually burst." SOURCES: Reuters, Business Insider, CNBChttps://www.reuters.com/article/uk-markets-Bitcoin/Bitcoin-hits-another-record-high-in-march-towards-20000-idUSKBN1E60PEhttp://www.businessinsider.com/coinbase-halts-ether-and-litecoin-trading-2017-12https://www.cnbc.com/2017/11/28/novogratz-cryptocurrencies-are-going-to-be-the-biggest-bubble-of-our-lifetimes.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/13/3503903/3503903_BFCDFFA23A9A4C57884BAB2700B1698C_171213_3503903_Bitcoin_marches_towards__20_000__as_Litecoin_and_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F73/6A3/F736A3A87B2E4D669EC4BF825B454313_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Coinbase, cryptocurrency, digital currency, digital coins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3503773</guid>
      <title>The importance of Jerusalem's holy sites, explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEPresident Trump has announced that the U.S. will recognize Jerusalem as the capital of Israel, a highly controversial move that may spark an uproar in the Middle East.Jews and Arabs have fought over the city for years, both claiming it as their capital. But what's the big deal with Jerusalem, anyway?According to the Washington Post, the city of Jerusalem is sacred to the world's three major religions: Judaism, Islam, and Christianity.Jews flock to Old City to worship at the Western Wall, which is the last remnant of an ancient Jewish Temple.Islam's third holiest site, the Al-Aqsa Mosque, and the Dome of the Rock, are both in Jerusalem. It's also where the prophet Muhammad is believed to have ascended into heaven.For Christians, the most sacred site is the Church of the Holy Sepulchre- believed to be where Jesus was crucified, buried, and resurrected.The holy sites are governed by different bodies, with only the Western Wall directly controlled by the Israeli government A Muslim religious organization is in charge of the Islamic sites, while different Christian groups manage the Church.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Jerusalem sacred to Christianity, Judaism, Islam2. Muslim holy sites in Jerusalem3. Jewish holy sites4. Christian holy sitesVOICEOVER (in English): "The city of Jerusalem is sacred to the world's three major religions: Christianity, Judaism, and Islam.""Jews flock to Old City to worship at the Western Wall, which is the last remnant of an ancient Jewish Temple.""Islam's third holiest site, the Al-Aqsa Mosque, and the Dome of the Rock, are both in Jerusalem. It's also where the prophet Muhammad is believed to have ascended into heaven.""For Christians, the most sacred site is the Church of the Holy Sepulchre- believed to be where Jesus was crucified, buried, and resurrected."SOURCES: Washington Post, Straits Timeshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/acts-of-faith/wp/2017/12/06/questions-about-jerusalem-you-were-afraid-to-ask/?utm_term=.95dea719d007http://www.straitstimes.com/world/middle-east/why-trumps-decision-to-declare-jerusalem-as-israels-capital-is-so-controversial***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 07:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/13/3503773/3503773_A225B30CBD2345B18364C618FB21782F_171213_3503773_The_importance_of_Jerusalem_s_holy_sites__explai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7D4/B98/7D4B982B577D4F6CB24539F798B9D0F1_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, jerusalem, holy city, old city, jerusalem holy sites, israeli palestinian conflict, israel, palestine, islam, judaism, christianity, religion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3504707</guid>
      <title>Killer whales hunting great white sharks in South Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe bodies of five great white sharks washed up on the South African coast earlier this year and local scientists reckon orcas are to blame.Orcas are believed to attack great white sharks with their tails and turn them on their backs, reported Fox News. After being flipped, the shark is believed to undergo temporary paralysis and the orca then pushes it through the water. This would suffocate the shark. To finish its prey off, the orca is then believed to attack the shark's liver.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of incident. 2. Depiction of orca sneaking up on shark3. Depiction of shark on its back and orca pushing it4. Depiction of shark and orcaVOICEOVER (in English): "The bodies of five great white sharks washed up on the South African coast earlier this year.""Scientists reckon orcas are responsible.""Orcas are believed to attack great white sharks with their tails and turn them on their backs.""After being flipped, the shark is believed to undergo temporary paralysis. Next, the orca pushes it through the water.""This motion suffocates the sharks." "To finish its prey off, the orca is then believed to remove the shark's liver."SOURCES: Marine Dynamics, Fox News, The Inertiahttps://www.youtube.com/watch?time_continue=121&v=EN8jMaxJLSkhttp://www.theinertia.com/news/3-great-whites-washed-up-dead-in-south-africa-with-missing-livers-and-a-missing-heart/http://www.foxnews.com/science/2017/12/08/great-white-sharks-face-off-against-orcas-in-ocean-battleground.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 10:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/14/3504707/3504707_519B241A51184EFAA02D2D469B7DBBD2_171214_3504707_Killer_whales_hunting_great_white_sharks_in_Sout_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6E7/7C1/6E77C11C88194045BA5C5D94495106F2_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, orca v shark, shark v whale, marine dynamics, south africa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3504627</guid>
      <title>China collecting DNA from Xinjiang residents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAn international human rights organization has found that China is gathering DNA from a region in the far west that's home to a much-oppressed ethnic minority.The Xinjiang Uyghur Autonomous Region is home to about 10 million Uyghurs, a Muslim Turkic group with a long history of discord with the mainland. As such, it's one of the most tightly controlled parts of China.According to Human Rights Watch, authorities in Xinjiang are now collecting DNA samples and biometric data from all residents aged 12 to 65.Police officers collect photos, fingerprints, household registration data, and iris scans during home visits or at designated collection points.Blood types and DNA are gathered through a government health exam called "Physicals for All". Data is transmitted to a database and linked to the individual's national ID number.People originally from Xinjiang who have moved to other parts of China are also required to submit their information locally.Over 18 million people have participated in the physical as of November 2017. Though "Physicals for AlL" is a supposedly voluntary, residents are expected and often pressured to take part.Human Rights Watch has slammed the mandatory databanking as a gross violation of human rights, adding that carrying it out under the guise of a free healthcare program makes it even more disturbing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. DNA samples, biometrics collected from Xinjiang residents2. Police officers collect photos, household registration information, biometric data3. DNA, blood types collected using free physical health exams4. Xinjiang residents who have moved away also need to submit their dataVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Human Rights Watch, authorities in Xinjiang are now collecting DNA samples and biometric data from all residents aged 12 to 65.""Police officers collect photos, fingerprints, household registration data, and iris scans during home visits or at designated collection points.""Blood types and DNA are gathered through a government health exam called 'Physicals for All'. Data is transmitted to a database and linked to the individual's national ID number.""People originally from Xinjiang who have moved to other parts of China are also required to submit their information locally."SOURCES: Human Rights Watchhttps://www.hrw.org/news/2017/12/13/china-minority-region-collects-dna-millions***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 09:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/14/3504627/3504627_BFA23CAC9E28401FA1159BACD353682A_171214_3504627_China_collecting_DNA_from_Xinjiang_residents_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/069/DF8/069DF84BC647412C826BD738C7E556F7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, xinjiang, uighurs, uyghurs, china dna database, china dna collection, dna database, dna sample, biometric data, fingerprint, iris scan, police database]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3505142</guid>
      <title>Research discover ticks that fed on dinosaurs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew research in the journal Nature Communications discusses how ticks fed on feathered dinosaurs.The newly discovered species of tick is called Deinocroton draculi, meaning "Dracula's terrible tick".The ticks were found inside 99-million-year-old lumps of amber from Myanmar. Two of the ticks were found with a dinosaur feather. One was wrapped around it. Researchers say the finding the is the first direct evidence that ticks fed on feathered dinosaurs. Scientists suspect the feather belonged to an unknown type dinosaur or a ancient bird species called enantiornithine.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of discovered fossils2. Depiction of ticks inside tick fossil3. Depiction of ticks on surface of feathered dinosaur4. Depiction of enantiornithine bird bones in a walking pose.VOICEOVER (in English): "The ticks were found inside 99-million-year-old lumps of amber from Myanmar.""Two of the ticks were found with a dinosaur feather. One was wrapped around it. "Researchers say the finding the first direct evidence that ticks fed on feathered dinosaurs.""Scientists suspect the feather belonged to an unknown type dinosaur or an ancient bird species called enantiornithine[a]."SOURCES: Nature, Oxford Museum of Natural History, National Geographichttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-017-01550-z#Fig5https://morethanadodo.com/2017/12/12/bound-by-blood/https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/12/tick-dinosaur-feather-found-in-amber-blood-parastites-science/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 04:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/15/3505142/3505142_0A0D87344827463B96062F31F77979C7_171215_3505142_Research_discover_ticks_that_fed_on_dinosaurs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/300/BD2/300BD2F4CA3144EF97ACB4F094E4FE98_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dinosaur ticks, dinosaur tick, Deinocroton draculi, ticks drinking, dinosaur ticks, prehistoric ticks, Deinocroton draculi, oxford, dinosaur drinking tick]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3506025</guid>
      <title>China still developing bases in South China Sea: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina has kept on developing military bases in the South China Sea throughout 2017, a think tank has claimed in a new report.A new Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative report says China has continued developing its bases in the South China Sea. The country has reportedly installed wind turbines and a helipad at Tree Island, and towers on Triton Island, Reuters reported, citing the AMTI report. AMTI says China has continued development of Subi reef, creating underground tunnels for ammunition storage and installing further radar technology. On Fiery Cross Reef, China has created underground tunnels for supply and ammunition storage, as well as a high-frequency radar array. The report says that China also created underground storage tunnels, missile shelters and radar arrays on Mischief Reef.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Development on Tree Island and Triton Island2. Development on Subi Reef3. Development on Fiery Cross Reef4. Development on Mischiefl ReefVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, Reutershttps://amti.csis.org/constructive-year-chinese-building/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southchinasea-china/while-focus-is-on-north-korea-china-continues-south-china-sea-buildup-think-tank-idUSKBN1E834O?il=0***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 08:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/16/3506025/3506025_4A47AAD1509246929ECBEBCE93F0614D_171216_3506025_China_still_developing_bases_in_South_China_Sea__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A9F/672/A9F67287DA624ADA8D3896914FDA2C04_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, south China sea, China, military bases, 2017, amti, mischief reef, subi reef, triton island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3507402</guid>
      <title>Great Pyramid of Giza hidden chamber could be explored by inflatable robotic blimp</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers are developing a blimp-like drone that can explore a newly discovered hidden chamber in the Great Pyramid of Giza. Research institutions Inria and the French National Center for Scientific Research are designing the drone to squeeze through a 1.5-inch hole, before unfolding and inflating, Digital Trends reported. "The main challenge is to insert a complete exploration robot in a hole that is as small as possible," Inria researcher Dr. Jean-Baptiste Mouret told Digital Trends. "It's important to use a hole as small as possible because we want to leave as few traces as we can. This is what we call 'minimally invasive robotics.' We chose a diameter of 1.5 inches because it is a good trade-off between the size of the hole, the kind of machines that can bore holes, and the current robotic technologies."The blimp model was chosen over conventional multi-rotor drones because it's safer the surrounding environment during exploration. The blimp drone can make contact with obstacles without damaging the monument. They are also more stable than multi-rotor drones, which is important for taking photos in low-light conditions. The camera equipped drone will be remotely operated by radio, however can also operate autonomously via small onboard sensors. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The blimp drone being inserted into a chamber2. The blimp drone inflating and deploying3. The blimp drone exploring the hidden chamber4. The blimp drone making contact with the hidden chamber without damaging itVOICEOVER (in English): "French researchers are developing a blimp-like drone in order to explore a newly discovered hidden Chamber in the Great Pyramid of Giza." "The robotic drone is designed to squeeze through a 1.5-inch hole, before unfolding and inflating on a docking station." "The blimp model was chosen over conventional multi-rotor drones because it's safer the surrounding environment during exploration." "The drone can make contact with obstacles without damaging the monument. They are also more stable, which is important for taking photos in low-light conditions." SOURCES: Digital Trendshttps://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/pyramid-blimp-robot/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 10:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/18/3507402/3507402_D2645930A26D4640AA8D78E855719D12_171218_3507402_Great_Pyramid_of_Giza_hidden_chamber_could_be_ex_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/98E/249/98E2496F83D543148C4229885BEC8D92_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Great Pyramid Giza, Great Pyramid Giza hidden chamber, robotic blimp drone, blimp drone, mini blimp drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3507076</guid>
      <title>Alibaba to begin selling cars using massive vending machines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChinese e-commerce giant Alibaba will soon be selling cars through vending machines.Customers use Alibaba's Taobao mobile app to scan a car they want to test, and are asked by the system to pick a color, enter basic information, and take a selfie, according to CNET.At the automated car vending machine, facial recognition matches the customer with their car order, which is then dispatched from storage.Customers are given three days to test-drive the vehicle, after which they can buy directly through the app, or arrange to test drive a different model.The company is planning to open two facilities in January 2018, one in Shanghai and another in Nanjing.The service is limited to users who have a sesame credit score of at least 700, and belong to the higher tiers of the Alibaba 88 membership program.To curb abuses, users can only test a model once, with no more than five test drives within the first two months of signing up.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Customers scan car, pick color, input information and a selfie2. Facial recognition technology matches customer with car order3. Customers given three days to test-drive car, can buy car directly from app4. Test-drives available only for elite members of Alibaba 88 program with high sesame creditVOICEOVER (in English): "Customers use the Alibaba app to scan a car they want to test, and are asked by the system to pick a color, enter basic information, and take a selfie.""At the automated car vending machine, facial recognition matches the customer with their car order, which is then dispatched from storage.""Customers are given three days to test-drive the vehicle, after which they can buy directly through the app, or arrange to test drive a different model.""The service is limited to users who have a sesame credit score of at least 700, and belong to the higher tiers of the Alibaba 88 membership program."SOURCES: CNET, TechCrunchhttps://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/alibaba-launches-cat-shaped-car-vending-machines-in-china/https://techcrunch.com/2017/12/14/alibaba-car-vending-machines/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 04:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/18/3507076/3507076_2F63A2CDB3684D81BAD7B6F3627770C6_171218_3507076_Alibaba_to_begin_selling_cars_using_massive_vend_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8A6/A39/8A6A399F1B0E49B8A287F4BC412DEB83_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, alibaba, car vending machine, car mall, tmall, giant vending machine, taobao app, mobile app, test drive, car test drive, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3506992</guid>
      <title>Eighth planet found orbiting Kepler-90 star</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAn artificial intelligence algorithm sifted through data from the Kepler space telescope and uncovered an eighth planet in a distant star system, according to NASA.Google AI has discovered another planet orbiting Kepler-90, making it the first star known to support as many worlds as our sun, according to NASA.Though Kepler-90 is sunlike and its system is similar to ours, all eight planets' orbits are closer to their star than the earth is to the sun.The new planet, dubbed Kepler-90i, is 30% larger than Earth, and completes an orbit around its sun every 14.4 days.But with a rocky landscape and a surface temperature of over 800 degrees Fahrenheit, the planet is likely not habitable.Astronomers say it's possible that more planets are lurking around Kepler-90. They are planning to use the Google AI to analyze more data to hopefully uncover more exoplanets both in Kepler-90 system and beyond.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 8th planet discovered orbiting Kepler-90 2. Distance of all 8 planets to Kepler-90 closer than distance of Earth to Sun 3. Kepler-90i completes orbit around its sun every 14.4 days4. Kepler-90i has rocky landscape, high surface temperatureVOICEOVER (in English): "Google AI has discovered another planet orbiting Kepler-90, making it the first star known to support as many worlds as our sun.""Though Kepler-90 is sunlike and its system is similar to ours, all eight planets' orbits are closer to their star than the earth is to the sun.""The new planet, dubbed Kepler-90i, is 30% larger than Earth, and completes an orbit around its sun every 14.4 days.""But with a rocky landscape and a surface temperature of over 800 degrees Fahrenheit, the planet is likely not habitable."SOURCES: NASA, Science Newshttps://www.nasa.gov/press-release/artificial-intelligence-nasa-data-used-to-discover-eighth-planet-circling-distant-starhttps://www.sciencenews.org/article/ai-has-found-8-planet-system-ours-kepler-data***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 02:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/18/3506992/3506992_43879A6CD6AF46A48DBB48A2C1684FCB_171218_3506992_Eighth_planet_found_orbiting_Kepler_90_star_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EA2/1C6/EA21C6618D234FFD956D5D4A64C17889_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kepler, planet, new planet, exoplanet, kepler-90, kepler-90i, AI, google AI, artificial intelligence, kepler space telescope, space, planet hunting, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3508150</guid>
      <title>Israeli bus company invests millions in wireless charging electric roads</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEIsrael transit service Dan Bus Company will invest $2.2 million in technology that turns regular roads into electric power sources.Electric buses in Tel Aviv currently need to be charged via cable at departure stations, but this could soon be unnecessary, reports Globes.ElectRoad has developed technology that powers vehicles from the road while driving, using conduction coils to wirelessly charge them through magnetic induction.With this innovation, there is no need for batteries or cable charging. It also boasts zero emissions, high efficiency, and low cost.The startup will be focusing on public transportation, and will begin with laying charger coils underneath designated lanes to power the buses traversing the road daily. Eventually, ElectRoad says it may even be possible to share energy between vehicles.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Company already producing electric buses that run on a short charge2. ElectRoad's electric road technology3. Electric coils charge buses using magnetic induction4. Benefits of using electric road technology5. Charger coils laid underneath bus lane 6. Buses being charged while on the road VOICEOVER (in English): "Electric buses in Tel Aviv currently need to be charged via cable at departure stations, but this could soon be unnecessary.""ElectRoad has developed technology that powers vehicles from the road while driving, using conduction coils to wirelessly charge them through magnetic induction.""With this innovation, there is no need for batteries or cable charging. It also boasts zero emissions, high efficiency, and low cost.""The startup will be focusing on public transportation, and will begin with laying charger coils underneath designated lanes, to power the buses traversing the road daily."SOURCES: ElectRoad, Globes, Dan Public Transportationhttps://www.electroad.mehttp://www.globes.co.il/en/article-dan-to-invest-up-to-nis-8m-in-electric-road-1001211048http://www.dan.co.il/Eng/pages/1623.aspx***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 10:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/19/3508150/3508150_9F7AB3AFD50444D7855C8BC8535E5EB7_171219_3508150_Israeli_bus_company_invests_millions_in_wireless_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C59/350/C5935024D6B04E11ABC086F868159B77_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, electric road, electric bus, electric car, electroad, wireless charging, israel, israel transportation, dan bus company]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3508071</guid>
      <title>Flesh-eating dog disease surfaces in the UK</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAlabama rot, a fatal flesh gnawing skin disease, is claiming the lives of dogs all across the British Isles. According to Vets4Pets.com, many cases of Alabama Rot have been reported across the British Isles over the last several years. The disease is fatal to 9 out of 10 infected dogs.The cause remains unknown, but one commonality is that most reports come from dog owners who walk their pets in the countryside.British government information says the disease can present itself as skin lesions, ulcers and red patches of skin. In most cases, it eventually progresses to kidney failure.Dog owners are advised to avoid muddy forest areas and to clean their pet's paws and legs thoroughly after a walk.Thousands of UK dog owners walk their pets regularly in forests and only a small number of dogs are afflicted with Alabama Rot.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map showing Alabama Rot across UK 2. Woman walking dog in muddy forest area3. Woman cleaning dog after walkVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Vets4Pets.com, many cases of Alabama Rot have been reported across the British Isles over the last several years."The disease is fatal to 9 out of 10 infected dogs.""The cause remains unknown, but one commonality is that most reports come from dog owners who walk their pets in the countryside.""Dog owners are advised to avoid muddy forest areas and to clean their pet's paws and legs thoroughly after a walk."SOURCES: Leicester Mercury, Vets4Pets, Foresty (UK government information)http://www.leicestermercury.co.uk/news/uk-world-news/alabama-rot-kills-dogs-leicestershire-848866http://www.vets4pets.com/stop-alabama-rot/https://www.forestry.gov.uk/alabamarothttps://www.forestry.gov.uk/pdf/eng_NF_AlabamaRot_Mar14.pdf/$FILE/eng_NF_AlabamaRot_Mar14.pdf***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 09:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/19/3508071/3508071_D885C0CB217E402292CDB79174075039_171219_3508071_Flesh_eating_dog_disease_surfaces_in_the_UK_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E0C/34A/E0C34AA0DAF94A4991B351B534F89BA9_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, alabama rot in dogs, alabama rot, dog disease, British dogs walkers, dog owners, walking dog in forest, what is alabama rot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3508025</guid>
      <title>Amtrak train derails near Seattle, killing at least three</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONESeveral are dead and many more injured after a train on a new Amtrak service route derailed in Washington.The New York Times reports that on Monday morning, Amtrak Train No. 501 was on its inaugural run from Seattle to Portland with 77 passengers and seven crew members onboard.While approaching a curved overpass around 7:33 a.m., the lead engine ran off the track and sent passenger coaches tumbling onto Interstate-5 below.Thirteen of the 14 cars were derailed  some crashed into several vehicles on the road, while one was left dangling over the highway. According to the Washington State Patrol, least three are confirmed dead and over 100 are injured.Passengers say they felt a wobble before suddenly being catapulted forward. Some had to kick out the windows to escape, since the emergency doors didn't work properly.It has yet to be determined if the crash was due to speed, but the train was reportedly not using positive train control technology, which automatically slows trains exceeding speed limits.Washington Governor Jay Inslee declared a state of emergency following the deadly derailment, while Amtrak temporarily suspended service south of Seattle.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Amtrak train from Seattle to Portland had 77 passengers, 7 crew members2. Train derailed, 13 train cars go off track near I-5 highway overpass3. Highway vehicles crushed by derailed train cars; number of dead and injured4. Train not equipped with positive train controlVOICEOVER (in English): "On Monday morning, Amtrak Train No. 501 was on its inaugural run from Seattle to Portland with 77 passengers and seven crew members onboard.""While approaching a curved overpass, the lead engine ran off the track and sent passenger coaches tumbling onto Interstate-5 below.""The derailed cars crashed into several vehicles on the road, while one was left dangling over the highway. The Washington State Patrol confirmed at least three are dead, and 100 injured.""It has yet to be determined if the crash was due to speed, but the train was reportedly not using positive train control technology, which automatically slows trains exceeding speed limits."SOURCES: CNN, New York Times, The News Tribunehttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/18/us/amtrak-derailment-washington/index.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/18/us/amtrak-derailment-washington.htmlhttp://www.thenewstribune.com/news/local/article190312794.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 08:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/19/3508025/3508025_3A8680931338418083FBF78056A4D4B0_171219_3508025_Amtrak_train_derails_near_Seattle__killing_at_le_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D12/4E1/D124E1E3FE7B465E871A71ABDB0FD2B0_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, amtrak derailment, amtrak, cascades, train derailment, train crash, fatal train crash, amtrak derailed, amtrak, us train crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3507934</guid>
      <title>California issues cellphone guidelines to reduce possible radiation risk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe California Department of Public Health (CDPH) released a set of new guidelines last week dealing with cell phones and radiation risk. The department issued a guidance on how to reduce exposure to radio-frequency energy released by cell phones, despite hard evidence that exposure poses any health risks, Ars Technica reported. Some studies have suggested long-term use of smartphones could be linked to brain or salivary gland cancer, low sperm count and headaches, according to the CDPH, KQED reported. The guidelines suggest to avoid holding your phone to your head when talking on it. Send texts instead of talking. Avoid carrying your phone in your pocket, bra or belt holster. Carry it in a bag or a backpack. They also suggested to avoid using your phone with it's sending high levels of radio-frequency energy, such as when you're driving, streaming content or when your signal is weak. Try not to keep your phone by your head while you're sleeping.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People using their cell phones as they emit radio frequency energy2. The CDPH suggests texting instead of talking on phone3. The CDPH suggests carrying your phone in a bag or backpack4. The CDPH suggests avoid phone use when it's sending high levels of radio-frequency energy VOICEOVER (in English): "The California Department of Public Health released guidelines on how to reduce exposure to radio-frequency energy released by cell phones, despite the lack of hard evidence that exposure poses any health risks.""The guidelines suggest to avoid holding your phone to your head when talking on it. Send texts instead of talking." "Avoid carrying your phone in your pocket, bra or belt holster. Carry it in a bag or a backpack." "They also suggested avoiding using your phone while it's sending high levels of radio-frequency energy, such as when you're driving, streaming content or when your signal is weak." SOURCES: Ars Technica, KQEDhttps://arstechnica.com/science/2017/12/california-heres-how-to-handle-unfounded-fears-of-cell-phone-cancer/https://ww2.kqed.org/futureofyou/2017/12/15/california-issues-guidelines-to-reduce-potential-harm-from-cell-phones/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 06:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/19/3507934/3507934_1862CD40A35046E4BE7CE189C32F908F_171219_3507934_California_issues_cellphone_guidelines_to_reduce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C36/798/C3679855924A41CDADDECCB764467C21_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, California cellphone guidelines, radio-frequency energy, radio-frequency energy exposure, cellphone risks, smartphone risks  
:]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3508729</guid>
      <title>Facebook is rolling out new facial recognition features</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFacebook announced on Tuesday it will soon be introducing new facial recognition features in order to give users more tools to manage their identity on the platform. People will soon be able to activate facial recognition with an on/off switch to enable three different features, according to a Facebook blog post. First, Facebook will alert you when pictures of you are uploaded even if you have not been tagged in them, Gizmodo reported. Second, Facebook will notify you if your face is being used in a profile picture. Third, visually impaired users can now hear aloud the people tagged around them in group photos. To activate these features, users will have to authorize Facebook to access, store and match their face data with all uploads across the social media platform.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Facebook user having his face scanned2. Facebook's facial recognition can be turned on with an on/off switch3. Facial recognition will alert users when pictures of them have been uploaded or if their face is used for a profile picture 4. Visually impaired user listening to people tagged in photoVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook announced on Tuesday it will soon be introducing new facial recognition features in order to give users more tools to manage their identity on the platform." "People will soon be able to activate facial recognition with an on/off switch to enable three different features, according to a Facebook blog post." "First, Facebook will alert you when pictures of you are uploaded even if you have not been tagged in them. Second, you will be notified if your face is being used as a profile picture.""Third, visually impaired users can now hear aloud the people tagged around them in group photos." SOURCES: Gizmodo, Facebookhttps://gizmodo.com/facebook-wants-your-face-and-youll-probably-let-them-ha-1821428981https://newsroom.fb.com/news/2017/12/managing-your-identity-on-facebook-with-face-recognition-technology/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 07:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/20/3508729/3508729_B35D03DFB3214AD7AD4DAB5B8E452DE0_171220_3508729_Facebook_is_rolling_out_new_facial_recognition_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/31C/396/31C3969FAD20458180A7421BE1C35ABF_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Facebook, facial recognition, facial recognition data, facial data, face data, biometric data]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3508652</guid>
      <title>China flies tourist to Antarctica</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina claims it has flown its first commercial flight to Antarctica carrying 22 tourists. The trip consisted of a 15-hour flight from Hong Kong to South Africa, refueling in Cape Town and then another 5.5 hours to Antarctica. After reaching Antarctica, it was another five to six hours to the South Pole, where the plane landed on a 1.5-mile long runway carved into the ice, the BBC reported. The Chinese tour operator claims Chinese tourists no longer have to book through foreign agencies.  Although the trip from Cape Town onwards is actually organized and run by tour operator White Desert. White Desert regularly flies trips to the pole. So in reality, the Chinese are running the tours in cooperation with other foreign agencies.  Chinese tourists now make up the second largest group of tourists to the eighth continent, second only to U.S. tourists. The number of Chinese tourists in Antarctica has grown from 100 in 2008 to 3,944 in 2016.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flight from Hong Kong to Cape Town, then Cape Town to Antarctica2. Chinese tour plane flying over Antarctica3. Tourists getting off plane on runway4. Chinese tourists in AntarcticaVOICEOVER (in English): "China claims it has flown its first commercial flight to Antarctica carrying 22 tourists. The trip consisted of a 15-hour flight from Hong Kong to South Africa, refueling in Cape Town and then another 5.5 hours to Antarctica." "After reaching Antarctica, it was another five to six hours to the South Pole, where the plane landed on a 1.5-mile long runway carved into the ice.""The number of Chinese tourists in Antarctica has reportedly grown from 100 in 2008 to 3,944 in 2016." SOURCES: BBC http://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-42388788#***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 06:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/20/3508652/3508652_C944F7FDCF974CA8A8C1F1EA749E62E4_171220_3508652_China_flies_tourist_to_Antarctica_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ABE/439/ABE439F93E59412481EE44B1F9E24AF4_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China Antarctica commercial flight, China Antarctica tourism, China Antarctica flight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3508604</guid>
      <title>MIT researchers create plant that can glow in the dark</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMIT researchers have engineered a plant that can glow in the dark from the same enzyme fire flies use to glow.According to an MIT news release, scientists laced watercress plants with the luciferase enzyme. They envision the plant being used as a desk lamp replacement, but say it could possibly be applied to street lamps in the future.Details of the research were published in the journal Nanoletters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of plant being used for reading2. Depiction of fire fly, enzyme and plant3. Depiction of street lamps using plants for lightsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists at MIT have developed a plant that can glow in the dark.""They say it can be used for late night reading.""To light up the plants, they used an enzyme in fire flies known as luciferase. "This provides the insect with their glow.""The scientists say their work could possibly be applied to street lamps"SOURCES: MIThttp://news.mit.edu/2017/engineers-create-nanobionic-plants-that-glow-1213https://www.youtube.com/watch?time_continue=110&v=hp-vqd8zJM4***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 04:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/20/3508604/3508604_B61FCF5F6B4B4F8996F0A4A68B6590C1_171220_3508604_MIT_researchers_create_plant_that_can_glow_in_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/615/D0B/615D0B53EEB0405B88699139E8CCBAC3_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, glow in the dark plant, glowing plant, desk lamp plant, MIT, glowing flower, firefly]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3509488</guid>
      <title>Winter solstice arrives on Thursday</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe winter solstice arrives on Thursday, making it the shortest day of the year in the Northern Hemisphere. The Earth's axis has a 23.5-degree tilt, which is responsible for the seasons. As Earth makes its way around the sun each year, the Northern Hemisphere spends half of the year tilted slightly towards the sun during summer, and half the year tilted slightly  away during winter, the New York Times reported.  The winter solstice will occur at 11:28 a.m., the moment the North Pole is tilted farthest from the sun and the South Pole is tilted closest to it, according to the Baltimore Sun. Although it's the shortest day of the year in the north, the length of daylight varies by longitude and latitude. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The winter solstice from space2. The Earth's 23.5-degree tilt3. The Earth orbiting the sun4. The winter solstice VOICEOVER (in English): "The winter solstice will occur at 11:28 a.m. on Thursday, making it the shortest day of the year in the Northern Hemisphere." "The Earth's axis has a 23.5-degree tilt, which is responsible for the seasons." "As Earth makes its way around the sun each year, the Northern Hemisphere spends half of the year tilted slightly towards the sun during summer, and half the year tilted slightly  away during winter.""The winter solstice marks the moment the North Pole is tilted farthest from the sun and the South Pole is tilted closest to it."SOURCES: New York Times, Baltimore Sunhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/20/science/winter-solstice-december-21.htmlhttp://www.baltimoresun.com/news/weather/weather-blog/bs-md-winter-solstice-20171220-story.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 07:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/21/3509488/3509488_5002F6BBB1DE441095F9608B4C3B2498_171221_3509488_Winter_solstice_arrives_on_Thursday_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/37F/6CB/37F6CB50518E41DCB8D47E5D4B36DEA4_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, winter solstice, solstice, winter solstice explainer, shortest day of the year]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3509440</guid>
      <title>British telecom unveils wearable tech nail that doubles as phone handset</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEBritish telecom O2 has unveiled a prototype for a new wearable gadget that bridges the gap between fashion and tech.Mobile News reports that O2 has teamed up with London beauty brand Nails Inc. to create the "Mobile Nail", a wearable tech nail that can be used as a phone handset.The Mobile Nail pairs with a phone using bluetooth, and allows the user to answer a call, redial the last dialled number, or play music. The tech nail is also customizable, and can be modified with different nail art designs.Along with the unveiling of Mobile Nail, O2 published its 'Future of Mobile Life Report', which predicts that embeddable and wearable tech will advance to such a degree that the human body will replace smartphones by 2049.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Wearable tech nail made by O2 and Nails Inc. 2. Features and functions of tech nail3. Tech nail customizableVOICEOVER (in English): "O2 has teamed up with London beauty brand Nails Inc. to create the 'Mobile Nail', a wearable tech nail that can be used as a phone handset.""The Mobile Nail pairs with a phone using bluetooth, and allows the user to answer a call, redial the last dialled number, or play music.""The tech nail is also customizable, and can be modified with different nail art designs."SOURCES: Mobile News, Internet Retailinghttp://www.mobilenewscwp.co.uk/2017/12/19/o2-unveils-wearable-tech-phone-nail/http://internetretailing.net/2017/12/might-like-mobile-2049/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 06:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/21/3509440/3509440_0B2B4686B8274328B448FB70F42EA103_171221_3509440_British_telecom_unveils_wearable_tech_nail_that__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9CC/DB9/9CCDB98E29EA4A0AB740A6B60B775D9D_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, wearable tech, tech nail, mobile nail, O2, wearable technology, nail phone, nail inc, bluetooth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3509380</guid>
      <title>Baby born after being frozen as embryo for 24 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe longest known frozen human embryo to result in a successful birth was born last month in Tennessee.Emma Wren Gibson was born on November 25 from an embryo that was cryogenically frozen 24 years ago, CNN reported. Emma's parents, Tina and Benjamin Gibson, chose embryo adoption after realizing they were unable to have children.  The Gibsons selected Emma after viewing around 300 donor profiles listing basic genetic information about the genetic parents. They were surprised to find out the age of the embryo when it thawed on March 13 at the National Embryo Donation Center. The embryo that led to Emma was created for in vitro fertilization by an anonymous couple and placed in cryogenic storage on October 14, 1992. The previous record was set in 2011 when a New York woman gave birth to a boy born from an embryo created 20 years earlier, the Washington Post reported. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A lab technician working on an embryo in the lab2. A lab technician freezing embryos for storage3. A lab technician working on a test tube4. The Gibsons looking at donor profilesVOICEOVER (in English): "Emma Wren Gibson was born on November 25 from an embryo that was cryogenically frozen 24 years ago.""The embryo was created for in vitro fertilization by an anonymous couple and placed in cryogenic storage on October 14, 1992." "Emma's parents, Tina and Benjamin Gibson, chose embryo adoption after realizing they were unable to have children."  "The Gibsons selected Emma after viewing around 300 donor profiles listing basic genetic information about the genetic parents."SOURCES: CNN, KMOV, Washington Post http://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/19/health/snowbaby-oldest-embryo-bn/index.htmlhttp://www.kmov.com/story/37102095/baby-born-after-being-frozen-as-an-embryo-for-24-yearshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2017/12/19/this-baby-was-born-from-an-embryo-frozen-24-years-ago/?utm_term=.6a3ea817bb48***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 04:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/21/3509380/3509380_36BC375BB4994C7FB48DACF6BC5B4DB3_171221_3509380_Baby_born_after_being_frozen_as_embryo_for_24_ye_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1C4/A58/1C4A58E5136440878856D2B252D306DB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, frozen embryo, frozen human embryo, in vitro fertilization]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3510400</guid>
      <title>What is toxic shock syndrome?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA lost part of her right leg to a rare but potentially life-threatening condition known as toxic shock syndrome, which she claims came courtesy of her tampon.Toxic shock syndrome is typically associated with menstruating women, and is caused by toxins from the Staphylococcus aureus bacteria, reports the Washington Post.TSS is linked with tampon use, since the synthetic fibers and high absorbency provide the ideal breeding ground for the bacteria.According to Mayo Clinic, symptoms include gastrointestinal distress, a sudden high-fever, low blood pressure, a sunburn-like rash, and redness of the eyes, mouth, and throat.Toxic shock progress rapidly, and can lead to kidney failure. Though fatal, it is treatable with antibiotics and fluids if diagnosed early. Another variety of the syndrome is caused by group A streptococcus bacteria, with those having cuts or burns, or having had recent surgery especially at risk.Toxic shock syndrome is rare enough that there's little information on how to prevent the onset of the disease.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Toxic shock syndrome caused by toxin-producing staphylococcus bacteria2. Symptoms of toxic shock syndrome3. Complications and treatment of toxic shock syndrome4. Some cases of Toxic shock syndrome caused by streptococcus bacteriaVOICEOVER (in English): "Toxic shock syndrome is typically associated with menstruating women, and is caused by toxins from the Staphylococcus aureus bacteria.""Symptoms include gastrointestinal distress, a sudden high-fever, low blood pressure, a sunburn-like rash, and redness of the eyes, mouth, and throat.""Toxic shock progress rapidly, and can lead to kidney failure. Though fatal, it is treatable with antibiotics and fluids if diagnosed early. ""Another variety of the syndrome is caused by group A streptococcus bacteria, with those having cuts or burns, or having had recent surgery especially at risk."SOURCES: Mayo Clinic, Washington Post, Timehttps://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/toxic-shock-syndrome/symptoms-causes/syc-20355384https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2017/12/19/this-model-lost-a-leg-because-of-an-infection-from-tampons-heres-what-she-wants-you-to-know/?utm_term=.c309a485e1c8http://time.com/5074295/what-is-toxic-shock-syndrome/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 08:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/22/3510400/3510400_7B5032C6993942ADB67EF180DFF54AF5_171222_3510400_What_is_toxic_shock_syndrome__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/911/EC9/911EC9EE56AD4230A0544E33C8A6FE3B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, toxic shock syndrome, tss, staph, staphylococcus, strep, streptococcus menstruation, tampons, toxic shock, kidney failure, flu like symptoms, staph bacteria, strep bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3512845</guid>
      <title>New report warns of privacy-violating facial recognition program at US airports</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA report has found that an airport biometric program is improperly gathering data on Americans, and violating their privacy.According to a report from the Georgetown Law Center for Privacy and Technology, the Department of Homeland Security has installed facial scanners in nine international airports across the U.S., as part of their biometric exit program.The program is part of efforts to nab travelers who are overstaying their visas, or using fraudulent documents. Passengers' faces are scanned at the boarding gate, and matched to a DHS database for verification.Face scans are mandatory for foreign nationals, but U.S. citizens on international flights can opt out and have their documents manually checked.It's unclear though, if American passengers are being informed of this option.According to Homeland Security's own data, 1 in 25 travelers are erroneously rejected by the system despite using valid credentials.The technology also reportedly had high error rates, and often inaccurately identified women and African Americans.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Facial recognition machines deployed at nine airports in the U.S. 2. How Biometric exit program works3. Face scans mandatory for foreign nationals, US citizens can opt out4. 1 in 25 travelers erroneously rejected despite having valid credentialsVOICEOVER (in English): "The Department of Homeland Security has installed facial scanners in nine international airports across the U.S., as part of their biometric exit program.""Passengers' faces are scanned at the boarding gate, and matched to a DHS database for verification.""Face scans are mandatory for foreign nationals, but U.S. citizens on international flights can opt out and have their documents manually checked.""According to Homeland Security's own data, 1 in 25 travelers are erroneously rejected by the system despite using valid credentials."SOURCES: Georgetown Law, U.S. Customs and Border Protectionhttps://www.documentcloud.org/documents/4334243-Georgetown-Law-report-on-airport-facial.htmlhttps://www.cbp.gov/newsroom/local-media-release/cbp-deploys-biometric-exit-technology-miami-international-airport***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 07:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/26/3512845/3512845_36978B372A8647689750A90C652A60BA_171226_3512845_New_report_warns_of_privacy_violating_facial_rec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4E6/08A/4E608A1A3AED4139B370FF5049D536A2_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, facial recognition, facial scanner, face scans, biometric exit program, homeland security, dhs, cbp, airport security, airport scanner, privacy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3512757</guid>
      <title>Male rub-on contraceptive proceeds to human trials</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEGovernment researchers in the U.S. are getting ready to test a topical contraceptive gel designed to lower sperm production.The clinical trial will begin in April and run for around four years, and will be the largest study conducted to test a hormonal form of male birth control, MIT Technology Review reported. Researchers at the National Institute of Child Health and Human Development are working on a hormonal gel that reduces sperm count when applied to the skin. The gel contains two synthetic hormones  nestorone and testosterone. The nestorone blocks the testes from making enough testosterone to produce normal levels of sperm. The synthetic testosterone is needed to prevent hormonal imbalance caused by the nestorone.More than 400 couples in the U.S., the U.K., Italy, Sweden, Chile and Kenya will participate in the clinical trial. Couples will use the treatment for over four months while their sperm levels are checked.  Men in the study will take home a bottle of the gel and rub around half a teaspoon of it on their upper arms or shoulders every day. The gel takes about a minute to dry. According to researchers, the gel can lower sperm count for about 72 hours.      RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The topical gel is made from synthetic nestorone and testosterone2. Nestorone blocks the testes from making enough testosterone to produce normal sperm levels3. Synthetic testosterone is used to prevent hormonal imbalance4. Man applying the topical gel to shoulder areaVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers are working on a contraceptive hormonal gel that reduces sperm count when applied to the skin. The gel contains two synthetic hormones  nestorone and testosterone." "The nestorone blocks the testes from making enough testosterone to produce normal levels of sperm." "The synthetic testosterone is needed to prevent hormonal imbalance caused by the nestorone.""Men in the study will take home a bottle of the gel and rub around half a teaspoon of it on their upper arms or shoulders every day. The gel takes about a minute to dry." SOURCES: MIT Technology Review, Science Alerthttps://www.technologyreview.com/s/609773/a-contraceptive-gel-for-men-is-about-to-go-on-trial/http://www.sciencealert.com/nestorone-topical-gel-contraceptive-men-clinical-trial-2018***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 05:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/26/3512757/3512757_2BE3C79025B441188C9BBB9255B7DCC0_171226_3512757_Male_rub_on_contraceptive_proceeds_to_human_tria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/319/C20/319C2040242A42EDA6B4A618C785ED8B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, rub on male contraceptive, male birth control, male topical gel contraceptive, male contraceptive clinical trial]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3513791</guid>
      <title>August solar eclipse created bow waves in Earth's atmosphere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe total solar eclipse in August 2017 left bow waves in the Earth's upper atmosphere, like a boat sailing through water. On August 21, researchers from MIT's Haystack Observatory and the University of Troms in Norway were able to find "the first unambiguous evidence" of atmospheric bow-waves.  The team published their findings in the journal Geophysical Research Letters. The bow-wave theory says that a total solar eclipse will create high-pressure pockets under the moon's shadow that then slice through low-pressure air as the path of totality moves across the planet. These air pockets then generate small bow waves in the atmosphere.During the August eclipse, the scientists collected data from around 2,000 satellite sensors placed across North America. They detected tiny bow waves in Earth's ionosphere, the section of the atmosphere that begins 37 miles above the surface. The researchers said their study, "reveals complex interconnections between the Sun, Moon and Earth's neutral atmosphere and ionosphere."   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Solar eclipse2. The total solar eclipse creating high-pressure pockets under the moon's shadow3. 2,000 satellite sensors were placed across North America4. Total solar eclipseVOICEOVER (in English): "The total solar eclipse in August 2017 left bow waves in the Earth's upper atmosphere, like a boat sailing through water." "The bow-wave theory says that a total solar eclipse will create high-pressure pockets under the moon's shadow that slice through low-pressure air as the shadow moves across Earth. These air pockets then generate small bow waves in the atmosphere.""Researchers from MIT and University of Troms in Norway collected data from around 2,000 satellite sensors placed across North America and for the first time detected tiny bow waves in Earth's ionosphere."  "The researchers said their study, 'reveals complex interconnections between the Sun, Moon and Earth's neutral atmosphere and ionosphere.'"   SOURCES: National Geographic, Newsweekhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/12/solar-eclipses-earth-bow-waves-atmosphere-space-science/http://www.newsweek.com/august-solar-eclipse-created-bow-waves-earths-atmosphere-phenomenon-never-seen-758831***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/27/3513791/3513791_F7D2C4E7423347B794892C80B5578AFD_171227_3513791_August_solar_eclipse_created_bow_waves_in_Earth__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/713/185/7131850EC1CB4293A825404BB8D1FC08_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bow wave theory, bow wave phenomenon, total solar eclipse, solar eclipse bow wave theory, total solar eclipse bow wave phenomenon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3514279</guid>
      <title>Implant lets chronic pain sufferers lessen aches</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONESmall spine implants can help numb pain in patients dealing with chronic aches and agony.The technology, by Abbott Laboratories, works by the patient receiving an implant in their body that stimulates an area of the spine.The implant interacts with an area called the dorsal root ganglion via remote control operated by the patient. Pain processed here is from certain areas of the body can be counteracted with electricity from the device. A patient with chronic pain told Bloomberg the implant doesn't eliminate pain completely but can help make something they can live with.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of device2. Depiction of dorsal ganlion root3. Depiction of person using controller to dull painVOICEOVER (in English): "Abbott Laboratories has developed an implant that helps mitigate pain by stimulating an area of the spine after the device is inserted into a patient's body." "The device interacts with the dorsal root ganglion, and is controlled by the patient via remote control.""Pain that is processed in this area is counteracted with electrical pulses produced by the device.""A patient with chronic pain told Bloomberg the implant doesn't eliminate pain completely, but can help make it more manageable."SOURCES: Abbott Laboratohttps://www.sjm.comries, Bloomberg, Press Heraldhttps://www.sjm.comhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-12-26/spinal-cord-implants-to-numb-pain-emerge-as-alternative-to-pillshttp://www.pressherald.com/2017/12/26/spinal-cord-implants-to-numb-pain-emerge-as-alternative-to-opioids/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 07:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/28/3514279/3514279_0AE0EF94F468419292EE55B56B5F8A78_171228_3514279_Implant_lets_chronic_pain_sufferers_lessen_aches_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/32A/08D/32A08D0F3FC74850A236927FAFB54EE1_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, pain elimination, spine implant, chronic pain elimination, pain implant, abbott laboratories, dorsal root ganglion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3515267</guid>
      <title>New Year's Eve security in NYC to be tightest ever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew York City is planning to have the most security ever for the annual New Year's Eve celebration in Times Square.   Police said this year they would send more rooftop observation teams and counter-snipers into more buildings, the New York Times reported. Authorities will be patrolling hotels in the days prior to New Year's Eve. The NYPD is also attaching reflective markers on the outsides of buildings, so in the event of an attack, officers can more quickly locate shooters. The police will also deploy explosive-detecting dogs. Sand trucks and blocker vehicles will be positioned to stop cars or truck attacks. New York usually deploys around 5,000 police officers for New Year's celebrations, but this year, the numbers would be higher, police said. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NYPD counter sniper team on a rooftop building2. Reflective markers will be attached on the outsides of buildings3. Vapor-wake dog smelling for explosives4. Sand trucks and blocker vehicles will be deployed to stop car or truck attacksVOICEOVER (in English):"New York is planning to have the most security ever for the annual New Year's Eve celebration in Times Square. Police said they will be sending more rooftop observation teams and counter-snipers into more buildings.""The NYPD is also attaching reflective markers on the outsides of buildings, so in the event of an attack, officers can more quickly locate shooters." "The police will also deploy vapor-wake dogs, Labrador retrievers that can smell explosives in the air that trails behind people as they walk." "Sand trucks and blocker vehicles will be positioned to stop cars or truck attacks." SOURCES: New York Times, ABC 7https://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/28/nyregion/times-square-new-years-eve-security.htmlhttp://abc7ny.com/city-lays-out-heavy-security-plans-for-new-years-eve-/2834200/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 11:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/29/3515267/3515267_71CBF63644DF4C6FBD3CCE08659C70A1_171229_3515267_New_Year_s_Eve_security_in_NYC_to_be_tightest_ev_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CDF/B80/CDFB801CD5B84ADA903EB0322FA90B7F_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, New York New Year's Eve security, New Year's Eve security, New Year's security, New York Times Square, Times Square New Year's security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3515214</guid>
      <title>How passengers can board the wrong flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFederal investigators may charge two brothers who allegedly boarded a Los Angeles to Tokyo flight with a duplicate boarding pass, which caused pilots to divert the plane mid-flight.An L.A. to Tokyo flight was forced to turn back four hours into its journey when airline staff discovered an "unauthorized person".The mishap happened after a pair of Tokyo-bound brothers, booked on different flights, were somehow allowed onto the same ANA flight on December 26. According to ABC News, the FBI suspects they used a duplicate boarding pass to do so. No one has been arrested but federal investigators are considering charges, ABC News reports.Law enforcement told CNN that the brothers had similar names. Aviation expert Buck Rodger told CNN that there are three checks for passengers to make sure they're on the right plane. These are boarding gate checks, in-flight destination announcements and assigned seating. Rodger said that a combination of faults from these can create a flight mix-up.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of what can cause a flight mix-up.2. Depicts passenger at boarding gate with defective scanner3. Depicts passenger sleeping through inflight announcement4. Depicts half-empty plane and passenger realizing they're on the wrong flightVOICEOVER (in English): "Aviation expert Buck Rodger told CNN there are three primary flight checks for passengers to make sure they're on the right flight."These are the gate check, in-flight destination announcements and their assigned seats.""Rodgers said that a combination of faults from these can create a flight mix-up.""For example a passenger may encounter a stressed gate agent, or defective boarding gate scanner.""And then may also not hear the flight announcements.""CNN reports that a flight mix up can be resolved when the right passenger finds the mistaken passenger in their seat.""But if the plane is half-empty and no one's in the confused passenger's seat, this coupled with other factors can lead to a flight mix-up."SOURCES: CNN, BBC, ABC Newshttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/27/us/wrong-flight-passengers-trnd/index.htmlhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/27/us/chrissy-teigen-flight-mixup-trnd/index.htmlhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-42507247http://abcnews.go.com/International/ana-flights-mid-air-turn-result-criminal-charges/story?id=52024185***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 11:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/29/3515214/3515214_21D0F12AA8E144998301718EFB1AC190_171229_3515214_How_passengers_can_board_the_wrong_flight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B50/08B/B5008B08776D49C284287A336084C5B3_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  ana, lax, boarding the wrong plane, getting on the wrong flight, got on the wrong flight, got on the wrong plane, Japan, USA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3515121</guid>
      <title>Force 47: Fighting against what the Vietnamese government deems wrong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONE[DESCRIPTION GOES HERE]RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 2. 3. 4. VOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Tuoi Tre, Reuters, BBC, Human Rights Watch, Freedom Househttps://tuoitrenews.vn/news/politics/20171226/vietnam-has-10000strong-cyber-troop-general/43326.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-vietnam-internet/vietnams-facebook-dissidents-test-the-limits-of-communist-state-idUSKCN1B92UQhttp://www.bbc.com/news/technology-42494113https://www.hrw.org/world-report/2017/country-chapters/vietnamhttps://freedomhouse.org/report/freedom-net/2017/vietnam***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 09:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/29/3515121/3515121_B00BC168E17E4A5C85A6B4C6B400DE8E_171229_3515121_Force_47__Fighting_against_what_the_Vietnamese_g_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A4/DD3/1A4DD31A9D764DD58D1CD04C3F057102_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, vietnam, vietnam force 47, vietnam internet taskforce, vietnam internet policy, thought police]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3515038</guid>
      <title>Energous long-distance charging system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA San Jose startup's long-distance charging system has just gotten approval from the Federal Communications Commission. Energous announced on Tuesday that it received consumer safety certification for its midfield transmitter, which puts it one step closer to commercial availability.The Wattup midfield transmitter converts electricity into radio frequencies, and can be attached or embedded into a desktop computer monitor.Wattup can charge devices fitted with a receiver from a distance of up to three feet.It can power multiple gadgets simultaneously, including computer accessories and personal devices, and automatically stops charging when the battery is full.Energous also has a far field transmitter, which can reportedly power up devices from as far as 15 feet away, but has yet to receive FCC approval.The company is set to showcase this new technology at CES 2018, which will run from January 9 to 12 in Las Vegas.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Wattup midfield transmitter converts electricity into radio frequencies2. Wattup charges devices fitted with a receiver at a distance of up to three feet3. Multiple devices can be charged at the same time, charging stops when battery is fullVOICEOVER (in English): "The Wattup midfield transmitter from Energous converts electricity into radio frequencies, and can be attached or embedded into a desktop computer monitor.""Wattup can charge devices fitted with a receiver from a distance of up to three feet.""It can power multiple gadgets simultaneously, including computer accessories and personal devices, and automatically stops charging when the battery is full."SOURCES: Fortune, Energous, Engadgethttp://fortune.com/2017/12/27/energous-fcc-approval-wireless-charging/https://ir.energous.com/press-releaseshttps://www.engadget.com/2017/12/26/fcc-approves-first-wireless-power-at-a-distance-charging-syste/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 08:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/29/3515038/3515038_FD6D060EB2F0461FB77A226BD3A0D23E_171229_3515038_Energous_long_distance_charging_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7CE/F09/7CEF09FCF15F497EBC9E2E2828FDD0A9_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, long distance charging, wireless charging, midfield transmitter, energous, wattup, wattup transmitter, wattup midfield transmitter, battery life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3514871</guid>
      <title>How serious is the anthrax threat from North Korea?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew reports from South Korea have raised fears that Kim Jong Un's government may be using anthrax to develop biological weapons.CNN reports that one of at least four soldiers who defected from North Korea was found with anthrax antibodies in his system, suggesting he was either vaccinated, or exposed to the virus at some point.The North has also reportedly begun testing loading anthrax into intercontinental ballistic missiles, to determine whether the bacteria can withstand the high temperatures of atmospheric reentry.Anthrax is caused by exposure to Bacillus anthracis spores. It causes flu-like symptoms, and can kill 80% of those exposed within 24 hours, unless antibiotics are administered.South Korea's Centers for Disease Control and Prevention bought 1,000 doses of anthrax vaccine for agents or civilians. The Blue House  South Korea's executive office  has an additional 350, ordered by the previous government.Fears of a biochemical attack come just weeks before the South is set to host the 2018 Winter Olympics.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Soldier defected from North Korea found with anthrax antibodies2. North Korea tests loading anthrax on missiles3. Anthrax description and symptoms4. South Korea bought anthrax vaccines in case of exposureVOICEOVER (in English): "One of at least four soldiers who defected from North Korea had anthrax antibodies in his system, suggesting he was either vaccinated, or exposed to the virus at some point.""The North has also reportedly begun testing loading anthrax into intercontinental ballistic missiles, to determine whether the bacteria can withstand the high temperatures of atmospheric reentry.""Anthrax is caused by exposure to Bacillus anthracis spores. It causes flu-like symptoms, and can kill 80% of those exposed within 24 hours, unless antibiotics are administered.""South Korea's Centers for Disease Control and Prevention bought 1,000 doses of anthrax vaccine for agents or civilians. The Blue House  South Korea's executive office  has an additional 350, ordered by the previous government."SOURCES: CNN, Asahi Shimbun, USA Todayhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/27/asia/north-korea-anthrax-intl/index.htmlhttp://www.asahi.com/ajw/articles/AJ201712200036.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2017/12/27/anthrax-defector-raises-new-fears-north-korea-developing-biological-weapons/983810001/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 05:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/12/29/3514871/3514871_36B243333AA94083B7C89A023704BD59_171229_3514871_How_serious_is_the_anthrax_threat_from_North_Kor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4FB/60C/4FB60C5CB3E84B26B5A50B26B368BF44_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, north korea, anthrax, biological weapons, bio weapons, biological warfare, north korea missile, north korea weapons, anthrax vaccine, anthrax threat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
