<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3944040</guid>
      <title>The oceanic current that regulates Europe's climate might seize up within a century: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe North Atlantic Current is a vast flow of warm seawater from the Gulf of Mexico that makes northwestern Europe's mild climate possible.According to a study in Science Reports, Netherlands-based scientists warn that global warming might temporarily halt this important current in the next century.According to the British Meteorological Office, the North Atlantic Current is driven by differentials in salinity and temperature levels in the sea.As the hot current flows north, the water loses salinity and heat. This cold, dense water then sinks deep into the ocean and flows back to tropical waters.According to the researchers' news release, climate change-related ice melt in Greenland and excessive rains over the seas are adding freshwater to the North Atlantic.The scientists say the new study's mathematical model has bolstered previous theories that freshwater inclusions would slow the current or even interrupt it.A study co-author says that their simulations predict a 15 percent chance that the current would seize up temporarily in the next 100 years.The scientists say that such a disruption might lead to cold spells in the northern Atlantic region.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The North Atlantic Current circulates energy and moderates climate in Europe2. Salinity, temperature and density differentials drives the currents3. Increased rainfall and melting glaciers in Greenland disrupts the current4. Scientists predict 15 percent chance of current temporarily seizing movementVOICEOVER (in English): "The North Atlantic Current is a vast flow of warm seawater from the Gulf of Mexico that makes northwestern Europe's mild climate possible.""According to a study in Science Reports, Netherlands-based scientists warn that global warming might temporarily halt this important current in the next century.""According to the British Meteorological Office, the North Atlantic Current is driven by differentials in salinity and temperature levels in the sea.""As the hot current flows north, the water loses salinity and heat. This cold, dense water then sinks deep into the ocean and flows back to tropical waters.""According to the researchers' news release, climate change-related ice melt in Greenland and excessive rains over the seas are adding freshwater to the North Atlantic.""The scientists say the new study's mathematical model has bolstered previous theories that freshwater inclusions would slow the current or even interrupt it.""A study co-author says that their simulations predict a 15 percent chance that the current would seize up temporarily in the next 100 years.""The scientists say that such a disruption might lead to cold spells in the northern Atlantic region."SOURCES: Science Reports, EurekAlert, The Meteorological Office (UK)https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-019-56435-6https://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-12/uog-nac122719.phphttps://www.metoffice.gov.uk/weather/learn-about/weather/oceans/amoc***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/02/3944040/3944040_428314B73FEA478DA84DC11663A26519_200102_3944040_The_oceanic_current_that_regulates_Europe_s_clim_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, North Atlantic Current, Atlantic Ocean Circulation, climate change, global warming, Greenland, ice melt, melting glaciers, Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943917</guid>
      <title>U.S. to investigate nuclear waste site on Marshall Islands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Congress is demanding an investigation into the Runit Dome in the Marshall Islands, which contains radioactive waste and is being threatened by rising sea levels.The dome was built in the late 1970s during the Cold War era. It was originally built to contain radioactive waste from nuclear tests conducted by the U.S on the islands, according to CBS News.The U.S. conducted 64 nuclear weapons tests at Bikini and Enewetak atolls between 1946 to 1958.As part of the National Defense Authorization Act, the Department of Energy must investigate the deteriorating concrete site and submit a report about the risks the dome poses to the people, wildlife, and surrounding environment by June 2020, the Los Angeles Times reports. The report must also assess how rising sea levels could affect the nuclear dome.In May 2019, UN Secretary General Antonio Guterres had raised concerns about the risk of the dome's radioactive material leaking into the sea, reports BBC News. According to the U.S. Department of Interior, the Marshall Islands was a UN trust territory that was administered by the U.S. from 1947 to 1978. It became a sovereign nation in 1979.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Runit dome2. Why the dome was built3. Nuclear weapons tests the U.S. conducted on the islands4. The amount of radioactive ash and soil the dome holds5. The Department of Energy is tasked at investigating the dome to assess the risk the site poses to the surrounding area and environment6. The report must also assess how rising sea levels could affect the domeVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Congress is demanding an investigation into the Runit Dome in the Marshall Islands, which contains radioactive waste and is being threatened by rising sea levels.""The dome was built in the late 1970s during the Cold War era.""According to CBS News, it was originally built to contain radioactive waste from nuclear tests conducted by the U.S on the islands.""The U.S. conducted 64 nuclear weapons tests at Bikini and Enewetak atolls between 1946 to 1958.""Al Jazeera reports the tests included the 'Bravo' hydrogen bomb, which was said to be 1,000 times more powerful than the atomic bomb the U.S. dropped on Hiroshima.""According to the Los Angeles Times, the site holds more than 3.1 million cubic feet of radioactive ash and soil from the nuclear explosions, which was closed with a concrete dome that is 18 inches thick.""This was originally meant to be a temporary solution since the bottom of the crater was never lined.""The Los Angeles Times reports that as part of the National Defense Authorization Act, the Department of Energy must investigate the deteriorating concrete site and submit a report about the risks the dome poses to the people, wildlife, and surrounding environment by June 2020.""The report must also assess how rising sea levels could affect the nuclear dome."SOURCES: BBC News, Los Angeles Times,  Al Jazeera, CBS News, The Guardian, U.S. Department of Interior https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50951981https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-12-30/new-us-law-probe-marshall-islands-nuclear-waste-site-threatened-by-rising-seashttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/05/chief-guterres-concerned-nuclear-coffin-leaking-pacific-190516073758642.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/enewetak-atoll-dome-un-antonio-guterres-concerns-marshall-islands-structure-leaking-radioactive-material-pacific/https://www.theguardian.com/world/2015/jul/03/runit-dome-pacific-radioactive-wastehttps://www.doi.gov/oia/islands/marshallislands***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 08:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/02/3943917/3943917_B8260C40E7A84FBDB1DE2AB4EC9E1225_200102_3943917_U_S__to_investigate_nuclear_waste_site_on_Marsha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Nuclear coffin, pacific, marshall islands, nuclear coffin in pacific, nuclear coffin leaking in pacific, nuclear coffin marshall islands, nuclear coffin leaking, nuclear coffin cold war, concrete dome, atomic bomb tests, radioactive material, runit dome, cold war era nuclear tests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943883</guid>
      <title>North Korean hackers stole sensitive information from Microsoft users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMicrosoft has filed a lawsuit against two anonymous North Korean hackers for stealing user information in a hacking operation called Thallium.The hackers were using 50 domains as part of their cyber operation, according to ZDNet. In the court documents for the lawsuit, which was filed on December 18, Microsoft explained that hackers would send spear phishing emails to users that pretended to be from a Microsoft Account Team.The emails would include a link to a host phishing page that would encourage users to enter their account credentials. Once hackers gained access gained access to a users' account, they would be able to review user emails, contact lists and other information.In addition, Microsoft said the hackers were able to use misleading domains to trick users into clicking links that would result in malware such as KimJongRAT and BabyShark, which are remote access trojans, being installed on a user's computer.This type of malware is able to exfiltrate information and wait to receive additional commands from the hackers who installed it, ZDNet reports. Most targeted users were based in the U.S., Japan and South Korea.According to ZDNet, Microsoft has since been granted a court order by U.S. authorities to take over the 50 domains used by the North Korean hackers. The tech company has since taken those websites down.Microsoft had previously notified 10,000 users in July that their accounts had been targeted by hackers from North Korea, Russia and Iran over the past 12 months, CBS News reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korean hacking operation against Microsoft users2. How hackers gained access to user accounts3. How hackers tricked users into downloaded malware4. Where most targeted users were basedVOICEOVER (in English): "Microsoft has filed a lawsuit against two anonymous North Korean hackers for stealing user information in a hacking operation called Thallium.""According to ZDNet, the hackers were using 50 domains as part of their cyber operation.""In the court documents for the lawsuit, which was filed on December 18, Microsoft explained that hackers would send spear phishing emails to users that pretended to be from a Microsoft Account Team.""The emails would include a link to a host phishing page that would encourage users to enter their account credentials.""Once hackers gained access gained access to a users' account, they would be able to review user emails, contact lists and other information.""In addition, Microsoft said the hackers were able to use misleading domains to trick users into clicking links that would result in malware such as KimJongRAT and BabyShark, which are remote access trojans, being installed on a user's computer.""ZDNet reports this type of malware is able to exfiltrate information and wait to receive additional commands from the hackers who installed it.""Most targeted users were based in the U.S., Japan and South Korea."SOURCES: CNN, ZDNet, CBS News, Microsoft v John Doeshttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/30/tech/microsoft-hackers-lawsuit-north-korea/index.htmlhttps://www.zdnet.com/article/microsoft-takes-down-50-domains-operated-by-north-korean-hackers/https://www.cbsnews.com/news/microsoft-says-hackers-linked-to-north-korea-tried-to-steal-customer-data/https://www.scribd.com/document/441295185/Microsoft-v-John-Does***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 07:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/02/3943883/3943883_1F5F114C01814A9882709157F7831057_200102_3943883_North_Korean_hackers_stole_sensitive_information_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea, cyber attacks, north korea cyber attacks, north korean cyber attacks, north korea microsoft, pyongyang cyber space, north korea cyber attack microsoft users]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943856</guid>
      <title>The CDC says Vitamin E additives may be responsible for vaping-related lung injuries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. health officials have linked vitamin E acetate additives to a "vast majority" of vaping illness cases.The CDC made those remarks in a news conference on December 20, citing the latest papers in a series of studies the agency carried out. The agency says it has been tracking the vaping cases since July and confirmed that incidents of illnesses have declined.According to a study in the New England Journal of Medicine, the CDC took bronchus and lung fluid samples from a large number of vaping illness patients across 16 states.Analysis found vitamin E, a substance identified in e-cigarette product samples, in 48 out of 51 patients, but not in healthy people. According to the Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, the CDC studied 38 vaping illness patients who died or were rehospitalized after hospital discharge.The median time for patients to go back to the hospital was three days, and the median time from hospital discharge to death was four days.The CDC advises doctors to follow up on patients soon after hospital discharge.According to the same report, vaping illness patients over 50 years of age are more likely to die than other patients.The CDC says that vaping illness patients with heart diseases and diabetes are significantly more likely to be readmitted after their initial hospitalization.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. CDC links vitamin E to vaping-related lung injuries 2.  Bronchus and lung fluid samples of patients tested positive for substance3. Health care providers advised to follow up after discharge4. Age, pre-existing chronic conditions increase fatality and rehospitalization risksVOICEOVER (in English): "U.S. health officials have linked vitamin E acetate additives to a 'vast majority' of vaping illness cases.""The CDC made those remarks in a news conference on December 20, citing the latest papers in a series of studies the agency carried out.""The agency says it has been tracking the vaping cases since July and confirmed that incidents of illnesses have declined.""According to a study in the New England Journal of Medicine, the CDC took bronchus and lung fluid samples from a large number of vaping illness patients across 16 states.""Analysis found vitamin E, a substance identified in e-cigarette product samples, in 48 out of 51 patients, but not in healthy people.""According to the Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, the CDC studied 38 vaping illness patients who died or were rehospitalized after hospital discharge.""The median time for patients to go back to the hospital was three days, and the median time from hospital discharge to death was four days.""The CDC advises doctors to follow up on patients soon after hospital discharge.""According to the same report, vaping illness patients over 50 years of age are more likely to die than other patients.""The CDC says that vaping illness patients with heart diseases and diabetes are significantly more likely to be readmitted after their initial hospitalization."SOURCES: New England Journal of Medicine, Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, Centers for Disease Control https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1916433https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/68/wr/mm685152e2.htm?s_cid=mm685152e2_whttps://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2019/t1220_telebriefing_update_lung_injury.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2019/p1220-cases-EVALI.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 06:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/02/3943856/3943856_1BB047FB3EB14E88824AF7C280E7EDB3_200102_3943856_The_CDC_says_Vitamin_E_additives_may_be_responsi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, vape, vaping, lung injury, lung injuries, evali, vaping illness, vitamin e, e-cigarette, e-cigarettes, e-cigs, cdc, centers for disease control and prevention, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944584</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's military chief killed in helicopter crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan's Chief of General Staff, General Shen Yi-ming, was en route to visit troops at a military base in Yilan when the Blackhawk helicopter he was traveling in crashed on Thursday, killing him and seven other officers.Citing a military spokesman, the Liberty Times reports that the reason for the incident is unknown as visibility was good that day. According to the United Daily News, the pilots reported favorable conditions for landing in their last communication at 8:07 p.m.Shortly afterward, the military lost contact with the helicopter as the radar signature disappeared over a naval base in Yilan.Citing first responders, the Liberty Times reports that the helicopter crashed to the west of its last reported location in the mountains between New Taipei City and Yilan.Eight high-ranking officers and aircrew were killed, including Sheng. Five other passengers were rescued.The United Daily News reports that a Military News Agency journalist, who was pinned by the wreckage, was able to call for help with her cellphone. She was rescued with injuries.Another wounded officer helped guide rescuers to the crash site through heavy mist by blowing a rescue whistle.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The helicopter was carrying Taiwan's military chief Shen Yi-ming2. Flight route of the helicopter and last reported location3. The crash and its casualties4. Survivors helped rescuers find their location by phone and rescue whistleVOICEOVER (in English): "Taiwan's Chief of General Staff, General Shen Yi-ming, was en route to visit troops at a military base in Yilan when the Blackhawk helicopter he was traveling in crashed on Thursday, killing him and seven other officers.""Citing a military spokesman, the Liberty Times reports that the reason for the incident is unknown as visibility was good that day.""According to the United Daily News, the pilots reported favorable conditions for landing in their last communication at 8:07 p.m.""Shortly afterward, the military lost contact with the helicopter as the radar signature disappeared over a naval base in Yilan.""Citing first responders, the Liberty Times reports that the helicopter crashed to the west of its last reported location in the mountains between New Taipei City and Yilan.""Eight high-ranking officers and aircrew were killed, including Sheng. Five other passengers were rescued.""The United Daily News reports that a Military News Agency journalist, who was pinned by the wreckage, was able to call for help with her cellphone. She was rescued with injuries.""Another wounded officer helped guide rescuers to the crash site through heavy mist by blowing a rescue whistle."SOURCES: Liberty Times, United Daily News, Apple Daily, FTV News,https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/politics/breakingnews/3027346https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/politics/breakingnews/3028419https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/politics/paper/1343398https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/politics/breakingnews/3027530https://udn.com/news/story/10930/4263593https://topic.udn.com/event/blackhawk_crashhttps://tw.appledaily.com/new/realtime/20200102/1685251/https://www.ftvnews.com.tw/news/detail/2020102P25M1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/03/3944584/3944584_7812CE8FB27B49608769072D757E6346_200103_3944584_Taiwan_s_military_chief_killed_in_helicopter_cra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Blackhawk crash, helicopter crash, crash, UH-60, Blackhawk, helicopter, top general, chief of general staff, Taiwan, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944522</guid>
      <title>India plans for third lunar mission, Chandrayaan-3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Indian Space Research Organization on Tuesday announced plans for a third lunar mission called Chandrayaan-3 and said it is most likely to be launched later this year, according to the Times of India.Speaking at a press conference, the space agency's chairperson K Sivan explained that the spacecraft's configuration will be similar to its predecessor, Chandrayaan-2.According to AFP, he said the agency will build a new propulsion module, lander and surface rover for the mission.Sivan told the Times of India the mission will cut costs by reusing the same orbiter from India's second lunar mission as it is already orbiting the moon.The aim is to land the spacecraft on the moon's south pole, the same area that the Chandrayaan-2 tried to land in but failed to do so in September of 2019.If the mission is successful, this would make India the fourth nation to achieve a soft landing on the lunar surface.India's second moon mission failed as the Chandrayaan-2 spacecraft had a hard landing on the moon's south pole and lost communication with Indian spacecraft operators.The mission was aimed at searching for water and minerals on the moon as well as measuring moonquakes.Sivan said the Indian space agency plans to launch at least 25 space missions this year as part of India's plans to become a low-cost space power.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. India's third moon mission2. The new spacecraft will be similar to its predecessor3. How the new mission would cut costs4. Where the spacecraft aims to landVOICEOVER (in English): "The Indian Space Research Organization on Tuesday announced plans for a third lunar mission called Chandrayaan-3 and said it is most likely to be launched later this year, according to the Times of India.""Speaking at a press conference, the space agency's chairperson K Sivan explained that the spacecraft's configuration will be similar to its predecessor, Chandrayaan-2.""According to AFP, he said the agency will build a new propulsion module, lander and surface rover for the mission.""Sivan told the Times of India the mission will cut costs by reusing the same orbiter from India's second lunar mission as it is already orbiting the moon.""The aim is to land the spacecraft on the moon's south pole, the same area that the Chandrayaan-2 tried to land in but failed to do so in September of 2019.""If the mission is successful, this would make India the fourth nation to achieve a soft landing on the lunar surface."SOURCES: BBC News, AFP, Times of India, India Today https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/amp/world-asia-india-50965778https://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/jan/02/chandrayaan-3-india-unveils-fresh-35m-attempt-to-put-a-rover-on-the-moonhttps://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/chandrayaan-3-will-be-economical-likely-to-be-launched-in-2020-mos-jitendra-singh/articleshow/73048925.cmshttps://www.indiatoday.in/science/story/isro-k-sivan-chandrayaan-3-mission-1633025-2020-01-01***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 10:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/03/3944522/3944522_6BFC2E1316714A9B80C968DC893D3A46_200103_3944522_India_plans_for_third_lunar_mission__Chandrayaan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Space, space exploration, india, moon, Chandrayaan-3 , Chandrayaan-3  spacecraft, Chandrayaan-3 mission, Chandrayaan-3 lunar mission, india's third lunar mission, india lunar mission,  india moon mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944401</guid>
      <title>Protesters attack U.S embassy in Baghdad</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. embassy in Iraq was hit with attacks during violent protests, an action which has been condemned by President Donald Trump. He has since called on Iraq to use its forces to protect the embassy.According to CBS News, an estimated 6000 protesters, including Iraqi Shiite militiamen gathered outside the American embassy in Baghdad on Tuesday during a hostile protest. Several dozen managed to break into the compound and were heard shouting, 'down, down, USA!', whilst they smashed a main door and set fire to a reception area.Protesters also threw stones over the walls, pulled down security cameras, stormed empty guard posts and were seen hanging yellow flags belonging to the Kataeb Hezbollah militia on the walls of the embassy. U.S. soldiers watched from the roof and used a loudspeaker to urge the crowd to stay away.Videos posted to social media captured smoke funneling out from one guard checkpoint on the perimeter of the compound. Iraqi special forces responded by firing tear gas to try and disperse the protesters. According to the New York Times, the demonstration was in retaliation to U.S. airstrikes that killed 25 Iran-backed Kataeb Hezbollah, an Iraqi Shia paramilitary group just two days earlier. The Pentagon, however, says their airstrikes were in retaliation to an attack consisting of more than 30 rockets on an Iraqi military base near Kirkuk, northern Iraq. The attack killed an American defense contractor and injured four U.S. service members.A U.S. defense official told CBS News that the military is sending reinforcements to the embassy from units already within the country, adding, "there are no plans to evacuate Embassy Baghdad."President Trump accused Iran of "orchestrating" the break-in, adding that "they will be held fully responsible."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Protesters break into U.S. embassy2. U.S. soldiers use megaphones to manage crowd3. Iraqi Special Forces fire tear gas at the crowd4. Attack on U.S. servicemen in Iraqi military base VOICEOVER (in English): "According to CBS News, an estimated 6000 protesters, including Iraqi Shiite militiamen gathered outside the American embassy in Baghdad on Tuesday during a hostile protest. Several dozen managed to break into the compound and were heard shouting, 'down, down, USA!', whilst they smashed a main door and set fire to a reception area.""Protesters also threw stones over the walls, pulled down security cameras, stormed empty guard posts and were seen hanging yellow flags belonging to the Kataeb Hezbollah militia on the walls of the embassy. U.S. soldiers watched from the roof and used a loudspeaker to urge the crowd to stay away.""Videos posted to social media captured smoke funneling out from one guard checkpoint on the perimeter of the compound. Iraqi special forces responded by firing tear gas to try and disperse the protesters." "According to the New York Times, the demonstration was in retaliation to U.S. airstrikes that killed 25 Iran-backed Kataeb Hezbollah, an Iraqi Shia paramilitary group just two days earlier.""The Pentagon, however, says their airstrikes were in retaliation to an attack consisting of more than 30 rockets on an Iraqi military base near Kirkuk, northern Iraq. The attack killed an American defense contractor and injured four U.S. service members."SOURCES: New York Times, CBS News, New York Times, https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/01/world/middleeast/us-embassy-baghdad-iraq.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/us-iraq-airstrikes-protests-american-embassy-baghdad-anger-over-strikes-iran-militia-today-2019-12-31/https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/01/world/middleeast/iraq-embassy-iran.html?auth=login-google***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 07:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/03/3944401/3944401_953B02B449D94D36B01CDB09D58530C7_200103_3944401_Protesters_attack_U_S_embassy_in_Baghdad_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, TomoNews, protests, Iraq, Baghdad, Iran, Baghdad embassy protests, protesters break into U.S. embassy, tear gas protesters]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944254</guid>
      <title>A designer has invented 3D printed artificial fruits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Israel-based designer has invented 3D printed synthetic fruits that are edible and contain essential minerals and vitamins.According to Dezeen, Meydan Levy created five types of artificial "neo fruits."The neo fruits' structure is made of cellulose, an organic compound that forms the structure of living plants.The artificial fruits' cellulose microtubes also contain the liquid mixture that gives the fruit nutrients and flavor.  Citing Levy, the online outlet says the artificial fruits do not take up their final shape until liquid is injected. Levy says that without the liquids, the artificial fruits could be stored for long periods and transported easily until the injections are added before consumption.According to Levy, industrial agriculture will not be able to meet the nutritional needs that coincide with a global population increase.  Dezeen reports that nutritionists helped Levy to create different ingredients for each type of neo fruit in order to meet the wide range of nutrition the human body requires.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Five types of 3D printed synthetic neo fruits2. Artificial fruits utilize cellulose microtubes for structure3. Nutrition and flavoring liquid is injected last to facilitate storage and transportation4. Artificial fruits designed to meet the nutritional needs of the world's rising populationVOICEOVER (in English): "An Israel-based designer has invented 3D printed synthetic fruits that are edible and contain essential minerals and vitamins.""According to Dezeen, Meydan Levy created five types of artificial 'neo fruits.'""The neo fruits' structure is made of cellulose, an organic compound that forms the structure of living plants.""The artificial fruits' cellulose microtubes also contain the liquid mixture that gives the fruit nutrients and flavor." "Citing Levy, the online outlet says the artificial fruits do not take up their final shape until liquid is injected.""Levy says that without the liquids, the artificial fruits could be stored for long periods and transported easily until the injections are added before consumption.""According to Levy, industrial agriculture will not be able to meet the nutritional needs that coincide with a global population increase." "Dezeen reports that nutritionists helped Levy to create different ingredients for each type of neo fruit in order to meet the wide range of nutrition the human body requires."SOURCES: Dezeen, Meydanishhttps://www.dezeen.com/2019/12/07/meydan-levy-neo-fruit-4d-print-design/https://meydanish.wixsite.com/portpoliome/concept***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 03:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/03/3944254/3944254_912A03B978094EB39ABE9AFBF31E7E69_200103_3944254_A_designer_has_invented_3D_printed_artificial_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Neo Fruit, fake fruit, synthetic fruit, artificial fruit, imitation fruit, 3d printed, 3d printing, 3d printed food, 3d printed fruit, Meydan Levy, dezeen, science, sustainability]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944247</guid>
      <title>U.S. deploying 750 paratroopers after protestors breach U.S. embassy in Iraq: Pentagon chief</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Army's 82nd Airborne Division is deploying paratroopers to Kuwait, after Iran-affiliated rioters swarmed the U.S. embassy in Baghdad.U.S. Secretary of Defense Mark Esper said in a written statement on Tuesday that Air Force C-17s were already flying in 750 paratroopers of the division's Immediate Response Force.The Military Times reports that the 750 paratroopers will be joined by an additional 4,000 U.S. soldiers from the division's IRF in the following week.The 82 Airborne Division said in a statement that the 1st Brigade Combat Team is currently assigned to the IRF role. According to Fox News, the alert sequence for the Division Ready Brigade is to have one rifle battalion ready in 18 hours, another rifle battalion in 36 hours and a third in 54 hours.The alert brigade should be ready to deploy for operations within a 96-hour alert window. Fox reports that the aircraft carrier USS Harry S. Truman has been in the Gulf of Oman with its carrier strike group, armed with F-18 fighters and Tomahawk cruise missiles.Citing the Pentagon, Fox reports that there are 60,000 US troops in the Middle East, including the 14,000 reinforcements added since May in response to Iran's rising threat.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 82 Airborne Division's Immediate Response Force deploying 750 soldiers to Kuwait2. Additional 4,000 troops will join the paratroopers in the following week3. The division's alert cycle enables the ready brigade to deploy in 96 hours4. U.S. Navy carrier strike group and 60,000 ground troops are already in the regionVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Army's 82nd Airborne Division is deploying paratroopers to Kuwait, after Iran-affiliated rioters swarmed the U.S. embassy in Baghdad.""U.S. Secretary of Defense Mark Esper said in a written statement on Tuesday that Air Force C-17s were already flying in 750 paratroopers of the division's Immediate Response Force.""The Military Times reports that the 750 paratroopers will be joined by an additional 4,000 U.S. soldiers from the division's IRF in the following week.""The 82 Airborne Division said in a statement that the 1st Brigade Combat Team is currently assigned to the IRF role." "According to Fox News, the alert sequence for the Division Ready Brigade is to have one rifle battalion ready in 18 hours, another rifle battalion in 36 hours and a third in 54 hours.""The alert brigade should be ready to deploy for operations within a 96-hour alert window.""Fox reports that the aircraft carrier USS Harry S. Truman has been in the Gulf of Oman with its carrier strike group, armed with F-18 fighters and Tomahawk cruise missiles.""Citing the Pentagon, Fox reports that there are 60,000 US troops in the Middle East, including the 14,000 reinforcements added since May in response to Iran's rising threat."SOURCES: U.S. Department of Defense, 82nd Airborne Division (Facebook), Fox News, Military Timeshttps://www.defense.gov/Newsroom/Releases/Release/Article/2048934/sd-statement-on-deployment-of-82nd-airborne-division/https://www.facebook.com/287901225386/posts/10162999888165387/?d=nhttps://www.foxnews.com/politics/troops-middle-east-baghdad-embassy-kuwaithttps://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2020/01/01/750-soldiers-with-82nd-airborne-headed-for-centcom-additional-4000-troops-expected-to-deploy-as-iran-tensions-mount/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 03:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/03/3944247/3944247_68D114CFCE384F1D9F91D9101569FFCF_200103_3944247_U_S__deploying_750_paratroopers_after_protestors_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 82nd Airborne Division, 82nd Airborne, 82nd division, Airborne Infantry Brigade, U.S., US, Kuwait, Iran, Iraq, ambassy, Baghdad, ambassy, riot, riots, demonstration, defenes, security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945635</guid>
      <title>U.S. company to open first ever human composting facility in 2021</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUS-based company Recompose will start the first ever funeral service that turns human bodies into compost soil next year.Citing architects involved in the project, Dezeen reports that the flagship facility in Seattle will be capable of housing 75 bodies in its compost vessels.According to Recompose, prosthetics and pacemakers will be removed from the cadaver to prepare the body for the natural organic reduction process.Citing company founder Katrina Spade, the Washington Post reports that the vessels accelerate natural decomposition.According to Recompose, the company's technology is designed for urban areas that do not have space for burials.The body is interred in a vessel 4 feet wide and 8 feet tall with alfalfa, wood chips and straw and then heated to a temperature of 150 degrees Fahrenheit.After 30 days, the microbes will have decomposed the body and eliminated most pathogens and residual pharmaceuticals.The process creates about a cubic yard of soil from each person and the decedent's friends and family may take part of the soil for their garden.Recompose claims their services save one tonne of carbon emissions per person when compared to conventional burial or cremation, which increases sustainability. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Recompose's planned flagship facility for human composting2. Procedures to prepare human bodies for the process3. Proprietary compositing vessel accelerates natural decomposition4. Claimed environmental benefits of human compostingVOICEOVER (in English): "US-based company Recompose will start the first ever funeral service that turns human bodies into compost soil next year.""Citing architects involved in the project, Dezeen reports that the flagship facility in Seattle will be capable of housing 75 bodies in its compost vessels.""According to Recompose, prosthetics and pacemakers will be removed from the cadaver to prepare the body for the natural organic reduction process.""Citing company founder Katrina Spade, the Washington Post reports that the vessels accelerate natural decomposition.""The body is interred in a vessel 4 feet wide and 8 feet tall with alfalfa, wood chips and straw and then heated to a temperature of 150 degrees Fahrenheit.""After 30 days, the microbes will have decomposed the body and eliminated most pathogens and residual pharmaceuticals.""The process creates about a cubic yard of soil from each person and the decedent's friends and family may take part of the soil for their garden.""Recompose claims their services save one tonne of carbon emissions per person when compared to conventional burial or cremation, which increases sustainability." SOURCES: Recompose, Dezeen, Seattle Times, Washington Posthttps://www.recompose.life/faqhttps://www.dezeen.com/2019/11/20/recompose-seattle-human-composting-olson-kundig/https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/life-after-death-recompose-a-soil-based-alternative-to-burial-and-cremation-moves-closer-to-reality/https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2019/04/26/washington-passes-bill-become-first-state-compost-human-bodies/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 09:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/06/3945635/3945635_F8DC83BA40B7413A97101F84A7FB616B_200106_3945635_U_S__company_to_open_first_ever_human_composting_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Human compost, human composting, green burial, recompose, recomposelife, sustainability, Seattle, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945627</guid>
      <title>Study estimates the amount of microplastics consumed by humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the World Wide Fund for Nature and the University of Newcastle, Australia suggests that humans consume roughly 2,000 pieces of microplastics, or five grams of plastic, a week. This is equivalent to eating a credit card a week.Microplastic particles are less than five millimeters in length and are approximately the size of a sesame seed.The study found that the number increases to 21 grams of plastic pieces a month, which is equivalent to the weight of a hanger or the amount of microplastics needed to fill half a rice bowl.Every six months we consume 125 grams of plastic, which is enough plastic to fill an entire cereal bowl. According to the study, this turns into roughly 250 grams of microplastics in a year, or a dinner plate full of plastic.The study found that we consume approximately 20 kilograms of microplastics in our lifetime, or roughly the weight of two mobile recycling bins, according to Reuters.The study notes that the largest source of plastic ingestion around the world is through water consumption, either ground water, surface water, tap water or bottled water.The study also estimates that a small number of microplastics may enter the body through inhalation.Researchers mentioned that the long term effect of microplastics on our health is unclear and that additional studies are still needed to understand the effect of plastic on human health.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How many pieces of microplastics humans consume in a week2. The amount of microplastics consumed by humans in a month is equivalent to the weight of a hanger or half a rice bowl3. How much plastic we consume in six months and a year4. How much plastic is consumed by humans in a lifetimeVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the World Wide Fund for Nature and the University of Newcastle, Australia suggests that humans consume roughly 2,000 pieces of microplastics, or five grams of plastic, a week. This is equivalent to eating a credit card a week.""Microplastic particles are less than five millimeters in length and are approximately the size of a sesame seed.""The study found that the number increases to 21 grams of plastic pieces a month, which is equivalent to the weight of a hanger or the amount of microplastics needed to fill half a rice bowl.""Every six months we consume 125 grams of plastic, which is enough plastic to fill an entire cereal bowl.""According to the study, this turns into roughly 250 grams of microplastics in a year, or a dinner plate full of plastic.""The study found that we consume approximately 20 kilograms of microplastics in our lifetime, or roughly the weight of two mobile recycling bins, according to Reuters."SOURCES: University of Newcastle, Australia, World Wide Fund for Naturehttps://www.newcastle.edu.au/newsroom/featured/plastic-ingestion-by-people-could-be-equating-to-a-credit-card-a-week/how-much-microplastics-are-we-ingesting-estimation-of-the-mass-of-microplastics-ingestedhttps://www.newcastle.edu.au/newsroom/featured/plastic-ingestion-by-people-could-be-equating-to-a-credit-card-a-week/how-much-microplastics-are-we-ingesting-estimation-of-the-mass-of-microplastics-ingestedhttp://awsassets.panda.org/downloads/plastic_ingestion_press_singles.pdfhttps://wwf.panda.org/wwf_news/press_releases/?348337/Revealed-plastic-ingestion-by-people-could-be-equating-to-a-credit-card-a-week***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 09:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/06/3945627/3945627_EB900A70CDC04028806E4EDE0234F91F_200106_3945627_Study_estimates_the_amount_of_microplastics_cons_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, microplastic pollution,  plastic pollution, microplastic particles, microplastics in human body, humans ingesting plastic, humans ingesting microplastics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945482</guid>
      <title>Australia's bushfires are creating their own weather systems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCBS News reports that bushfires in Australia are burning so fiercely that they are creating pyrocumulonimbus clouds which are then creating thunderstorms.  The Bureau of Meteorology in Victoria tweeted that the bushfires in East Grippland had triggered one such storm in a warning issued on Thursday last week. CBS News meteorologists say that bushfires heat the air so intensely that they could send ash upwards at a speed of 100 miles an hour or more.The updrafts can then cause ash and smoke to rise miles up into the atmosphere where cooler temperature causes water to condense into clouds.According to CBS News, freak storms like this could increase as our planet continues to heat up. According to CBS News, the more violent the bushfire, the faster the updraft and the more likely the clouds will form thunderstorms.Unlike normal storms, bushfire-caused storms do not result in much rain since the falling raindrops are evaporated by the heat from the fires raging below.CBS News warns that lightning strikes from these storms are far more likely to cause further bushfires due to the lack of rain. According to the University of New South Wales, the dangerous weather system is to blame for the fire tornado that devastated Canberra in 2003.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bushfires in Australia and a recent incident of pyrocumulonimbus2. Fire sends ash and smoke high in the atmosphere3. Ashes help the formation of thunderclouds4. Pyrocumulonimbus lightning cause fires they do not produce normal rainfall VOICEOVER (in English): "CBS News reports that bushfires in Australia are burning so fiercely that they are creating pyrocumulonimbus clouds which are then creating thunderstorms."  "The Bureau of Meteorology in Victoria tweeted that the bushfires in East Grippland had triggered one such storm in a warning issued on Thursday last week.""CBS News meteorologists say that bushfires heat the air so intensely that they could send ash upwards at a speed of 100 miles an hour or more.""The updrafts can then cause ash and smoke to rise miles up into the atmosphere where cooler temperature causes water to condense into clouds.""According to CBS News,  freak storms like this could increase as our planet continues to heat up." "According to CBS News, the more violent the bushfire, the faster the updraft and the more likely the clouds will form thunderstorms.""Unlike normal storms, bushfire-caused storms do not result in much rain since the falling raindrops are evaporated by the heat from the fires raging below.""CBS News warns that lightning strikes from these storms are far more likely to cause further bushfires due to the lack of rain."SOURCES: CBS News, NASA, Bureau of Meteorology, Victoria (Twitter), University of New South Wales https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fires-in-australia-pyrocumulonimbus-thunderstorm-clouds-victoria-sydney/https://www.nasa.gov/topics/earth/features/pyrocb.htmlhttps://newsroom.unsw.edu.au/news/science/turn-and-burn-strange-world-fire-tornadoes***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 04:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/06/3945482/3945482_6A0372CC69B046AE8559595757DB95E2_200106_3945482_Australia_s_bushfires_are_creating_their_own_wea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Bushfire, new weather system, weather system, storm, thunderstorm, pyrocumulonimbus, lightening, Australia, climate change, global warming, science, climnate TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946126</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's endangered leopard cats saved by road culverts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan's Miaoli County passed an ordinance to protect leopard cats by rewarding eco-friendly farming and mandating impact studies for some construction projects on December 28.Liberty Times reports that Miaoli is an important breeding ground for leopard cats, an endangered species in Taiwan. The busy traffic on Taiwan's freeways poses a significant danger to the leopard cats and at least 21 cats were killed by cars in 2019.Taiwan's government has been trying to address the problem by building culverts to help leopard cats safely cross roads.Citing the Forestry Bureau, United Daily News reports that its camera detected 39 leopard cats at one culvert.Last year, the government and the National Chung Hsing University unveiled a safe crossing system.The system features a speedometer linked traffic sign, fences, light sound emitters to slow down cats, animal biometrics, and a safe passage culvert.The Forestry Bureau says that cats have learned to use those systems and that a combination of LED lights, fences and speeding enforcement may help save the cats.Liberty Times reports that Miaoli's laws would require construction of a certain size--such as roads over 1 km long--to pass an environmental impact study before they are built.According to the Liberty Times, there are less than 1,000 living leopard cats in Taiwan. The government has issued repeated calls for motorists to slow down in areas that the cats inhabit.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Taiwan's Miaoli County pass regulations to protect local leopard cats2. Traffic hazards on freeways poses significant danger to the cats3. Culverts designed to give leopard cats safe passage4. Major constructions will have to pass environmental impact studiesVOICEOVER (in English): "Taiwan's Miaoli County passed an ordinance to protect leopard cats by rewarding eco-friendly farming and mandating impact studies for some construction projects on December 28.""Liberty Times reports that Miaoli is an important breeding ground for leopard cats, an endangered species in Taiwan.""The busy traffic on Taiwan's freeways poses a significant danger to the leopard cats and at least 21 cats were killed by cars in 2019.""Last year, the government and the National Chung Hsing University unveiled a safe crossing system.""The system features a speedometer linked traffic sign, fences, light sound emitters to slow down cats, animal biometrics, and a safe passage culvert.""Liberty Times reports that Miaoli's laws would require construction of a certain size--such as roads over 1 km long--to pass an environmental impact study before they are built."SOURCES: Forestry Bureau (Facebook), Liberty Times, United Daily News, National Chung Hsin Universityhttps://www.facebook.com/twforest/photos/a.635174639987935/1184494825055911/?type=3&theaterhttps://www.facebook.com/watch/?v=380888136171572https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/life/paper/1342019https://udn.com/news/story/7324/4020066https://www2.nchu.edu.tw/news-detail/id/45986***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 09:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/07/3946126/3946126_1841C3C58034460BB3544DC22EA82CFF_200107_3946126_Taiwan_s_endangered_leopard_cats_saved_by_road_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Taiwan, Taiwan leopard cat, Taiwan leopard cats road culverts, Taiwan leopard cat endangered, leopard cats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946058</guid>
      <title>How the U.S. killed top Iranian general in a drone strike</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGeneral Qassim Soleimani, head of Iran's expeditionary Quds Force, was killed early Friday by a U.S. drone that fired missiles into his convoy near Baghdad International Airport. The U.S. military has confirmed that it carried out the attack. The Times of Israel reports that a MQ-9 Reaper drone fired four missiles into two cars and destroyed the vehicles on the airport's access road.Citing local media sources, the paper reports that the blast tore Soleimani apart and the general was later identified by the ring he wore on his hand.The strike killed Soleimani, his son-in-law and five Iranian Revolutionary Guards members.According to the New York Times, several Tehran-backed Iraqi militia leaders in the convoy were also killed.The Times of Israel reported 10 fatalities for the airstrike.The Washington Examiner reports that the MQ-9 drone was favored for its quiet propellers and loitering capabilities.Citing debris analysis by independent observers, Forbes reports that the missiles utilized could be the JAGM, a missile type that adds advanced sensors to the Hellfire missile.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. General Qassim Soleimani in a motor convoy near Baghdad International Airport2. MQ-9 Reaper drone fires four missiles at the convoy, killing Soleimani 3. Ten Iranian and Iraqi fatalities reported4. MQ-9 speculated to have fired new missiles known as JAGM in the attackVOICEOVER (in English): "General Qassim Soleimani, head of Iran's expeditionary Quds Force, was killed early Friday by a U.S. drone that fired missiles into his convoy near Baghdad International Airport." "The U.S. military has confirmed that it carried out the attack.""The Times of Israel reports that a MQ-9 Reaper drone fired four missiles into two cars and destroyed the vehicles on the airport's access road.""Citing local media sources, the paper reports that the blast tore Soleimani apart and the general was later identified by the ring he wore on his hand.""The strike killed Soleimani, his son-in-law and five Iranian Revolutionary Guards members.""According to the New York Times, several Tehran-backed Iraqi militia leaders in the convoy were also killed.""The Times of Israel reported 10 fatalities for the airstrike.""The Washington Examiner reports that the MQ-9 drone was favored for its quiet propellers and loitering capabilities.""Citing debris analysis by independent observers, Forbes reports that the missiles utilized could be the JAGM, a missile type that adds advanced sensors to the Hellfire missile."SOURCES: U.S. Department of Defense, New York Times, Times of Israel, Gulf News, Washington Examiner, Forbes https://www.defense.gov/Newsroom/Releases/Release/Article/2049534/statement-by-the-department-of-defense/https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/02/world/middleeast/qassem-soleimani-iraq-iran-attack.htmlhttps://www.timesofisrael.com/four-hellfire-missiles-and-a-severed-hand-the-killing-of-qassem-soleimani/https://gulfnews.com/world/mena/killing-soleimani-how-was-the-operation-carried-out-1.1578063347074https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/laser-guided-hellfire-missile-traveling-230-mph-killed-qassem-soleimanihttps://www.forbes.com/sites/sebastienroblin/2020/01/04/did-the-pentagon-use-new-joint-air-to-ground-missiles-in-killing-of-general-soleimani/#7cbbc35e4bb6***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 08:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/07/3946058/3946058_4EB82D79D0CE4F95972369ADEDD03A86_200107_3946058_How_the_U_S__killed_top_Iranian_general_in_a_dro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Qassim Soleimani, drone, drone strike, airstrike, killed, MQ-9, MQ-9 Reaper, Reaper, Baghdad, JAGM, Hellfire missile, Baghdad International Airport, Iraq, Iran, US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946043</guid>
      <title>How SIM swapping works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSIM swapping occurs when scammers gain access to your sim card number, usually by telling the cell phone service provider that the device has been lost or damaged, according to the Federal Trade Commission.Once the same number is activated on a new device, the hacker receives all your text messages, calls and data.According to the agency, scammers may log into your email accounts, social media accounts and change your passwords to potentially lock you out of your own accounts.They could also use your login credentials to access money in your bank account. This is because once hackers have gained access to your phone number, they can receive verification codes through SMS and bypass two-factor authentication.The agency urges users to limit the amount of personal information shared online, and in emails and text messages, in order to prevent becoming a victim of SIM swapping.Users are also advised to set a password or a PIN on their cellular account in order to better protect their phone numbers.Those who have fallen victim to SIM swapping are urged to contact their cell service provider to gain back access to their account. Once access has been restored, users should change their account passwords.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. What SIM swapping is2. How scammers could log you out of your account3. How to protect yourself from SIM swapping4. What you should do after an SIM swapping attackVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Federal Trade Commission, SIM swapping occurs when scammers gain access to your sim card number, usually by telling the cell phone service provider that the device has been lost or damaged.""Once the same number is activated on a new device, the hacker receives all your text messages, calls and data.""According to the agency, scammers may log into your email accounts, social media accounts and change your passwords to potentially lock you out of your own accounts.""They could also use your login credentials to access money in your bank account.""This is because once hackers have gained access to your phone number, they can receive verification codes through SMS and bypass two-factor authentication.""The agency urges users to limit the amount of personal information shared online, and in emails and text messages, in order to prevent becoming a victim of SIM swapping." "Users are also advised to set a password or a PIN on their cellular account in order to better protect their phone numbers." SOURCES: ABC 7 News, Wired, FTC, New Scientist https://abc7chicago.com/in-sim-card-swap-scam-thieves-steal-your-identity-by-hacking-your-phone/5749616/https://www.wired.com/story/sim-swap-attack-defend-phone/https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/blog/2019/10/sim-swap-scams-how-protect-yourselfhttps://www.newscientist.com/article/2228252-phone-number-theft-through-sim-jacking-is-on-the-rise-in-the-uk/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 07:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/07/3946043/3946043_BB1FD08CD6304B70A8BCD58E7ABC385E_200107_3946043_How_SIM_swapping_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sim card, sim jacking, sim swapping, sim swap attack, sim card swap scam, sim swapping news, sim swap hack, sim hack, sim hacking technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945911</guid>
      <title>How Carlos Ghosn escaped Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to Turkish private jet firm, MNG, two of their aircraft were used to facilitate ex-Nissan boss, Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan. MNG state that two separate private jets to two different clients were leased using faked documents forged by an employee of the company who acted within "his own capacity."According to Business Insider, Ghosn was seen fleeing his home in Tokyo on the 29th of December. MNG state that the first private jet used in his escape flew from Osaka's Kansai Airport at 11 p.m. and landed in Istanbul the following day. At 6 a.m. just forty-five minutes after landing, Ghosn then took a second MNG flight bound for his home in Beirut, Lebanon.65-year-old Ghosn, who holds Brazilian, French and Lebanese nationalities, reportedly entered Beirut legally using his French passport and his Lebanese identification despite Japanese lawyers stating they had possession of all three of his passports. Japanese outlet, NHK, however, reported that Mr. Ghosn had a duplicate French passport.On Wednesday the 1st of January 2020, Turkish private jet firm, MNG filed a criminal complaint concerning the illegal use of its aircraft in relation to Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan.Mr. Ghosn is now a fugitive in Lebanon, which has no extradition treaty with Japan. Interpol has since filed a "red notice" for his arrest with authorities there.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How Carlos Ghosn's flights were booked2. The flight journey Ghosn took3. Carlos Ghosn's passports4. Flight company file a criminal complaintVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Turkish private jet firm, MNG, two of their aircraft were used to facilitate ex-Nissan boss, Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan. MNG state that two separate private jets to two different clients were leased using faked documents forged by an employee of the company who acted within 'his own capacity.'""According to Business Insider, Ghosn was seen fleeing his home in Tokyo on the 29th of December. MNG state that the first private jet used in his escape flew from Osaka's Kansai Airport at 11 p.m. and landed in Istanbul the following day. At 6 a.m. just forty-five minutes after landing, Ghosn then took a second MNG flight bound for his home in Beirut, Lebanon.""65-year-old Ghosn, who holds Brazilian, French and Lebanese nationalities, reportedly entered Beirut legally using his French passport and his Lebanese identification despite Japanese lawyers stating they had possession of all three of his passports. Japanese outlet, NHK, however, reported that Mr. Ghosn had a duplicate French passport.""On Wednesday the 1st of January 2020, Turkish private jet firm, MNG filed a criminal complaint concerning the illegal use of its aircraft in relation to Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan.""Mr. Ghosn is now a fugitive in Lebanon, which has no extradition treaty with Japan. Interpol has since filed a 'red notice' for his arrest with authorities there."SOURCES: MNG Jet, Business Insider, NHKhttps://www.mngjet.com/https://www.businessinsider.com/timeline-how-carlos-ghosn-escaped-japan-lebanon-secret-2020-1#december-30-515-am-the-plane-believed-to-have-carried-ghosn-landed-in-istanbul-having-flown-over-russia-10https://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/tags/62/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 03:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/07/3945911/3945911_48B466E4BC0C4F3CB5CA7AB27911D971_200107_3945911_How_Carlos_Ghosn_escaped_Japan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Carlos Ghosn, Ghosn escape from Japan, how did Ghosn escape, Ghosn escape explained, Nissan boss, Ghosn escapes Japan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946658</guid>
      <title>The moon lost its magnetic fields one billion years ago: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBillions of years ago, the ancient moon had a powerful dynamo at its core that produced a strong global magnetic field.Scientists at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology say that they have pinned down when that dynamo stopped, leading to the field's dissipation.In a study published in Science Advances, researchers say that the Apollo mission collected lunar rocks that preserve a record of the moon's ancient magnetic field.However, most of these rocks dated to between 3 and 4 billion years, or too long ago for studying the end of the moon's internal dynamo. To research the moon's later magnetic history, the scientists tested two samples that were 1 billion years old and found them to record a weak lunar magnetic field. As the rocks were left by a meteor impact, scientists reheated the rocks and obtained the same readings to make sure the impact's heat did not interfere with the rocks' magnetic records.According to the MIT news release, the moon used to be much closer to earth, and the gravitational effect caused the liquid lunar core to wobble, which created the magnetic field.The weak magnetism recorded by the two rocks suggests the gravitational effects had begun to seize up one billion years ago.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New study pins down the time when the moon stopped generating its own magnetic field2. MIT scientists analyze lunar rocks to reconstruct the moon's magnetic history3. Two rocks dated to one billion years ago show signs of weak magnetic field4. The moon's internal dynamo system as it used to functionVOICEOVER (in English): "Billions of years ago, the ancient moon had a powerful dynamo at its core that produced a strong global magnetic field.""Scientists at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology say that they have pinned down when that dynamo stopped, leading to the field's dissipation.""In a study published in Science Advances, researchers say that the Apollo mission collected lunar rocks that preserve a record of the moon's ancient magnetic field.""However, most of these rocks dated to between 3 and 4 billion years, or too long ago for studying the end of the moon's internal dynamo.""To research the moon's later magnetic history, the scientists tested two samples that were 1 billion years old and found them to record a weak lunar magnetic field.""As the rocks were left by a meteor impact, scientists reheated the rocks and obtained the same readings to make sure the impact's heat did not interfere with the rocks' magnetic records.""According to the MIT news release, the moon used to be much closer to earth, and the gravitational effect caused the liquid lunar core to wobble, which created the magnetic field.""The weak magnetism recorded by the two rocks suggests the gravitational effects had begun to seize up one billion years ago."SOURCES: Science Advances, Phys.orghttps://advances.sciencemag.org/content/6/1/eaax0883https://phys.org/news/2020-01-scientists-pin-lunar-dynamo-demise.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/08/3946658/3946658_5568EB763A8341A58AFF201D56EAD3B0_200108_3946658_The_moon_lost_its_magnetic_fields_one_billion_ye_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Moon, magnetic field, dynamo, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, MIT, core, Apollo, lunar rocks, lunar rock, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946539</guid>
      <title>Mysterious virus spreads in central China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA mysterious strain of viral pneumonia has affected 59 people in Wuhan, China since mid-December 2019, China Daily reports. The cause of the infection has yet to be determined.According to the Wuhan Municipal Health Commission, some of the victims were sellers at a local seafood market, sparking fear that the virus may have been transmitted from animals to humans. The market has since been temporarily shut down for disinfection, and patients placed in quarantine.Symptoms of the virus include fever, with a few of the patients having breathing difficulties. Chest X-rays from the victims show invasive lesions on both lungs.Wuhan's health commission said that they have eliminated the possibility of the virus being SARS, MERS or bird flu.Although a preliminary analysis found no clear evidence of the virus being transmitted from one human to another, at least 163 others were placed under medical observation for coming into close contact with the infected.Asian nations such as Singapore and Hong Kong have taken precautionary measures to prevent the spread of the virus by conducting temperature screenings at airports for visitors from China, as reported by BBC News. The World Health Organization said on its website that it "does not recommend any specific measure for travelers." They said that they are closely monitoring the situation and are in close contact with authorities in China.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mysterious strain of pneumonia2. How the virus may have been transmitted3. Symptoms of the virus4. No clear evidence that the virus had been transmitted from one human to another VOICEOVER (in English): "China Daily reports that a mysterious strain of viral pneumonia has affected 59 people in Wuhan, China since mid-December 2019.""The cause of the infection has yet to be determined.""According to the Wuhan Municipal Health Commission, some of the victims were sellers at a local seafood market, sparking fear that the virus may have been transmitted from animals to humans.""The market has since been temporarily shut down for disinfection, and patients placed in quarantine.""Symptoms of the virus include fever, with a few of the patients having breathing difficulties.""Chest X-rays from the victims show invasive lesions on both lungs.""Wuhan's health commission said that they have eliminated the possibility of the virus being SARS, MERS or bird flu.""Although a preliminary analysis found no clear evidence of the virus being transmitted from one human to another, at least 163 others were placed under medical observation for coming into close contact with the infected."SOURCES: CNN, Reuters, BBC News, China Daily, World Health Organization, Wuhan Municipal Health Commissionhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/06/health/china-pneumonia-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health-pneumonia/chinese-officials-investigate-cause-of-pneumonia-outbreak-in-wuhan-idUSKBN1YZ0GPhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51000910http://global.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202001/06/WS5e128c27a310cf3e3558299a.htmlhttps://www.who.int/csr/don/05-january-2020-pneumonia-of-unkown-cause-china/en/http://wjw.wuhan.gov.cn/front/web/showDetail/2020010309017***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 07:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/08/3946539/3946539_2E61129D89B7417BB84B3FA108A77A12_200108_3946539_Mysterious_virus_spreads_in_central_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china pneumonia, mystery pneumonia, pneumonia, mysterious virus in china, china pneumonia outbreak, wuhan pneumonia outbreak, unknown pneumonia strain]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947137</guid>
      <title>SpaceX launches 60 satellites into orbit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpaceX launched its third batch of Starlink satellites into orbit from a U.S. Air Force base in Florida on Monday evening.Space.com reports that a Falcon 9 rocket carried the satellites in its first stage and that the launch marked the second time SpaceX reused a booster four times.Citing SpaceX, AFP reports that after deployment, the satellites would utilize ion thrusters to reach an orbit of 550 km to avoid collisions at higher, more congested space.MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX now operates 180 Starlinks, making the company the owner of the world's largest constellation of commercial satellites.According to the publication, the reusable first stage booster was successfully recovered by a drone ship in the Atlantic Ocean, but not a payload fairing.The lost component is worth an estimated US$3 million.However, the program has come under criticism because the satellites reflect glare that interferes with astronomical observatories.The MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX has applied a light absorbing coating to the new satellites to address those concerns.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A Falcon 9's first stage booster carries the 60 Starlink satellites to space2. Satellites deploy ion thrusters to reach low-Earth orbit3. SpaceX recovers the reusable booster but not a fairing half4. New coating is applied to new Starlink satellites to reduce light pollutionVOICEOVER (in English): "SpaceX launched its third batch of Starlink satellites into orbit from a U.S. Air Force base in Florida on Monday evening.""Space.com reports that a Falcon 9 rocket carried the satellites in its first stage and that the launch marked the second time SpaceX reused a booster four times.""Citing SpaceX, AFP reports that after deployment, the satellites would utilize ion thrusters to reach an orbit of 550 km to avoid collisions at higher, more congested space.""MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX now operates 180 Starlinks, making the company the owner of the world's largest constellation of commercial satellites.""According to the publication, the reusable first stage booster was successfully recovered by a drone ship in the Atlantic Ocean, but not the payload fairing.""The lost component is worth an estimated US$3 million.""However, the program has come under criticism because the satellites reflect glare that interferes with astronomical observatories.""The MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX has applied a light absorbing coating to the new satellites to address those concerns."SOURCES: MIT Technology Review, Space.com, AFP, SpaceXhttps://www.technologyreview.com/f/615016/spacex-now-operates-the-worlds-biggest-commercial-satellite-network/https://www.space.com/spacex-starlink-2-launch-success.htmlhttps://www.afp.com/en/news/826/spacex-launches-third-batch-starlink-satellites-doc-1ni2a93https://www.spacex.com/falcon9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 11:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/09/3947137/3947137_0641B5F79DE04F9285FD023F3020EC91_200109_3947137_SpaceX_launches_60_satellites_into_orbit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Starlink, Falcon 9, SpaceX, Elon Musk, satellite, commercial satellite constellation, drone ship, U.S., space, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947005</guid>
      <title>NASA's TESS finds its first Earth-sized planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, or 'TESS' mission, devised to specifically find Earth-sized planets orbiting nearby stars has identified TOI 700 d as a potential candidate occupying a star's habitable zone where conditions may be just right to allow the presence of liquid water on the surface.NASA explains that TESS observes large regions of the sky known as sectors for 27 days at a time. TESS identifies and tracks changes in stellar brightness caused by an orbiting planet passing in front of its star.During recent observations, TESS tracked a total of three planets.The closest to the star, TOI 700 b is Earth-sized, rocky and has an orbit of ten days. The middle planet, TOI 700 c, is 2.6 times larger than Earth, likely gas-dominated and orbits every 16 days. TOI 700 d, the only one in the habitable zone, measures 20 percent larger than Earth and orbits every 37 days.While the exact conditions on TOI 700 d are unknown, researchers at NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center created models to explore its potential conditions to help narrow future predictions of the planet's atmosphere. One model showed a water-covered world and the other, a completely dry version of today's earth. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite finds star2. The satellites observation3. Detail of the three discovered planets4. Two NASA models of TOI 700 d VOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, or 'TESS' mission, devised to specifically find Earth-sized planets orbiting nearby stars has identified TOI 700 d as a potential candidate occupying a star's habitable zone where conditions may be just right to allow the presence of liquid water on the surface.""NASA explains that TESS observes large regions of the sky known as sectors for 27 days at a time. TESS identifies and tracks changes in stellar brightness caused by an orbiting planet passing in front of its star." "During recent observations, TESS tracked a total of three planets.""The closest to the star, TOI 700 b is Earth-sized, rocky and has an orbit of ten days. The middle planet, TOI 700 c, is 2.6 times larger than Earth, likely gas-dominated and orbits every 16 days. TOI 700 d, the only one in the habitable zone, measures 20 percent larger than Earth and orbits every 37 days.""While the exact conditions on TOI 700 d are unknown, researchers at NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center created models to explore its potential conditions to help narrow future predictions of the planet's atmosphere. One model showed a water-covered world and the other, a completely dry version of today's earth." SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2020/nasa-planet-hunter-finds-its-1st-earth-size-habitable-zone-worldhttps://www.nasa.gov/tess-transiting-exoplanet-survey-satellite***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 07:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/09/3947005/3947005_87E9C73632CB4CC5A07D314757A8B6D1_200109_3947005_NASA_s_TESS_finds_its_first_Earth_sized_planet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, NASA finds planet, Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, TESS, planet hunter, TOI 700 b explainer, TOI 700 b, TESS finds its first earth-sized planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946977</guid>
      <title>New details emerge about Ghosn's escape</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOn December 29, former Nissan, Renault boss Carlos Ghosn, who was under house arrest facing charges of diverting millions in company funds for his personal use, walked out of his house in Tokyo wearing a hat and a surgical mask.Citing Japan's NTV, Bloomberg reports Ghosn boarded a bullet train in Tokyo and arrived at Osaka, then called a cab to a hotel near Kansai International Airport.Ghosn hid in a case too big to fit the airport's X-ray machines. At 11 p.m., Ghosn's Bombardier Global Express took off to Istanbul.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ghosn leaves home in disguise2. He travels by bullet train from Tokyo to Osaka3. Ghosn hides in a case, board jet to Turkey4. Jet course laid to avoid extradition5. Ghosn's ties in Russia6. Ghosn hides in a box at airport in Turkey7. Ghosn has access to a second French passport8. He enters Lebanon legallyVOICEOVER (in English): "On December 29, former Nissan, Renault boss Carlos Ghosn, who was under house arrest facing charges of diverting millions in company funds for his personal use, walked out of his house in Tokyo wearing a hat and a surgical mask in plain view of security cameras.""Bloomberg reports that police surveillance was lax during the holidays and that Ghosn's lawyers had filed a legal complaint that prevented Nissan's hired agents from following him.""Citing Japan's NTV, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn boarded a bullet train in Tokyo and arrived at Osaka at about 4:30 pm. He then called a cab to a hotel near Kansai International Airport.""Citing sources familiar with the matter, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn apparently evaded security by hiding in a case that was too big to be scanned by the airport's X-ray machines. Earlier, Ghosn's alleged accomplices had flown in on a Bombardier Global Express Jet with the case. Ghosn would use both in his escape.""At 11 p.m., the Bombardier Global Express took off and headed for Istanbul with Ghosn on board. Bloomberg reports that Ghosn's alleged rescuers carefully plotted the flight to avoid countries with extradition treaties with Japan such as South Korea and instead flew through Russian airspace.""Russia was viewed as more friendly territory as Ghosn is credited with saving the ailing automaker AvtoVAZ, which he brought in to the Renault-Nissan Alliance's fold.""The jet landed at Istanbul's Ataturk Airport at around 5:00 a.m. After that, Ghosn would again secrete himself as cargo in the box before boarding a smaller Bombardier that would take him to Beirut.""In addition to Brazlian and Lebanese passports, Ghosn has two French passports. One was taken by the Japanese authorities and another kept by his lawyer as a condition of his bail but stored in a flimsy box that could be broken easily with a tool. However Reuters reports the French government denies Ghosn used the nation's passport.""Citing a Lebanese judiciary official, Reuters reports that Lebanon has received a request to extradite Ghosn from Japan, not Interpol. Bloomberg reports that Ghosn entered Lebanon legally, where extradition of citizens is denied as a matter of policy."SOURCES: Bloomberg, Business Insider, Reutershttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2020-01-06/how-carlos-ghosn-became-the-world-s-most-famous-fugitivehttps://uk.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn-idUKKBN1Z50BOhttps://uk.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn-france/ghosn-did-not-use-french-documents-to-travel-to-lebanon-french-minister-idUKKBN1Z51W2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 06:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/09/3946977/3946977_574BE13D562F4A86B998A3890A551F70_200109_3946977_New_details_emerge_about_Ghosn_s_escape_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,Carlos Ghosn, Ghosn escape from Japan, how did Ghosn escape, Ghosn escape explained, Nissan boss, Ghosn escapes Japan, Bombardier, case, box, hid in a box, hid in a case]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946969</guid>
      <title>New details emerge about Ghosn's escape</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOn December 29, former Nissan, Renault boss Carlos Ghosn, who was under house arrest facing charges of diverting millions in company funds for his personal use, walked out of his house in Tokyo wearing a hat and a surgical mask.Citing Japan's NTV, Bloomberg reports Ghosn boarded a bullet train in Tokyo and arrived at Osaka, then called a cab to a hotel near Kansai International Airport.Bloomberg reports that Ghosn hid in a case too big to fit the airport's X-ray machines. At 11 p.m., Ghosn's Bombardier Global Express took off to Istanbul.Bloomberg reports that Ghosn's alleged rescuers plotted the flight to fly through Russian airspace. Ghosn would hide in a box before boarding a smaller jet that took him to Beirut.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ghosn leaves home in disguise2. He travels by bullet train from Tokyo to Osaka3. Ghosn hides in a case, board jet to Turkey4. Jet course laid to avoid extradition5. Ghosn's ties in Russia6. Ghosn hides in a box at airport in Turkey7. Ghosn has access to a second French passport8. He enters Lebanon legallyVOICEOVER (in English): "On December 29, former Nissan, Renault boss Carlos Ghosn, who was under house arrest facing charges of diverting millions in company funds for his personal use, walked out of his house in Tokyo wearing a hat and a surgical mask in plain view of security cameras.""Bloomberg reports that police surveillance was lax during the holidays and that Ghosn's lawyers had filed a legal complaint that prevented Nissan's hired agents from following him.""Citing Japan's NTV, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn boarded a bullet train in Tokyo and arrived at Osaka at about 4:30 pm. He then called a cab to a hotel near Kansai International Airport.""Citing sources familiar with the matter, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn apparently evaded security by hiding in a case that was too big to be scanned by the airport's X-ray machines. Earlier, Ghosn's alleged accomplices had flown in on a Bombardier Global Express Jet with the case. Ghosn would use both in his escape.""At 11 p.m., the Bombardier Global Express took off and headed for Istanbul with Ghosn on board. Bloomberg reports that Ghosn's alleged rescuers carefully plotted the flight to avoid countries with extradition treaties with Japan such as South Korea and instead flew through Russian airspace.""Russia was viewed as more friendly territory as Ghosn is credited with saving the ailing automaker AvtoVAZ, which he brought in to the Renault-Nissan Alliance's fold.""The jet landed at Istanbul's Ataturk Airport at around 5:00 a.m. After that, Ghosn would again secrete himself as cargo in the box before boarding a smaller Bombardier that would take him to Beirut.""In addition to Brazlian and Lebanese passports, Ghosn has two French passports. One was taken by the Japanese authorities and another kept by his lawyer as a condition of his bail but stored in a flimsy box that could be broken easily with a tool. However Reuters reports the French government denies Ghosn used the nation's passport.""Citing a Lebanese judiciary official, Reuters reports that Lebanon has received a request to extradite Ghosn from Japan, not Interpol. Bloomberg reports that Ghosn entered Lebanon legally, where extradition of citizens is denied as a matter of policy."SOURCES: Bloomberg, Business Insider, Reutershttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2020-01-06/how-carlos-ghosn-became-the-world-s-most-famous-fugitivehttps://uk.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn-idUKKBN1Z50BOhttps://uk.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn-france/ghosn-did-not-use-french-documents-to-travel-to-lebanon-french-minister-idUKKBN1Z51W2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 06:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/09/3946969/3946969_F278E10E899B43C19BFC522679CA783F_200109_3946969_New_details_emerge_about_Ghosn_s_escape_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,Carlos Ghosn, Ghosn escape from Japan, how did Ghosn escape, Ghosn escape explained, Nissan boss, Ghosn escapes Japan, Bombardier, case, box, hid in a box, hid in a case]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947760</guid>
      <title>China identifies new coronavirus strain for Wuhan outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have identified a new virus as a possible cause for the mysterious pneumonia outbreak in China's Wuhan.Citing researchers, China's Central Television reports that the pathogen is a coronavirus in the same family with the deadly MERS and SARS viruses.Citing experts involved in the effort, the channel reports tests showed that an isolated sample to have appearances similar to the coronavirus.The lab was also able to reconstruct the virus's genome sequence from 15 patient samples.CNN reports that the symptoms of the mystery pneumonia include having difficulty breathing and fever, adding that the condition does not appear to be deadly.According to CCTV, eight patients have been discharged from hospitals as of Thursday.The pneumonia outbreak occurred in December and some of the patients were employed at a local seafood market.According to Chinese authorities, there has been no clear evidence of a human to human infection and no fatalities have been reported.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A new coronavirus strain related to MERS, SARS caused pneumonia outbreak in China2. Microscopy and nucleic acid tests identified the virus3. Pneumonia symptoms are severe but eight have recovered4. No fatalities reported so far and no evidence for human to human transmissionVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have identified a new virus as a possible cause for the mysterious pneumonia outbreak in China's Wuhan.""Citing researchers, China's Central Television reports that the pathogen is a coronavirus in the same family with the deadly MERS and SARS viruses.""Citing experts involved in the effort, the channel reports tests showed that an isolated sample to have appearances similar to the coronavirus.""The lab was also able to reconstruct the virus's genome sequence from 15 patient samples.""CNN reports that the symptoms of the mystery pneumonia include having difficulty breathing and fever, adding that the condition does not appear to be deadly.""According to CCTV, eight patients have been discharged from hospitals as of Thursday.""The pneumonia outbreak occurred in December and some of the patients were employed at a local seafood market.""According to Chinese authorities, there has been no clear evidence of a human to human infection and no fatalities have been reported."SOURCES:  China Central Television, Reuters, CNNhttp://news.cctv.com/2020/01/09/ARTIJBz4xvs1P6SsczdZvQHf200109.shtml?spm=C94212.P4YnMod9m2uD.ENPMkWvfnaiV.79https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-virus-who/china-pneumonia-outbreak-may-be-linked-to-new-virus-who-idUSKBN1Z7304https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/08/health/china-wuhan-pneumonia-virus-intl-hnk/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 14:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/10/3947760/3947760_B8D7B4717CD740ED9E3A5068C2664F82_200110_3947760_China_identifies_new_coronavirus_strain_for_Wuha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China virus outbreak 2020, China virus outbreak, Chinese virus outbreak 2020, Chinese virus, pneumonia, MERS, SARS, coronavirus, mystery virus, Chinese disease, epidemic, Wuhan, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947742</guid>
      <title>Sustainable green towers constructed in central Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSingaporean architectural firm WOHA has designed a sustainable, mixed-use building called Sky Green, in Taichung, Taiwan.According to the company's project website, the development features two towers with sky gardens and terraces filled with lush greenery.One of the tower's facades is lined with mesh screens with vegetation on it, while the other consists of balconies with plants and other flora.The first three floors of the structure includes retail stores, while the rest of the building consists of residential apartments stacked on top of one another.The tower's interior offers open spaces with green vegetation for residents to relax in.According to Arch Daily, the design of the structure was chosen to adapt to Taiwan's local culture and climate.Construction on the building was completed in November of 2019.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sky Green, a new development in Taichung, Taiwan2. Green vegetation on the towers3. The structure will include retail stores and apartments4. Open green space inside the building's interiorVOICEOVER (in English): "Singaporean architectural firm WOHA has designed a sustainable, mixed-use building called Sky Green, in Taichung, Taiwan.""According to the company's project website, the development features two towers with sky gardens and terraces filled with lush greenery." "One of the tower's facades is lined with mesh screens with vegetation on it, while the other consists of balconies with plants and other flora.""The first three floors of the structure includes retail stores, while the rest of the building consists of residential apartments stacked on top of one another.""The tower's interior offers open spaces with green vegetation for residents to relax in."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Design Boom, Arch Daily, WOHAhttps://inhabitat.com/lush-sky-green-towers-are-the-first-of-their-kind-in-taichung/https://www.designboom.com/architecture/woha-sky-green-taiwan-trees-plants-12-02-2019/https://www.archdaily.com/930021/woha-completes-first-green-mixed-use-development-in-taiwanhttps://www.woha.net/#Sky-Green,-Taichung***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 13:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/10/3947742/3947742_BC049A6487F84ADAA4F1BFA116B6A0F2_200110_3947742_Sustainable_green_towers_constructed_in_central__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Lush Sky Green towers, sustainable buildings, green buildings, taiwanese architecture,  WOHA architecture firm, taichung architecture, green buildings, green development, sky green development]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947736</guid>
      <title>Trudeau says Iranian missile fire may have shot down Ukranian Boeing 737</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe BBC reports that Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau says intelligence shows that Iran had shot down the Ukrainian passenger plane with a missile, possibly in error.According to CNN, U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson states that British intelligence has reached the same conclusion.CNN reports that the plane had crashed shortly after it took off from Tehran airport on Wednesday.The Boeing 737 was carrying 176 passengers and aircrew, all killed in the crash.On Thursday, CNN aired a video it obtained that apparently shows a missile striking an object over Tehran's skies at the time of the commercial jet's crash.CNN states that it cannot independently verify the video.Citing U.S. officials, CBS News reports that a satellite detected infrared blips of two missile launches, then another of an explosion. The network states that officials were confident the plane was shot down by a missile.Newsweek quotes three US and Iraqi officials as saying they believe a Russian-made Tor M1 surface to air missile had struck the plane.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Justin Trudeau, Boris Johnson say Iranian missiles caused the jet crash2. The Ukrainian Boeing 737 went down near Tehran on Wednesday, killing 1763. CNN obtained footage apparently showing a missile hitting a plane over Tehran4. U.S. officials confident that Iranian missiles are to blameVOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports that Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau says intelligence shows that Iran had shot down the Ukrainian passenger plane with a missile, possibly in error.""According to CNN, U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson states that British intelligence has reached the same conclusion.""CNN reports that the plane had crashed shortly after it took off from Tehran airport on Wednesday.""The Boeing 737 was carrying 176 passengers and aircrew, all killed in the crash.""On Thursday, CNN aired a video it obtained that apparently shows a missile striking an object over Tehran's skies at the time of the commercial jet's crash.""CNN states that it cannot independently verify the video.""Citing U.S. officials, CBS News reports that a satellite detected infrared blips of two missile launches, then another of an explosion. The network states that officials were confident the plane was shot down by a missile.""Newsweek quotes three US and Iraqi officials as saying they believe a Russian-made Tor M1 surface to air missile had struck the plane."SOURCES:  CNN, BBC, CBS News, NewsWeek, Twitterhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/09/politics/is-iran-ukraine-plane/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/iran-plane-crash-live-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-51055219https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/plane-crash-us-officials-confident-iran-shot-down-passenger-jet-bound-for-ukraine-today-2020-01-09-live-stream-updates/https://twitter.com/krisvancleave/status/1215309192086675459?s=12https://www.newsweek.com/iranians-shot-down-ukraine-flight-mistake-sources-1481313https://www.flightradar24.com/data/flights/ps752#23732569***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 13:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/10/3947736/3947736_F2DBB4A5568645FA99B49054D91CC77B_200110_3947736_Trudeau_says_Iranian_missile_fire_may_have_shot__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Iranian missiles, Iranian missile, shoot down, shot down, missile fire, missiles, Trudeau, Johnson, Ukranian jet, Ukranian Boeing, jet crash, Ukrainian jet crash, Ukraine, Iran, accident, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947579</guid>
      <title>Israel introduces laser that can intercept missiles and aerial threats</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIsrael's Defense Ministry said in a news release that it made a technological breakthrough in a defensive laser weapon that intercepts aerial threats.Israel-based Defense Update reports that the laser can shoot down range rockets fired at close range and other threats that are too costly for the Iron Dome to engage.Defense Update reports that Israeli air defense batteries, armored vehicles and aerial drones will be outfitted with the lasers to bolster defense systems already in use.The Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon is electrically powered and that it combines multiple beams into one beam capable of overcoming atmospheric conditions. The active defense system is precise and the laser has successfully intercepted various projectiles in tests, including mortar shells and anti-tank missiles.Citing a military researcher, the Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon could fire a beam the diameter of a coin from Tel Aviv to Herzliya, which "provides a dramatic solution to rocket fire."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Israel's new defensive lasers are designed to intercept aerial threats2. Weapon combines several beams into one powerful, accurate beam3. Lasers will be used by anti-missile batteries, armored vehicles and drones 4. Laser has a claimed range of Tel Aviv to HerzliyaVOICEOVER (in English): "Israel's Defense Ministry said in a news release that it made a technological breakthrough in a defensive laser weapon that intercepts aerial threats.""Israel-based Defense Update reports that the laser can shoot down range rockets fired at close range and other threats that are too costly for the Iron Dome to engage.""Defense Update reports that Israeli air defense batteries, armored vehicles and aerial drones will be outfitted with the lasers to bolster defense systems already in use.""The Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon is electrically powered and that it combines multiple beams into one beam capable of overcoming atmospheric conditions." "The active defense system is precise and the laser has successfully intercepted various projectiles in tests, including mortar shells and anti-tank missiles.""Citing a military researcher, the Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon could fire a beam the diameter of a coin from Tel Aviv to Herzliya, which 'provides a dramatic solution to rocket fire.'"SOURCES: Israel Ministry of Defense, The Jerusalem Post, Defense Updatehttps://www.mod.gov.il/Defence-and-Security/articles/Pages/8.1.20.aspxhttps://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Israels-Defense-Ministry-announces-breakthrough-in-laser-technology-613568https://defense-update.com/20200108_hel_israel.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 09:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/10/3947579/3947579_9F32ABF3B4B84D81A6D8524A1087129F_200110_3947579_Israel_introduces_laser_that_can_intercept_missi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Lasers, laser, directed energy weapon, missile, missiles, aerial threats, anti-missile, antitank guided missile, active defense system, active defense systems, Israel, defense, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947346</guid>
      <title>Toyota unveils plans for futuristic city in Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDanish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group has been commissioned by Toyota to build a prototype futuristic city called Woven City at the base of Mt. Fuji in Japan.In a press release, Toyota said the city will be built on a 175-acre site and will be used to test futuristic vehicles, AI robots and smart homes in a "real-world environment."Designs of the city were unveiled at the Consumer Electronic Show in Las Vegas on January 7.Woven City will include buildings made mostly of wood for sustainability, with its rooftops covered with solar panels to produce energy. In addition to solar power, the city will also be powered by hydrogen fuel cells.Homes will be equipped with AI robots and sensors to take care of residents' basic needs and to monitor their health.The futuristic city's main roads will only allow fully-autonomous vehicles, such as the Toyota e-Palettes, to operate. There will be separate roads for pedestrians and those using personal mobility vehicles such as bicycles.A central plaza, neighborhood parks and a large central park will be included for social gatherings among residents.Toyota explained in its press release that it plans to populate the city with company employees, families, retired couples, visiting scientists and others.The city will initially be populated with 2,000 people. The company plans to break ground by early 2021.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woven City2. Buildings in the city3. How the city will be powered4. Autonomous vehicles roaming the city5. Social areas for residentsVOICEOVER (in English): "Danish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group has been commissioned by Toyota to build a prototype futuristic city called Woven City at the base of Mt. Fuji in Japan.""In a press release, Toyota said the city will be built on a 175-acre site and will be used to test futuristic vehicles, AI robots and smart homes in a 'real-world environment.'""Woven City will include buildings made mostly of wood for sustainability, with its rooftops covered with solar panels to produce energy.""In addition to solar power, the city will also be powered by hydrogen fuel cells.""Homes will be equipped with AI robots and sensors to take care of residents' basic needs and to monitor their health.""The futuristic city's main roads will only allow fully-autonomous vehicles, such as the Toyota e-Palettes, to operate.""There will be separate roads for pedestrians and those using personal mobility vehicles such as bicycles.""A central plaza, neighborhood parks and a large central park will be included for social gatherings among residents."SOURCES: Dezeen, Toyota, Woven City, Forbes, The Vergehttps://www.dezeen.com/2020/01/07/big-toyota-woven-city-future-mount-fuji-japan/https://pressroom.toyota.com/toyota-to-build-prototype-city-of-the-future/https://www.woven-city.global/https://www.forbes.com/sites/nargessbanks/2020/01/07/ces-2020-toyota-future-city/#4d1564611c75https://www.theverge.com/2020/1/6/21052324/toyota-woven-city-japan-bjarke-ingels-ces-2020***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 02:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/10/3947346/3947346_D5F051245E56401AB4DEAAC3D7A366D9_200110_3947346_Toyota_unveils_plans_for_futuristic_city_in_Japa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Futuristic cities, toyota futuristic city, japanese futuristic city, Woven City, Toyota Woven city, city of the future, toyota city of the future, futuristic toyota city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948903</guid>
      <title>NASA rolls out space launch system booster for testing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA rolled out the core stage of the Space Launch System "mega-rocket" from a New Orleans factory on Wednesday.BBC reports that the core stage was loaded onto the Pegasus barge to sail down the Mississippi River for testing at the Stennis Space Center.According to NASA, the SLS rocket is the backbone of U.S. plans to land on the moon again by 2024 and to explore Mars. It has a top speed of Mach 23.NASA states that the rocket's core stage is 212 feet tall and 27.6 feet wide, making it the largest booster ever built.The core stage features a forward skirt for housing avionics, a liquid oxygen fuel tank, an intertank that joins the boosters' tanks, a liquid hydrogen fuel tank and quadruple RS-24 engines.The four engines create more than 2 million pounds of combined thrust.The BBC reports that the SLS will deliver the Orion spacecraftwhich is undergoing testingto Luna for the uncrewed Artemis 1 mission planned for next year.According to European Space Agency, the Orion spacecraft will feature foldable solar panels and it will orbit the moon for the Artemis 1 mission.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA rolls out core stage for SLS rocket2. SLS maximum speed, dimension of core stage3. Core stage components4. SLS will deliver Orion spacecraft uncrewed Artemis I missionVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA rolled out the core stage of the Space Launch System 'mega-rocket' from a New Orleans factory on Wednesday.""BBC reports that the core stage was loaded onto the Pegasus barge to sail down the Mississippi River for testing at the Stennis Space Center.""According to NASA, the SLS rocket is the backbone of U.S. plans to land on the moon again by 2024 and to explore Mars. It has a top speed of Mach 23.""NASA states that the rocket's core stage is 212 feet tall and 27.6 feet wide, making it the largest booster ever built.""The core stage features a forward skirt for housing avionics, a liquid oxygen fuel tank, an intertank that joins the boosters' tanks, a liquid hydrogen fuel tank and quadruple RS-24 engines.""The four engines create more than 2 million pounds of combined thrust.""The BBC reports that the SLS will deliver the Orion spacecraftwhich is undergoing testingto Luna for the uncrewed Artemis 1 mission planned for the next year.""According to European Space Agency, the Orion spacecraft will feature foldable solar panels and it will orbit the moon for the Artemis 1 mission."SOURCES: BBC News, Space.com, U.S. NASA, European Space Agency,https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-51048986https://www.space.com/nasa-sls-megarocket-core-stage-barge-rollout-photos.htmlhttps://www.nasaspaceflight.com/2019/12/sls-ksc-ground-systems-critical-year/https://www.nasa.gov/sites/default/files/thumbnails/image/core_stage_infographic_reboot.jpghttps://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Human_and_Robotic_Exploration/Orion/Fuel_tanks_and_wings_for_Orion_module***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/13/3948903/3948903_4EA56B9FBF31415A948F3888973BB2EF_200113_3948903_NASA_rolls_out_space_launch_system_booster_for_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mega-rocket, megarocket, core stage, space launch system, sls, giant rocket, huge rocket, Artemis, Orion, booster, space, spacecraft, barge, New Orleans, NASA, Mississippi, US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948778</guid>
      <title>Chinese paddlefish has been declared extinct</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Chinese paddlefish has been declared extinct due to overfishing and dams. The species was thought to be the world's largest freshwater fish with an average length of 10 feet. Some reports recorded them reaching 23 feet and weighing half a ton. The Chinese paddlefish had a long, silver-gray body and their name derived from their protruding snout that resembled a paddle.The fish were prominent in many parts of the Yangtze, Asia's largest river flowing 3914 miles from the Tibetan Plateau to the East China Sea.They used their special sword-like snout to sense electrical activity to find prey, such as crustaceans and fish, however, they haven't been spotted since 2003.In the journal Science of The Total Environment, a team of researchers at the Chinese Academy of Fishery Sciences in Wuhan declared the paddlefish as extinct. They believe overfishing in the 1970s, which harvested 25 tons of paddlefish per year on average, was the root cause of the gradual decline in paddlefish.  However, the main contributor which led to extinction was the loss of habitat through the construction of the Gezhouba Dam, built on the main stem of the Yangtze.The dam was constructed without a fish ladder or bypass, cutting off the paddlefish from their only spawning grounds upstream.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese Paddlefish details2. Chinese Paddlefish habitat3. Extinction causes4. How we know they're extinctVOICEOVER (in English): "The Chinese paddlefish was thought to be the world's largest freshwater fish with an average length of 10 feet. Some reports recorded them reaching 23 feet and weighing half a ton." "The Chinese paddlefish had a long, silver-gray body and their name derived from their protruding snout that resembled a paddle." "The fish were prominent in many parts of the Yangtze, Asia's largest river flowing 3914 miles from the Tibetan Plateau to the East China Sea." "They used their special sword-like snout to sense electrical activity to find prey, such as crustaceans and fish, however, they haven't been spotted since 2003.""In the journal Science of The Total Environment, a team of researchers at the Chinese Academy of Fishery Sciences in Wuhan declared the paddlefish as extinct." "They believe overfishing in the 1970s, which harvested 25 tons of paddlefish per year on average, was the root cause of the gradual decline in paddlefish."  "However, the main contributor which led to extinction was the loss of habitat through the construction of the Gezhouba Dam, built on the main stem of the Yangtze.""The dam was constructed without a fish ladder or bypass, cutting off the paddlefish from their only spawning grounds upstream."SOURCES: National Geographic, Phys.org, Science Directhttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2020/01/chinese-paddlefish-one-of-largest-fish-extinct/https://phys.org/news/2020-01-chinese-paddlefish-declared-extinct.htmlhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048969719362382***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/13/3948778/3948778_CDA029CC07A14104ACB3ECD29D633283_200113_3948778_Chinese_paddlefish_has_been_declared_extinct_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Chinese paddlefish, Chinese paddlefish extinct, Yangtze river, Yangtze paddlefish, conservation, world's largest fish extinct, Chinese fish extinct]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948712</guid>
      <title>Vulnerabilities found in TikTok: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCybersecurity firm Check Point has conducted an investigation into video-sharing app TikTok and found major vulnerabilities within the app.In a report, researchers from the company explained that hackers could access a person's account by using a function on TikTok's website that allows users to enter their phone number, which will text them a link to download the app.Hackers could use this flaw to change the download url and send a fraudulent SMS link containing a malicious link created by the attacker. This allowed attackers to access a user's account and to send requests on their behalf.Attackers could use this to manipulate a user's content feed by deleting videos from their feed and uploading unauthorized videos onto their feed instead. Hackers would also have the authority to change a user's video privacy settings from hidden, or private, to public.Researchers found that attackers could also execute JavaScript code in order to retrieve sensitive information about the user. This includes emails, payment information or birthdates.According to the BBC, Check Point said they informed TikTok's parent company ByteDance about the vulnerabilities in November.TikTok says the security flaws have since been fixed in their latest app version.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Security flaws found in TikTok2. How hackers are able to access a user's account3. They could manipulate a user's content feed4. Hackers could also gain access to user's sensitive informationVOICEOVER (in English): "Cybersecurity firm Check Point has conducted an investigation into video-sharing app TikTok and found major vulnerabilities within the app.""In a report, researchers from the company explained that hackers could access a person's account by using a function on TikTok's website that allows users to enter their phone number, which will text them a link to download the app.""Hackers could use this flaw to change the download url and send a fraudulent SMS link containing a malicious link created by the attacker.""This allowed attackers to access a user's account and to send requests on their behalf.""Attackers could use this to manipulate a user's content feed by deleting videos from their feed and uploading unauthorized videos onto their feed instead.""Hackers would also have the authority to change a user's video privacy settings from hidden, or private, to public." "Researchers found that attackers could also execute JavaScript code in order to retrieve sensitive information about the user. This includes emails, payment information or birthdates."SOURCES: Check Point Research, CNBC, BBC News https://research.checkpoint.com/2020/tik-or-tok-is-tiktok-secure-enough/https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/09/tiktok-security-flaw-found-that-allowed-hackers-to-access-accounts.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/technology-51010408***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 05:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/13/3948712/3948712_E510FC2613CC4E37858EFFD418C8B514_200113_3948712_Vulnerabilities_found_in_TikTok__Report_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, TikTok, Tik tok vulnerabilities, tiktok security flaws, tik tok security, tik tok security breach, checkpoint tik tok, tik tok news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949366</guid>
      <title>Japan will expand air defenses to counter North Korean ballistic missiles: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan's Type-03 Air Defense System is a surface to air missile system that utilizes a truck-mounted launcher to shoot interceptor missiles, according to Missile Advocacy.Citing unnamed defense officials, Japan Forward reports the Japanese military will give the missile an anti-ballistic capability to respond to the North Korean threat.According to Global Security, the Chu-SAM is 490 cm long, 30 cm wide, and weighs 580 kg.Missile Advocacy states that the current version of the missile has a top speed of Mach 2.5.According to Global Defense, the rocket uses a single stage solid fuel design and includes an active radar homing system.Japan Forward reports that the Defense Agency is testing technologies that will improve both components of the projectile.North Korea's new ballistic missile, which was tested last year and is based on Russia's Iskander missile, flies in an erratic trajectory that Japan's other air defense missiles cannot track.According to Japan Forward, the upgraded the Chu-SAM will be able to predict the irregular trajectory and achieve a shootdown of the enemy missile.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Japan's Type-03 Air Defense System launcher vehicle and interceptor projectile2. Interceptor projectile dimensions and specifications3. Improvements planned for the rocket's design and guidance system4. The upgraded Type-03 is expected to counter North Korea's new ballistic missilesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Missile Advocacy, Japan's Type-03 Air Defense System is a surface to air missile system that utilizes a truck-mounted launcher to shoot interceptor missiles.""Citing unnamed defense officials, Japan Forward reports the Japanese military will give the missile an anti-ballistic capability to respond to the North Korean threat.""According to Global Security, the Chu-SAM is 490 cm long, 30 cm wide, and weighs 580 kg.""Missile Advocacy states that the current version of the missile has a top speed of Mach 2.5.""According to Global Defense, the rocket uses a single stage solid fuel design and includes an active radar homing system.""Japan Forward reports that the Defense Agency is testing technologies that will improve both components of the projectile.""North Korea's new ballistic missile, which was tested last year and is based on Russia's Iskander missile, flies in an erratic trajectory that Japan's other air defense missiles cannot track.""According to Japan Forward, the upgraded the Chu-SAM will be able to predict the irregular trajectory and achieve a shootdown of the enemy missile."SOURCES: Japan-Forward.com, Missileadvocacy.org, Global Securityhttps://japan-forward.com/japan-to-develop-interception-system-for-north-koreas-irregular-trajectory-missiles/https://missiledefenseadvocacy.org/defense-systems/type-03/https://www.globalsecurity.org/military/world/japan/chu-sam.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 11:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/14/3949366/3949366_B049690648DF4B4AAA7B9BA05DC8ECA7_200114_3949366_Japan_will_expand_air_defenses_to_counter_North__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Japan upgrades anti-ballistic missiles, Japan upgrades anti-ballistic missile, Japan upgrades SAMs, erratic trajectory, ballistic missile, ballistic missiles, North Korea, Chu-SAM, Type-03 Air Defense System, Type-03, Iskander, Chu-SAM]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949349</guid>
      <title>Philippines evacuates millions after Taal volcano spews lava with 'explosive eruption' feared</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPhilippine officials have urged a "total evacuation" of millions of people close to Manila, after a volcano spewed ash up to nine miles into the air on Sunday prompting warning of a possible "explosive eruption," CNN reports. The BBC reports that early Monday, a weak flow of lava began seeping out of Taal volcano, which is located around 45 miles south of Manila. According to the BBC, Taal had earlier emitted a huge plume of ash, triggering the mass evacuation of 8,000 people from the immediate area. The BBC cites that Taal is the country's second most active volcano, located in the middle of a lake. CNN reports that the Philippine Institute of Volcanology and SeismologyPHIVOLCShas raised the alert level to four, meaning an "explosive eruption" could happen in the coming hours or days. The highest alert level is five, indicating that an eruption is taking place. According to CNN, in explosive eruptions, magma is fragmented and violently released from the volcano as opposed to thick lava flowing out. PHIVOLCS has requested a "total evacuation" of citizens within a 10.5 mile radius around the volcano.    The BBC reports that Taal is also one of the world's smallest volcanoes and has recorded at least 34 eruptions in the past 450 years. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Taal spewing lava2. Taal spewing ash cloud3. Taal alert level 44.  Volcanic eruption and Taal eruption exclusion zoneVOICEOVER (in English): "The BBC reports that early Monday, a weak flow of lava began seeping out of Taal volcano, which is located around 45 miles south of Manila." "According to the BBC, Taal had earlier emitted a huge plume of ash, triggering the mass evacuation of 8,000 people from the immediate area.""The BBC cites that Taal is the country's second most active volcano, located in the middle of a lake." "CNN reports that the Philippine Institute of Volcanology and SeismologyPHIVOLCShas raised the alert level to four, meaning an "explosive eruption" could happen in the coming hours or days. The highest alert level is five, indicating that an eruption is taking place." "According to CNN, in explosive eruptions, magma is fragmented and violently released from the volcano as opposed to thick lava flowing out." "PHIVOLCS has requested a "total evacuation" of citizens within a 10.5 mile radius around the volcano."    SOURCES: BBC, CNNhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-51086961https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/12/asia/taal-volcano-eruption-philippines-trnd/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/14/3949349/3949349_E47FE1B3F1F244F2813922AF6169D82B_200114_3949349_Philippines_evacuates_millions_after_Taal_volcan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Taal volcano, Taal volcano eruption, Taal volcano lava flows, Philippines Taal volcano]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949344</guid>
      <title>Iran admits to accidentally downing Ukraine's Flight 752</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIran's military on Saturday admitted that its air defense system had shot down Ukraine's Flight 752 by mistake.Citing Iranian official statements, the New York Times said the passenger jet had been misidentified as a U.S. cruise missile.The New York Times reports that the Tor is a mobile system carrying eight missiles, that can be operated without input from other air defense infrastructure.Citing defense analyst Steven Zaloga, Bloomberg reports that the missile's guidance system is unable to distinguish cruise missiles from military aircraft or civilian airplanes.Citing FlightRadar24, Bloomberg reports that the Boeing 737 made a slight right turn two minutes after its takeoff from Tehran International Airport, which was normal.The plane was clearly transmitting its identity and position until it climbed to about 7,900 feet of altitude, presumably because it was hit by missile fire.The plane plunged into a field in between the cities of Parand and Shariar. All 176 passengers and crew were killed.Due to the Tor's indiscriminate guidance system, most nations do not operate the weapon without connecting it into a command structure.Bloomberg reports that according to Zaloga, SA-15 operators were not supposed to fire without authorization.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A mobile surface to air missile battery misidentified Flight 752 as a U.S. cruise missile2. The Tor SAM system's guidance system does not discriminate target types3. The last flight of PS 752; all passenger and crew killed in the crash4. Typically Tor operators cannot open fire without authorizationVOICEOVER (in English): "Iran's military on Saturday admitted that its air defense system had shot down Ukraine's Flight 752 by mistake.""Citing Iranian official statements, the New York Times said the passenger jet had been misidentified as a U.S. cruise missile.""The New York Times reports that the Tor is a mobile system carrying eight missiles, that can be operated without input from other air defense infrastructure." "Citing defense analyst Steven Zaloga, Bloomberg reports that the missile's guidance system is unable to distinguish cruise missiles from military aircraft or civilian airplanes.""Citing FlightRadar24, Bloomberg reports that the Boeing 737 made a slight right turn two minutes after its takeoff from Tehran International Airport, which was normal.""The plane was clearly transmitting its identity and position until it climbed to about 7,900 feet of altitude, presumably because it was hit by missile fire.""The plane plunged into a field in between the cities of Parand and Shariar. All 176 passengers and crew were killed.""Due to the Tor's indiscriminate guidance system, most nations do not operate the weapon without connecting it into a command structure.""Bloomberg reports that according to Zaloga, SA-15 operators were not supposed to fire without authorization."SOURCES: The New York Times, Bloomberg News, FlightRadar24 https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/11/world/middleeast/plane-crash.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-13/multiple-failures-led-to-iran-s-accidental-attack-on-jetliner?sref=hBxgxhfNhttps://www.flightradar24.com/blog/ukrainian-flight-ps752-crashes-shortly-after-take-off-from-tehran/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/14/3949344/3949344_F43941C385E645DE9CDECD63AB416106_200114_3949344_Iran_admits_to_accidentally_downing_Ukraine_s_Fl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Iran shoots down plane, Iran accidentally shoots down plane, Iran shoots down Ukrainian plane, Tor, Tor SA-15, surface to air missile, SAM, missile, missiles, Iranian missile, Iranian missiles, Flight PS 752, Flight 752, Boeing 737]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949154</guid>
      <title>Water on Mars is disappearing faster than expected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research by France's National Center for Scientific Research suggests that water on Mars is evaporating faster than previously thought.Scientists analyzed data from the Trace Gas Orbiter, which orbits around Mars, and found seasonal changes affect how water vapor is distributed around the atmosphere.As the sun warms up the red planet's ice poles, water molecules, in the form of water vapor, are released into the atmosphere. The molecules are then carried by the wind to higher altitudes.During the warmest parts of the year, Mars' atmosphere becomes "supersaturated" with 10 to 100 times more water vapor than its frigid cold temperatures typically allow. This allows the water to reach the planet's upper atmosphere.As water molecules make their way to Mars' upper atmosphere, ultraviolet rays from the sun breaks them down into hydrogen and oxygen atoms where the atoms are able to escape into space.The researchers were surprised at their findings, as they expected that the water vapor would be limited by Mars' cold temperatures and would condense into clouds, according to Space.com.Franck Montmessin, one of the scientists involved with the study, told the publication that further research would be needed to find out how much water exactly is making its way to Mars' upper atmosphere and escaping so that scientists can get a better understanding of the process.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mars losing water2. How water vapor is released into the planet's atmosphere3. Mars' atmosphere becoming super saturated with water vapor4. UV rays from the sun breaking down the water moleculesVOICEOVER (in English): "New research by France's National Center for Scientific Research suggests that water on Mars is evaporating faster than previously thought.""Scientists analyzed data from the Trace Gas Orbiter, which orbits around Mars, and found seasonal changes affect how water vapor is distributed around the atmosphere.""As the sun warms up the red planet's ice poles, water molecules, in the form of water vapor, are released into the atmosphere.""The molecules are then carried by the wind to higher altitudes.""During the warmest parts of the year, Mars' atmosphere becomes 'supersaturated' with 10 to 100 times more water vapor than its frigid cold temperatures typically allow.""This allows the water to reach the planet's upper atmosphere.""As water molecules make their way to Mars' upper atmosphere, ultraviolet rays from the sun breaks them down into hydrogen and oxygen atoms where the atoms are able to escape into space."SOURCES: French National Center for Scientific Research, Science, Space.com http://www.cnrs.fr/en/mars-water-could-disappear-faster-expectedhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2020/01/08/science.aay9522https://www.space.com/mars-water-escape-into-space-rapidly.html ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/14/3949154/3949154_70BCA8F90EC6424C80CF2AA800A3E05A_200114_3949154_Water_on_Mars_is_disappearing_faster_than_expect_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mars water, mars, martian atmosphere, mars is losing water, mars water evaporating, mars water disappearing, water on mars, mars water vapor, water vapor on mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949908</guid>
      <title>At least 20 children injured after Delta aircraft dumps jet fuel over school</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDelta Airlines Flight 89 was enroute to Shanghai from Los Angeles International Airport on Tuesday when the plane experienced an engine issue shortly after takeoff. The plane then proceeded to return to the airport and release jet fuel before conducting an emergency landing. The jet fuel was dumped over a Los Angeles schoolyard and school buildings, reports NBC News. According to the Los Angeles County Fire Department, at least 20 children and 11 adults are being treated for minor injuries for fuel exposure. Those affected were being treated by firefighters on the scene for skin irritation and breathing problems.The fire department said none of the injured needed to be hospitalized.The airline explained the release of fuel is required as part of standard procedure to reach a safe landing weight, Reuters reports, citing a statement from Delta Airlines.In a statement on Twitter, the Federal Aviation Administration explained that there are special fuel-dumping procedures which require airplanes to release jet fuel over designated unpopulated areas. The agency said that the fuel is typically released at higher altitudes so that it dissolves before reaching the ground.The FAA said in the same statement that it is "thoroughly investigating" the circumstances around the incident.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Delta Airlines Flight 89 taking off2. Jet fuel being dumped over a school3. Victims of the incident4. How fuel-dumping procedures typically workVOICEOVER (in English): "Delta Airlines Flight 89 was enroute to Shanghai from Los Angeles International Airport on Tuesday when the plane experienced an engine issue shortly after takeoff." "The plane then proceeded to return to the airport and release jet fuel before conducting an emergency landing.""NBC News reports the jet fuel was dumped over a Los Angeles schoolyard and school buildings.""According to the Los Angeles County Fire Department, at least 20 children and 11 adults are being treated for minor injuries for fuel exposure.""Those affected were being treated by firefighters on the scene for skin irritation and breathing problems.""The fire department said none of the injured needed to be hospitalized.""In a statement on Twitter, the Federal Aviation Administration explained that there are special fuel-dumping procedures which require airplanes to release jet fuel over designated unpopulated areas.""The agency said that the fuel is typically released at higher altitudes so that it dissolves before reaching the ground."SOURCES: NBC News, Los Angeles Times, L.A. County Fire Department Twitter, Federal Aviation Administration Twitter, Reutershttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/17-kids-injured-after-delta-jet-dumps-fuel-l-playground-n1115586https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-14/tracking-delta-flight-89s-path-before-it-dumped-fuel-on-an-elementary-schoolhttps://twitter.com/LACoFDPIO/status/1217224364824752128https://twitter.com/FAANews/status/1217213895066169345/photo/1https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-14/why-did-delta-jet-dump-fuelhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-airplane-school/delta-flight-dumps-fuel-on-l-a-school-26-treated-for-minor-injuries-idUSKBN1ZD2OP***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/15/3949908/3949908_0878371511354DDD956272D245D3DDCC_200115_3949908_At_least_20_children_injured_after_Delta_aircraf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Delta jet, delta jet dumps fuel, delta plane, delta emergency, delta jet fuel release, delta fuel release]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949810</guid>
      <title>EU, Russia to launch joint ExoMars mission in July 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe EU and Russia are collaborating on a mission to Mars to try and answer the question of whether life has ever existed on the Red Planet.According to the European Space Agency, the ExoMars program is comprised of two missions. The first  the Trace Gas Orbiter  launched in 2016 to orbit Mars and examined its atmosphere.The Schiaparelli lander had been deployed with the Trace Gas Orbiter to the surface but crashed during a touchdown attempt.The second mission, slated for July 2020, will launch Roscosmos' Kazachok surface platform and the ESA's Rosalind Franklin rover to Mars via a Proton rocket.After a nine-month journey, a descent module will separate from the carrier and perform a controlled landing on the surface of the Red Planet, at a site called the Oxia Planum.Space reports that the Oxia Planum is a plain in the planet's northern hemisphere that is rich in clay deposits, indicating ancient water activity.After touchdown, the Kazachok platform will remain at the landing site to study the surface environment. Instruments on board will be used to take images of the landing point, study subsurface water distribution, as well as the planet's atmosphere and internal structure.The rover, meanwhile, will travel across the planet's surface, using stereo cameras to build navigation maps and collision avoidance cameras to navigate the terrain. It will drill up to 2 meters down to retrieve underground samples that may contain preserved biomarkers, which will be subject to chemical, physical, and spectral analysis.New Atlas reports that the mission has had trouble in the past with the parachutes, which tore in high-altitude tests.The team has since worked with NASA to iron out the issues, and have announced that the previous problems have been eliminated. But to be sure, further tests will be conducted ahead of the official launch later in the year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. ExoMars program's two missions2. ExoMars module landing on Mars3. Kazachok surface platform remaining at landing site to study surface environment4. Rover navigating terrain, drilling to collect samplesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the European Space Agency, the ExoMars program is comprised of two missions. The first  the Trace Gas Orbiter  launched in 2016 to orbit Mars and examined its atmosphere.""The second mission, slated for July 2020, will launch Roscosmos' Kazachok surface platform and the ESA's Rosalind Franklin rover to Mars via a Proton rocket.""After a nine-month journey, a descent module will separate from the carrier and perform a controlled landing on the surface of the Red Planet, at a site called the Oxia Planum.""After touchdown, the Kazachok platform will remain at the landing site to study the surface environment.""Instruments on board will be used to take images of the landing point, study subsurface water distribution, as well as the planet's atmosphere and internal structure.""The rover, meanwhile, will travel across the planet's surface, using stereo cameras to build navigation maps and collision avoidance cameras to navigate the terrain.""It will drill up to 2 meters down to retrieve underground samples that may contain preserved biomarkers, which will be subject to chemical, physical, and spectral analysis."SOURCES: ESA, Space, New Atlashttps://exploration.esa.int/web/mars/-/48088-mission-overviewhttps://www.space.com/mars-exploration-2020s-alien-life-colonization.htmlhttps://newatlas.com/space/exomars-2020-into-the-great-unknown/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 10:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/15/3949810/3949810_4D5A1FFEDA7F40F2950DBC0E7E95B7FA_200115_3949810_EU__Russia_to_launch_joint_ExoMars_mission_in_Ju_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, exomars 2020, exomars, mars mission, mission to mars, esa, roscosmos, mars rover, exomars rover, exomars 2020 rover, Rosalind Franklin rover, Kazachok surface platform, Oxia Planum, mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949582</guid>
      <title>New artificial trees installed in London</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGerman startup Green City Solutions has installed artificial trees called CityTrees across London to absorb urban pollution.According to the company's website, the CityTree is the world's first bio-tech filter that has been able to considerably improve air quality.The CityTree is a tower filled with different types of moss which collect toxins such as particulate matters such as PM 10 and nitrogen dioxide from the air while giving off oxygen. Each artificial tree is able to produce as much clean air as 275 real trees, according to Dezeen.The structure is powered by solar panels and collects rainwater which is evenly distributed using a fully automated irrigation system.Green City Solutions explains on their website that the CityTrees also contain Internet-of-Things technology to gather environmental data about the trees' surrounding as well as data about its own performance. The artificial trees also have the ability to create an immense cooling effect in its surrounding atmosphere as mosses can store large amounts of moisture.CityTrees were previously trialled in London in 2018 as a trial. The current project is a permanent installation.The structures have previously been installed in Oslo, Paris, Brussels and Hong Kong,  according to CNN. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. CityTrees2. How the trees collect toxins and produce oxygen3. What the structure is powered by4. The trees can create a cooling effectVOICEOVER (in English): "German startup Green City Solutions has installed artificial trees called CityTrees across London to absorb urban pollution.""According to the company's website, the CityTree is the world's first bio-tech filter that has been able to considerably improve air quality.""The CityTree is a tower filled with different types of moss which collect toxins such as particulate matters such as PM 10 and nitrogen dioxide from the air while giving off oxygen.""According to Dezeen, each artificial tree is able to produce as much clean air as 275 real trees.""The structure is powered by solar panels and collects rainwater which is evenly distributed using a fully automated irrigation system.""Green City Solutions explains on their website that the CityTrees also contain Internet-of-Things technology to gather environmental data about the trees' surrounding as well as data about its own performance.""The artificial trees also have the ability to create an immense cooling effect in its surrounding atmosphere as mosses can store large amounts of moisture."SOURCES: Secret London, Time Out, CNN, Green City Solutions, Dezeen https://secretldn.com/city-trees-london-pollution/https://www.timeout.com/london/news/artificial-trees-are-popping-up-in-london-to-suck-up-the-citys-pollution-011020https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/citytree-urban-pollution/index.htmlhttps://greencitysolutions.de/en/solutions/#section2https://www.dezeen.com/2018/03/21/moss-covered-citytree-bench-combats-urban-pollution-london-uk/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 02:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/15/3949582/3949582_7A5164FB90024B93A449C23487371193_200115_3949582_New_artificial_trees_installed_in_London_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, CityTree bench, artificial trees, london artificial trees, london smart bench, mossy living wall, london CityTree, Green City Solutions, Green City Solutions CityTrees]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950342</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy plans hypersonic missiles for stealth destroyers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Navy plans to arm the fleet's newest destroyers with a classified hypersonic missile.Citing a naval officer's remarks at the Surface Naval Association's annual symposium, Fox News reports that the Zumwalt class may obtain the Conventional Prompt Strike weapon.The Zumwalts are stealthy warships that feature two advanced 155mm guns, vertical launching systems, advanced radars in the deckhouse, and electric drive propulsion. No details about the prompt strike weapons are available, but Fox reports that the missile combines a conventional warhead with a ballistic missile.This allows the U.S. to launch conventional strikes with the speed and range of nuclear weapons.According to Fox, the stealthy warships will be able to deliver missiles to any target in the world in an hour and some targets could be struck within minutes.The outlet reports that the missiles will potentially allow the U.S. to launch attacks rapidly and without giving away time or the element of surprise.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. Navy proposes hypersonic missiles for Zumwalt-class stealth destroyers2. Zumwalt-class destroyer explained3. Prompt Strike weapon combines hypersonic rocket with conventional warhead4. Missile will have the ability to strike any target in the world in an hourVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Navy plans to arm the fleet's newest destroyers with a classified hypersonic missile.""Citing a naval officer's remarks at the Surface Naval Association's annual symposium, Fox News reports that the Zumwalt class may obtain the Conventional Prompt Strike weapon.""The Zumwalts are stealthy warships that feature two advanced 155mm guns, vertical launching systems, advanced radars in the deckhouse, and electric drive propulsion." "No details about the prompt strike weapons are available, but Fox reports that the missile combines a conventional warhead with a ballistic missile.""This allows the U.S. to launch conventional strikes with the speed and range of nuclear weapons.""According to Fox, the stealthy warships will be able to deliver missiles to any target in the world in an hour and some targets could be struck within minutes.""The outlet reports that the missiles will potentially allow the U.S. to launch attacks rapidly and without giving away time or the element of surprise."SOURCES: Fox News, U.S. Navy institute News, The National Interest, U.S. Navyhttps://www.foxnews.com/tech/navy-may-arm-its-new-destroyer-with-a-conventional-missile-able-to-hit-anywhere-on-earth-in-an-hourhttps://news.usni.org/2019/08/14/report-to-congress-on-conventional-prompt-global-strike-and-long-range-ballistic-missileshttps://nationalinterest.org/blog/buzz/secret-no-more-how-us-navy-keeps-its-stealth-destroyers-stealth-59802https://www.navy.mil/navydata/fact_display.asp?cid=4200&tid=900&ct=4***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/16/3950342/3950342_DF46EDDD50E343EDAC285A4681938CB6_200116_3950342_U_S__Navy_plans_hypersonic_missiles_for_stealth__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US Navy, USN, Zumwalt, Zumwalt-class, destroyer, destroyers, missiles, hypersonic missile, Prompt Strike, Conventional Prompt Strike]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950326</guid>
      <title>NASA's Moon to Mars exploration program</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Moon to Mars exploration program first proposed in 2015 consists of three phases.The first, called 'Earth Reliant', involves using the International Space Station until 2024 to research deep space technologies, and study the effects of long-term space missions on the human body.It also covers the development of the Orion spacecraft and the Space Launch System super heavy lift launch vehicle, or SLS.The second phase, 'Proving Grounds', involves the creation of infrastructure in cislunar space such as the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway, to help the agency learn how to conduct operations in a deep space environment.Missions to Mars and its moons would begin during 'Earth Independent', the third and final phase, which could see NASA using the Lunar Gateway and a spacecraft such as the Deep Space Transport.According to Universe Today, a station in the Red Planet's orbit, like Lockheed Martin's proposed Mars Base Camp, could also be built to allow crewed missions to journey to the Martian surface.Based on a White House directive, NASA will be aiming to land astronauts on the moon by 2024, and then on Mars by the 2030s.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Moon to Mars 'Earth Reliant' phase2. Development of Orion, SLS3. Moon to Mars 'Proving Grounds' phase4. Gateway space station construction5. Gateway space station uses6. Moon to Mars 'Earth Independent' phaseVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Moon to Mars exploration program first proposed in 2015 consists of three phases.""The first, called 'Earth Reliant', involves using the International Space Station until 2024 to research deep space technologies, and study the effects of long-term space missions on the human body.""It also covers the development of the Orion spacecraft and the Space Launch System super heavy lift launch vehicle, or SLS.""The second phase, 'Proving Grounds', involves the creation of infrastructure in cislunar space such as the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway, to help the agency learn how to conduct operations in a deep space environment.""The Gateway space station is slated for completion in the mid-2020s.""According to Space.com, NASA's 2019 fiscal budget request calls for a 2022 launch of the power and propulsion module.""Two additional launches by 2025 will add habitation, logistics, and airlock functions.""According to the ESA, Gateway will serve as a staging post where astronauts can dock and leave their spacecraft, then travel to the lunar surface in a lander.""It will also provide them shelter, a place to stock up on fuel and supplies and relay communications, and a base to dispatch crew and robots to the moon.""Missions to Mars and its moons would begin during 'Earth Independent', the third and final phase, which could see NASA using the Lunar Gateway and a spacecraft such as the Deep Space Transport.""According to Universe Today, a station in the Red Planet's orbit, like Lockheed Martin's proposed Mars Base Camp, could also be built to allow crewed missions to journey to the Martian surface."SOURCES: SOURCES: NASA, Universe Today, ESA https://www.nasa.gov/johnson/exploration/overviewhttps://www.universetoday.com/142758/is-nasa-sacrificing-sending-astronauts-to-mars-in-order-to-get-to-the-moon-sooner/http://www.esa.int/Our_Activities/Operations/Angelic_halo_orbit_chosen_for_humankind_s_first_lunar_outpost***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/16/3950326/3950326_3299ADB36B804F13811771E17AE2D014_200116_3950326_NASA_s_Moon_to_Mars_exploration_program_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mars mission, moon to mars, Nasa moon to mars, moon mission, lunar mission, NASA moon mission, NASA lunar mission, gateway space station, lunar orbital platform gateway, deep space transport, Orion, SLS, Mars base camp]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950963</guid>
      <title>Sepsis linked to one in five deaths around the world: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study in The Lancet estimates that sepsis is associated with one in five deaths around the world, or more deaths than cancer.Citing the authors, the University of Washington says in a news release that the study's figure doubled the previous estimates of global sepsis deaths.Sepsis is triggered by diarrhoeal infections or lung diseases that cause the immune system to overreact.The immune cells attack the patient's own body and can lead to organ failure followed by death. In adults, sepsis symptoms include passing little urine, shivering, extreme shivering or muscle pain, and mottled or discolored skin.According to the paper, low and middle income countries are overwhelmingly more affected by sepsis cases.Those deaths could have been prevented by better sanitation, clean water, and access to vaccines.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New study in Lancet estimates that sepsis is associated to one in five deaths globally2. Sepsis is triggered by certain infections that cause the immune system to overreact3. Symptoms of sepsis in adults4. Better sanitation and medical care could reduce sepsis cases in poor countriesVOICEOVER (in English): "A study in The Lancet estimates that sepsis is associated with one in five deaths around the world, or more deaths than cancer.""Citing the authors, the University of Washington says in a news release that the study's figure doubled the previous estimates of global sepsis deaths.""Sepsis is triggered by diarrhoeal infections or lung diseases that cause the immune system to overreact.""The immune cells attack the patient's own body and can lead to organ failure followed by death." "In adults, sepsis symptoms include passing little urine, shivering, extreme shivering or muscle pain, and mottled or discolored skin.""According to the paper, low and middle income countries are overwhelmingly more affected by sepsis cases.""Those deaths could have been prevented by better sanitation, clean water, and access to vaccines."SOURCES: The Lancet, University of Washington, BBC News, Mayo Clinichttps://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(19)32989-7/fulltexthttps://newsroom.uw.edu/news/sepsis-associated-1-5-deaths-globallyhttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-51138859***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 12:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/17/3950963/3950963_D0CF8A8DC0FC447BA92B47B55F3D8B48_200117_3950963_Sepsis_linked_to_one_in_five_deaths_around_the_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sepsis, sepsis symptoms, sepsis deaths, sepsis mortality rate, sepsis death stats, university of washington, lancet, the lancet, university of Pittsburgh, health, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950840</guid>
      <title>Scientists identifies new class of celestial objects near the galactic black hole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists identified a new class of celestial bodies near the Sagittarius A, the Milky Way Galaxy's supermassive black hole.According to the paper in Nature Astronomy, the six strange objects, named G1 through G6, orbit around Sagittarius A in circuits that range from 100 to 1,000 years.Citing the authors, the University of California Los Angeles says that as the objects are close to Sagittarius A, the black hole stretches them out of shape and strip away their outer gas shell.Observing one of the objects G2, the researchers found that even after the black hole dramatically elongates its gas shell, the object retains a relatively coherent dust core.This suggests G2and by inference, the rest of the G-class objectshad stellar objects inside the core.Co-author and UCLA professor Andrea Ghez speculates that all six G objects were formerly binary stars that fell under the black hole's influence.Ghez says that Sagittarius A's powerful gravity may have caused the binary stars to merge and to give rise to the weird G-class objects.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Scientists have so far identified six weird objects near the galactic core2. The objects become elongated when they get close to black hole Sagittarius A 3. The object's core may contain stars that allow them to retain their shape4. The galactic black hole may have merged binary stars to form the objectsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists identified a new class of celestial bodies near the Sagittarius A, the Milky Way Galaxy's supermassive black hole.""According to the paper in Nature Astronomy, the six strange objects, named G1 through G6, orbit around Sagittarius A in circuits that range from 100 to 1,000 years.""Citing the authors, the University of California Los Angeles says that as the objects are close to Sagittarius A, the black hole stretches them out of shape and strip away their outer gas shell." "Observing one of the objects G2, the researchers found that even after the black hole dramatically elongates its gas shell, the object retains a relatively coherent dust core.""This suggests G2and by inference, the rest of the G-class objectshad stellar objects inside the core.""Co-author and UCLA professor Andrea Ghez speculates that all six G objects were formerly binary stars that fell under the black hole's influence.""Ghez says that Sagittarius A's powerful gravity may have caused the binary stars to merge and to give rise to the weird G-class objects."SOURCES: Nature Astronomy, University of California Los Angeleshttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1883-yhttp://newsroom.ucla.edu/releases/astronomy-strange-objects-galaxy-black-hole***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/17/3950840/3950840_0D7A4EB26AD443D4ACB6D589AA7696CB_200117_3950840_Scientists_identifies_new_class_of_celestial_obj_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Weird objects, binary stars, bizarre objects, black hole, center of the galaxy, galactic core, supermassive black hole, Sagittarius A, the milky way galaxy, the galaxy, star, gas, UCLA, Galactic Center]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950822</guid>
      <title>'The One' to become the tallest building in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSupertall skyscraper "The One" is set to become the tallest building in Canada at 309 meters once it is completed in Toronto later this year.The mixed-use development is designed by British architecture firm Foster + Partners and Canadian design firm Core Architects.The skyscraper's exterior consists of multiple champagne-hued rectangular blocks stacked on top of one another. The tower's facade has two diagonal columns with diagonal bracing on each side of the building.Residents will be able to see the diagonal bracing through their window as they look out to the city.The top of the skyscraper will feature a green space with trees, according to Urban Toronto. The 85-story tower will include retail stores, restaurants, hotels and apartments.Toronto currently has 67 skyscrapers and is set to add 31 more to its skyline. An additional 59 skyscrapers have been proposed by architects and design firms. According to data from the Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitat, this will make Toronto home to the second highest number of skyscrapers in North America.Chicago currently has 126 skyscrapers while 19 other skyscrapers are either under construction or have been proposed for the city.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Supertall skyscraper2. The structure's exterior3. Green spaces in the building4. What the mixed-use development will includeVOICEOVER (in English): "Supertall skyscraper 'The One' is set to become the tallest building in Canada at 309 meters once it is completed in Toronto later this year.""The mixed-use development is designed by British architecture firm Foster + Partners and Canadian design firm Core Architects.""The skyscraper's exterior consists of multiple champagne-hued rectangular blocks stacked on top of one another.""The tower's facade has two diagonal columns with diagonal bracing on each side of the building.""Residents will be able to see the diagonal bracing through their window as they look out to the city.""According to Urban Toronto, the top of the skyscraper will feature a green space with trees.""The 85-story tower will include retail stores, restaurants, hotels and apartments."SOURCES: The Globe and Mail, Urban Toronto, Dezeen, Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitathttps://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/toronto/the-one/article36498485/https://urbantoronto.ca/news/2019/04/completed-mega-caissons-revealed-one-progresseshttps://urbantoronto.ca/news/2019/10/exclusive-preview-one%E2%80%99s-exterior-finisheshttps://urbantoronto.ca/database/projects/onehttps://www.dezeen.com/2017/10/10/foster-partners-the-one-supertall-skyscraper-tallest-building-toronto-canada/https://www.ctbuh.org/groups/12***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/17/3950822/3950822_3A981252C5A7478C80DC1E19069DF63C_200117_3950822__The_One__to_become_the_tallest_building_in_Cana_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Canada skyscrapers, toronto the one, toronto the one skyscraper, toronto buildings, toronto skyscrapers, toronto skyline, skyscrapers in toronto]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950605</guid>
      <title>Golden tower proposed for Toronto</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCanadian architectural firm Giannone Petricone Associates has unveiled plans to build a 79-story golden tower in Toronto. The skyscraper would be 266 meters in height.The building's exterior resembles a pleated curtain which reflects sunlight from different angles to create a sense of movement, according to Urban Toronto. The development would cover a gross floor area of roughly 121,965 square meters.It would include three levels of retail space at the bottom of the building, while the rest of the tower would be residential.The building's main lobby would include escalators to the tower's shopping areas, while elevators would be available for residents looking to return home or visit the building's sky lobby.Architects have also proposed a five-level underground garage and 500 bicycle parking spaces, reports Urban Toronto.  Once completed, the building would be connected to Toronto's Bay subway station.According to Urban Toronto, if the building was completed today, it would be the fifth tallest building in the city.Toronto is expected to surpass Chicago as home to the second highest number of skyscrapers in North America, Bloomberg reports , citing data from the Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitat. The city is currently home to 67 skyscrapers. Toronto currently has 31 skyscrapers under construction and has proposed an additional 59 towers.Chicago now has 126 skyscrapers and 19 other skyscrapers that are either under construction or have been proposed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Golden tower2. The building would include retail space as well as residential units3. Building amenities4. Underground garage and bicycle parking spacesVOICEOVER (in English): "Canadian architectural firm Giannone Petricone Associates has unveiled plans to build a 79-story golden tower in Toronto.""The skyscraper would be 266 meters in height.""According to Urban Toronto, the building's exterior resembles a pleated curtain which reflects sunlight from different angles to create a sense of movement." "The development would cover a gross floor area of roughly 121,965 square meters.""It would include three levels of retail space at the bottom of the building, while the rest of the tower would be residential.""The building's main lobby would include escalators to the tower's shopping areas, while elevators would be available for residents looking to return home or visit the building's sky lobby.""Urban Toronto reports that architects have also proposed a five-level underground garage and 500 bicycle parking spaces.""Once completed, the building would be connected to Toronto's Bay subway station."SOURCES: Urban Toronto, Toronto Storeys, Bloomberghttps://urbantoronto.ca/news/2019/11/79-storey-mixed-use-tower-proposed-80-bloor-westhttps://urbantoronto.ca/database/projects/80-bloor-street-westhttps://torontostoreys.com/golden-skyscraper/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-09/toronto-building-boom-set-to-lift-city-s-skyscraper-ranks-chart***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/17/3950605/3950605_BF4643A4EA234000B229A60121228AC9_200117_3950605_Golden_tower_proposed_for_Toronto_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Toronto skyscraper, toronto golden skyscraper, toronto architecture, Giannone Petricone Associates,  toronto golden building, golden skyscraper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952137</guid>
      <title>Experts estimate more than 1,700 people are infected by China's virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCiting Chinese officials, the BBC reports that the coronavirus outbreak in China's city of Wuhan has killed three people and infected more than 200 as of Monday.The news comes days after researchers at London Imperial College's MRC Centre for Global Infectious Disease Analysis warned that there may be far more infection cases than what Beijing had reported.Citing the MRC-GIDA, the BBC reports that the China-based virus outbreak has infected two people in Thailand and one in Japan.The researchers say that their model, based on the virus, Wuhan's population and flight data, estimates that more than 1,700 people have been infected.Chinese authorities speculate that the virus likely crossed the species barrier from infected animals to people at a seafood and wildlife market in Wuhan.Citing an MRC-GIDA researcher, the BBC says that the authorities should seriously consider the possibility of "substantial human-to-human transmission."According to the BBC, the new coronavirus more closely resembles SARs than any other viral strain.Coronavirus is a large family of viruses and only seven are known to infect humans, including the new one discovered in China.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Wuhan pneumonia has infected more than 200 people and killed three as of Jan. 202. The new estimate puts infection cases at over 1,7003. Scientists believe the virus might be capable of human to human transmission 4. Genetic analysis shows that the new virus closely resembles SARSVOICEOVER (in English): "Citing Chinese officials, the BBC reports that the coronavirus outbreak in China's city of Wuhan has killed three people and infected more than 200 as of Monday.""The news comes days after researchers at London Imperial College's MRC Centre for Global Infectious Disease Analysis warned that there may be far more infection cases than what Beijing had reported.""Citing the MRC GIDA, the BBC reports that the China-based virus outbreak has infected two people in Thailand and one in Japan.""The researchers say that their model, based on the virus, Wuhan's population and flight data, estimates that more than 1,700 people have been infected.""Chinese authorities speculate that the virus likely crossed the species barrier from infected animals to people at a seafood and wildlife market in Wuhan.""Citing an MRC-GIDA researcher, the BBC says that the authorities should seriously consider the possibility of "substantial human-to-human transmission."'"According to the BBC, the new coronavirus more closely resembles SARs than any other viral strain.""Coronavirus is a large family of viruses and only seven are known to infect humans, including the new one discovered in China."SOURCES: Imperial College London, MRC Center for Global Infectious Disease Analysis (Twitter), National Health Commission (China), BBC Newshttps://www.imperial.ac.uk/mrc-global-infectious-disease-analysis/news--wuhan-coronavirus/https://twitter.com/mrc_outbreak/status/1218175738337284096?s=21http://www.nhc.gov.cn/yjb/s7860/202001/de5f07afe8054af3ab2a25a61d19ac70.shtmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51171035?ns_mchannel=social&ns_source=facebook&ns_campaign=bbcnews&ocid=socialflow_facebook&fbclid=IwAR1MX41-hoOjOb-7TaDoQ83TkT4JRVDzZPOU4_jQoVA50SXzQYDEcYura28https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51148303https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51168333***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 11:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/20/3952137/3952137_70385EAC078244B3A8E0B60BCD748AC0_200120_3952137_Experts_estimate_more_than_1_700_people_are_infe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China virus outbreak 2020, China virus outbreak, Chinese virus outbreak 2020, Chinese virus, pneumonia, SARS, coronavirus, mystery virus, Chinese disease, epidemic, China's virus, China's new virus, Wuhan pneumonia, coronavirus, new coronavirus, Wuhan, China, MRC Centre for Global Infectious Disease, Imperial College London, UK]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952095</guid>
      <title>Local fish species in U.K. waters predicted to decline by 2050</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report by the Marine Climate Change Impacts Partnership has predicted that cold-water fish species in British waters may be replaced with warm-water species as sea temperatures continue to rise in the next 30 years.Researchers explained that local fish such as cod may decline and be replaced with fish that are typically found in warmer waters, such as the European anchovy.The study also pointed out that the number of Atlantic bluefin tuna has been increasing in British waters, and that this may be partially related to rising temperatures.Likewise, warming waters has caused mackerel to become the dominant fish off of Scotland's west coast over the past 30 years, while the Northern hake has repopulated in the northern part of the North Sea after being largely absent for more than 50 years.The study also predicts that fish may evolve to have smaller bodies as oxygen levels decrease in the warming waters, and fish have to swim farther to find food.Researchers involved in the study explained that this could be bad news for the British fishing industry, which could face a limited quota allocation, and may have to make their livelihood with tinier fish.They projected the net value of the British fishing industry to decrease by 10 percent by 2050 under a "high-emissions scenario."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How British waters could change if the sea temperatures continue to rise2. Local fish may decline and be replaced with fish typically found in water waters3. How warming waters have changed waters off Scotland and the North Sea4. Fish may evolve to have smaller bodiesVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report by the Marine Climate Change Impacts Partnership has predicted that cold-water fish species in British waters may be replaced with warm-water fish species as sea temperatures continue to rise in the next 30 years.""Researchers explained that local fish such as cod may decline and be replaced with fish that are typically found in warmer waters, such as the European anchovy." "The study also pointed out that the number of Atlantic bluefin tuna has been increasing in British waters, and that this may be partially related to rising temperatures.""Likewise, warming waters has caused mackerel to become the dominant fish off of Scotland's west coast over the past 30 years, while the Northern hake has repopulated in the northern part of the North Sea after being largely absent for more than 50 years.""The study also predicts that fish may evolve to have smaller bodies as oxygen levels decrease in the warming waters, and fish have to swim farther to find food."SOURCES: The Telegraph, Herald Scotland, Marine Climate Change Impacts Partnershiphttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2020/01/14/climate-change-could-see-uk-seas-filled-hake-anchovies-herring/https://www.heraldscotland.com/news/18163333.tuna-replace-cod-2050-due-warmer-scottish-seas/http://www.mccip.org.uk/impacts-report-cards/full-report-cards/2020/http://www.mccip.org.uk/media/1999/mccip-report-card-2020_webversion.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/20/3952095/3952095_2F35DBBAC8EC468497BD7132105D0AD9_200120_3952095_Local_fish_species_in_U_K__waters_predicted_to_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Tuna, anchovies, codfish, UK seas, global warming, climate change, warm oceans, acidic ocean, coldwater fish, shellfish]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952077</guid>
      <title>France deploys aircraft carrier for Middle East operations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrance is deploying its sole aircraft carrier Charles de Gaulle to the Middle East.Citing President Emmanuel Macron's speech to the military, Reuters reports that the carrier and its battle group will support counterterrorism operations from January to April.According to Naval Technology, Charles de Gaulle is a 261.5 m long nuclear powered carrier with a displacement of 38,000 tonnes.The de Gaulle's air group includes up to 40 Rafale M fighters, E-2C early warning aircraft, and various helicopters, including the Dauphin PEDRO.The carrier's deck load is supplemented by an internal hanger equipped with two lifts for aircraft.The ship is also armed with the Aster and Mistral air to air missiles and 20mm guns for close range defense.Citing Macron, Reuters reports that after its deployment in the Middle East, the carrier will proceed to the Atlantic Ocean and the North Sea.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. France deploys its aircraft carrier Charles de Gaulle to the Middle East2. Carrier's dimension and composition of its air group 3. Other ship design features and weapons4. Carrier will then deploy to the Atlantic Ocean and the North SeaVOICEOVER (in English): "France is deploying its sole aircraft carrier Charles de Gaulle to the Middle East.""Citing President Emmanuel Macron's speech to the military, Reuters reports that the carrier and its battle group will support counterterrorism operations from January to April." Reuters reports that the move is likely due to concerns that U.S.-Iran tensions may weaken operations against ISIS."According to Naval Technology, Charles de Gaulle is a 261.5 m long nuclear powered carrier with a displacement of 38,000 tonnes."The de Gaulle's air group includes up to 40 Rafale M fighters, E-2C early warning aircraft, and various helicopters, including the Dauphin PEDRO.""The carrier's deck load is supplemented by an internal hanger equipped with two lifts for aircraft.""The ship is also armed with the Aster and Mistral air to air missiles and 20mm guns for close range defense.""Citing Macron, Reuters reports that after its deployment in the Middle East, the carrier will proceed to the Atlantic Ocean and the North Sea."SOURCES: Reuters, Radio Free Europe, Global Security, Naval Technologyhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-macron-military/france-to-deploy-charles-de-gaulle-aircraft-carrier-to-support-middle-east-operations-idUSKBN1ZF2HS?utm_source=reddit.comhttps://www.rferl.org/a/france-deploys-carrier-middle-east-islamic-state/30382245.htmlhttps://www.globalsecurity.org/military/world/europe/cdg.htmhttps://www.naval-technology.com/projects/gaulle/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/20/3952077/3952077_9EBB2B730FEE49029986AB3461FD7998_200120_3952077_France_deploys_aircraft_carrier_for_Middle_East__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Charles de Gaulle, de Gaulle, aircraft carrier, carrier, French aircraft carrier, French carrier, R91, deploy, deploying, middle east, Emanneul Macron, Macron, ISIS, ISIL, Middle East, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3951941</guid>
      <title>How sugar addiction impacts the brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the journal Scientific Reports has found that sugar has the ability to transform our brain chemistry.Scientists from Denmark's Aarhus University performed their experiment on seven pigs to test out their theory. These pigs were fed two liters of sugar water on a daily basis over a 12-day period.The pigs' brains were imaged using a brain scanner prior to the experiment, after the first day of the experiment and after the last day of the experiment.Researchers found significant changes in the pigs' brains' dopamine and opioid systems.Michael Witherdahl, one the researchers involved in the study, said in a Aarhus University press release that the pigs' opioid system, which is associated with well-being and pleasure, had been activated after the pig's first sugar intake.Witherdahl explained both natural stimuli and artificial stimuli have the ability to activate the brain to release dopamine and opioids.He said humans may end up replacing natural stimuli, such as socializing, with artificial stimuli, such as sugar, in order to get a rush of dopamine and opioids to the brain.As part of the bigger picture, the study was looking to see how palatable food, such as sugar, is addicting and how it affects the human body.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sugar changing the brain's chemistry2. The experiment was performed on seven pigs3. How the pigs' brains had changed 4. How the brain can be activated to release dopamine and opioidsVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the journal Scientific Reports has found that sugar has the ability to transform our brain chemistry.""To test out their theory, scientists from Denmark's Aarhus University performed their experiment on seven pigs." "These pigs were fed two liters of sugar water on a daily basis over a 12-day period.""The pigs' brains were imaged using a brain scanner prior to the experiment, after the first day of the experiment and after the last day of the experiment.""Researchers found significant changes in the pigs' brains' dopamine and opioid systems.""Michael Witherdahl, one the researchers involved in the study, said in a Aarhus University press release that the pigs' opioid system, which is associated with well-being and pleasure, had been activated after the pig's first sugar intake.""Witherdahl explained both natural stimuli and artificial stimuli have the ability to activate the brain to release dopamine and opioids." "He said humans may end up replacing natural stimuli, such as socializing, with artificial stimuli, such as sugar, in order to get a rush of dopamine and opioids to the brain."SOURCES: New Atlas, Aarhus University, Scientific Reports https://newatlas.com/medical/pig-study-sugar-brain/https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2020-01/au-sct011420.phphttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-019-53430-9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 07:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/20/3951941/3951941_A4F19EB5A03344B58AE692E37254B64B_200120_3951941_How_sugar_addiction_impacts_the_brain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Sugar, impact of sugar, addictive impacts of sugar on the brain, sugar brain effects, sugar intake, sugar intake health effects, sugar artificial stimuli]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952619</guid>
      <title>Viral outbreak's confirmed cases soar as China confirms human transmission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCases of novel coronavirus infection in China have tripled over the weekend, sparking global concerns about an outbreak.China's state-run Xinhua News reports that there are 218 confirmed cases, mostly in the city of Wuhan. The BBC reports that three have died and nine are in critical condition.China Daily yesterday reported that a fourth fatality occurred in Wuhan, where 15 medical workers have caught the disease as they try to help the patients.The BBC reports that the virus has spread, with five cases in Beijing, one in Shanghai and one in Shenzhen.Outside of China, four cases have been confirmed, two in Thailand, one in Japan and a new case in South Korea.China's state-run Xinhua News Agency reports that health officials have confirmed that human to human transmission has occurred in two cases.According to the BBC, genetic analysis has identified the pathogen as a SARS-like coronavirus strain and one of the seven coronaviruses capable of infecting humans.The pneumonia-like infection causes coughing, shortness of breath, breathing difficulties and fever.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cases of novel coronavirus have tripled over the weekend in China2. Fourth fatality and 15 medical workers infected is reported in Wuhan3. Outbreak spread to Beijing, Shanghai and Shenzhen as Lunar New Year nears4. Cases confirmed in Thailand, Japan, South Korea5. Virus can transmit animal to human and human to human6. Symptoms of novel coronavirus infectionVOICEOVER (in English): "Cases of novel coronavirus infection in China have tripled over the weekend, sparking global concerns about an outbreak.""China's state-run Xinhua News reports that there are 218 confirmed cases, mostly in the city of Wuhan. The BBC reports that three have died and nine are in critical condition.""China Daily yesterday reported that a fourth fatality occurred in Wuhan, where 15 medical workers have caught the disease as they try to help the patients.""Millions of Chinese are traveling in the country to celebrate the Lunar New Year vacation, which will begin on Friday.""The BBC reports that the virus has spread, with five cases in Beijing, one in Shanghai and one in Shenzhen.""Outside of China, four cases have been confirmed, two in Thailand, one in Japan and a new case in South Korea.""The BBC reports that in each case, the infected person had recently visited Wuhan before falling ill.""Scientists believe the infection's main source is animal-based and have advised people not to handle live chickens without protection and to thoroughly cook meat and eggs.""However, China's state-run Xinhua News Agency reports that health officials have confirmed that human to human transmission has occurred in two cases.""According to the BBC, genetic analysis has identified the pathogen as a SARS-like coronavirus strain and one of the seven coronaviruses capable of infecting humans.""According to the WHO, scientists are calling the pathogen 2019-nCoV.""The pneumonia-like infection causes coughing, shortness of breath, breathing difficulties and fever."SOURCES: BBC, Xinhua News Agency, China Daily, World Health Organization (Twitter)https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51171035http://api.xinhua-news.com/mroute/newsdetail/101002020012000004158?dest=A2BDp0suQ5YFdRirZW51bAbgWO8p4xBiAbw5oCraqUwYhttps://cn.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202001/21/WS5e263e0aa3107bb6b579b0d2.htmlhttps://twitter.com/WHO/status/1219317208205209600***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 11:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/21/3952619/3952619_D3AA903370D64CC1A65F791F0B4AA377_200121_3952619_Viral_outbreak_s_confirmed_cases_soar_as_China_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China virus outbreak 2020, China virus outbreak, Chinese virus outbreak 2020, Chinese virus, pneumonia, SARS, coronavirus, mystery virus, Chinese disease, epidemic, China's virus, China's new virus, Wuhan pneumonia, coronavirus, new coronavirus, infection, surge, surged, tripled, triple, Wuhan, China, Lunar New Year, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953236</guid>
      <title>Groups hunting for 'ghost net' near Hawaii</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGhost nets are commercial fishing nets discarded by fishers or lost in the ocean.The Maui News reports that local authorities are asking for the public's help to recover a very large ghost net floating in Hawaii's near seas.According to the paper, the giant net is 50 feet long, 70 feet wide and drifting at a depth of about 50 feet. It is also believed to have a yellow floater bucket.The massive net could ensnare whales and potentially inflict serious damage to boats.According to CNN, the net has not been found as of January 18, although the debris is possibly in the area of Maui, Kahoolawe, Lanai, and Molokai.According to the institute, the ghost net may have collected up to 18 tons of plastic trash.The network reports that ocean nonprofits are hoping to retrieve the ghost net before it sank, or rescuers would have to remove net carefully to avoid harming the reefs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Discarded or lost nets from commercial fishing vessels become ghost nets2. The ghost net's dimensions, identifying features3. The dangers a massive ghost net could pose to wild life, shipping4. Conservation groups fear the net would be hard to remove after it sank on reefsVOICEOVER (in English): "Ghost nets are commercial fishing nets discarded by fishers or lost in the ocean.""The Maui News reports that local authorities are asking for the public's help to recover a very large ghost net floating in Hawaii's near seas.""According to the paper, the giant net is 50 feet long, 70 feet wide and drifting at a depth of about 50 feet. It is also believed to have a yellow floater bucket.""The massive net could ensnare whales and potentially inflict serious damage to boats.""According to CNN, the net has not been found as of January 18, although the debris is possibly in the area of Maui, Kahoolawe, Lanai, and Molokai.""According to the institute, the ghost net may have collected up to 18 tons of plastic trash.""The network reports that ocean nonprofits are hoping to retrieve the ghost net before it sank, or rescuers would have to remove net carefully to avoid harming the reefs."SOURCES: The Maui News, CNN, Love the Sea (Facebook), Olive Ridley Project,https://www.mauinews.com/news/local-news/2020/01/mariners-should-be-on-the-lookout-for-ghost-net-that-threatens-whales/https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/18/us/ghost-net-threatens-sea-life-trnd/index.htmlhttps://www.facebook.com/LoveTheSeaPlasticFree/?__tn__=kC-R&eid=ARDiVm0SMXYjz-AHeMNxed8T2TzaTb4MAXanXaHQvo6CuSkiGRcPwQWYOLhYp2brRlnpg_wk5dtRfgpY&hc_ref=ARTBWycfpI7yiaVdxAFugJ-YEGpTJcgCBQW84J8JEJKpEOgADy5VfOCIcGkS6GRgnwc&ref=nf_targethttps://oliveridleyproject.org/what-are-ghost-nets***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 13:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/22/3953236/3953236_44320C343D9C42848B818D5DE74CFEA9_200122_3953236_Groups_hunting_for__ghost_net__near_Hawaii_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ghost net, huge net, ocean debris, marine debris ghost fishing, plastics, pollution, ocean, environment, Hawaii]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953222</guid>
      <title>Immune discovery could be universal cure to cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCardiff University researchers have identified a mechanism in our immune system that could be utilized to treat most cancers.According to the study published in Nature Immunology, certain T-cells can be engineered to kill prostate, breast, lung and other cancers, albeit only in lab settings.T-cells are a type of lymphocytes found in the blood that searches and destroys threats to the body that include infections to cancers.Cardiff University says in a press statement that one type of T-cells was found to possess a unique receptor that allows them to detect almost all cancer cells.The BBC reports that scientists may be able to take blood from a cancer patient and isolate their T-cells.The T-cells could then be reprogrammed by a harmless virus to grow the special receptor and cultured before the immune cells are reintroduced to fight the patient's cancer cells.T-cells with the special receptors are able to ignore healthy cells and attack the cancerous tissue, including tumors, which normal T-cells cannot.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A kind of T-cell may be engineered to become a standard cure for cancer2. T-cell and receptors explained3. Researchers hope to equip T-cells with a special receptor to fight cancer4. Engineered T-cells can attack VOICEOVER (in English): "Cardiff University researchers have identified a mechanism in our immune system that could be utilized to treat most cancers.""According to the study published in Nature Immunology, certain T-cells can be engineered to kill prostate, breast, lung and other cancers, albeit only in lab settings.""T-cells are a type of lymphocytes found in the blood that searches and destroys threats to the body that include infections to cancers.""Cardiff University says in a press statement that one type of T-cells was found to possess a unique receptor that allows them to detect almost all cancer cells.""The BBC reports that scientists may be able to take blood from a cancer patient and isolate their T-cells.""The T-cells could then be reprogrammed by a harmless virus to grow the special receptor and cultured before the immune cells are reintroduced to fight the patient's cancer cells.""T-cells with the special receptors are able to ignore healthy cells and attack the cancerous tissue, including tumors, which normal T-cells cannot."SOURCES: Nature Immunology, Cardiff University, BBC https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-019-0578-8https://www.cardiff.ac.uk/news/view/1749599-discovery-of-new-t-cell-raises-prospect-of-universal-cancer-therapyhttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-51182451***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/22/3953222/3953222_6A16AA4513BA40F59593DC08C844D832_200122_3953222_Immune_discovery_could_be_universal_cure_to_canc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cancer research, cancer treatment, cancer t cells, t cell receptors]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953198</guid>
      <title>China's novel coronavirus claims first victim in U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new virus from the Chinese city of Wuhan has made 440 people sick, at least nine of whom have died, as of Wednesday, Reuters reports, citing China's National Health Commission.The state-run Xinhua news agency on Monday reported that the commission confirmed the virus is capable of human-to-human transmission.According to NBC, a man who recently visited Wuhan and lives alone near Seattle became the first case of the virus in the U.S.The man fell ill and read about the outbreak online before he contacted his doctor.Citing U.S. officials, the network reports that he was sequestered but is doing well.Taiwan's Liberty Times reports that a Taiwanese woman working in Wuhan got sick and decided to return to Taiwan because she did not trust Chinese hospitals.The woman informed the flight crew of her condition and was sent to a hospital upon landing. She is confirmed to have been infected.The novel coronavirus's rapid spread from across China to Thailand, Japan, South Korea and Taiwan has sparked fears of a larger epidemic.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Novel coronavirus has infected 440 people, including nine who later died2. The first case of the novel coronavirus in the U.S.3. The first case of the novel coronavirus in Taiwan4. The virus has spread to nations neighboring China and to the U.S.5. Symptoms of the coronavirus6. Explainer for how the virus was identified VOICEOVER (in English): "A new virus from the Chinese city of Wuhan has made 440 people sick, at least nine of whom have died, as of Wednesday, Reuters reports, citing China's National Health Commission.""The state-run Xinhua news agency on Monday reported that the commission confirmed the virus is capable of human-to-human transmission.""According to NBC, a man who recently visited Wuhan and lives alone near Seattle became the first case of the virus in the U.S.""The man fell ill and read about the outbreak online before he contacted his doctor.""Citing U.S. officials, the network reports that he was sequestered but is doing well."SOURCES: Reuters, CNN, Xinhua News Agency, NBC, Liberty Times, CCTV, Wuhan Municipal Health Commission, South China Morning Posthttps://www.reuters.com/article/china-health-transmission/china-says-virus-cases-rise-to-440-with-9-deaths-idUSB9N28C01Thttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health-virus-mutuation/china-says-new-virus-adapting-and-mutating-idUSKBN1ZL0A1http://api.xinhua-news.com/mroute/newsdetail/101002020012000004158?dest=A2BDp0suhttps://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/21/asia/china-china-coronavirus-sars-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/1st-case-coronavirus-china-confirmed-u-s-n1119486https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/life/paper/1347666http://news.cctv.com/2020/01/09/ARTIJBz4xvs1P6SsczdZvQHf200109.shtml?spm=C94212.P4YnMod9m2uD.ENPMkWvfnaiV.79http://wjw.wuhan.gov.cn/front/web/showDetail/2020010309017https://www.scmp.com/news/china/politics/article/3046984/china-warns-cadres-cover-spread-virus-and-be-nailed-pillar***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/22/3953198/3953198_0048FB5D02B544DEA6E71B69E1F5904E_200122_3953198_China_s_novel_coronavirus_claims_first_victim_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China virus outbreak 2020, China virus outbreak, Chinese virus outbreak 2020, Chinese virus, pneumonia, SARS, coronavirus, mystery virus, Chinese disease, epidemic, China's virus, China's new virus, Wuhan pneumonia, coronavirus, new coronavirus, Wuhan, China, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953016</guid>
      <title>Malaysia returns 'illegal' plastic waste to U.S., U.K.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMalaysia announced that it has returned 150 shipping containers filled with plastic waste to their country of origin after they were found to be contaminated and mixed in with other trash.Malaysia has sent back 3,737 metric tons of plastic waste to a total of 13 countries, including France, the United Kingdom, the United States and Canada, according to the BBC. France received 43 containers, while the United Kingdom received 42 containers. The United States and Canada received 17 and 11 containers, respectively.Malaysian authorities said that they hope to send back another 110 containers by mid-2020. Sixty of the containers are from the U.S., 15 from Canada and 14 from Japan.Malaysia's environmental minister Yeo Bee Yin said the shipping companies and the countries that shipped out the containers will be responsible for the cost of the returns, CNN reports. Many countries export recyclable waste abroad as this reduces domestic landfill, helps them meet recycling targets and is also inexpensive.In a Facebook post, Yeo said that their government will ensure that Malaysia does not become the "garbage dump of the world."Malaysia is not the only country in Southeast Asia facing this problem. According to the BBC, Indonesia and the Philippines have all sent back unwanted plastic waste to developed countries over the past year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Malaysia has sent back 150 shipping containers filled with plastic waste2. Where the plastic waste was sent back to3. The country plans to send back another 110 containers4. Why countries export recyclable waste abroadVOICEOVER (in English): "Malaysia announced that it is returning 150 shipping containers filled with plastic waste to their country of origin after they were found to be contaminated and mixed in with other trash.""According to the BBC, Malaysia has sent back 3,737 metric tons of plastic waste to a total of 13 countries, including France, the United Kingdom, the United States and Canada.""France received 43 containers, while the United Kingdom received 42 containers. The United States and Canada received 17 and 11 containers, respectively.""Malaysian authorities said that they hope to send back another 110 containers by mid-2020. Sixty of the containers are from the U.S., 15 from Canada and 14 from Japan.""CNN reports that Malaysia's environmental minister Yeo Bee Yin said the shipping companies and the countries that shipped out the containers will be responsible for the cost of the returns.""Many countries export recyclable waste abroad as this reduces domestic landfill, helps them meet recycling targets and is also inexpensive."SOURCES: BBC News, CNN, Free Malaysia Today, Straits Timeshttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-51176312https://www.bbc.com/news/world-48444874https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/20/asia/malaysia-plastic-waste-return-scli-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2020/01/20/150-containers-of-plastic-waste-shipped-back-110-more-to-follow/https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/se-asia/kl-sends-illegal-plastic-waste-back-to-exporting-countries***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 08:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/22/3953016/3953016_AA2C503BD26741D5962FC946B44D9490_200122_3953016_Malaysia_returns__illegal__plastic_waste_to_U_S__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Malaysia plastic waste, malaysia returns plastic waste, imported plastic waste, plastic pollution, plastic waste, importing plastic waste, illegal plastic waste]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952918</guid>
      <title>China's single-use plastic ban explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina will be implementing a ban on single-use plastics over the next five years.A new policy will ban plastic bags in all major Chinese cities, such as Shanghai and Beijing, by the end of 2020 and in all Chinese towns by 2022, Reuters reports, citing China's National Development and Reform Commission. Markets that sell fresh produce will be exempt until 2025.Restaurants will be banned from providing single-use straws by the end of this year, while takeaway food services will not be allowed to provide single-use utensils by 2025. China aims to reduce single-use plastic consumption in its restaurant industry by 30 percent in the next five years.Other plastic items such as plastic courier packaging will be phased out by the end of 2025.China also stated that the production and sale of plastic bags thinner than 0.025 millimeters, as well as plastic film for agricultural use that is less than 0.01 millimeters thick, would be banned.According to the online publication Our World in Data based at the University of Oxford, China produced nearly 60 million tons of plastic waste in 2010. The research noted that the projections are expected to be similar up to the year 2025.The research also said that mismanaged plastic waste around the world is at "significant risk" of leaking and impacting our environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Where plastic bags will be banned2. Single-use straws and utensils will also be phased out3. Other plastic items that will be banned4. The production and sale of certain plastic bags and plastic film would also be bannedVOICEOVER (in English): "Citing China's National Development and Reform Commission, Reuters reports that a new policy will ban plastic bags in all major Chinese cities, such as Shanghai and Beijing, by the end of 2020 and in all Chinese towns by 2022.""Markets that sell fresh produce will be exempt until 2025.""Restaurants will be banned from providing single-use straws by the end of this year, while takeaway food services will not be allowed to provide single-use utensils by 2025.""China aims to reduce single-use plastic consumption in its restaurant industry by 30 percent in the next five years.""Other plastic items such as plastic courier packaging will be phased out by the end of 2025.""China also stated that the production and sale of plastic bags thinner than 0.025 millimeters , as well as plastic film for agricultural use that is less than 0.01 millimeters thick, would be banned."SOURCES: Reuters, BBC News, CNN, EcoWatch https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-environment-plastic/china-moves-to-phase-out-single-use-plastics-idUSKBN1ZI0CVhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51171491https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/20/business/china-single-use-plastics-intl-hnk/index.htmlhttps://www.ecowatch.com/china-plastic-phaseout-2644862834.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 05:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/22/3952918/3952918_6A3298B1A65049E99ADAA26AED0CD6DF_200122_3952918_China_s_single_use_plastic_ban_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Plastic pollution, plastic problem, china plastic pollution, china single-use plastic, single-use plastics, china plastic ban, plastic ban, plastic contamination, plastic waste china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953757</guid>
      <title>Wuhan suspends public transport amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAuthorities in the Chinese city of Wuhan have shut down public transport to stop the spread of a new strain of coronavirus.All flight and passenger train services in and out of Wuhan have temporarily been stopped as of Thursday, January 23, BBC News reports. Public buses, subways and ferry services have also been shut down starting from Thursday, 10:00 a.m. local time.In addition, those residing in Wuhan have already been advised to avoid crowds and to minimize public gatherings. Large-scale activities that were planned at tourist attractions throughout the city have also been suspended ahead of the Lunar New Year holidays.According to CNN, Wuhan has already made it mandatory for everyone in the city to wear face masks in public after the city confirmed more than 500 coronavirus cases.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flights and trains services have been stopped in Wuhan2. Public buses, subways and ferry services have been halted as well3. Wuhan residents have already been advised to avoid crowds 4. It is now mandatory for everyone in the city to wear face masks when in public5. The new strain of coronavirus6. How the virus was spread7. The virus was originally spread from wild animals to humans, though it can now be transmitted between people8. Symptoms of the virus9. Where the virus has spread VOICEOVER (in English): "Authorities in the Chinese city of Wuhan have shut down public transport to stop the spread of a new strain of coronavirus.""BBC News reports, all flight and passenger train services in and out of Wuhan have temporarily been stopped as of Thursday, January 23.""Public buses, subways and ferry services have also been shut down starting from Thursday, 10:00 a.m. local time.""In addition, those residing in Wuhan have already been advised to avoid crowds and to minimize public gatherings.""Large-scale activities that were planned at tourist attractions throughout the city have also been suspended ahead of the Lunar New Year holidays.""According to CNN, Wuhan has already made it mandatory for everyone in the city to wear face masks in public after the city confirmed more than 500 coronavirus cases.""BBC News reports, the virus is now known as 2019-nCOV and is believed to be a new strain of coronavirus that had not been previously identified in humans.""Chinese officials believe that the virus was spread from a local seafood market in Wuhan." "The coronavirus originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there is now evidence that the virus can be transmitted between people.""The seafood market has since been closed for disinfection.""Symptoms of the virus include fever, with some experiencing difficulty breathing.""Chest X-rays from the victims show invasive lesions on both lungs.""The virus has since spread to countries such as Thailand, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan and the United States."SOURCES: BBC News, CNN, The Guardian https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51215348#https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/22/world/wuhan-coronavirus-visual-guide-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jan/22/coronavirus-china-measures-rein-spread-mutate-disease-death-toll***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 10:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/23/3953757/3953757_C007FAA97E1344A48BCD5A0EA0DBA926_200123_3953757_Wuhan_suspends_public_transport_amid_virus_outbr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953641</guid>
      <title>X-ray echoes allows scientists to map out black holes: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers have found a novel way to explore the regions around a black hole.In a paper published in Nature Astronomy, researchers say that they were able to use x-ray echoes around a black hole to map the celestial body's surroundings.According to the University of Cambridge's news release that black hole's gravitational force is extremely powerful and causes massive spatial distortions around itself.As objects caught in the black hole pull are drawn to the event horizon, they heat up and radiate x-rays that "echo and reverberate" against nearby gas.Using the European Space Agency's XMM x-ray observatory, the team was able to observe x-ray echoes of a black hole at the heart of a distant galaxy.The echoes allowed the team to determine the spin and mass of the black hole.The team also made the unexpected discovery that a black hole's the corona--or hot electrons above the accretion disk--changed its size often and quickly.By raising and lowering the roof of the comic echo chamber, the corona's shift in size affected the light echoes and changed their quality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Astronomer use x-ray echoes to map out a black hole's surrounding region2. X-ray echoes are created gas and objects falling toward the black hole 3. Echoes allow astronomers to measure a black hole's spin and mass 4. Light echoes show that the size of black hole coronas shifts rapidlyVOICEOVER (in English): "Astronomers have found a novel way to explore the regions around a black hole.""In a paper published in Nature Astronomy, researchers say that they were able to use x-ray echoes around a black hole to map the celestial body's surroundings.""According to the University of Cambridge's news release that black hole's gravitational force is extremely powerful and causes massive spatial distortions around itself.""As objects caught in the black hole pull are drawn to the event horizon, they heat up and radiate x-rays that 'echo and reverberate' against nearby gas.""Using the European Space Agency's XMM x-ray observatory, the team was able to observe x-ray echoes of a black hole at the heart of a distant galaxy.""The echoes allowed the team to determine the spin and mass of the black hole.""The team also made the unexpected discovery that a black hole's the corona--or hot electrons above the accretion disk--changed its size often and quickly.""By raising and lowering the roof of the comic echo chamber, the corona's shift in size affected the light echoes and changed their quality."SOURCES: Phys.org, Nature Astronomyhttps://phys.org/news/2020-01-astronomers-cosmic-echolocation-black-hole.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-019-1002-x***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/23/3953641/3953641_03B914EE91D545A890AD4273A07672B7_200123_3953641_X_ray_echoes_allows_scientists_to_map_out_black__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Black hole, black holes, x-ray, xray, light echoes, light echo, x-ray echoes, x-ray echo, University of Cambridge, space, European Space Agency, ESA, XMM]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954294</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus continues to spread amid Lunar New Years celebrations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to Reuters, the coronavirus death toll has now risen to 18, after the death of an 80-year-old victim in Hebei province. The South China Morning Post, citing Hebei Daily, reported the victim had spent more than two months in Wuhan visiting relatives.This is the first death due to coronavirus infection outside of Hubei province. The number of infected individuals has risen to 650 worldwide.So far, the virus has been detected in 23 Chinese provinces and four municipalities as well as in Hong Kong, Macau, Thailand, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, Singapore, Vietnam and the United States. According to the South China Morning Post, local governments have issued travel bans in eight cities in Hubei which include Wuhan, Huanggang, Ezhou, Chibi, Xiantao, Qianjiang, Zhijiang and Lichuan.BBC News reports, the city of Wuhan has halted all flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city as of Thursday, January 23. The travel ban includes ride-sharing services. Wuhan authorities asked Didi, a Chinese company similar to Uber or Lyft, to stop all ride services starting Friday at noon. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Coronavirus death toll and new victim2. Total number of individuals, regions and countries affected so far3. Local government travel bans4. Wuhan city public transport bans5. Wuhan city halts ride-hailing services6. Transmission of coronavirus 7. Wuhan market suspected source of coronavirus8. Market disinfection9. Coronavirus symptomsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, the coronavirus death toll has now risen to 18, after the death of an 80-year-old victim in Hebei province. The South China Morning Post, citing Hebei Daily, reported the victim had spent more than two months in Wuhan visiting relatives.""This is the first death due to coronavirus infection outside of Hubei province. The number of infected individuals has risen to 650 worldwide.""So far, the virus has been detected in 23 Chinese provinces and four municipalities as well as in Hong Kong, Macau, Thailand, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, Singapore, Vietnam and the United States." "According to the South China Morning Post, local governments have issued travel bans in eight cities in Hubei which include Wuhan, Huanggang, Ezhou, Chibi, Xiantao, Qianjiang, Zhijiang and Lichuan.""BBC News reports, the city of Wuhan has halted all flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city as of Thursday, January 23.""The travel ban includes ride-sharing services. Wuhan authorities asked Didi, a Chinese company similar to Uber or Lyft, to stop all ride services starting Friday at noon." "The coronavirus originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there is now evidence that human to human transmission of the virus is possible.""Chinese officials believe that the virus originated from a local seafood market in Wuhan. The market has since been closed for disinfection.""The virus has an incubation period of 5 days. Symptoms of the virus include fever, with some experiencing difficulty breathing. Chest x-rays from infected patients show invasive lesions on both lungs."SOURCES: Reuters, South China Morning Post, BBC Newshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health/china-locks-down-city-of-11-million-at-epicenter-of-virus-outbreak-idUSKBN1ZM087https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3047453/china-coronavirus-first-fatality-reported-outside-epicentrehttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51230011***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/24/3954294/3954294_57821724FB6E47AD8D3168BFEFEDE9BB_200124_3954294_Coronavirus_continues_to_spread_amid_Lunar_New_Y_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954225</guid>
      <title>Increase in HFC-23 emissions linked to China, India: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the University of Bristol has found that atmospheric levels of hydrofluorocarbon gas, or HFC-23, have continued to rise despite China and India saying they had stopped emissions.Scientists involved with the study said they expected to find a roughly 90 percent decline in greenhouse gas emissions as part of the Montreal Protocol, an international treaty signed by countries around the world to protect the ozone layer from greenhouse gas emissions.Researchers gathered data from the Advanced Global Atmospheric Gas Experiment network baseline stations and created model simulations for data between 2015 to 2018. Their research linked HFC-23 emissions to China and India, even though both countries were said to have almost completely halted emissions in 2017.According to a news release from the University of Bristol, HFC-23 is an extremely potent greenhouse gas, with one ton of HFC-23 emissions being equivalent to more than 12,000 tons of carbon dioxide emissions.HFC-23 is typically used in cooling systems such as refrigerators and air conditioners, the Guardian reports.Lead author of the study Kieran Stanley explained in the news release that it is very likely that China wasn't as successful in its endeavor to reduce HFC-23 emissions as was previously reported.As for India, Stanley said that without additional measurements, the team can't be sure whether or not India was able to implement an emissions reduction program.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. HFC-23 emissions have continued to rise2. How researchers gathered data and created model simulations3. Why HFC-23 is much more potent than CO24. Where HFC-23 is typically usedVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the University of Bristol has found that atmospheric levels of hydrofluorocarbon gas, or HFC-23, have continued to rise despite China and India saying they had stopped emissions.""Scientists involved with the study said they expected to find a roughly 90 percent decline in greenhouse gas emissions as part of the Montreal Protocol, an international treaty signed by countries around the world to protect the ozone layer from greenhouse gas emissions." "Researchers gathered data from the Advanced Global Atmospheric Gas Experiment network baseline stations and created model simulations for data between 2015 to 2018.""Their research linked HFC-23 emissions to China and India, even though both countries were said to have almost completely halted emissions in 2017.""According to a news release from the University of Bristol, HFC-23 is an extremely potent greenhouse gas, with one ton of HFC-23 emissions being equivalent to more than 12,000 tons of carbon dioxide emissions.""The Guardian reports that HFC-23 is typically used in cooling systems such as refrigerators and air conditioners."SOURCES: The Guardian, Nature Communications, Science Daily, University of Bristol https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/jan/21/study-finds-shock-rise-in-levels-of-potent-greenhouse-gas-hfc-23https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-019-13899-4https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/01/200121113039.htmhttps://phys.org/news/2020-01-emissions-potent-greenhouse-gas-contradicting.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 09:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/24/3954225/3954225_37781E0973F347E2BF906D08CD9A516F_200124_3954225_Increase_in_HFC_23_emissions_linked_to_China__In_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Greenhouse gases, potent greenhouse gases, greenhouse gas emissions, carbon emissions, greenhouse gases and global warming, greenhouse gas emissions rise, global warming, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954145</guid>
      <title>Four leaks found in Japan's Fukushima Nuclear Plant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAfter surviving a massive earthquake, tsunami and nuclear meltdowns in 2011, Japan's Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Plant is now dealing with four different leaks in its walls.According to NHK Japan, there are four coolant leaks at four different locations of the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Station. According to Tokyo Electric Power Company Holdings, also known as TEPCO, the coolant has been found seeping through pipes located in the nuclear station's underground wall of frozen soil. This wall surrounds the facility's reactor and turbine buildings.The leaks are specifically located in the pipes between the plant's No. 2 and 3 reactor buildings.TEPCO found the leaks in late 2019 after noticing a reduction in coolant liquids in its tanks. The company estimates it has lost a total of 20 cubic meters of coolant due to the leak.The cooling liquid is an important tool in disaster prevention for the plant. As it circulates through the underground pipes, it freezes the soil surrounding the reactor buildings, this keeps groundwater from flowing into the nuclear station.Although a leak at a major nuclear station sounds alarming, TEPCO assures that the chemical composition of the cooling liquid is commonly found in snow-melting agents and therefore is not harmful to the environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Visualization of coolant leaks at the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Station2. Close-up of coolant leaks and underground frozen soil3. Location of leaks and amount of coolant lost4. Use of coolant in the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power StationVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NHK Japan, there are four coolant leaks at four different locations of the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Station." "According to Tokyo Electric Power Company Holdings, also known as TEPCO, the coolant has been found seeping through pipes located in the nuclear station's underground wall of frozen soil. This wall surrounds the facility's reactor and turbine buildings." "The leaks are specifically located in the pipes between the plant's No. 2 and 3 reactor buildings.""TEPCO found the leaks in late 2019 after noticing a reduction in coolant liquids in its tanks. The company estimates it has lost a total of 20 cubic meters of coolant due to the leak.""The cooling liquid is an important tool in disaster prevention for the plant. As it circulates through the underground pipes, it freezes the soil surrounding the reactor buildings, this keeps groundwater from flowing into the nuclear station."SOURCES: NHK Japan, Nuclear Engineering International, The Mainichihttps://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20200117_10/https://www.neimagazine.com/news/newsleaks-found-in-the-fukushima-ice-wall-7611042https://mainichi.jp/english/articles/20200117/p2a/00m/0na/022000c***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 07:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/24/3954145/3954145_E3CA325C007B40D98592F38F2DF00519_200124_3954145_Four_leaks_found_in_Japan_s_Fukushima_Nuclear_Pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, fukushima, fukushima nuclear reactor, fukushima power plant, fukushima leak, fukushima problems, japan fukushima reactor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955203</guid>
      <title>Wuhan coronavirus contagious even during incubation period</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCiting China's National Health Commission, the South China Morning Post reports that the new strain of coronavirus is contagious during its incubation period, that is before patients start showing visible symptoms. The incubation period of the coronavirus lasts up to 14 days.Symptoms of the virus include fever and cough with some experiencing difficulty breathing.National Health Commission Minister Ma Xiaowei, told media during a press conference on January 26 that 1,350 doctors had been sent to Hubei province with 1,000 more to come in the following days.According to the South China Morning Post, so far there are 2,510 cases of coronavirus infections around the world. The death toll has risen to 80.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Incubation period of coronavirus2. Symptoms of coronavirus3. Doctors deployed to Hubei4. Total cases of coronavirus and death toll update5. Believed origin of virus6. Wuhan limit access to transportation services7. China temporarily bans sale of wildlife8. Ways to prevent spread of virusVOICEOVER (in English): "Citing China's National Health Commission, the South China Morning Post reports that the new strain of coronavirus is contagious during its incubation period, that is before patients start showing visible symptoms. The incubation period of the coronavirus lasts up to 14 days.""Symptoms of the virus include fever and cough with some experiencing difficulty breathing.""National Health Commission Minister Ma Xiaowei, told media during a press conference on January 26 that 1,350 doctors had been sent to Hubei province with 1,000 more to come in the following days.""According to the South China Morning Post, so far there are 2,510 cases of coronavirus infections around the world. The death toll has risen to 80.""The virus is believed to have originated from a wet market in Wuhan.""In an effort to contain the virus, the city of Wuhan has halted all flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city as of Thursday, January 23. Other transportation systems have been curtailed." "According to Reuters, China announced it was temporarily banning the sale of wildlife in markets, restaurants, and online retailers throughout the whole country.""The best way to prevent the spread of the virus is to compound wearing masks with other sanitary measures such as washing hands thoroughly and frequently as well as avoiding hand to mouth and eye contact."SOURCES: SCMP, The New York Times, Reuters, BBC Newshttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3047701/coronavirus-contagious-even-incubation-stage-chinas-healthhttps://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/26/world/asia/coronavirus-wuhan-china-hubei.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health/china-virus-deaths-rise-to-80-as-hong-kong-bans-visitors-from-worst-hit-province-idUSKBN1ZQ01Qhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51254523***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 13:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/27/3955203/3955203_E8490E3D01F24AD692FA685750B5B0C9_200127_3955203_Wuhan_coronavirus_contagious_even_during_incubat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955126</guid>
      <title>Do masks prevent the spread of the coronavirus outbreak?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMore than 80 million masks were sold on Chinese online retailer, Taobao, on January 20 and 21 following the outbreak of the deadly coronavirus, according to the BBC. However, wearing facemasks alone is not the most efficient way to avoid transmission of viruses or prevent the contraction of them.Talking to BBC News, Dr. David Carrington of St George's, University of London explained that surgical masks do not provide sufficient protection from airborne viruses as they have no filter and do not shield the wearer's eyes.They do however protect against and prevent the spray of coughing and sneezing. They also provide limited protection against hand-to-mouth viral transmission. According to the Centers for Disease Control, the best way to prevent the current coronavirus outbreak is to compound wearing a facemask with the following actions:covering your mouth when coughing or sneezing, washing hands often for at least 20 seconds, avoid touching eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands, avoid sharing items that could be infected and consistently monitor for coronavirus symptoms.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Amount of masks sold in China on Taobao2. Masks alone are not efficient in preventing viral transmission3. Type of prevention masks provide4. Other ways to prevent the spread of viral diseasesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to BBC News, more than 80 million masks were sold on Chinese online retailer, Taobao, on January 20 and 21 following the outbreak of the deadly coronavirus.""However, wearing facemasks alone is not the most efficient way to avoid transmission of viruses or prevent the contraction of them.""Talking to BBC News, Dr. David Carrington of St George's, University of London explained that surgical masks do not provide sufficient protection from airborne viruses as they have no filter and do not shield the wearer's eyes.""They do however protect against and prevent the spray of coughing and sneezing. They also provide limited protection against hand-to-mouth viral transmission.""According to the Centers for Disease Control, the best way to prevent the current coronavirus outbreak is to compound wearing a facemask with the following actions:covering your mouth when coughing or sneezing, washing hands often for at least 20 seconds, avoid touching eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands, avoid sharing items that could be infected and consistently monitor for coronavirus symptoms."SOURCES: Centers for Diseases Control and Prevention, BBC Newshttps://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/guidance-prevent-spread.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-51205344***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/27/3955126/3955126_DB4831E52D1347A88D9CECFBC1A3EC82_200127_3955126_Do_masks_prevent_the_spread_of_the_coronavirus_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, do masks work, how to prevent viral spreading, how to not catch virus, do surgical masks work, china virus outbreak 2020, china virus outbreak, chinese virus, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955449</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus origins still in question</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe number of confirmed cases and deaths from the novel coronavirus infection continues to rise with more than 4,000 confirmed cases in China and a death toll of 106 as of January 28, according to Al Jazeera. The death toll includes its first fatality in Beijing.According to a report published in The Lancet by a group of Chinese researchers, the earliest patient that contracted the virus had not visited the seafood market.The report also notes that the first cases of coronavirus occurred on December 1, 2019. This means the viral disease first began spreading in November 2019, during its incubation period.According to Deutsche Welle, the virus has now reached Germany. The Bavarian Health Ministry reported its first case of coronavirus in Starnberg, a town located 30 kilometers southwest of Munich.The man is in medical isolation and, according to the Bavarian Health Ministry, there is a low risk of infection.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cases and deaths from coronavirus so far2. First case of coronavirus not related to Wuhan market3. Virus may have spread earlier than thought4. Virus spreads to Germany5. Coronavirus symptoms6. Wuhan limits transportation7. Doctors deployed to HubeiVOICEOVER (in English): "The number of confirmed cases and deaths from the novel coronavirus infection continues to rise with more than 4,000 confirmed cases in China and a death toll of 106 as of January 28, according to Al Jazeera." "The death toll includes its first fatality in Beijing.""The virus was believed to have originated from a seafood market in Wuhan, however, according to a report published in The Lancet by a group of Chinese researchers, the earliest patient that contracted the virus had not visited the seafood market.""The report also notes that the first cases of coronavirus occurred on December 1, 2019. This means the viral disease first began spreading in November 2019, during its incubation period.""According to Deutsche Welle, the virus has now reached Germany. The Bavarian Health Ministry reported its first case of coronavirus in Starnberg, a town located 30 kilometers southwest of Munich.""The man is in medical isolation and, according to the Bavarian Health Ministry, there is a low risk of infection.""The symptoms of the novel coronavirus include severe coughing, fever, and difficulty breathing. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.""The city of Wuhan's transportation has been on lockdown since January 27. All flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city have been canceled.""In an effort to aid overcrowded hospitals in Wuhan, National Health Commission Minister Ma Xiaowei told media during a press conference on January 26 that 1,350 doctors had been sent to Hubei province with 1,000 more to come in the following days."SOURCES: The Lancet, Al Jazeera, South China Morning Post, Deutsche Wellehttps://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(20)30183-5/fulltexthttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2020/01/cloneofchina-battles-coronavirus-outbreak-latest-200127233550044.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3047646/no-link-seafood-market-first-case-china-coronavirus-chinesehttps://www.dw.com/en/first-coronavirus-case-confirmed-in-germany/a-52169007***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/28/3955449/3955449_1DFCFB11DEDC4464B0664F7E198F6165_200128_3955449_Wuhan_virus_origins_still_in_question_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, coronavirus, beijing virus, corona virus explained, what is coronavirus, china outbreak, china virus, wuhan virus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955443</guid>
      <title>Rolls-Royce to build mini nuclear reactors in the U.K.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRolls-Royce has announced that it plans to build small modular reactors, or SMRs, and install them in old nuclear sites across the United Kingdom by 2029.The company said they will build approximately 10 to 15 mini nuclear stations. These are expected to last for 60 years.Rolls-Royce explained that these modular reactors will be mass produced while prefabricated components will be delivered onsite in order to reduce costs.Chief technology officer at Rolls-Royce, Paul Stein, told the BBC that lower reactor building costs would eventually lead to cheaper electricity for the public.These nuclear reactors will be roughly 1.5 acres in size, BBC News reports. This is 16 times smaller than the size of Hinkley Point, a major nuclear power station in the United Kingdom.A press release by the company states that one reactor will be able to provide roughly 220 to 440 megawatts of energy which is equivalent to up to 150 onshore wind turbines.Roll-Royce said that it also plans to sell these tiny modular reactors to other foreign countries such as Canada, the U.S. and China.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Small modular reactors2. These will be mass produced and delivered onsite3. Size of the reactors4. How much energy one reactor will provideVOICEOVER (in English): "Rolls-Royce has announced that it plans to build small modular reactors, or SMRs, and install them in old nuclear sites across the United Kingdom by 2029.""The company said they will build approximately 10 to 15 mini nuclear stations. These are expected to last for 60 years.""Rolls-Royce explained that these modular reactors will be mass produced while prefabricated components will be delivered onsite in order to reduce costs.""BBC News reports these nuclear reactors will be roughly 1.5 acres in size." "This is 16 times smaller than the size of Hinkley Point, a major nuclear power station in the United Kingdom.""A press release by the company states that one reactor will be able to provide roughly 220 to 440 megawatts of energy which is equivalent to up to 150 onshore wind turbines."SOURCES: Rolls-Royce, BBC News, Design Boom https://www.rolls-royce.com/https://www.rolls-royce.com/media/press-releases.aspxhttps://www.rolls-royce.com/~/media/Files/R/Rolls-Royce/documents/customers/nuclear/smr-brochure-july-2017.pdfhttps://www.bbc.com/news/business-51233444https://www.designboom.com/design/rolls-royce-nuclear-reactors-generate-power-in-the-uk-01-24-2020/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/28/3955443/3955443_09438A7C866B4CED913BF09A5EAD5886_200128_3955443_Rolls_Royce_to_build_mini_nuclear_reactors_in_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Rolls royce, rolls royce nuclear reactors, rolls royce nuclear reactors UK, mini nuclear reactors, rolls royce nuclear power, rolls royce nuclear power plant, rolls royce nuclear energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955868</guid>
      <title>Japan and United States evacuate their citizens in Wuhan amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to Bloomberg, China has confirmed over 5,900 cases of coronavirus nationwide and at least 132 deaths. About 60 thousand patients are being monitored. The number of confirmed cases now surpasses the number of SARS epidemic in China in 2003.Channel News Asia reports, Japan successfully evacuated 206 of its citizens from Wuhan on Wednesday. All passengers will be tested for the virus and will be asked to stay home until test results are ready.According to CNN, the U.S. has also evacuated 240 American citizens from Wuhan on a flight chartered by the U.S. State Department. There are roughly 1,000 Americans currently trapped in the city of Wuhan.BBC News reports Chinese authorities in Beijing and Shanghai are implementing a 14-day monitoring period for individuals entering the cities from Hubei province, where Wuhan is located.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Total amount of confirmed cases and casualties of coronavirus in China2. Japan evacuates its citizens from Wuhan3. United States evacuates its citizens from Wuhan4. Beijing and Shanghai viral spread preventative methods5. Origin of virus debatable6. Coronavirus symptoms7. Prevention methods for coronavirus spreadVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Bloomberg, China has confirmed over 5,900 cases of coronavirus nationwide and at least 132 deaths. About 60 thousand patients are being monitored. The number of confirmed cases now surpasses the number of SARS epidemic in China in 2003.""Channel News Asia reports, Japan successfully evacuated 206 of its citizens from Wuhan on Wednesday. All passengers will be tested for the virus and will be asked to stay home until test results are ready.""According to CNN, the U.S. has also evacuated 240 American citizens from Wuhan on a flight chartered by the U.S. State Department. There are roughly 1,000 Americans currently trapped in the city of Wuhan.""BBC News reports Chinese authorities in Beijing and Shanghai are implementing a 14-day monitoring period for individuals entering the cities from Hubei province, where Wuhan is located.""A report published in The Lancet by a group of Chinese researchers states that the earliest patient that contracted the virus had not visited Wuhan's seafood market." "The symptoms of the novel coronavirus include severe coughing, fever, and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.""According to the Centers for Disease Control, the best way to prevent spreading or catching the virus is to wear a facemask, cover your mouth when coughing or sneezing, washing your hands often for at least 20 seconds, avoid touching eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands, avoid sharing items that could be infected and consistently monitoring for coronavirus symptoms."SOURCES: Bloomberg, CNA, CBS News, CNN, BBC News, The Lancethttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-29/china-death-toll-climbs-to-132-as-cases-soar-virus-updatehttps://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/japan-us-evacuees-leave-chinese-virus-epicentre-as-toll-spikes-12363384https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/china-coronavirus-outbreak-us-plans-wuhan-evacuation-death-toll-number-cases-rises-today-2020-01-28/https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/28/health/coronavirus-cdc-us-evacuate-americans-china-tuesday/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51275896https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(20)30183-5/fulltext***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 10:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/29/3955868/3955868_863B4F0B6D1047C39E45583C06F87DCA_200129_3955868_Japan_and_United_States_evacuate_their_citizens__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, coronavirus, beijing virus, corona virus explained, what is coronavirus, china outbreak, china virus, wuhan virus, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956368</guid>
      <title>Novel coronavirus vaccine still months away: scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers say previous work on the closely related MERS and SARS could benefit the vaccine development strategy to fight the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak.The University of Michigan's Aubree Gordon and Icahn School of Medicine's Florian Kramer say that nucleic acid vaccine technology, which utilizes viral DNA or RNA material, might lead to a viable vaccine.Writing in an op-ed published in Live Science, the authors explain that making a vaccine involves creating a construct, such as an antigen, that the body's immune system could use to target and attack the virus.A vaccine has to be tested in animal and human trials before it is judged safe and effective.According to the authors, scientists do not have isolated virus samples or enough antibodies for testing the vaccine, and they have not established the animal species suitable for animal trials.The vaccine development process will likely take months to complete.The authors state that better global surveillance of viruses would be important to mitigate future epidemics, as coronavirus, Zika, Ebola and influenza outbreaks have shown.They say novel vaccine technologies that could be quickly adapted to different strains are needed as part of a proactive approach to combating pathogens.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Experience with MERS, SARS and technology could help with making a new vaccine2. Vaccine constructs allow the immune system to attack the virus3. Limiting factors for developing a vaccine would take months to overcome4. Proactive measures to surveil epidemics and develop vaccines are neededVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers say previous work on the closely related MERS and SARS could benefit the vaccine development strategy to fight the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak.""The University of Michigan's Aubree Gordon and Icahn School of Medicine's Florian Kramer say that nucleic acid vaccine technology, which utilizes viral DNA or RNA material, might lead to a viable vaccine.""Writing in an op-ed published in Live Science, the authors explain that making a vaccine involves creating a construct, such as an antigen, that the body's immune system could use to target and attack the virus.""A vaccine has to be tested in animal and human trials before it is judged safe and effective.""According to the authors, scientists do not have isolated virus samples or enough antibodies for testing the vaccine, and they have not established the animal species suitable for animal trials.""The vaccine development process will likely take months to complete.""The authors state that better global surveillance of viruses would be important to mitigate future epidemics, as coronavirus, Zika, Ebola and influenza outbreaks have shown.""They say novel vaccine technologies that could be quickly adapted to different strains are needed as part of a proactive approach to combating pathogens."SOURCES: Live Sciencehttps://www.livescience.com/china-coronavirus-vaccine-update.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/30/3956368/3956368_7A5C7C31121342979971D7572AFCD9DE_200130_3956368_Novel_coronavirus_vaccine_still_months_away__sci_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, vaccine, Wuhan virus vaccine, Wuhan virus, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, coronavirus, beijing virus, corona virus explained, what is coronavirus, china outbreak, china virus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956063</guid>
      <title>Futuristic campus proposed for Tencent headquarters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDutch architectural firm MVRDV has proposed a smart green campus for Tencent's next headquarters in Shenzhen, China.The campus is expected to have a total floor space of 2 million square meters. Sloped buildings throughout the campus will be topped with solar panel roofs, while green terraces would also be present around the smart campus, according to a news release by the architectural firm. The campus' primary means of transport will include autonomous cars and a shuttle bus loop.The smart campus will also feature a conference center in the shape of a rock as well as a spherical information plaza that would display messages for Tencent employees.The futuristic campus is expected to include office space for 80,000 to 100,000 employees and houses for up to 19,000 Tencent employees. The campus will also include amenities such as schools, sports centers and a waterfront park.Designers explained that there would also be metro lines and bus lines that connect the Tencent campus to the rest of Shenzhen.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New smart green campus2. Sustainable features of the campus3. A conference center and an information plaza4. Features of the smart green campusVOICEOVER (in English): "Dutch architectural firm MVRDV has proposed a smart green campus for Tencent's next headquarters in Shenzhen, China.""The campus is expected to have a total floor space of 2 million square meters." "According to a news release by the architectural firm, sloped buildings throughout the campus will be topped with solar panel roofs, while green terraces would also be present around the smart campus.""The campus' primary means of transport will include autonomous cars and a shuttle bus loop.""The smart campus will also feature a conference center in the shape of a rock as well as a spherical information plaza that would display messages for Tencent employees.""The futuristic campus is expected to include office space for 80,000 to 100,000 employees and houses for up to 19,000 Tencent employees.""The campus will also include amenities such as schools, sports centers and a waterfront park."SOURCES: ArchDaily, Design Boom, MVRDV  https://www.archdaily.com/931767/mvrdv-reveals-a-smart-city-proposal-for-the-tencent-headquarters-campus-in-qianhai-bayhttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/mvrdv-tencent-campus-shenzhen-undulating-mountain-range-china-01-13-2020/https://www.mvrdv.nl/news/2503/mvrdvs-tencent-campus-competition-entry-shows-the-green-potential-of-smart-city-technology ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 02:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/20/01/30/3956063/3956063_5AD81147631C45209E8D5843483FD2A8_200130_3956063_Futuristic_campus_proposed_for_Tencent_headquart_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Tencent, tencent, MVRDV, tencent green smart city, futuristic cities, MVRDV shenzhen, MVRDV green smart cities, futuristic cities shenzhen, tencent enormous smart city district]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
