<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3537908</guid>
      <title>Russian jet flies within 5 feet of U.S. Navy plane over Black Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEA Russian fighter jet unsafely intercepted a U.S. Navy surveillance plane, the latest in a series of close calls between the two countries over the Black Sea.According to a press release from the U.S. Naval Forces Europe-Africa, a U.S. EP-3 plane was conducting a reconnaissance mission in international airspace over the Black Sea on Monday when it encountered a Russian aircraft.The Russian military reportedly detected an unidentified aircraft approaching their airspace, and sent a Sukhoi SU-27 fighter jet to intercept it.The SU-27 came within five feet of the U.S. plane, crossing directly in front and causing it to fly through a trail of turbulent air.The intercept lasted a total of 2 hours and 40 minutes.According to the Pentagon, the EP-3 did not do anything to provoke the Russians, and that such actions increase the risk of miscalculation and mid-air collisions.But Russia's Defense Ministry denies any wrongdoing, claiming its jet flew in accordance with international law when it intercepted the U.S. plane, reports CNN.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of U.S. naval plane doing reconnaissance work over Black Sea 2. SU-27 sent to intercept U.S. plane3. SU-27 passed within 5 feet and crossed directly in front of EP-3 4. Intercept lasted for 2 hours, 40 minutesVOICEOVER (in English): "On Monday, a U.S. EP-3 plane was conducting a reconnaissance mission in international airspace over the Black Sea""The Russian military reportedly detected an unidentified aircraft approaching their airspace, and sent a SU-27 to intercept it.""The SU-27 came within five feet of the U.S. plane, crossing directly in front and causing it to fly through a trail of turbulent air.""The intercept lasted for 2 hours and 40 minutes."SOURCES: U.S. Naval Forces Europe-Africa, CNNhttp://www.c6f.navy.mil/news/us-ep-3-intercepted-black-seahttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/29/politics/russia-jet-us-navy-black-sea/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 15:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/30/3537908/3537908_E8324A51CBBB4532B243FA0ADA30F045_180130_3537908_Russian_jet_flies_within_5_feet_of_U_S__Navy_pla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1F9/7F8/1F97F8D6BCB8470A88549789A6C0FA57_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, russian jet, US navy plane, unsafe intercept, SU-27, EP-3, black sea, russian military, US military]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3537818</guid>
      <title>Trump administration considering nationalizing 5G network</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONENational security officials in the Trump administration are considering nationalizing a part of the country's mobile network to protect it against China, Axios reported. A PowerPoint and memo made by a senior National Security Council were obtained by Axios. The documents suggest the U.S. needs a centralized nationwide 5G network within three years. The government could pay for and build a single network or it could have wireless providers build their own 5G networks. The presentation talked about the need to build a network in order to compete with China's dominant position in the manufacture and operation of network infrastructure. The documents say that it would be faster for the government to build a network and then rent access to carriers like AT&T and Verizon.  They also argue that a secure 5G network is vital for the development of emerging technologies like autonomous vehicles or virtual reality, as well as to counter Chinese threats to US economic and cyber security.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. 5G network2. 5G network3. One plan would be for government to build network and then rent out to carriers4. 5G network important for development of emerging technologiesVOICEOVER (in English): "National security officials in the Trump administration are considering nationalizing a part of the country's 5G mobile network to protect it against China.""A PowerPoint and memo obtained by Axios show the government is considering paying for and building a single network or having wireless providers build their own 5G networks." "The documents say that it would be faster for the government to build a network and then rent access to carriers like AT&T and Verizon."  "They also argue that a secure 5G network is vital for the development of technologies like autonomous vehicles or virtual reality, as well as to counter Chinese threats to US economic and cyber security."  SOURCES: AXIOS https://www.axios.com/trump-team-debates-nationalizing-5g-network-f1e92a49-60f2-4e3e-acd4-f3eb03d910ff.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 13:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/30/3537818/3537818_696226EFC2AB41B9B8CA22268B47D40E_180130_3537818_Trump_administration_considering_nationalizing_5_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7A8/2F4/7A82F4B132E9494788803FD68E2D614A_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, 5G network, Trump nationalized 5G network, wireless technology, information infrastructure]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3538475</guid>
      <title>Chinese airlines cancel nearly 200 flights over Taiwan-China dispute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONETaiwan and China are locked in a fierce dispute over new flight routes, with Chinese new year travelers bearing the consequences.Bloomberg reports that China Eastern Airlines and Xiamen Air have cancelled 176 flights during the February 15 to 20 lunar holiday, affecting roughly 50,000 passengers.The Chinese carriers failed to get approval on four flight routes over the Taiwan Strait, which passses within 7.8 kilometers of the country's territorial line at its nearest point.Taiwan says the routes pose a safety threat since they come close to airspace used by Taiwanese commercial and military aircrafts.CNN reports that China Eastern airlines accused Taiwan of "violating the humanitarian needs" of passengers and their families, while China's Civil Aviation Administration condemned authorities for refusing to give approval, according to Bloomberg.But Taiwan says it hadn't been consulted over the routes, as it should have been under a 2015 agreement.Taiwanese passengers have been advised to take other flights, though military planes will be deployed at Taiwan-controlled Kinmen to to transport citizens to the main island.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China Eastern and Xiamen Airlines cancelled 176 flights over Chinese New Year2. Four disputed flight routes passing near Taiwan's airspace3. Depiction of planes coming close to each other4. Taiwan military planes to help transport Taiwanese passengers VOICEOVER (in English): "China Eastern Airlines and Xiamen Air have cancelled 176 flights during the February 15 to 20 Lunar New Year holiday, affecting roughly 50,000 passengers.""The Chinese carriers failed to get approval on four flight routes over the Taiwan strait, which passses within 7.8 kilometers of the country's territorial line at its nearest point.""Taiwan says the routes pose a safety threat since they come close to airspace used by Taiwanese commercial and military aircrafts.""Taiwanese passengers have been advised to take other flights, though military planes will be deployed at Taiwan-controlled Kinmen to to transport citizens to the main island."SOURCES: Bloomberg, Nikkeihttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-01-30/china-eastern-cancels-holiday-flights-amid-dispute-with-taiwanhttps://asia.nikkei.com/Politics-Economy/International-Relations/Strait-denial-Taiwan-says-no-to-China-using-airline-routes***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 10:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/31/3538475/3538475_7CB9CFD655FA49378CE5055AFF05AC4E_180131_3538475_Chinese_airlines_cancel_nearly_200_flights_over__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/36E/B77/36EB7778E7794BF289C9425FA5D42414_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China Taiwan conflict, China Taiwan tension, flight dispute, flight routes, cancelled flights, chinese new year, lunar new year]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3538423</guid>
      <title>'Zombie' NASA satellite found by civilian astronomer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEA long-lost NASA "zombie" satellite has been found by an civilian astronomer after being missing for more than a decade.A signal from a NASA "zombie" satellite, lost in 2005, was detected last week by amateur radio astronomer, reported the Smithsonian Mag. Scott Tilley received a signal from a spacecraft numbered 2000-017A, 26113. That's NASA's missing IMAGE satellite.After being launched in 2000 by the space agency, the satellite was thought long gone after scientists lost contact with it in 2005. The satellite was sent into space to investigate Earth's magnetosphere, the space around our planet controlled by our planetary magnetic field.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of signal being shown to be IMAGE satellite2. Depiction of IMAGE satellite sending signal3. Depiction of Earth's magnetosphere and IMAGE satelliteVOICEOVER (in English): "Scott Tilley received a signal from a spacecraft numbered 2000-017A, 26113. That's NASA's missing IMAGE satellite.""After being launched in 2000 by the space agency, the satellite was thought to be long gone after scientists lost contact with it in 2005.""The satellite was sent into space to investigate Earth's magnetosphere, the space around our planet controlled by our planetary magnetic field".SOURCES: Riddles in the Sky (astronomy blog), Smithsonian Mag, NASA, Science Mag, Chron.comhttps://skyriddles.wordpress.com/2018/01/21/nasas-long-dead-image-satellite-is-alive/#more-32https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/long-lost-nasa-satellite-found-amateur-astronomer-180967974/https://image.gsfc.nasa.govhttp://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/01/amateur-astronomer-discovers-revived-nasa-satellitehttps://www.chron.com/news/science-environment/article/Amateur-astronomer-discovers-long-lost-NASA-12534624.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/31/3538423/3538423_86CFCA5DCB5D4A3CBD31017EB8A88251_180131_3538423__Zombie__NASA_satellite_found_by_civilian_astron_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A0C/38C/A0C38CDBFBBD40F996F5A01BF1DAE4BB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, zombie satellite, zombie nasa satellite, zombies, nasa, lost nasa satellite, nasa satellite, IMAGE satellite, zuma satellite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3538362</guid>
      <title>Underwater sound waves could help early tsunami detection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEMathematicians may have devised a way to calculate the size and force of a tsunami well in advance, using underwater sound waves.A tsunami is a series of waves caused by the displacement of a large volume of water. Waves can surge as high as 100 feet and devastate coastal areas, reports Scientific American.Tsunamis are mainly caused by underwater earthquakes and are currently detected using pressure sensors and buoys. However, the system relies on a tsunami physically reaching a buoy to trigger an alarm.Scientists at Cardiff University in Wales have found that an early warning system can be developed by using a hydrophone to record acoustic gravity waves radiating from an earthquake.The waves carry information about the earthquake and can be used to determine the characteristics of a forthcoming tsunami, allowing for early detection.In the future, the team aims to be able to activate a tsunami alarm in near real-time, within seconds of recording the signals.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of a tsunami 2. Depiction of current tsunami warning system3. Hydrophone detecting acoustic gravity waves after a tsunami trigger event4. Acoustic gravity waves can help scientists identify tsunami characteristicsVOICEOVER (in English): "A tsunami is a series of waves caused by the displacement of a large volume of water. Waves can surge as high as 100 feet and devastate coastal areas.""Tsunamis are mainly caused by underwater earthquakes and are currently detected using pressure sensors and buoys. However, the system relies on a tsunami physically reaching a buoy to trigger an alarm.""Scientists at Cardiff University in Wales have found that an early warning system can be developed by using a hydrophone to record acoustic gravity waves radiating from an earthquake.""The waves carry information about the earthquake and can be used to determine the characteristics of a forthcoming tsunami, allowing for early detection."SOURCES: BBC, Scientific Americanhttp://www.bbc.com/news/uk-wales-south-east-wales-42803111https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/new-real-time-tsunami-early-warning-system-calculates-size-and-distance-using-underwater-sound-waves/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 08:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/31/3538362/3538362_E77411FC1A524D369912B1E0E8449F50_180131_3538362_Underwater_sound_waves_could_help_early_tsunami__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/357/AB6/357AB61ADA4A4BF1A7FDE57E09A29501_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tsunami, tsunami warning, early tsunami warning, tsunami detection, natural disaster, sound waves, early warning system, hydrophone, dart buoys]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3538280</guid>
      <title>Astronauts feces could be recycled to make food</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers are developing a system that uses microbes and human waste to make food. In the future, astronauts traveling to Mars will need to recycle and reuse as much as possible, including their feces, CNET reported.Scientists from Penn State University have been able to create a substance, as geosciences professor Christopher House describes as "a little bit like Marmite or Vegemite where you're eating a smear of 'microbial goo.'"The system introduces microbes into the waste, which then break it down through anaerobic digestion. The researchers then took the methane released during the process to grow the microbe Methylococcus capsulatus, which is used in animal feed and is a good source of protein and fat. The research was partly funded by a NASA grant, as the agency looks for creative solutions for eventual manned missions to Mars. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Spaceship flying towards Mars2. Spaceship landing on Mars surface3. System adds microbes to waste to break it down through anaerobic digestion4. Methane produced is used to grow Methylococcus capsulatusVOICEOVER (in English): "In the future, astronauts traveling to Mars will need to recycle and reuse as much as possible, including their feces." "Researchers are developing a system that uses microbes and human waste to make food for astronauts on long-haul missions."  "The system introduces microbes into the waste, which then break it down through anaerobic digestion." "The methane released during the process is then used to grow the microbe Methylococcus capsulatus, which is used in animal feed and is a good source of protein and fat." SOURCES: CNEThttps://www.cnet.com/news/nasa-astronauts-poop-waste-food-microbes-penn-state/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 07:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/31/3538280/3538280_F2DA7EB1082346B1BA5F111CD4455ECD_180131_3538280_Astronauts_feces_could_be_recycled_to_make_food_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E04/FFD/E04FFD5153D341BAA74E6430A06763F7_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Mars missions, astronauts recycle waste, astronauts recycle human waste, Mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3539257</guid>
      <title>Samsung confirms its making cryptocurrency mining chips</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSamsung Electronics has made a chip designed to specifically mine for cryptocurrency. The company made the disclosure in its latest earnings report, the BBC reported. Samsung's foundry business is manufacturing an Application Specific Integrated Circuit (ASIC), which is a specialized processor custom-designed to mine for cryptocurrency. Mining refers to the solving of complex mathematical equations as a way to verify cryptocurrency transactions. People who use their computers to mine are given digital coins in exchange.Korean media claims the company made the move as a joint venture with an unnamed Chinese distribution firm, according to TechCrunch.  Samsung already produces high-capacity memory chips for GPUs (graphics processing unit), which are used for computer graphics but are also used to mine cryptocurrency.  According to Korean paper The Bell, the tech giant began mass producing the chip earlier this month. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chip manufacturing lab producing ASIC chips2. Cryptocurrency mining3. Cryptocurrency miners are rewarded with digital coins4. Chip manufacturing labVOICEOVER (in English): "Samsung is manufacturing an Application Specific Integrated Circuit (ASIC), which is a custom-designed processor with the single task of mining for cryptocurrency." "Mining refers to the solving of complex mathematical equations as a way to verify cryptocurrency transactions." "People who use their computers to mine are given digital coins in exchange.""According to Korean media, Samsung began mass-producing the ASIC chips earlier this month." SOURCES: BBC, TechCrunchhttp://www.bbc.com/news/technology-42892380https://techcrunch.com/2018/01/31/samsung-confirms-asic-chips/?ncid=rss***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/01/3539257/3539257_2383BBEA159F4DE6934A2D6F869BC121_180201_3539257_Samsung_confirms_its_making_cryptocurrency_minin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DF9/6F8/DF96F81A2DD240468F1721E53A941687_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency mining chips, Samsung ASIC mining chips, Samsung ASIC chips, Samsung cryptocurrency chips]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3539024</guid>
      <title>What happens if Earth's magnetic poles switch?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEEarth's magnetic poles change position every few hundred thousand years.Earth's rotation around its core generates a magnetic field around the planet. This field creates two magnetic poles. Unlike the the geographical south and north poles which remain affixed, the magnetic poles are constantly shifting.Writing in The Conversation in January 2017, scientists from the University of Leeds said a reversal of the poles could happen in the next 2,000 years. They warn such events are difficult to predict, but speculate such an event could lead to multiple poles and a weakened magnetic field.This would allow more radiation to pass through onto the planet and could also impact the planet's electrical and electronic infrastructure.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Earth, its core and magnetic field2. Depiction of Earth and magnetic field3. Depiction of new poles created by magnetic reversal4. Depiction of what a reversal would impactVOICEOVER (in English): "Earth's rotation around its planetary core generates a magnetic field around the planet.'" "This field creates two magnetic poles.""Unlike the the geographical south and north poles which remain affixed, the magnetic poles are constantly shifting.""Writing in the Conversation, scientists from the University of Leeds say a reversal of the poles could happen in the next 2,000 years.""They warn such events are difficult to predict, but speculate such an event could lead to multiple poles and a weakened magnetic field ""This would allow more radiation to pass through onto the planet and could also impact the planet's electrical and electronic infrastructure."SOURCES: International Business Times, The Conversation, NASAhttp://www.ibtimes.co.uk/earths-magnetic-poles-could-be-about-flip-serious-consequences-humanity-1657368https://theconversation.com/why-the-earths-magnetic-poles-could-be-about-to-swap-places-and-how-it-would-affect-us-71910https://www.nasa.gov/topics/earth/features/2012-poleReversal.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/vision/earth/lookingatearth/29dec_magneticfield.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 05:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/01/3539024/3539024_35D9C21D8F664D6DB2BC7074442426F2_180201_3539024_What_happens_if_Earth_s_magnetic_poles_switch__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1FC/8A2/1FC8A23CA2A34E6F9CE5133BE50E0B4F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  magnetic pole flip, magnetic pole reversal, what happens when the Earth's magnetic field flips, NASA, Earth, Earth magnetic field, south pole, north pole]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3540389</guid>
      <title>New cancer 'vaccine' completely eliminates tumors in mice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANStanford University researchers successfully used immune stimulators to eliminate cancerous tumors.T-cells that defend against cancer often end up overpowered by the disease, but scientists find they can be rejuvenated using CpG oligonucleotides and anti-OX40 antibodies, according to the Stanford University School of Medicine.When a microgram of the the immune-stimulating agents were injected directly into mouse tumors, the growths disappeared in about 10 days.CpG activates dendritic cells that help against tumor counterattacks, while anti-OX40 antibodies stimulate T-cells into attacking the cancer.Once a tumor is destroyed, the cells move through the body to find and eliminate other similar growths.The experiment eradicated lymphoma in 87 out of 90 mice, and also worked on breast, colon, and melanoma cancers.The team is looking to start clinical trials to see if the treatment will be as successful in humans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of immune cells attacking a cancerous tumor, 2. Tumor injected directly with two immuno boosters disappeared in 10 days3. Immuno boosters activate different immune cells to fight cancer4. Cells move throughout body to eliminate other tumors of the same type or strainVOICEOVER (in English): "T-cells that defend against cancer often end up overpowered by the disease, but scientists find they can be rejuvenated using CpG oligonucleotides and anti-OX40 antibodies.""When a microgram of the the immune-stimulating agents were injected directly into mouse tumors, the growths disappeared in about 10 days.""CpG activates dendritic cells that help against tumor counterattacks, while anti-OX40 antibodies stimulate T-cells into attacking the cancer.""Once a tumor is destroyed, the cells move through the body to find and eliminate other similar growths." SOURCES: Science, Stanford University School of Medicinehttp://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/01/injection-helps-immune-system-obliterate-tumors-least-micehttp://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2018/01/cancer-vaccine-eliminates-tumors-in-mice.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/02/3540389/3540389_6DAB80B720844D179F91CBFD0E695333_180202_3540389_New_cancer__vaccine__completely_eliminates_tumor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7C8/0B8/7C80B83A5C874518B6FCA31420BF0156_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cancer treatment, cancer cure, cancer vaccine, immunotherapy, cure for cancer, cancer, cancer cells, tumor, immuno boosters, vaccine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3540379</guid>
      <title>Mass Surveillance at Super Bowl LII</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThousands of security cameras and police officers will be watching out for public safety at this weekend's Super Bowl in Minneapolis.Law enforcement will be watching fans through the lenses of some 2,000 fixed surveillance cameras, reports the Pioneer Press. Around 3,000 police officers will be deployed on the day, with 2,000 carrying smartphones. Those devices are equipped with a video application that'll let officers record and broadcast any suspicious activity to a command center. There, 80 staff from various law enforcement agencies will monitor public safety across Minneapolis. According to Pioneer Press, command center officials will watch the movements of officers in real-time by tracking blue and white badges on a map. Officials will also be able to monitor and deal with most incidents within the U.S. Bank Stadium via enhanced surveillance technology.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Minneapolis, U.S. Bank Stadium and number of security cameras2. Depiction of police officers, watching and recording fans with the smartphone app3. Depiction of officials at command center monitoring events4. Depiction of how the command center tracks officer movement in Minneapolis on game day and monitors the U.S. Bank StadiumVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Twin Cities, Fox 9 KMSP-TV, CBS Minnesotahttps://www.twincities.com/2018/01/30/be-on-your-best-behavior-because-thousands-of-security-cameras-will-show-super-bowl-activity/http://www.fox9.com/news/309913809-videohttp://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/01/31/super-bowl-security-3/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/02/3540379/3540379_25ACA09A0E69427F85489D1F44D95394_180202_3540379_Mass_Surveillance_at_Super_Bowl_LII_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0D7/812/0D7812E27C944D28B6B77B64E2283F8B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Super Bowl 52 stadium, Super Bowl 52, Super Bowl security, surveillance operation, public safety operations, Super Bowl 2018, Super Bowl Sunday]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3540288</guid>
      <title>Cape Town</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCape Town is running out of water and implemented new water restrictions on Thursday.Residents are being asked to reduce their daily water use to 50 liters down from an already restricted 87 liters, CNN reported.  Officials are predicting if reservoir levels continue to fall as expected, Cape Town will run dry by April 16, which is being called "Day Zero." With 50 liters, a person could use 18 liters for dishes & laundry, 15 liters for a 90 second shower, 9 liters for one toilet flush, 3 liters for hygiene, 2 liters for cooking, 2 liters for drinking water and 1 liter for pets. Several factors have contributed to the water crisis. The city has been experiencing a three year drought. Some residents have also not cut back on their water use. Only around 55 percent of Capetonians have been sticking to their water allowance, according to South African officials. The city is now working to improve its water infrastructure by rushing to construct desalination, aquifer and water-recycling projects. If the government declares Day Zero, water will be shut off for the city until it rains again. Residents will only be allowed 25 liters, to be collected from one of 200 stations.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Daily water allowance reduced to 50 liters per day 2. Person washing dishes, showering, flushing toilet3. Person washing hands, cooking, drinking and giving water to pet4. Cape Town is working on desalination, aquifer and water recycling projectsVOICEOVER (in English): "Cape Town is running out of water and implemented new water restrictions Thursday, reducing the previous 87-liter limit to 50 liters per day.""With 50 liters, a person could theoretically use 18 liters for dishes & laundry, 15 liters for a 90 second shower, 9 liters for one toilet flush, 3 liters for hygiene, 2 liters for cooking, 2 liters for drinking water and 1 liter for pets." "The city is now working to improve its water infrastructure by rushing to construct desalination, aquifer and water-recycling projects." SOURCES: CNN, REUTERShttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/01/africa/cape-town-water-crisis-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-drought-lesotho/south-africas-water-crisis-spreads-from-cape-town-idUSKBN1FK27A***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/02/3540288/3540288_B742E7EEA3A6491A86A85EB16C9ACEC9_180202_3540288_Cape_Town_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6D3/E34/6D3E34822FC94004BAA99E213568344D_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Cape Town, Cape Town water crisis, Cape Town drought, Cape Town Day Zero, Cape Town water allowance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3539928</guid>
      <title>Chinese researchers grow new ears for children with microtia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEChinese researchers have successfully grown ears for five children with microtia, using a procedure that used the kids' own cells.According to the U.S. National Library of Medicine, microtia is a congenital deformity of the ear, the severity of which ranges from structural abnormalities to a complete absence of the external ear.The typical treatment for microtia is reconstructive surgery, often through rib cartilage ear reconstruction, or silicone prosthetic ears.CNN reports that according to a new study in China, scientists grew ears via a biodegradable scaffold that replicates the patient's normal ear. Cells from the microtia ear were seeded into the scaffold and cultured for three months.The new ears were then implanted to reconstruct ears in five patients, and monitored for up to two and a half years.While the idea itself is not novel, what's groundbreaking is that the scientists were able to carry out the procedure successfully in a series of patients, and had long-term results to boot.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of microtia2. Depiction of typical microtia reconstructive treatments3. Depiction of Chinese scientists growing ears4. New ears implanted in five childrenVOICEOVER (in English): "Microtia is a congenital deformity of the ear, the severity of which ranges from structural abnormalities to a complete absence of the external ear.""The typical treatment for microtia is reconstructive surgery, often through rib cartilage ear reconstruction, or silicone prosthetic ears.""In China, scientists grew ears via a biodegradable scaffold that replicates the patient's normal ear. Cells from the microtia ear were seeded into the scaffold and cultured for three months.""The new ears were then implanted to reconstruct ears in five patients, and monitored for up to two and a half years."SOURCES: CNN, U.S. National Library of Medicine, EbioMedicinehttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/29/health/growing-ears-on-humans-study/index.htmlhttps://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3482263/http://www.ebiomedicine.com/article/S2352-3964(18)30016-1/fulltext***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 07:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/02/3539928/3539928_B3CD85CBE388462380EDBEDAF3C37D66_180202_3539928_Chinese_researchers_grow_new_ears_for_children_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/042/61F/04261FE3821641E9A23376A9638DD34F_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, microtia, ear defect, deformed ears, growing ears, cultured ears, reconstructive surgery ear implants, prosthetic ears, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3541960</guid>
      <title>Amtrak train crashes into parked freight train, killing 2 and injuring 116</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo people are dead and dozens more injured after an Amtrak collided into a freight train early Sunday  the second deadly Amtrak crash in less than a week.The Washington Post reports that the accident occurred around 2:35 a.m. in Cayce, South Carolina, as Amtrak train 91 was travelling from New York to Miami with 139 passengers and 9 crew members onboard.Freight giant CSX managed tracks in the area, but had dispatchers manually routing trains since signal systems were down. Amtrak 91 was cleared to pass a railroad switch and continue straight down the main line, but the switch was set in the wrong position. Instead of heading straight, the train was diverted into a side track, where it crashed into a stationary freight train.The impact destroyed several freight cars and caused the Amtrak train to derail. Two crew members were killed and 116 passengers wounded in the collision.The National Transportation Safety Board is currently looking into the crash, and will focus its investigation on why the rail switch was lined and locked toward the siding.So far, officials have recovered the front-facing video camera from the Amtrak train, but have been unable to retrieve the event data recorders from either train due to the catastrophic damage.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of train location, route, and number of passengers2. Depiction of Amtrak train going straight through the main line3. Depiction of rail switch diverting train, causing it to crash into parked train4. Depiction of crash aftermath, number of casualtiesVOICEOVER (in English): "The accident occurred in Cayce, South Carolina, as Amtrak train 91 was travelling from New York to Miami with 139 passengers and 9 crew members onboard.""Freight giant CSX managed tracks in the area, but had dispatchers manually routing trains since signal systems were down. Amtrak 91 was cleared to go straight down the main line...""...but the way the railroad switch was aligned meant the train was instead diverted into a side track, where it crashed into a stationary freight train.""The impact destroyed several freight cars and caused the Amtrak train to derail. 2 crew members were killed and 116 passengers wounded in the collision."SOURCES: Washington Post, Reuters, NBChttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/dr-gridlock/wp/2018/02/04/at-least-2-dead-after-amtrak-train-collides-with-freight-train-in-south-carolina/?utm_term=.191ae55572echttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-train/two-dead-more-than-100-injured-in-amtrak-crash-in-south-carolina-idUSKBN1FO0CBhttps://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/New-York-Miami-Amtrak-Train-Collides-with-CSX-Train-in-South-Carolina-Injuries-Reported-472588173.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 09:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/05/3541960/3541960_BE214127B6CA497BA04F57530F5051C2_180205_3541960_Amtrak_train_crashes_into_parked_freight_train___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9C4/12B/9C412B693FBE4DA8AF2A4467D7B3E419_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, amtrak crash, amtrak, amtrak freight crash, train crash, amtrak derailment, wrong track, railroad switch, csx, diverted train, side track, south carolina train crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3541901</guid>
      <title>Venezuela to launch oil-backed cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVenezuela announced that is will enter the cryptocurrency market with its launch of the "petro," backed by oil reserves. The petro will be backed by oil, gas, gold and diamond reserves, President Nicolas Maduro said on Sunday, Reuters reported. Maduro said the government will issue 100 million tokens, each valued at the price of one barrel of Venezuelan crude. That would value the petro issuance at just over $6 billion, according to CNBC. The government said the cryptocurrency will help the cash-strapped nation make financial transactions and overcome U.S. sanctions against the country. Venezuela's actual currency  the bolivar  is in a freefall, with the nation in need of basic necessities like food and medicine. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Oil pumps and petro coin2. Petro coin will be backed by oil, gas, gold and diamond reserves3. 100 million petro coins will be issued4. The petro may help the country complete financial transactionsVOICEOVER (in English): "Venezuela announced that is will enter the cryptocurrency market with its launch of the 'petro' digital coin.""According to President Nicolas Maduro, the petro will be backed by oil, gas, gold and diamond reserves.""Maduro said the government will issue 100 million tokens, each valued at the price of one barrel of Venezuelan crude. That would value the petro issuance at just over $6 billion.""The government said the cryptocurrency will help the cash-strapped nation make financial transactions and overcome U.S. sanctions against the country." SOURCES: Reuters, CNBC https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-economy/enter-the-petro-venezuela-to-launch-oil-backed-cryptocurrency-idUSKBN1DX0SQhttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/01/31/venezuela-says-will-pre-sell-petro-cryptocurrency-on-feb-20.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 08:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/05/3541901/3541901_5E1B35AFAE444B9C88FC7ED0B7C354F8_180205_3541901_Venezuela_to_launch_oil_backed_cryptocurrency_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4FB/428/4FB428C13B774AC0AD6288FBFE17A341_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Venezuela cryptocurrency, Venezuela petro cyptrocurrency, Venezuela petro issuance, digital currency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3541817</guid>
      <title>Africa launches single aviation market</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAfrica is finally taking a big step towards freeing their skies for air travel, nearly three decades after it was first proposed.CNN reports that 23 African countries have signed on to the Single African Air Transport Market initiative, or SAATM, which was launched by the African Union on January 28. 32 other AU member countries have yet to join.Africans make up 17% of the world population, but only 2-4 percent of global air travelers. Flights within the continent are often inconvenient and time-consuming.But with the single air market, more direct routes are expected to open up between African countries, with lower ticket prices.The increased service will result in more jobs, and a boost in intra-African trade and tourism could generate millions in additional spending.The aviation initiative is part of the Agenda 2063 project, which aims for a unified Africa.It successfully pushed for relaxed visa rules for citizens in several countries, and is now working to launch an African Union passport for all Africans by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 23 signatories of  African Union's Single African Air Transport Market2. Travel within Africa inconvenient and time-consuming3. African single air market to open up direct routes, lower ticket prices4. Economic benefits of African single air marketVOICEOVER (in English): "Twenty-three African countries have signed on to the Single African Air Transport Market initiative launched by the African Union on January 28.""Africans make up 17% of the world population, but only 2 to 4% of global air travelers. Flights within the continent are often inconvenient and time-consuming.""But with the single air market, more direct routes are expected to open up between African countries, with lower ticket prices.""The increased service will result in more jobs, and a boost in intra-African trade and tourism could generate millions in additional spending."SOURCES: African Union, IATA, CNNhttps://au.int/sites/default/files/newsevents/workingdocuments/33100-wd-6a-brochure_on_single_african_air_transport_market_english.pdfhttp://www.iata.org/policy/promoting-aviation/Documents/single-african-air-transport-market.pdfhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/31/africa/african-union-single-air-airline/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/05/3541817/3541817_7D22C85D3C4E4A2F9B92E419E03EAC1A_180205_3541817_Africa_launches_single_aviation_market_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/317/A9E/317A9EB461A04A2B99AEDACF26AB0C7F_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, africa travel, african union, single african air transport market, SAATM, AU, africa open skies, african airlines, free skies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3542814</guid>
      <title>Large comet may have triggered mini ice age on Earth 13,000 years ago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found evidence that a huge event thousands of years ago may have caused a climate shift that greatly affected the evolution of life on Earth.Newsweek reports that according to a new two-part study published in the Journal of Geology, fragments of a large, disintegrating comet struck the Earth and triggered a massive firestorm some 12,800 years ago.The fires produced thick clouds of smoke and dust that covered the sky and cut off sunlight, causing the climate to cool rapidly and triggering a mini ice age.The cold climate lasted for a thousand years, killing off plants and many large animal species, and causing human populations to decline.Researchers came up with the impact theory after examining samples from 170 sites around the world, with chemical signatures indicating that 10% of the land surface was on fire.Analysis of pollen levels also suggests that pine forests had burned off and been replaced by poplar trees, a species that grows in barren ground.The theory is theorized to be the trigger event for the Younger Dryas period, a climate anomaly which saw gradual warming suddenly reverse.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of comet fragments striking Earth2. Depiction of smoke from fires blocking sunlight, mini ice age3. Depiction of effect on plants, animals, humans4. Depiction of research samples examined5. Depiction of pollen analysis and findingsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study, fragments of a large, disintegrating comet struck Earth and triggered a massive firestorm some 12,800 years ago.""The fires produced thick clouds of smoke and dust that covered the sky and cut off sunlight, causing the climate to cool rapidly and triggering a mini ice age.""The cold climate lasted for a thousand years, killing off plants and many large animal species, and causing human populations to decline.""Researchers came up with the impact theory after examining samples from sites around the world, with chemical signatures indicating that 10% of the land surface was on fire."SOURCES: University of Kansas, Newsweekhttps://news.ku.edu/2018/01/30/new-research-suggests-toward-end-ice-age-human-beings-witnessed-fires-larger-dinosaurhttp://www.newsweek.com/comet-earth-ice-age-799236***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 11:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/06/3542814/3542814_5DB27559E8B44E2F8A408922730AA3E6_180206_3542814_Large_comet_may_have_triggered_mini_ice_age_on_E_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/17C/05B/17C05BA7D414479FABA36ADB55BDA8FE_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, comet, mini ice age, cosmic impact, impact hypothesis, ice age, firestorm, comet hits earth, younger dryas, impact theory, extinct animals, animal extinction, climate]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3542427</guid>
      <title>How eruptions can lower global temperatures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe New York Times reports NASA is developing plans to study how eruptions cool the planet.The plan involves sending high-altitude balloons into the air to observe a volcanic eruption event. When sulfur dioxide from an eruption mixes with airborne water vapor, the two create aerosols that reflect sunlight.In 1991, a volcanic eruption in the Philippines sent 20 million tons of sulfur dioxide planet's atmosphere. As a result, global temperatures cooled by one degrees centigrade.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of eruption2. Depiction of NASA's air balloon plan3. Depiction of sulfur dioxide and water reflecting sunlight4. Overview of 1991 Philippines eruption and impact on global temperatureVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: New York Times, JSTOR, Tech Timeshttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/02/01/climate/volcano-geoengineering.htmlhttps://daily.jstor.org/can-single-volcano-cool-earth/http://www.techtimes.com/articles/220300/20180203/can-volcanoes-help-cool-the-earth-scientists-are-preparing-for-the-next-big-eruption.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 02:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/06/3542427/3542427_1E05EB70F57E4699B5DF5D318EA0AB0A_180206_3542427_How_eruptions_can_lower_global_temperatures_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FC6/6A8/FC66A8D0A0B742DDA04A5CA59477472E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, volcanoes and global warming, volcanoes, how volcanoes cool the climate, climate change and eruptions, volcanoes and climate change, nasa, volcano research]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3543774</guid>
      <title>Tesla, South Australia to build world's largest virtual power plant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe South Australia government has announced plans to install rooftop solar panel systems and Tesla Powerwall-2 batteries in 50,000 residential homes over the next four years.The equipment generate power and provide electricity for each home, while collectively forming a virtual power plant with a 250-megawatt capacity.Any excess energy will feed into the main power grid, to be used to supply electricity to other homes, or during an emergency.Participants will still need to pay for any electricity they use, but will save 30% on their electric bill. Their homes will also be protected from blackouts.The first trial for the project is currently ongoing, with systems being installed at Housing Trust homes first, before being offered to other South Australian households.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tesla solar panels and batteries to be fitted onto 50,000 homes2. Depiction of how the solar panels and batteries work3. Excess electricity from each home feeds into main power grid4. Homes save on electricity costs, protected from blackoutsVOICEOVER (in English): "The South Australia government will be installing rooftop solar panel systems and Tesla Powerwall-2 batteries in 50,000 residential homes over the next four years.""The equipment generate power and provide electricity for each home, while collectively forming a virtual power plant with a 250-megawatt capacity.""Any excess energy will feed into the main power grid, to be used to supply electricity to other homes, or during an emergency.""Participants will still need to pay for any electricity they use, but will save 30% on their electric bill. Their homes will also be protected from blackouts."SOURCES: Government of South Australiahttp://ourenergyplan.sa.gov.au/virtual-power-plant***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 10:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/07/3543774/3543774_5793719A839A4AFBB5972E5D6772B758_180207_3543774_Tesla__South_Australia_to_build_world_s_largest__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9EC/9D1/9EC9D12EAECF429D936DDC0868B24523_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, virtual power plant, solar power, power plant, power grid, world's largest, Tesla, South Australia, solar panels, powerwall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3543753</guid>
      <title>Taiwan 6.4-magnitude earthquake leaves at least 2 dead, more than 200 injured</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA 6.4-magnitude earthquake off the eastern coast of Taiwan has left at least two people dead and more than 200 injured.  The quake struck at 11:50 local time 18.3 km off the coast of Hualien, at a depth of 10 kilometers, according to the Taiwan's Central Weather Bureau.  At least five buildings have collapsed, two bridges are closed and sections of two highways have been temporarily closed to traffic, the Taiwan News reported. Around 40,000 homes are without water. The basement and ground floor of the 10-story Marshal Hotel collapsed after the quake. One staff member was rescued, while two others are still trapped. Government agencies and the army have been called in for emergency rescues. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Time and location of the earthquake2. 5 buildings collapsed, 2 bridges are closed and 2 highway sections are closed3. Basement and ground floor of the Marshal Hotel collapsed4. First responders rescuing peopleVOICEOVER (in English): "A 6.4-magnitude earthquake struck at 11:50 local time 18.3 km off the coast from Hualien, at a depth of 10 kilometers, leaving at least 2 dead and over 200 injured.""At least five buildings have collapsed, two bridges are closed and sections of two highways have been temporarily closed to traffic.""The basement and ground floor of the 10-story Marshal Hotel collapsed after the quake." "Government agencies and the army have been called in for emergency rescues." SOURCES: Taiwan News, CNN, BBChttps://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3358134https://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/06/world/taiwan-earthquake/index.htmlhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-42966916***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 09:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/07/3543753/3543753_45DCB407253A4BE8AB07F08C986FBDD6_180207_3543753_Taiwan_6_4_magnitude_earthquake_leaves_at_least__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/41C/85B/41C85B7FBF2241C1B01D79C751D3F805_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Taiwan earthquake, Hualien earthquake, building collapse, bridges closed, emergency responders]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3543648</guid>
      <title>Archaeologist find Mayan mega city</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of archaeologists have visualized an ancient Mayan mega city using laser scanning.National Geographic reports that researchers have uncovered an the 800 square mile settlement in northern Guatemala.Archaeologists used light detection and ranging technology, more commonly called LiDAR, to uncover the area. According to the National Ocean Service LiDAR is a remote sensing method use a combination of light, aircraft and pulse lasers to measure and visualize 3D structures.This let them remove the surrounding environment to show the scale of the interconnected area. Researcher found some 60,000 structures and said the area was home to millions of people.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of area2. Depiction of area being visualized3. Depiction of areaVOICEOVER (in English): "National Geographic reports that researchers have uncovered an ancient 800 square mile Mayan mega city in northern Guatemala.""Archaeologists used light detection and ranging technology, more commonly called LiDAR, to uncover the area."According to the National Ocean Service, LiDAR is a remote-sensing method that uses a combination of light, aircraft and pulse lasers to measure and visualize 3D structures.""This lets them remove the surrounding environment to show the scale of the interconnected area. "Researchers found some 60,000 structures and said the area was home to millions of people."SOURCES: National Geographic, Newsweek, National Ocean Servicehttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/02/maya-laser-lidar-guatemala-pacunam/http://www.newsweek.com/hidden-ancient-mayan-megalopolis-60000-structures-discovered-guatemala-using-797865https://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/lidar.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 08:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/07/3543648/3543648_174ED01286E741BA8AC8E1A66157F677_180207_3543648_Archaeologist_find_Mayan_mega_city_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/317/0F5/3170F5D5D9B744CEB55A28A7148DC80A_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mayan city, guatemala, Ancient Mayan city found in jungle, mayan city found, liDAR technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3544622</guid>
      <title>Smart TV hacking exploit discovered</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSmart TVs from Samsung and TCL were shown to be vulnerable to hacking exploits, according to an investigation by Consumer Reports.The publication says it tested sets from Sony, Samsung, LG, TCL Roku, and Vizio against hacks.  In the Samsung and TCL Roku models, they found that the hackers could gain remote control of the television and play videos, adjust volume, install apps and disconnect it from the Wi-Fi network.  Both companies told Consumer Reports they are investigating the claims. In a blog post, Roku said the publication "got it wrong" and said there was "no security risk."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of hacker sending out exploit2. Depiction of hacker gaining access to TV via exploit and Wi-Fi network3. Depiction of which TV features can be hackedVOICEOVER (in English): According to Consumer Reports, a user may become a victim of a smart-TV hack when they download apps or visit websites with malicious code.If a user's device becomes compromised while connected to the same network as the TV, then a hacker maybe able to gain access to a vulnerable smart TV.Consumer Reports said they discovered exploits in Samsung and TLC Roku Smart televisions. This would let hackers play unwanted videos, adjust volume, install apps and even disconnect the TV from the Wi-Fi network.  SOURCES: Consumer Reports, Roku, USA Todayhttps://www.consumerreports.org/televisions/samsung-roku-smart-tvs-vulnerable-to-hacking-consumer-reports-finds/https://blog.roku.com/consumer-reports-got-wronghttps://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2018/02/07/your-smart-tv-may-prey-hackers-and-collecting-more-info-than-you-realize-consumer-reports-warns/311903002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 09:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/08/3544622/3544622_9C0BCA3704064D6CB727334E942CCF55_180208_3544622_Smart_TV_hacking_exploit_discovered_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/03D/382/03D38236754B4436A50243142816EFB5_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hacking into smart tv, smart tv hack, tv hack 2018, consumer reports tv hack, samsung tv hack, roku tv hack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3544484</guid>
      <title>Certain foods may influence cancer growth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that breast tumors in mice struggled without the nutrient asparagine in their diets. The study, published in the journal Nature, looked at mice with an aggressive form of breast cancer. Asparagine is found in asparagus, poultry, seafood and many other foods, according to the BBC. It is an amino acid, a key building block of protein. Scientists from the Cancer Research UK Cambridge Institute found that when mice were given a low-asparagine diet or asparagine blocking drugs, tumor growth struggled in the mice. "In the future, by modifying a patient's diet or by using drugs that change the way that tumor cells can access these nutrients we hope to improve outcomes in therapy," said Prof. Greg Hannon, the BBC reported. Cancer tumors become deadly when the cancer spreads throughout the body (metastasises). Cancer cells need to go through considerable changes before they can spread throughout the body. Researchers believe it is this process for which asparagine is needed, however further studies are needed. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cancerous lab mice with asparagine taken out of their diets2. Asparagine is found in foods like asparagus, poultry and fish3. Tumor growth struggled in mice without asparagine in their diets4. Patient talking to doctorVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study looking at mice with an aggressive form of breast cancer found that tumors struggled when the nutrient asparagine was missing from their diets." "Asparagine is found in asparagus, poultry, seafood and many other foods. It is an amino acid, a key building block of protein." "Cambridge scientists found that when mice were given a low-asparagine diet or asparagine-blocking drugs, tumor growth struggled in the mice." "In the future, cancer therapies could be improved by modifying a patient's diet or by using drugs that change the way tumor cells can access nutrients."SOURCES: BBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/health-42976851***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 07:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/08/3544484/3544484_5F08853C360045379192315B20177D3B_180208_3544484_Certain_foods_may_influence_cancer_growth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/405/925/4059259671C743FEA29B2BB5036A2BA0_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cancer, cancer growth, breast cancer, asparagine, cancer research, cancer tumors]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3544447</guid>
      <title>North Korea may be behind Coincheck cryptocurrency heist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea may be involved in the world's biggest cryptocurrency heist, which happened in Tokyo last month.Reuters reports that on January 26, $530 million worth of virtual coins were stolen from Tokyo cryptocurrency exchange Coincheck, affecting 260,000 customers.South Korea's National Intelligence Agency told lawmakers on Monday that it's possible North Korean hackers are behind the theft.It probably isn't the reclusive regime's first crypto crime either, as they're believed to have masterminded quite a number of attacks in recent years, according to Bloomberg.UN Sanctions blocking the North's exports have led to a trade deficit, and experts believe the pariah state is turning to cryptocurrency to get cash.Pyongyang hackers had previously targeted the South's cryptocurrency exchanges in 2017, reportedly stealing 26 billion won through malicious codes in emails and bogus forms.South Korea currently has no evidence to prove the North's involvement, but is now working with international authorities to look into the incident.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. $530 million in virtual tokens stolen from Coincheck 2. North Korean hackers as culprits3. North Korea low on cash reserves due to UN sanctions4. North Korean hackers stealing from South Korean cryptocurrency exchangeVOICEOVER (in English): "On January 26, $530 million worth of virtual coins was stolen from Tokyo cryptocurrency exchange Coincheck, affecting 260,000 customers.""South Korea's National Intelligence Agency told lawmakers on Monday that it's possible North Korean hackers are behind the theft.""UN Sanctions blocking the North's exports have led to a trade deficit, and experts believe the pariah state is turning to cryptocurrency to get cash.""Pyongyang hackers had previously targeted the South's cryptocurrency exchanges in 2017, reportedly stealing 26 billion won through malicious codes in emails and bogus forms."SOURCES: Reuters, Nikkei, Chosun Ilbo, Bloomberghttps://www.reuters.com/article/uk-southkorea-northkorea-cryptocurrency/south-korean-intelligence-says-n-korean-hackers-possibly-behind-coincheck-heist-sources-idUSKBN1FP2XXhttps://asia.nikkei.com/Spotlight/Bitcoin-evolution/North-Korea-suspected-in-Coincheck-cryptocurrency-heisthttp://english.chosun.com/site/data/html_dir/2018/02/06/2018020600817.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-02-06/north-korea-is-said-to-be-suspected-of-hatching-coincheck-heist***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/08/3544447/3544447_548F1383124642D7B3FCE3ABAB8D38DA_180208_3544447_North_Korea_may_be_behind_Coincheck_cryptocurren_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7E6/986/7E69863705184BA69DC6809CF54BCD24_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency heist, coincheck, coincheck heist, virtual currency, north korea, japan cryptocurrency, XEM, NEM, hackers, north korean hackers, Kim jong un]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3544416</guid>
      <title>China tests anti-missile system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's Defence Ministry this week said that the country had conducted a successful test of a land-based anti-missile system.Missiles launched from land-based midcourse defense systems are designed to intercept incoming projectiles over Earth, reported the Asia Times. These are launched after the incoming projectile is tracked by satellite and radar systems. The Ministry of Defence said this week's land-based midcourse defense systems test wasn't directed at any country, reported Chinese state-run media outlet the Global Times.The U.S., along with the UK, France, Russia, India, North Korea and China are all reported to have intercontinental ballistic missiles. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of ICBM2. Depiction of ICBM being intercepted3. Depiction of which countries have ICBMsVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Reuters, News.com.au, Global Timeshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-defence/china-says-carries-out-another-anti-missile-test-idUSKBN1FQ08Xhttp://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/china-conducts-successful-interception-of-ballistic-missile-in-earths-orbit/news-story/76554886bd4f48b19f24b06237d8f1aehttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1088484.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 06:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/08/3544416/3544416_8FE11FADD7EF4C2590466A819D7D5666_180208_3544416_China_tests_anti_missile_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E57/53B/E5753B88D5F947A4A09463C43E3F4697_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, anti missile defence system, china icbm, icbm defense system, icbm defense system test, missile defense system china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3544280</guid>
      <title>Scientists grow hair on bald mouse using McDonald's French fries additive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at Yokohama National University have successfully grown hair on a bald mouse using an additive found in McDonald's French Fries.The study used dimethylpolysiloxane, an anti-frothing additive. Scientists used the chemical to produce 5,000 hair follicle germs, or HFGs. These are reportedly critical in treating hair loss.Researchers used this as the base of a culture vessel full of other materials.  When applied to to a bald mouse via an HFG chip, they found that mouse had grown black hairs within days, Newsweek reported citing the research.Details of the Yokohama National University study were published in the journal, Biomaterials. The research could help spur new advances in for hair loss treatment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of dimethylpolysiloxane in fryer with French fries2. Depiction of dimethylpolysiloxane being used to create hair follicle germs3. Depiction of hair follicles growingVOICEOVER (in English): "The study used dimethylpolysiloxane, an anti-frothing additive used in McDonald's French fries.""Scientists used it to produce 5,000 hair follicle germs, or HFGs. These are reportedly critical in treating hair loss.""Researchers used this as the base of a culture vessel of other materials.""When applied to a bald mouse via microwell array chips, they found that the mouse had grown black hairs within days."SOURCES: Biomaterials, Science Daily, Newsweekhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0142961217307214?via%3Dihubhttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/02/180201142853.htmhttp://www.newsweek.com/chemical-mcdonalds-fries-may-cure-male-baldness-study-say-799439 ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 02:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/08/3544280/3544280_97E4C4E16B9E4EE08356F40CE5B68F5B_180208_3544280_Scientists_grow_hair_on_bald_mouse_using_McDonal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CAA/059/CAA0595AE21947CEA2BC3967F1B93C46_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mcdonalds hair loss, hair loss, baldness, dimethylopolysiloxane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3545602</guid>
      <title>Hackers are targeting the 2018 Winter Olympics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Pyeongchang Olympics had been plagued by numerous cyber attacks well before the opening ceremony, and it seems the hackers are only just getting started.As millions tune in to see the 2018 Winter Olympics, security experts warn that malicious scams and cyber crimes may be on the rise, according to the New York Times.McAfee researchers told Wired that hackers believed to be from North Korea sent out phishing emails to Olympic-related organizations, with codes hidden in attached Word documents programmed to install spyware.Members of Russian cyber espionage group Fancy Bear have also accessed private emails from Olympic agencies and leaked them online, supposedly as evidence of doping in Western countries.According to experts, the worst case scenario would be if hackers tried to tamper with a venue's electronic system, or an event's results.Currently protecting the Olympics is a team of cyber security analysts, who are monitoring any potential threats. Whether or not this will be enough to deter cyber criminals, however, is still uncertain.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pyeongchang Winter Olympics being targeted by hackers2. Hackers installing spyware on South Korean Olympics-related computers3. Russian hackers leaking emails and documents from Olympic agencies4. Hackers could tamper with stadium lights and electronic resultsVOICEOVER (in English): "As millions tune in to see the 2018 Winter Olympics, security experts warn that malicious scams and cyber crimes may be on the rise.""Hackers believed to be from North Korea sent out phishing emails to Olympic-related organizations, with codes hidden in attached Word documents programmed to install spyware.""Russian cybercriminals have also accessed private emails from Olympic agencies and leaked them online, supposedly as evidence of doping in Western countries.""The worst case scenario, according to experts, would be if hackers tried to tamper with a venue's electronic system, or an event's results."SOURCES: New York Times, Wiredhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/02/08/technology/winter-olympics-hackers.htmlhttps://www.wired.com/story/pyeongchang-winter-olympics-cyberattacks/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 10:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/09/3545602/3545602_65DE3800B2EA44849E2EF593E5A2ADEB_180209_3545602_Hackers_are_targeting_the_2018_Winter_Olympics_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4DC/723/4DC7237015854E278E36D32E7DC17AEB_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, winter olympics, pyeongchang 2018, cyber attack, cyber security, hackers, russian hackers, north korean hackers, spyware, leaked emails]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3545333</guid>
      <title>Chinese police use facial recognition glasses to identify suspects</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese authorities have begun donning high-tech glasses to spot suspects  the latest use of facial recognition technology in an increasingly all-seeing state.The South China Morning Post reports that police in Zhengzhou can now verify people's identities within minutes, using sunglasses with a camera attachment, which is connected to a database via a portable device.Officers who spot a suspicious person from as far as 5 meters away need only take a photo showing at least 70% of the face. The photo is run through the system, allowing officers access to information like name, ethnicity, gender, and address. It also details which hotel they are staying at, recent internet history, and whether they are wanted for any crime.Seven suspects involved in kidnapping and hit-and-run incidents have been arrested so far, with 26 others apprehended for using fake IDs.The use of facial scanners and other similar technology are widespread in China, where there are fewer privacy concerns.The government is in the process of amping up surveillance, starting with a database containing relevant information on its 1.3 billion citizens.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Features of facial recognition glasses 2. Depiction of how glasses work3. Depiction of available information in database4. Depiction of suspects being apprehendedVOICEOVER (in English): "Police in Zhengzhou can now verify people's identities within minutes, using sunglasses with a camera attachment, which is connected to a database via a portable device.""Officers who spot a suspicious person from as far as five meters away need only take a photo showing at least 70% of the face. The photo is run through the system...""...allowing officers access to information like name, ethnicity, gender, and address. It also details the hotel a person is staying at, recent internet history, and whether he is wanted for any crime.""Seven suspects involved in kidnapping and hit-and-run incidents have been arrested so far, with 26 others apprehended for using fake IDs."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, The Telegraphhttp://www.scmp.com/tech/social-gadgets/article/2132465/travel-and-retail-banking-chinas-facial-recognition-systems-arehttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/02/07/chinese-police-using-facial-recognition-glasses-identify-suspects/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 06:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/09/3545333/3545333_5CA8F20ED0994501A53785A96E7BB17E_180209_3545333_Chinese_police_use_facial_recognition_glasses_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B65/203/B65203C1C7314BCBAC2D44B3223DE501_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, smart glasses, china surveillance, police surveillance, china facial recognition glasses, facial recognition, crime in china, police state, police database, chinese new year]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3545324</guid>
      <title>Study finds nitrogen fertilizers a major contributor to California smog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study finds that fertilized soils could be responsible for up to 40 percent of California's nitrogen oxides emissions.California has the poorest air quality in the U.S., according to a 2017 American Lung Association report, according to Mother Jones. Scientists from University of California, Davis published their findings in the journal Science Advances and found the state may be overlooking fertilizers as a major contributor to air pollution. According to the study, California's Air Resources Board currently estimates nitrogen oxides emissions at four percent from fertilizer. The team compared nitrogen oxides emissions over the Central Valley with fertilizer application rates, and discovered fertilized soils could be contributing up to 40 percent of the state's nitrogen oxides emissions. Hundreds of thousands of tons of nitrogen fertilizer are used on crops in the Central Valley each year. Excess fertilizer not used by crops is released into the atmosphere as nitrogen oxides and can create layers of smog that blanket towns and cities. Smog can lead to health complications like asthma and acute bronchitis, as well as cause missed school and work days. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tractor applying nitrogen fertilizer to a field2. Researchers compared emissions and fertilizers application rates3. Excess fertilizer contributing to Central Valley smog4. Health-related effects from smogVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study finds California may be overlooking fertilizers as a major contributor to smog. The state currently estimates nitrogen oxides emissions from fertilizers at four percent." "Scientists compared nitrogen oxides emissions over the Central Valley with fertilizer application rates and found fertilized soils may actually be responsible for 40 percent of emissions."  "Hundreds of thousands of tons of nitrogen fertilizer are used on crops in the Central Valley each year. Excess fertilizer is released into the atmosphere as nitrogen oxides, which can create layers of blanketing smog." "Smog can lead to health complications like asthma and acute bronchitis, as well as cause missed school and work days." SOURCES: Mother Jones, EESIhttps://www.motherjones.com/environment/2018/01/researchers-just-found-a-hidden-cause-of-californias-smog-problem/http://www.eesi.org/articles/view/new-study-finds-nitrogen-fertilizer-major-contributor-to-smog-in-california***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 06:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/09/3545324/3545324_E218F06BAA824DAC89EB9D2BB9A66225_180209_3545324_Study_finds_nitrogen_fertilizers_a_major_contrib_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7F8/A77/7F8A778CECCA471C848A1F9DB67026E0_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, California smog, nitrogen fertilizers smog, nitrogen oxides emissions, California air pollution, air pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3546141</guid>
      <title>Source code for key iPhone operating system leaked online</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA key iPhone code has just been revealed, in what some are calling the biggest leak in history.Motherboard reports that the source code for the iBoot, a core component of Apple's operating system, was posted on Github early this week.Despite being tied to the outdated iOS 9, the code could make it easier for hackers to find vulnerabilities that would allow them to decrypt an iPhone.Conversely, it could also be used by security researchers to develop protection against flaws that could compromise the device.With only 7% of devices currently running on iOS 9 or older, and several other safeguards in place, end users are not at risk. But keeping software up to date is still beneficial.Apple later confirmed that the leaked source code was genuine, but has since filed a DMCA notice to get GitHub to take it down.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. iBoot source code leaked to GitHub2. Depiction of hackers using code to decrypt iPhone3. Depiction of researchers using code to fix vulnerabilities4. iPhone end users not at riskVOICEOVER (in English): "Source code for the iBoot, a core component of Apple's operating system, was posted on Github early this week.""Despite being tied to the outdated iOS 9, the code could make it easier for hackers to find vulnerabilities that would allow them to decrypt an iPhone.""Conversely, it could also be used by security researchers to develop protection against flaws that could compromise the device.""With only 7% of devices currently running on iOS 9 or older, and several other safeguards in place, end users are not at risk. But keeping software up to date is still beneficial."SOURCES: Motherboard, CNET, TechCrunchhttps://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/a34g9j/iphone-source-code-iboot-ios-leakhttps://www.cnet.com/news/apple-calls-leaked-iphone-source-code-outdated/https://techcrunch.com/2018/02/08/apple-addresses-ios-source-code-leak-says-it-appears-to-be-tied-to-three-year-old-software/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 07:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/10/3546141/3546141_C36887B2A986436C85AA97E2020B46A8_180210_3546141_Source_code_for_key_iPhone_operating_system_leak_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C37/DBA/C37DBAC921D04EFA8FAAA1DBC6BCFFEA_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, iphone, iboot, source code, iphone leak, source code leak, iboot leak, github, apple source code, iOS 9, apple iOS, apple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3547521</guid>
      <title>Israel downs Iranian drone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Iranian drone was shot down on Saturday morning in northern Israel by the Israeli military.According to the Times of Israel, the drone was destroyed by an Israeli Apache helicopter that engaged it after it flew inside Israeli airspace. The aircraft is said to be a Iranian Saeqeh, drone, also known as Thunderbolt. This model is based on the American RQ-170 Sentinel spy drone, according to the Times of Israel. Both models bare resemblance to the B-2 stealth bomber .RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Iranian drone and Israeli Apache helicopter2. Depiction of Iranian drone being destroyed3. Depiction of American drone and Iranian drone, alongside B-2 bomberVOICEOVER (in English): "An Iranian drone was shot down on Saturday morning in northern Israel by the Israeli military.""According to the Times of Israel, the drone was destroyed by an attack helicopter that engaged it after it flew inside Israel's airspace.""The Iranian craft is said to be a called a Thunderbolt drone.""It is reportedly reverse-engineered from an American RQ-170 Sentinel spy drone that Tehran captured in 2011""Both models bare resemblance to the B-2 stealth bomber."SOURCES: Times of Israel, The Aviationisthttps://www.timesofisrael.com/iranian-uav-that-entered-israeli-airspace-seems-to-be-american-stealth-knock-off/https://theaviationist.com/2018/02/10/israeli-f-16i-sufa-crashes-after-coming-under-massive-anti-aircraft-fire-from-syrian-air-defenses/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 10:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/12/3547521/3547521_1265C68F26EC4730BEF4CD5586680F87_180212_3547521_Israel_downs_Iranian_drone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E17/16E/E1716EFE79EB4E52B984F4FBDB0193F2_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, iran, israel, iranian drone, iran uav, iran israel drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3547510</guid>
      <title>Russian plane crashes near Moscow, killing 71</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Russian plane crashed on Sunday, killing everyone on board and ending a 440-day streak without passenger airliner fatalities, which was the longest streak in modern aviation history, according to CNN.The Russian News Agency reports that Saratov Airlines flight 703 was set to fly from Moscow to Orsk with 65 passengers and six crew members.The Antonov AN-148 jet took off at 2:21 p.m. but reportedly disappeared from the radar about 5 minutes later.The BBC reports that according to flight-tracking site Flightradar24, the plane descended rapidly at a rate of 1,000 meters a minute. Eyewitnesses reported seeing it on fire as it fell from the sky and crashed near the village of Stepanovskoye, outside Moscow.Authorities searching through fragments of the wreckage have recovered the plane's black box, and confirmed the deaths of all 71 people onboard.Investigators have yet to determine what caused the crash, but say weather conditions or pilot error are possibilities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Saratov Airlines flight 703 from Moscow to Orsk2. Plane disappears from radar 5 minutes after takeoff3. Plane descending quickly while on fire4. Wreckage, bodies spread out over a snowy fieldVOICEOVER (in English): "Saratov Airlines flight 703 was set to fly from Moscow to Orsk with 65 passengers and six crew members."The Antonov AN-148 jet took off at 2:21 p.m. but reportedly disappeared from radar about 5 minutes later.""The plane descended rapidly, with eyewitnesses saying it was on fire as it fell from the sky and crashed near a village outside Moscow.""Authorities searching through fragments of the wreckage have recovered the plane's black box, and confirmed the deaths of all 71 people onboard."SOURCES: TASS, BBC, The Guardian, CNNhttp://tass.com/society/989524http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-43024235https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/feb/11/russian-passenger-plane-saratov-airlines-flight-6w703-crashes-outside-moscow-reportshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/11/europe/russia-plane-crash/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 09:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/12/3547510/3547510_3F37C16BCEAE461081118CF9DB8C022D_180212_3547510_Russian_plane_crashes_near_Moscow__killing_71_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F0E/96C/F0E96C48846842A4B5E3CF1D8477E266_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, russian plane crash, russia plane crash, plane crash, saratov flight 203, deadly crash, saratov plane crash, saratov airlines, antonov AN-148, saratov AN-148, plane on fire, moscow, orsk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3548426</guid>
      <title>Scientists develop electronic skin that can regenerate and be reused</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have developed electronic skin that can heal itself, according to new research published in the journal Science Advances.The electronic skin is made up of a polymer material named polymine and silver nanoparticles. The device can heal itself through a combination of heat and compounds found in ethanol, according to a University of Colorado news release.Healing agent is added to the electronic skin and it is then warmed on a heat press. This process sees the broken area heal itself with full sensory and mechanical ability, according to the researchers writing in Science Advances.When added to an ethanol solution, the device can be broken down and recycled to make more electronic skin. One of the researchers told Newsweek that, in the future, this recyclability concept could also be applied to other devices like smartphones and laptops.The electronic skin has sensors for airflow, temperature, humidity and pressure. According to Newsweek, if the device was used on a robotic or prosthetic hand, it could use these sensors to handle objects.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of electronic skin being cut2. Depiction of how electronic skin can "heal"3. Depiction of electronic skin can be recycled and make new electronic skin4. Depiction of sensors on electronic skinVOICEOVER (in English): "The electronic skin is made up of a polymer material named polymine and silver nanoparticles.""The device can heal itself through a combination of heat and compounds found in ethanol.""Healing agent is added to the electronic skin and it is then warmed on a heat press.""This process sees the broken area heal itself with full sensory and mechanical ability.""When added to an ethanol solution, the device can be broken down and recycled to make more electronic skin.""One of the researchers told Newsweek that, in the future, this recyclability concept could also be applied to other devices like smartphones and laptops.""The electronic skin has sensors for airflow, temperature, humidity and pressure.""Hypothetically, if the device was used on a robotic or prosthetic hand, it could use these sensors to handle objects."SOURCES: Science Advances, University of Colorado, Newsweekhttp://advances.sciencemag.org/content/4/2/eaaq0508.fullhttps://www.colorado.edu/today/2018/02/09/new-malleable-electronic-skin-self-healable-recyclablehttp://www.newsweek.com/self-healing-recyclable-electronic-skin-creates-way-prosthetic-limbs-feel-just-801743***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 11:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/13/3548426/3548426_AF38212E248541708827869F453DA286_180213_3548426_Scientists_develop_electronic_skin_that_can_rege_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/583/03B/58303B4728A24E34A065F0C04E57FAF1_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, self healing skin, electronic skin, smart skin, skin for robots, skin research, robot skin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3548330</guid>
      <title>Iran unveils new ballistic missiles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIran showcased its growing arsenal of weapons over the weekend, just weeks after deadly anti-government protests rocked the nation.The Washington Free Beacon reports that during rallies commemorating the 39th anniversary of the Islamic Revolution, Iranian leaders unveiled two new homemade missiles: the Ghadr and the Fajr-5.The Ghadr is a nuclear-capable, medium-range ballistic missile, which experts say bears striking similarities to North Korean technology.It can be launched from mobile platforms, and is equipped with a radar-evading system. It's also capable of striking Israel when fired from within Iran.The Fajr-5, meanwhile, is a long-range artillery rocket fuelled by solid propulsion, that is being used by Iran-backed anti-Israel groups like Hamas and Hezbollah.The Islamic nation currently holds the region's largest arsenal of ballistic missiles, and continues to develop them despite international criticism, most notably from U.S. President Donald Trump.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Iran unveils new missiles during Islamic Revolution anniversary rallies 2. Nuclear-capable Ghadr missile shares similarities with North Korean weapons3. Ghadr missile can be fired from anywhere in Iran to strike Israel 4. Fajr-5 artillery rocket spread to Iran-backed anti-Israel groupsVOICEOVER (in English): "During rallies commemorating the 39th anniversary of the Islamic Revolution, Iranian leaders unveiled two new homemade missiles: the Ghadr and the Fajr-5.""The Ghadr is a nuclear-capable, medium-range ballistic missile, which experts say bears striking similarities to North Korean technology.""It can be launched from mobile platforms, and is equipped with a radar-evading system. It's also capable of striking Israel when fired from within Iran.""The Fajr-5, meanwhile, is a long-range artillery rocket fuelled by solid propulsion, that is being used by Iran-backed anti-Israel groups like Hamas and Hezbollah."SOURCES: Washington Free Beacon, Al-Masdar Newshttp://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-unveils-new-homemade-nuclear-capable-ballistic-missiles-amid-massive-war-celebrations/https://www.almasdarnews.com/article/iran-presented-new-missiles-islamic-revolution-celebrations-reports/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 10:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/13/3548330/3548330_947CC1A089AC47C88FBAD9D324674121_180213_3548330_Iran_unveils_new_ballistic_missiles_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A5A/7CC/A5A7CCBE5F4049D68483D938EBBB5C1B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, iran weapons, iran missiles, iran nuclear missiles, ballistic missiles, nuclear missiles, nuclear weapons, nuclear technology, ghadr, qadr, fajr-5, anti-Israel, Islamic Revolution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3548125</guid>
      <title>The science of escaping from a vicious predator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEA years-long study has revealed how predators hunt in the African wild, and what tactics their prey use to outmaneuver them.BBC reports that researchers in Botswana fitted cheetahs, impalas, lions and zebras with custom radio collars to record each animal's location, speed, acceleration and deceleration, and how quickly they can turn.Muscle biopsies taken from each animal revealed that predators were 37% faster, and had muscles 20% more powerful that their prey, but were also less able to maneuver at lower speeds.Computer models suggest that running at full speed is not in the prey's best interest, since the predator can accelerate more quickly and take them down.Instead, prey should run at moderate speeds and turn sharply at the last minute in order to avoid capture.Lions and cheetahs were found to be successful in about a third of their hunts, generally when they are travelling just slightly faster than their prey.This is because the cats and their victims are co-evolving, in order to maintain balance between each group's numbers in the wild.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two pairs of predators and prey fitted with neck collars2. Muscle biopsies reveal predators more athletic than their prey3. Prey running at full speed often caught by faster predators4. Prey running slower but turning at the last minute to avoid captureVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers in Botswana fitted cheetahs, impalas, lions and zebras with custom radio collars to record each animal's location, speed, acceleration and deceleration, and how quickly they can turn.""Muscle biopsies taken from each animal revealed that predators were faster, and more powerful than their prey, but less able to maneuver at lower speeds.""Computer models suggest that running at full speed is not in the prey's best interest, since the predator can accelerate more quickly and take them down.""Instead, prey should run at moderate speeds and turn sharply at the last minute in order to avoid capture."SOURCES: BBC, New York Timeshttp://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-42792190https://www.nytimes.com/2018/01/24/science/cheetahs-lions-zebras-impalas.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 07:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/13/3548125/3548125_B4CC6433FCDF4A5E9F409FBD0FEB1A07_180213_3548125_The_science_of_escaping_from_a_vicious_predator_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8F9/CC4/8F9CC4C077304DB790A6DE24EF36EB4A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, survival of the fittest, predators, how to escape from a lion, how to escape from a cheetah, how to escape from a predator, prey, lion, cheetah, zebra, impala, survival, savannah, africa, botswana]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3548860</guid>
      <title>Woman's eye infected with rare eye worm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA woman from Oregon was shocked to discover that the source of her eye irritation were tiny parasitic worms.CNN reports that thelazia gulosa are parasitic worms typically found in cattle. They live on the surface of the eyeball, and produce larvae that stay in the tears.Face flies that feed off the animal's eye secretions ingest the larvae, which develop into a more advanced stage while in the flies' digestive system.The worms can enter a human host when an infected fly lands close to or in a person's eye.So far, only 10 other cases of eye worms have been reported in the U.S., with none caused by thelazia gulosa until now.Eye worms can be killed with anti-parasitic medicine, but may cause scarring. As such, patients are advised to just monitor the eyes and remove any worms.The parasites have been known to cause vision loss and blindness in animals, but fortunately not in people.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of eye worms in cows' eyes, larvae in tears2. Depiction of larvae being ingested by face flies3. Depiction of woman being infected with eye worms via face flies4. Woman removing eye wormsVOICEOVER (in English): "Thelazia gulosa are parasitic worms typically found in cattle. They live on the surface of the eyeball, and produce larvae that stay in the tears.""Face flies that feed off the animal's eye secretions ingest the larvae, which develop into a more advanced stage while in the flies' digestive system.""The worms can enter a human host when an infected fly lands close to or in a person's eye.""Eye worms can be killed with anti-parasitic medicine, but may cause scarring. As such, patients are advised to just monitor the eyes and remove any worms."SOURCES: Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, The Oregonian, CNN, Reutershttps://www.cdc.gov/dpdx/thelaziasis/index.htmlhttp://www.oregonlive.com/trending/2018/02/14_cattle_worms_found_oregon_w.htmlhttp://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/12/health/human-eye-worms/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-health-eyeworms/u-s-woman-found-with-eye-worm-previously-known-only-in-cattle-idUSKBN1FW2J5***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 05:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/14/3548860/3548860_F2FD03A755644652A99B31B350D808A1_180214_3548860_Woman_s_eye_infected_with_rare_eye_worm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3C7/AB2/3C7AB24CA31547AA85B404852B1603DE_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, eyeworms, eye worms, worms in eyes, parasite, worms, eye parasites, worm in eye, worm in woman's eye, cattle worms, eye infection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3549886</guid>
      <title>United Arab Emirates' Sustainable City slated to be complete sometime this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe United Arab Emirates' Sustainable City is located just outside of Dubai.Work on the project started in 2013, and is slated to end at some point in 2018. It is home to 11 so-called greenhouse 'biodomes' that act in combination with garden farms to create food. The Sustainable City has 500 villas and 89 apartment buildings. According to Tawahul Tech, the city agreed in January 2018 to allow testing of driverless electric vehicles inside it. That is reportedly part of the Dubai's plans to make a quarter of the public transport driverless by 2030. Cars are banned in most parts of the city, with residents getting around via electrical smart cars, golf carts, bicycles and horse-drawn carriages.According to Business Insider, 1,800 people have bought homes in the city and  900 are renting.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Globe, UAE and Sustainable City2. Overview of Sustainable City3. Sustainable City's 'biodomes'4. Number of apartments and villas inside Sustainable City5. Solar roofing in parking areas6. How much power the city can produce7. Depiction of driverless vehicle8. Depiction of driverless vehicles driving inside city9. Depiction of types of transport in city10. Number of people who have bought or are renting homes in the cityVOICEOVER (in English): "The United Arab Emirates' Sustainable City is located just outside of Dubai.""Work on the project started in 2013, and is slated to end at some point in 2018.""It is home to 11 so-called greenhouse 'biodomes' that act in combination with garden farms to create food.""The Sustainable City has 500 villas and 89 apartment buildings. "Reportedly, the paint on the villas repel ultraviolet rays and the roofs are laden with solar panels.""The solar roofing is also used to cover the city's various parking areas." "Those panels on the homes and carriages reportedly act in combination with other renewable power sources to generate 10 megawatts of power.""According to Tawahul Tech, the city agreed in January 2018 to allow testing of driverless electric vehicles inside it.""That is reportedly part of Dubai's plans to make a quarter of public transport driverless by 2030.""Cars are banned in most parts of the city, with residents getting around via electrical smart cars, golf carts, bicycles and horse-drawn carriages.""According to Business Insider, 1,800 people have bought homes in the city and  900 are renting."SOURCES: The Sustainable City, Business Insider, Tahawul Tech, https://www.thesustainablecity.aehttp://www.businessinsider.com/dubai-sustainable-city-uae-2018-1http://www.tahawultech.com/news/rta-begin-testing-autonomous-vehicles-sustainable-city/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 09:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/15/3549886/3549886_B933FFAFF9D944A88F68C50941C02E44_180215_3549886_United_Arab_Emirates__Sustainable_City_slated_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/421/735/421735B199784788B553F5EB0E65A91B_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sustainable city in dubai, uae sustainable city, driverless vehicles, driverless, mega projects, dubai mega projects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3549868</guid>
      <title>Cities that could run out of water like Cape Town</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs global fresh water supplies become scarce, several major cities across the world could run out of drinking water like Cape Town.  Only three percent of Earth's water is suitable for drinking. According to U.N. estimates, global demand for fresh water will exceed supply by 40 percent in 2030, due to climate change, human action and population growth, the BBC reported. Several major cities around the world may also face drinking water shortages in the future.So Paulo experienced a drinking water crisis in 2015 when its main reservoir fell below four percent capacity, and also had reservoir issues in January 2017.Bangalore's growing property market and tech industry have outpaced the city's ability to manage water and sewage systems. The city's water pipes also lose half its drinking water to waste. Beijing will increasingly struggle to meet its water needs. Figures from 2015, showed 40 percent of the city's surface water was so polluted it was not even suitable for agriculture or industrial use. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Global supplies of fresh water decreasing2. Sao Paulo has had reservoir issues3. Bangalore water issues4. Beijing surface water issuesVOICEOVER (in English): "As global fresh water supplies become scarce, several major cities across the world could run out of drinking water like Cape Town.""So Paulo experienced a drinking water crisis in 2015 when its main reservoir fell below four percent capacity, and also had reservoir issues in January 2017.""Bangalore's growing property market and tech industry have outpaced the city's ability to manage water and sewage systems. The city's water pipes also lose half its drinking water to waste." "Beijing will increasingly struggle to meet its water needs in the future. Figures from 2015, showed 40 percent of the city's surface water was so polluted, it was not even suitable for agriculture or industrial use." SOURCES: BBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-42982959***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 09:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/15/3549868/3549868_F087DDB09E1D46E48E991BD8EE4ED5C3_180215_3549868_Cities_that_could_run_out_of_water_like_Cape_Tow_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2BF/4C0/2BF4C00E16354D53A00A67EE5AC04D3C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, water scarcity, fresh water shortage, drinking water shortage, water crisis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3549840</guid>
      <title>Florida high school shooting kills at least 17</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMore than a dozen are dead after a gunman went on a violent rampage at a South Florida school.The Washington Post reports that the incident began outside a Parkland, Florida high school, when a suspect armed with an AR-15, several magazines and a smoke grenade shot at least two people.The gunman reportedly pulled a fire alarm to draw students out of their classrooms, before then open firing on them, according to USA Today.Students hid in classrooms until SWAT teams arrived and ushered them out. Seventeen people have been confirmed dead so far.The gunman left the scene and was apprehended by police an hour later, roughly a mile from the high school.Authorities have identified the suspect as 19-year-old Nikolas Cruz, a former student who was expelled from the school.Investigators looking into his social media accounts say they contained disturbing material.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman armed with AR-15 rifle, multiple magazines, smoke grenade2. Gunman pulled fire alarm before shooting3. Students hid in classrooms until SWAT team arrived; number of casualties4. Gunman apprehendedVOICEOVER (in English): "The incident began outside a Parkland, Florida high school, when a suspect armed with an AR-15, several magazines and a smoke grenade shot at least two people.""The gunman reportedly pulled a fire alarm to draw students out of their classrooms, before then open firing on them.""Students hid in classrooms until SWAT teams arrived and ushered them out. Seventeen people have been confirmed dead so far.""The gunman left the scene and was apprehended by police an hour later, roughly a mile from the high school."SOURCES: Sun Sentinel, WSVN, ABC, Washington Post, BBChttp://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/parkland/florida-school-shooting/fl-sb-active-shooter-marjory-stoneman-high-20180214-story.htmlhttps://wsvn.com/news/local/bso-17-dead-in-marjory-stoneman-douglas-high-school-shooting/http://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/shooting-florida-high-school-wounded-unclear-53087661https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/education/wp/2018/02/14/school-shooting-reported-at-florida-high-school/http://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-43066226***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 08:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/15/3549840/3549840_C0DFDCB6EB924C059DDAFBFAE2FA21C2_180215_3549840_Florida_high_school_shooting_kills_at_least_17_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/53F/7CA/53F7CA3483BA47C0BDBFE948BF259199_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, school shooting, florida school shooting, florida high school shooting, student shooting, florida shooting, gunman, AR-15, smoke grenade, marjory stoneman douglas high school]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3549764</guid>
      <title>Researchers discover new antibiotic in dirt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have discovered a new group of antibiotics in soil, according to research published in the journal Nature Microbiology.Researchers examined some 2,000 soil samples from across the U.S., Nature reported. The new group of antibiotics are called malacidins.The team applied the new antibiotics to rats infected with MRSA and found it annihilated the infection, the BBC reported. Lead researcher Sean Brady told the BBC it's impossible to tell when or if the discovery would make it to clinics.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  Overview of study 2.  Depiction of soil analysis3.  Depiction of malacidin treating MRSA in a ratVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers examined some 2,000 soil samples from across the U.S.""Following analysis of the samples, they discovered a new group of antibiotics called malacidins."  "The team applied the malacidin to rats infected with MRSA virus, and found it annihilated the infection."SOURCES: Nature Microbiology, Nature, BBChttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41564-018-0110-1https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-01931-4http://www.bbc.com/news/health-43032602***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 07:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/15/3549764/3549764_24BBE57A6E2247419DB2CD398613E02F_180215_3549764_Researchers_discover_new_antibiotic_in_dirt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/78B/82F/78B82FAA1E074ECCACA089F05EA6C8BD_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, new antibiotic, malacidin, rockefeller university, antibiotic soil samples, antibiotic dirt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3550303</guid>
      <title>Genes can help indicate time of death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch from Spain has found that gene activity in dead bodies can point to the time of death.Details of the study were published in the journal Nature Communication.According to Science, researchers found post death activity in the brain and spleen to showed little change. However, they also discovered post-mortem fluctuations across 600 muscle genes.According to Futurism, the research was done via an algorithm that looked at samples from 399 people. The program attempted to forecast the times of death for 129 people.In blood samples it found that DNA production, immune response and metabolism declined 6 hours after death. Most gene activity was found to occur between 7 and 14 hours after loss of life. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gene activity in different parts of the body 2. Gene activity in blood samples3. Overview of times of death.VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers found post death activity in the brain and spleen to show little change.""However, they also discovered post-mortem fluctuations across 600 muscle genes.""The research was done via an algorithm that looked at samples from 399 people. The program attempted to tell the times of death for 129.""In blood samples it found that DNA production, immune response and metabolism declined 6 hours after death.""Most gene activity was found to occur between 7 and 14 hours after loss of life."SOURCES: Nature, Science Mag, BBC, Futurismhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-017-02772-xhttp://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/02/changes-gene-activity-may-one-day-reveal-time-death-crime-victimshttp://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-43046905https://futurism.com/persons-genes-reveal-time-death/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 05:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/16/3550303/3550303_A4540384135A48BAAB390384907FA436_180216_3550303_Genes_can_help_indicate_time_of_death_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/25E/CBA/25ECBAFC909F478A915F05268D34CF53_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  genes, time of death, forensic investigation, gene research, genes and investigation, genes as evidence]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3550220</guid>
      <title>Grand minimum will cause sun to get dimmer by 2050</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists are predicting the sun will be cooler and dimmer by 2050. According to a study published in Astrophysical Journal Letters, the sun will cool down because of the "grand minimum," a period when sunspots form less frequently, the Sun's magnetism is reduced and less ultraviolet radiation makes it to Earth, Tech Times reported. The phenomenon comes at irregular intervals and is believed to be triggered by random fluctuations in the Sun's magnetic field. By analyzing nearly 20 years of data collected by the International Ultraviolet Explorer satellite mission, physicist Dan Lubin, from Scripps Institution of Oceanography, and his team predicted a grand minimum could occur within the next few decades. They also predicted the sun will be seven percent cooler than its usual minimum.  A dimmer sun will affect Earth by first thinning the stratospheric ozone layer, which will then impact wind and weather patterns.  However, the cooling effect will not be enough to stop global warming, according to Lubin. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Sun transitioning into a grand minimum2. Fluctuations in Sun's magnetic field3. Grand minimum characteristics4. Grand minimum effectsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists are predicting the sun will be dimmer by 2050 in a phenomenon referred to as a 'grand minimum.'""The phenomenon comes at irregular intervals and is believed to be triggered by random fluctuations in the sun's magnetic field." "During a grand minimum, sunspots form less frequently, the sun's magnetism is reduced and less ultraviolet radiation makes it to Earth.""A dimmer sun will affect Earth by first thinning the stratospheric ozone layer, which will then impact wind and weather patterns."  SOURCES: Tech Times, News.com.auhttp://www.techtimes.com/articles/220661/20180208/the-sun-would-be-dimmer-by-2050.htmhttp://www.news.com.au/technology/science/space/our-sun-is-about-to-get-unusually-cool-researchers-predict/news-story/dea38cc09657428b5d6f4dbd97b8d97b***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 02:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/16/3550220/3550220_676B9B2C514D4D67896FACA59D1707DE_180216_3550220_Grand_minimum_will_cause_sun_to_get_dimmer_by_20_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BC0/828/BC0828BBFCD646ABA6E6D19F12E1F3CE_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Sun dimmer, Sun dimmer 2050, Sun Grand Minimum, Solar Minimum]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3551741</guid>
      <title>FDA approves blood test that helps diagnose concussions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Food and Drug Administration approved a blood test last Wednesday to help detect concussions in adults. The Banyan Brain Trauma Indicator test looks for two biomarker proteins UCH-L1 and GFAP, which are released upon injury to the brain and pass through the blood-brain barrier, CNN reported.Elevated protein levels can be detected within 15 to 20 minutes of injury. The test can be administered within 12 hours of injury, and takes about three to four hours for results. Currently, patients are diagnosed with a concussion based on a combination of symptoms as well as imaging.CT scans can problematic in that they don't always detect concussion, have 200 times the radiation of a chest x-ray and are expensive. A CT scan can cost anywhere from $800 to $1,500 compared to the new test which would cost $150. The FDA estimates that by using the new blood test, imaging scans can be reduced by at least a third in patients who are suspected of having a concussion.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Football player getting concussion and releasing indicator proteins2. Blood test can be taken up to 12 hours after injury, results take 3 to 4 hours3. Concussions now are diagnosed with symptoms and imaging4. Difference in price between CT scan and new blood testVOICEOVER (in English): "The FDA approved a blood test to help diagnose concussions. The Brain Trauma Indicator test looks for two biomarker proteins   UCH-L1 and GFAP  which are released upon injury to the brain into the blood." "Elevated protein levels can be detected within 15 to 20 minutes of injury. The test can be administered within 12 hours of injury, and takes three to four hours for results." "Patients are currently diagnosed based on a combination of symptoms and imaging. CT scans can problematic in that they don't always detect concussion, have 200 times the radiation of a chest X-ray and are expensive." "A CT scan can cost anywhere from $800 to $1,500 compared to the new test which costs $150." SOURCES: CNN, NBC News, LA Timeshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/14/health/concussion-blood-test-fda-bn/index.htmlhttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-approves-new-blood-test-detect-concussions-n848131http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-concussion-blood-test-20180214-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 07:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/19/3551741/3551741_838E90056BB346AAAFA53C5F440A78B8_180219_3551741_FDA_approves_blood_test_that_helps_diagnose_conc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/16B/EAF/16BEAF560AA14142BC73CCA137B14FCB_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, concussion blood test, concussion, concussion diagnosis, Brain Trauma Indicator test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3551734</guid>
      <title>66 dead in Aseman Airlines plane crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAseman Airlines flight EP3704 crashed in central Iran on Sunday morning, killing all 66 passengers and crew on board.The plane was travelling from Tehran to the city of Yasuj, but crashed in a mountain area near the town of Semirom, according to Reuters.Aljazeera reports, citing a deleted Instagram photo from Aseman Airlines, that the plane was grounded for 7 years until October 26. The 25-year-old ATR-72 aircraft also reportedly performed an emergency landing in Tehran last month, where it was inspected and its problem was fixed. According to the Independent, Iran relies on old aircraft for old parts. This is reportedly due to sanctions in place against the country.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of plane accident area2. Depiction of plane flying3. Depiction of plane near mountain area4. Depiction of plane in hangarVOICEOVER (in English): Aseman Airlines flight EP3704 crashed in central Iran on Sunday morning.The plane was travelling from Tehran to the city of Yasuj, but crashed in a mountain area near the town of Semirom.The accident killed 60 passengers and 6 crew on board.Aljazeera reports, citing a deleted Instagram photo from Aseman Airlines, that the plane was grounded for seven years until October 26.The 25-year-old ATR-72 aircraft also reportedly performed an emergency landing in Tehran last month, where it was inspected and its problem was fixed. SOURCES: Reuters, Al Jazeera, The Independenthttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-airplane/all-65-passengers-crew-feared-dead-in-iranian-plane-crash-idUSKCN1G207Ihttp://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/iranian-passenger-plane-crashes-isfahan-180218074546342.htmlhttp://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/iran-aviation-crash-aseman-airlines-oldest-fleet-boeing-727-a8216221.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 07:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/19/3551734/3551734_4F05F0300C4C47C5B882C8271867E76F_180219_3551734_66_dead_in_Aseman_Airlines_plane_crash_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ADC/895/ADC8956C5810465CBD6F846EA1AC7FF9_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, plane crash, aseman airlines, flight ep3704, aseman airlines crash, iran plane crash, plane accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552318</guid>
      <title>Why heart attack symptoms are misinterpreted in women</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new Yale study indicates that women suffering from heart attack symptoms are less likely to have it diagnosed properly, leading to serious problems.Heart attacks occur when blood flow to the heart is cut off, often due to arterial blockage, which then results in tissue death or damage, according to the Cleveland Clinic.The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reports that in the U.S., heart disease is the leading cause of death for women, accounting for one in every four female deaths.The study led by the Yale School of Public Health analyzed data from 2,009 female and 976 male heart attack patients aged 18 to 55. Findings show that 53% of women who sought help prior to hospitalization were told their symptoms weren't heart-related, compared to only 37% of men.Ninety percent of men and women reported having chest pains, but women often had extra symptoms like indigestion, heart palpitations, and pain the jaw, neck, and arms.Instead of attributing their symptoms to muscle pain, the women were more likely to chalk it up to stress and anxiety.They also had multiple risk factors for heart disease, which suggests doctors should do more to rule out a heart attack when presented with such cases.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Heart attack as the leading cause of death in women2. Depiction of a heart attack3. Women suffering from heart attack symptoms often misdiagnosed4. Extra heart attack symptoms experienced by womenVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Yale News, CNN, Washington Times, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Cleveland Clinichttps://news.yale.edu/2018/02/19/heart-attack-symptoms-often-misinterpreted-younger-womenhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/19/health/heart-attack-symptoms-women-study/index.htmlhttps://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/feb/19/heart-disease-women-less-likely-be-diagnosed-early/https://www.cdc.gov/dhdsp/data_statistics/fact_sheets/fs_women_heart.htmhttp://www.clevelandclinicmeded.com/medicalpubs/diseasemanagement/cardiology/acute-myocardial-infarction/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 09:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/20/3552318/3552318_3F0C5882AA764F4DAC2FE7EEF1DF1A05_180220_3552318_Why_heart_attack_symptoms_are_misinterpreted_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/88B/241/88B2410A58E542CDB883E08DD170E620_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, heart attack symptoms, heart attack, heart attack women, chest pain, chest tightness, chest discomfort, heart problems, having a heart attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552278</guid>
      <title>Russia gets set for World Cup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe world will be watching Russia this summer when the country hosts the 2018 World Cup.The tournament will be played between June 14 and July 15 at 12 venues in 11 cities western Russia. Two of the venues are in Moscow.To attend matches, fans will need a FIFA Fan ID badge along with a ticket. According to FIFA, over 4.9 million tickets were requested for the tournament so far.The month-long tournament will see 32 countries from around the world play a total of 64 matches, with the winning nation being awarded $38 million and the iconic World Cup trophy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of stadium locations in Russia2. Depiction of fans and tickets requested so far3. Depiction of teams and games to be played4. Depiction of prize and trophyVOICEOVER (in English): "The tournament will be played between June 14 and July 15 at 12 venues in 11 cities western Russia.""Two of the venues are in Moscow.""To attend matches, fans will need a FIFA Fan ID badge along with a ticket.""According to FIFA, over 4.9 million tickets were requested for the tournament so far.""The month-long tournament will see 32 countries from around the world play a total of 64 matches, with the winning nation being awarded $38 million and the iconic World Cup trophy."SOURCES: FIFAhttp://www.fifa.com/worldcup/destination/index.htmlhttp://www.fifa.com/worldcup/news/y=2018/m=1/news=2018-fifa-world-cuptm-tickets-impressive-figures-mark-the-closing-of-t-2927411.htmlhttp://www.fifa.com/about-fifa/news/y=2017/m=10/news=fifa-council-confirms-contributions-for-fifa-world-cup-participants-2917806.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 08:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/20/3552278/3552278_AC0FA038A4F940D9909C9752B8AEADEF_180220_3552278_Russia_gets_set_for_World_Cup_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/941/A05/941A0518DC484B8C916F66617B492C45_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,2 018 world cup, 2018 world cup preview, russia, fifa fan id, fifa fans, russia 2018]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552259</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk's Tesla Roadster might crash into Earth over the next million years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team from the University of Toronto made a simulation of the Tesla Roadster's trajectory in space, which indicates that there might be a slight chance it will hit Earth over the next million years.SpaceX's Falcon Heavy rocket recently launched a red Tesla Roadster into orbit toward Mars.According to a new study predicting the car's future path, the Roadster will be roughly one lunar distance away from the planet in 2091. Over the next million years, it then has a 2.5% chance of hitting Venus, and a 6% chance of crashing into Earth. However, if does come crashing into the planet, it will likely burn up in the earth's atmosphere before reaching the surface.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tesla Roadster with Starman in space2. Roadster will be one lunar distance from Earth in 20913. Probability of Roadster crashing into Venus and Earth4. Roadster burning up in Earth's atmosphereVOICEOVER (in English): "SpaceX's Falcon Heavy rocket recently launched a red Tesla Roadster into orbit toward Mars.""According to a new study predicting the car's future path, the Roadster will be roughly one lunar distance away from the planet in 2091.""Over the next million years, it then has a 2.5% chance of hitting Venus, and a 6% chance of crashing into Earth.""But if does come crashing into the planet, it will likely burn up in the earth's atmosphere before reaching the surface."SOURCES: Science, National Geographichttp://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/02/don-t-panic-chance-space-traveling-sportscar-hitting-earth-just-6-next-million-yearshttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/02/spacex-falcon-heavy-tesla-roadster-orbit-earth-sun-space/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 08:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/20/3552259/3552259_6450A06ABE6B4DC79F61DD58174C6AFA_180220_3552259_Elon_Musk_s_Tesla_Roadster_might_crash_into_Eart_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/643/72E/64372E285B394F66809E5DB35955C0EA_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, space tesla, tesla, tesla roadster, tesla crash, elon musk, starman, Tesla in space, Tesla crashes into Earth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3553041</guid>
      <title>Tesla cloud account hijacked to mine cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at a cloud-monitoring firm discovered that cyber criminals had accessed Tesla's account and were using it to mine cryptocurrency.Fortune reports that unidentified hackers accessed an unprotected Kubernetes console owned by Tesla, and obtained login credentials to the company's Amazon Web Services cloud.They gained entry to the account using the login credentials, in the process exposing sensitive data stored inside about Tesla's test cars.The hackers than installed crypto mining software, which ran scripts that allowed them to mine cryptocurrency. In order to avoid detection, the intruders deliberately reduced CPU usage and masked their IP addresses.RedLock, the firm that discovered the breach, notified Tesla of the breach on January 30.Tesla has since resolved the issue, and reportedly found no indication that customer privacy or vehicle safety and security were compromised.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hackers obtain login credentials from Tesla's unprotected Kubernetes console2. Hackers access Tesla's AWS cloud, which contains data on test cars3. Hackers run crypto mining software to generate cryptocurrency4. Hackers reduced CPU usage, mask IP addresses to hide cryptojacking VOICEOVER (in English): "Unidentified hackers accessed an unprotected Kubernetes console owned by Tesla, and obtained login credentials to the company's Amazon Web Services cloud.""They gained entry to the account using the login credentials, in the process exposing sensitive data stored inside about Tesla's test cars.""The hackers then installed crypto mining software, which ran scripts that allowed them to mine cryptocurrency.""In order to avoid detection, the intruders deliberately reduced CPU usage and masked their IP addresses."SOURCES: Fortune, PCMaghttp://fortune.com/2018/02/20/tesla-hack-amazon-cloud-cryptocurrency-mining/https://www.pcmag.com/news/359340/cryptocurrency-miner-infiltrates-a-tesla-cloud-server***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 11:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/21/3553041/3553041_EFA3BEEA4F4C4DC396EC7D4D5D2734DF_180221_3553041_Tesla_cloud_account_hijacked_to_mine_cryptocurre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/120/16F/12016F04EF364A74B5A0A134B8090F61_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, crypto jacking, crypto mining, monero, tesla, cryptocurrency mining, tesla hacked, hackers, cyber criminals, crypto crime, crypto criminals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552969</guid>
      <title>How gun background checks work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWhen a person wants to buy a gun from a federal firearms licensed dealer (FFL), he or she must provide identification and pass a federal background check, according to Fox News. Buyers must fill out the Bureau of Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives' 4473 form. The form asks basic information with a Social Security Number suggested, but not required. The form also asks questions about criminal background, mental health and immigration status. After form 4473 is filled out, the dealer submits it to the National Instant Criminal Background Check System (NICS) online or over the phone. If the NICS indicates the purchase can proceed, the gun sale can continue. If the NICS cancels or denies the form, the seller cannot legally sell the gun to the buyer. If the NICS marks the form as delayed, the sale cannot be completed for three business days. Unless a denied designation is issued, the firearms purchase can proceed after the three days. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Buyer filling out ATF Form 44732. Questions asked on Form 44733. Gun sellers send completed Form 4473 to NICS4. NICS approves, denies or delays gun saleVOICEOVER (in English): "When a person wants to buy a gun from a federally licensed firearms dealer, he or she must provide identification and pass a federal background check by filling out ATF Form 4473." "The form asks basic information with a Social Security Number suggested, but not required. It also asks questions about criminal background, mental health and immigration status." "After form 4473 is filled out, the dealer submits it to the National Instant Criminal Background Check System (NICS) online or by phone." "The NICS will then allow the sale to proceed, be denied or canceled, or be delayed for three business days. With a delay, unless a denied designation is issued, the firearms purchase can proceed after the three days." SOURCES: Fox News http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/02/20/how-do-gun-background-checks-work-look-at-current-system.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 10:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/21/3552969/3552969_95F84982393A45B5ADB24AB28CC9C20B_180221_3552969_How_gun_background_checks_work_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9E7/CC8/9E7CC87967FB4F6BA095127B6FC9713E_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, gun background checks, federal gun background checks, gun purchases, firearms sales, NICS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552923</guid>
      <title>Tallest wooden skyscraper conceptualized for Tokyo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan's Sumitomo Forestry Company has unveiled plans to construct a 350-meter-tall wooden skyscraper in Tokyo.The 70-storey building would consist of 10% metal and 90% percent wood, with balconies that span all sides. Sumitomo says the interior of building will be made of pure wood, and will contain 8,000 homes.The building would use a brace tube structure system made from timber and steel. This comprises a column and beam framework, with steel braces inserted diagonally. This is meant to protect against deformation from forces such as wind and earthquakes. Sumitomo hopes to complete the building come 2041 to mark their 350th anniversary.The estimated cost of the project is 600 billion yen, or 5.6 billion dollars.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of concept building's outline, along with materials used2. Depiction of concept building's braced tube structure3. Depiction of concept building interior and amount of homes4. Depiction of concept building in TokyoVOICEOVER (in English): "Japan's Sumitomo Forestry Company has unveiled plans to construct a 350-meter-tall wooden skyscraper in Tokyo.""The 70-storey building would consist of 10% metal and 90% percent wood.""The building would use a brace tube structure system made from timber and steel.""This comprises a column and beam framework, with steel braces inserted diagonally.""This is meant to protect against deformation from forces such as wind and earthquakes.""Sumitomo says the interior of building will be made of pure wood, and will contain 8,000 homes.""The building will also feature balconies that span around each side.""Sumitomo hopes to complete the building come 2041 to mark their 350th anniversary."SOURCES: Sumitomo Forestry Company, BBC, Arch Daily, Design Boomhttp://sfc.jp/english/news/pdf/20180214_e_01.pdfhttp://sfc.jp/information/news/2018/2018-02-08.htmlhttp://www.bbc.com/news/technology-42839463https://www.archdaily.com/889142/japan-plans-for-supertall-wooden-skyscraper-in-tokyo-by-2041https://www.designboom.com/architecture/tokyo-plans-worlds-tallest-wooden-skyscraper-2041/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/21/3552923/3552923_5C80ADD1184C4025B91B769876C3F760_180221_3552923_Tallest_wooden_skyscraper_conceptualized_for_Tok_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/650/F33/650F332CCA69441BB49E5DDF17E31ABB_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tallest wooden skyscraper, sumitomo forest company, worlds tallest building, mega projects, skyscraper construction, wood skyscraper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552899</guid>
      <title>Mount Sinabung spews ash over Indonesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIndonesia's Mount Sinabung started spewing ash earlier this week, prompting the country to issue flight warnings.According to the Guardian, volcanic ash had been sent to heights of 7 kilometers. If ash comes into contact with aircraft engine, glass inside it can melt inside the combustion chamber, reports Wired. That can cause the plane's blades to stick together and stall the engine.Ash particles can also become lodged inside the pitot tubes, a plane's airspeed sensors. If blocked, they may provide pilots with false readings.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of eruption2. Depiction of eruption 3. Depiction of ash in plane engine4. Depiction of ash on planeVOICEOVER (in English): "Indonesia's Mount Sinabung started spewing ash earlier this week, prompting the country to issue flight warnings.""According to the Guardian, volcanic ash had been sent to heights of 7 kilometers.""If ash comes into contact with aircraft engine, glass inside it can melt inside the combustion chamber.""That can cause the plane's blades to stick together and stall the engine.""Ash particles can also become lodged inside the pitot tubes, a plane's airspeed sensors. "If blocked, they may provide pilots with false readings."SOURCES: The Guardian, Wiredhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/feb/20/indonesia-flight-warnings-mount-sinabung-volcano-ash-cloudhttps://www.wired.com/2014/08/volcano-ash-planes/https://www.wired.com/2015/07/volcanic-ash-closes-airports-across-indonesia/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/21/3552899/3552899_EE3BDB2A73CA4F5FA7020B46408E9000_180221_3552899_Mount_Sinabung_spews_ash_over_Indonesia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/82A/195/82A19501861F4CEBB352BB2FF0F3CC45_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mt sinabung, mount sinabung eruption, flights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552842</guid>
      <title>Human-sheep hybrids could grow human organs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers in California are working on reducing organ transplant rejections by using sheep and pig embryos with human cells.The team introduced adult stem cells into early-stage sheep embryos, and then returned them to the sheep to grow for three more weeks, Newsweek reported.The scientists say they achieved sheep embryos where one in every 10,000 cells was human. The findings were presented by Hiro Nakauchi from Stanford University and Pablo Ross from the University of California at the American Association for the Advancement of Science's annual meeting in Austin, Texas, UPI reported. In the U.S. alone last year, 34,770 organ transplants were performed, while 115,035 people are currently waiting for a transplant. Around 20 people die daily waiting for transplants.The research is still in its preliminary stages, but Nakauchi is optimistic that humans will one day receive organs grown in animals. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Researchers working on sheep embryos in the lab2. Researchers adding adult stem cells to sheep embryos3. Researchers achieved sheep embryos where one in every ten thousand were human cells4. Organ transplant and organ transplant waiting listVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers in California are working on reducing organ transplant rejections by using sheep and pig embryos to grow human organs.""Scientists introduced adult stem cells into early-stage sheep embryos, and then returned them to the sheep to grow for three more weeks." "They achieved sheep embryos where one in every 10,000 cells was human.""In the U.S. last year, 34,770 organ transplants were performed, while 115,035 people are currently waiting for a transplant. Around 20 people die daily waiting for transplants."SOURCES: UPI, Newsweekhttps://www.upi.com/Health_News/2018/02/19/Researchers-grow-human-cells-in-sheep-embryos/4381519060735/?spt=su&or=btn_twhttp://www.newsweek.com/sheep-cells-organ-transplants-embryo-810865***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 07:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/21/3552842/3552842_8BA49D8F691B4D099C6A1122BE1BCB62_180221_3552842_Human_sheep_hybrids_could_grow_human_organs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1E9/7DD/1E97DDF0A53E44078CD0FDEE696100AC_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, organ transplant, sheep embryos, pig embryos, human stem cell, human-sheep hybrid, human organs grown animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3552673</guid>
      <title>FIFA World Cup ball contains NFC chip</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe official World Cup match ball has a built-in chip that links up with users' smartphones.According to FIFA, the Adidas Telstar 18 features a near-field communication (NFC) chip. When the ball is tapped by a smartphone, it shows users personalized content. This feature is designed for consumer use and not World Cup matches. The Telstar 18 is also made up of six thermally bonded panels, each layered with a 3D-textured surface. This is said to provide players with greater control in different weather conditions. The ball's design is based on the iconic black and white Telstar ball from the 1970 World Cup ball. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of NFC chip.2. Depiction of ball's layers3. Depiction of ball in different weather conditions4. Depiction of 1970 Telstar ball and Telstar 18VOICEOVER (in English): "The Adidas Telstar 18 features a near-field communication chip." "When the ball is tapped by a smartphone, it'll show users personalized content.This feature is designed for consumer use and not world cup matches.""The Telstar 18 is also made up of six thermally bonded panels, each layered with a 3D-textured surface.""This is said to provide players with greater control in different weather conditions.""The ball's design is based on the iconic black and white Telstar ball from the 1970 World Cup ball."SOURCES: FIFA, Adidas, SoccerProVideo (YouTube), Reuters http://www.fifa.com/worldcup/news/y=2017/m=11/news=2018-fifa-world-cuptm-official-match-ball-unveiled-an-exciting-re-imag-2919272.htmlhttps://www.adidas.com/us/fifa-world-cup-official-game-ball/CE8083.htmlhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_HryrlnSeWMhttps://www.reuters.com/article/soccer-worldcup-ball/soccer-fifa-revives-the-1970-world-cup-ball-idUSL8N1NFA1T***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 03:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/21/3552673/3552673_D33BCC2EC2454F80A4A02D3A4C331150_180221_3552673_FIFA_World_Cup_ball_contains_NFC_chip_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B0C/2DD/B0C2DD7D00B14756820A4ECC1290470E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, world cup 2018, world cup smart ball, telstar 18, world cup 1970, nfc adidas ball, adidas world cup ball]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3553779</guid>
      <title>Chinese firms to build solar power plant near Chernobyl</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOnce the site of the world's worst nuclear disaster, Chernobyl is now undergoing a makeover that will turn it into a source of renewable energy.Reuters reports that Ukraine's Chernobyl power plant contaminated the region with radiation when it exploded in 1986, but is now being covered by a steel arch that will be completed in 2018.Surrounding the plant is an exclusion zone of forest and marshland, which the government allowed to be developed once the radiation was under control.Two Chinese firms plan to revive the the area by building a 1-gigawatt solar photovoltaic plant within the exclusion zone.The Chinese have previously converted damaged and contaminated land in its own territory into solar and wind farms, and hope to undertake the same endeavor globally.Aside from the Chinese project, a Ukrainian-German company has also begun installing solar panels just a hundred meters from the decommissioned nuclear plant, reports AFP.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New Safe Confinement covering damaged Chernobyl power plant2. Exclusion zone around Chernobyl for development; radiation under control3. Chinese companies to build giant 1-gigawatt solar power plant in exclusion zone4. China's previous experience turning damaged land into solar, wind farmsVOICEOVER (in English): "Ukraine's Chernobyl power plant contaminated the region with radiation when it exploded in 1986, but is now being covered by a steel arch that will be completed in 2018.""Surrounding the plant is an exclusion zone of forest and marshland, which the government allowed to be developed once the radiation was under control.""Two Chinese firms plan to revive the the area by building a 1-gigawatt solar photovoltaic plant within the exclusion zone.""The Chinese have previously converted damaged and contaminated land in its own territory into solar and wind farms, and hope to undertake the same endeavor globally."SOURCES: Reuters, AFPhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-solar-chernobyl/chinese-solar-firm-to-build-plant-in-chernobyl-exclusion-zone-idUSKBN13G0DMhttp://www.news.com.au/technology/environment/chernobyl-nuclear-power-plant-transformed-into-a-massive-solar-plant/news-story/2d8d365ca1a6a7bde0c75c2372e888ed***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 13:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/22/3553779/3553779_B1AF004EB7144533AD110256A6F0F2F8_180222_3553779_Chinese_firms_to_build_solar_power_plant_near_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E94/016/E9401691A6734DA4ACCF2D45A584EE68_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, chernobyl, nuclear, nuclear reactor, radiation, chernobyl power plant, china, solar power plant, solar power, solar energy, renewable energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3553412</guid>
      <title>Pod planes concept could change commercial aviation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at Switzerland's Federal Polytechnic Institute have conceptualized a new to ferry cargo and passengers.The pod plane concept could one day allow passengers to borad at rail stations. These pods each measure 30 meters in length. After being ferried to the airport, the pod would join others under a giant 60-meter wing.This modular concept aircraft is one of several developed by Swiss researchers called Clip-Air. According to CNN, its speed and range would be around the same as most mid-sized commercial aircraft.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of passengers at station entering pods2. Depiction of pods joining pod plane 3. Depiction of pod plane taking off 4. Depiction of pod plane flyingVOICEOVER (in English): "Developed at the Federal Polytechnic Institute, the pod plane concept could one day allow passengers to board at rail stations.""These pods each measure 30 meters in length.""After being ferried to the airport, the pod would join others under a giant 60-meter wing.""This modular concept aircraft is one of several developed by Swiss researchers called Clip-Air.""According to CNN, its speed and range would be around the same as most mid-sized commercial aircraft"SOURCES: Federal Polytechnic Institute, CNNhttps://clipair.epfl.chhttps://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/clip-air-pod-airplane-concept/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/22/3553412/3553412_E74C978337AB4A22B9D004027F3504E8_180222_3553412_Pod_planes_concept_could_change_commercial_aviat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/355/6F0/3556F017C4C94CC4AEF3EDB1E21E231C_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, future aircraft, aviation technology clip air, pod planes, epfl]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3554548</guid>
      <title>NASA study confirms Antarctica is rapidly losing ice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has provided the sharpest image yet on how fast the Antarctic ice sheets are melting.NASA reports that the research, published in the journal Cryosphere, used new software and computer vision techniques to look at data compiled over seven years. They found that in 2015, Antarctica lost roughly 1,929 gigatons of ice, 89 percent of which was from the western part of the continent.The study confirms that the West Antarctic ice sheets are melting more rapidly than those in the east, with glacier flows increasing in response to warming oceans.The area has also experienced major iceberg calving incidents in recent years, which renders the larger region of ice left behind more prone to melting.If the entire Western Antarctic ice sheet were to melt, a study from PNAS estimated it could cause a 3-meter rise in global sea levels.Scientists say the loss of the ice sheet might be inevitable unless the world can manage to decarbonize in the near future and keep emissions low.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Antarctica's overall ice loss in 2015 2. West Antarctic ice sheets melting more rapidly than those in the east3. Iceberg calving makes the ice left behind more vulnerable to melting4. Sea level might rise 9 feet if entire ice sheet were to meltVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers found that in 2015, Antarctica lost roughly 1,929 gigatons of ice, 89% of which was from the western part of the continent.""The study confirms that the West Antarctic ice sheets are melting more rapidly than those in the east, with glacier flows increasing in response to warming oceans.""The area has also experienced major iceberg calving incidents in recent years, which renders the larger region of ice left behind more prone to melting.""If the entire Western Antarctic ice sheet were to melt, previous studies estimate it could cause a 3-meter rise in global sea levels."SOURCES: Cryosphere, NASA, PNAS, International Business Timeshttps://www.the-cryosphere.net/12/521/2018/tc-12-521-2018.pdfhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/jpl/new-study-brings-antarctic-ice-loss-into-sharper-focushttp://www.pnas.org/content/112/46/14191http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/revolutionary-nasa-technique-captures-melting-antarctic-ice-like-never-before-1663181***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 14:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/23/3554548/3554548_611A71534A9A4C60AB22271B09B3B9D7_180223_3554548_NASA_study_confirms_Antarctica_is_rapidly_losing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BD0/62B/BD062BA6426447F38D5952B7264A58CE_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, antarctica, ice melting, west antarctic ice sheet, antarctica losing ice, antarctic ice loss, global warming, climate change, NASA, glacier flow, glacial melt, sea level rise]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3556258</guid>
      <title>Airbus flying drone taxi takes flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe flying car concept is a step closer to reality after Airbus successfully flew their drone taxi prototype last month.At the end of January, Airbus silicon valley carried out their first successful test of their autonomous aircraft. The all-electric drone flew at a height of 16 feet for 53 seconds by itself.According to Engadget, Airbus hopes to create a network of autonomous flying drones. The company aims to create a production-ready drone by 2020, the Verge reported.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of drone taking off during flight test2. Depiction of drone hovering during flight test3. Depiction of passenger getting into drone4. Depiction of drone flying over cityVOICEOVER (in English): "At the end of January, Airbus silicon valley carried out their first successful test of their autonomous aircraft.""The all-electric drone flew at a height of 16 feet for 53 seconds by itself.""According to Engadget, Airbus hopes to create a network of autonomous flying drones.""The Verge reports that Airbus aims to create a production-ready drone by 2020."SOURCES: Vahana, Engadget, The Verge, The Weekhttps://vahana.aero/vahanas-first-flight-a-success-ade26d26ba02https://www.engadget.com/2018/02/01/airbus-drone-taxi-first-test-flight/https://www.theverge.com/2018/2/22/17036750/airbus-vahana-flying-taxi-electric-first-flighthttps://www.theverge.com/2018/2/1/16961688/airbus-vahana-evtol-first-test-flighthttp://www.theweek.co.uk/91376/airbus-drone-taxi-completes-maiden-flight***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 11:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/26/3556258/3556258_921DDBAFC62C44949F3B6398359EAD27_180226_3556258_Airbus_flying_drone_taxi_takes_flight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/73D/0F9/73D0F95AD1144673858523B5F7A773D2_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, airbus, flying taxi drone, flying taxi drones, airbus, a3, a3 taxi drone, drone network]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3556247</guid>
      <title>Apple storing iCloud keys in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina-based iCloud users' data will be stored in servers based in the People's Republic of China from the end of February.Apple will move China-based iCloud users' data and keys from its servers in the U.S. to China. The company told Reuters this to comply with Chinese law.If a user's Apple device is connected to an iCloud account, it typically backs up photos, emails, messages, contacts and other information. From the end of February, Chinese authorities will be able to issue Apple with a warrant to access this data. According to Reuters, this only applies to users who set their home as China. Users in Hong Kong and Macau are not affected.The data will be stored on servers of state-controlled firm Guizhou-Cloud Big Data. Many are concerned how this will impact Chinese users' privacy, reported Reuters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of iCloud data and keys being moved.2. Depiction of what is stored on iCloud3. Depiction of access4. Depiction of iCloud in ChinaVOICEOVER (in English): "At the end of February, Apple will move China-based iCloud users' data and keys from its servers in the U.S. to China.""The company says this to comply with Chinese law.""If a user's Apple device is connected to an iCloud account, it typically backs up photos, emails, messages, contacts and other information.""From the end of February, Chinese authorities will be able to issue Apple with a warrant to access this data.""This only applies to users who set their home as China. Users in Hong Kong and Macau are not affected.""The data will be stored on state-controlled firm Guizhou-Cloud Big Data servers.""Many are concerned how this will impact China-based users' privacy."SOURCES: Reuters, Engadgethttps://www.reuters.com/article/china-apple-icloud/rpt-insight-apple-moves-to-store-icloud-keys-in-china-raising-human-rights-fears-idUSL2N1QG01Rhttps://www.engadget.com/2018/02/25/apple-will-store-icloud-keys-in-china/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 11:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/26/3556247/3556247_BDDFBA86B17746AB812B9D627A8C1E31_180226_3556247_Apple_storing_iCloud_keys_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/418/F0D/418F0DC40F434C858AF47FDC54E8E6A1_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, privacy in china, china privacy, apple icloud china, apple moves icloud to china, china data centers, apple, apple in china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3556127</guid>
      <title>Archaeologists uncover ancient necropolis in Egypt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn Egyptian mission has found an ancient necropolis south of Cairo containing several tombs, artifacts, and a fully preserved mummy.Reuters reports that archaeologists at the Tuna Al-Gabal site near Minya, Egypt uncovered a large number of burial shafts believed to be more than 2,000 years old.The mummified remains of a high priest of the Egyptian god Thoth were unearthed in the tombs, along with 1,000 figurines and four canopic jars made of alabaster.The team also found 40 limestone sarcophagi of various shapes and sizes, which may have belonged to the priest's family members.Excavation on the site began in late 2017 and is expected to continue on for at least five years.Egypt is planning to use the recent discoveries to revive tourism in the area, which was a popular destination for antiquities sightseeing until the political turmoil in 2011.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Large number of burial shafts discovered in Minya, Egypt2. Mummified remains of high priest of Thoth, statues, canopic jars found in tomb3. 40 sarcophagi believed to contain remains of priest's family members4. Excavation to take five years; artifacts to become new tourist attractionVOICEOVER (in English): "Archaeologists at the site near Minya, Egypt uncovered a large number of burial shafts believed to be more than 2,000 years old.""The mummified remains of a high priest of the Egyptian god Thoth were unearthed in the tombs, along with 1,000 figurines and four jars made of alabaster.""The team also found 40 limestone sarcophagi of various shapes and sizes, which may have belonged to the priest's family members.""Excavation on the site began in late 2017 and is expected to continue on for at least five years."SOURCES: Egypt Independent, Ahram Online, Reutershttp://www.egyptindependent.com/photos-egypt-announces-large-discovery-of-26th-dynasty-cemetery-in-minya/http://english.ahram.org.eg/NewsContent/9/40/291590/Heritage/Ancient-Egypt/th-Dynasty-cemetery-uncovered-in-Egypts-Minya.aspxhttps://in.reuters.com/article/egypt-archaeology/egypt-uncovers-ancient-necropolis-south-of-cairo-idINKCN1G80QS***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 09:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/26/3556127/3556127_B532655AE624495A9CE43CFC8E800629_180226_3556127_Archaeologists_uncover_ancient_necropolis_in_Egy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/167/8F1/1678F10DEF6F43E6BFF2E96A91E35F6B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, necropolis, egypt necropolis, ancient necropolis, ancient burial, egyptian tomb, tomb, cemetery, archaeologists, thoth, mummy, sarcophagus, egypt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3556107</guid>
      <title>Ancient underwater Mayan site threatened by pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe world's largest underwater archaeological site could be under threat from pollution.Speaking to British newspaper The Telegraph, archaeologist Guillermo de Anda said that the Sac Actun cave system in the Yucatan Peninsula maybe under threat from pollution and development. Many tourists use sinkholes the caves for snorkeling, The Telegraph reported.Reuters reports researchers recently found a network of 248 sinkholes throughout the 216 mile system. They also discovered 9,000 year-old human remains, as well bones of a giant sloth and ancient elephant.The discovery could help provide new information on the ancient Mayan civilization.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of cave system2. Depiction of underwater cave system3. Depiction of underwater cave4. Depiction of collapsing highway and people snorkelingVOICEOVER (in English): "The Sac Actun cave system is located on the Yucatan Peninsula, south of Cancun on the Mexican coast.""It is believed it to be the world's largest underwater cave system.""Recently, researchers found a network of 248 sinkholes spanning 216 miles there.""Divers also found 9,000-year-old human remains as well as bones from ancient elephants, extinct bears and giant sloths.""Archaeologists say the cave system may be under threat from pollution.""Many tourists use sinkholes for snorkeling, and a nearby coastal highway has been known to break apart and fall into the sinkholes."SOURCES: The Telegraph, Reutershttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/02/20/worlds-important-underwater-archaeological-site-threat-pollution/ https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-cave/ancient-human-remains-ice-age-animal-bones-found-in-giant-mexican-cave-idUSKCN1G40V3***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 08:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/26/3556107/3556107_572D89389A0A4A1E8D052DB6552173C2_180226_3556107_Ancient_underwater_Mayan_site_threatened_by_poll_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A8D/67C/A8D67CD170714DF489D2D70EE7ABF82E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, great mayan quifer project, underwater archaeological site, mayan civilization, yucatan peninsula, guillermo de anda]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3556796</guid>
      <title>New drug can kill flu in one day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Japanese health ministry has approved a groundbreaking new drug that can get rid of the flu in just one day.Nikkei reports that Osaka-based pharmaceutical company Shionogi has been cleared to manufacture and market its new drug Xofluza, which could rival Tamiflu, made by Swiss drugmaker Roche. The influenza virus causes an infection in the respiratory tract when it is transmitted. The virus hijacks the cells to make copies of itself, which then burst forth and infect other cells.Antivirals like Tamiflu are taken in multiple doses over several days, and stop the virus by binding to a coating on its surface to inhibit its ability to escape an infected cell.The new drug Xofluza requires a single pill, and suppresses virus replication by targeting an enzyme.During trials, the drug was shown to eliminate the flu virus in 24 hours, compared to three days using Tamiflu.Xofluza was approved in just four months under Japan's fast-track drug review system, and is set to go on sale once a price is determined by the government.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of flu virus spreading in the body2. Depiction of how current flu medication fights the virus3. Depiction of how Xofluza works4. Depiction of Xofluza killing off flu virus within 24 hoursVOICEOVER (in English): "When the influenza virus enters the body, it hijacks the cells to make copies of itself, which then burst forth and infect other cells.""Antivirals like Tamiflu are taken in multiple doses over several days, and stop the virus by binding to a coating on its surface to inhibit its ability to escape an infected cell.""New drug Xofluza requires a single pill, and suppresses virus replication by targeting an enzyme the virus needs to multiply.""During trials, the drug was shown to eliminate the flu virus in just 24 hours, compared to three days using Tamiflu."SOURCES: Fortune, Nikkei, Japan Times, University of Bristolhttp://fortune.com/2018/02/23/japan-shionogi-flu-drug-kills-virus-one-day/https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Companies/Singledose-flu-drug-approved-for-sale-in-Japanhttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2018/02/24/national/science-health/one-dose-flu-drug-xofluza-gets-nod-health-ministry/#.WpPMbRNua8ohttp://www.chm.bris.ac.uk/motm/tamiflu/how_work.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 07:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/27/3556796/3556796_B8D0C9753BA54EE79CF1F7A09EFEF447_180227_3556796_New_drug_can_kill_flu_in_one_day_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/067/32C/06732C09B9D44F4BB47227E7572A6897_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, flu, flu outbreak, flu epidemic, flu medicine, cure for flu, flu cure, tamiflu, xofluza, flu pill, japan, shionogi, medicine, medical]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3557659</guid>
      <title>Saudi Neom project awards palace building contracts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSaudi Arabia's awarded the first construction contracts for its Neom mega city project in mid-February.According to Reuters, Saudi Arabia asked companies to develop five palaces in the massive business zone. NEOM is part of Saudi's aim to diversify its economy away from oil and will reportedly be powered by renewable energy.According to British newspaper the Independent, the area NEOM is to be built upon is 33 times larger than New York City. The city will also reportedly have its own judicial system, separate from the rest of Saudi Arabia.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of Neom2. Depiction of palace area3. Depiction of futuristic city street4. Depiction of Neom and New York city sizeVOICEOVER (in English): "NEOM is located near the Saudi Arabia's Red Sea coast, close to where the country borders Jordan and Egypt.""Saudi Arabia asked companies to develop five palaces in the massive business zone.""NEOM is part of Saudi's aim to diversify its economy away from oil and will reportedly be powered by renewable energy.""The area NEOM is to be built upon is 33 times larger than New York City."SOURCES: The Independent, Reutershttp://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/saudi-arabia-building-billion-mega-bigger-new-york-city-a8230731.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/saudi-neom-palaces/update-1-saudi-awards-contracts-to-build-palaces-in-huge-new-business-zone-idUSL8N1PY22T***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 09:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/28/3557659/3557659_A322E453D1D44D36BF969464D357ADF0_180228_3557659_Saudi_Neom_project_awards_palace_building_contra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A89/C63/A89C63CEAB474E1282A108258A9888E0_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, saudi mega city, saudi arabia mega city, saudi arabia new city, saudi arabia vision 2030, saudi arabia, NEOM, neom mega city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3557649</guid>
      <title>Hyperloop commuter pod unveiled in Dubai</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA full-scale hyperloop pod model was unveiled on Thursday, giving a glimpse at the future of Dubai transport.The Khaleej Times reports that the Virgin Hyperloop One and Dubai's Road Transport Authority developed a prototype commuter pod for the hyperloop system, which can travel up to 1,200 kilometers per hour.Pods are divided into two classes, the gold class which can seat five passengers, and the silver, which can accommodate fourteen.Travel time from Dubai to Abu Dhabi is currently an hour and a half by car, but will take only twelve minutes via hyperloop.Initial tests estimate the pod can transport 10,000 people to and from Dubai every hour.Passengers won't not be able to see through any windows to avoid discomfort from the speed, but will be able access entertainment and information systems on the armrests.Though the project is still under testing, the high-speed transportation system could launch as early as 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of hyperloop commuter pod 2. Depiction of commuter pod's gold and silver classes3. Hyperloop reduces travel time from Dubai to Abu Dhabi4. No windows inside hyperloop podVOICEOVER (in English): "Virgin Hyperloop One and Dubai's Road Transport Authority developed a prototype commuter pod for the hyperloop system, which can travel up to 1,200 kilometers per hour.""Pods are divided into two classes, the gold class which can seat five passengers, and the silver, which can accommodate fourteen.""Travel time from Dubai to Abu Dhabi is currently an hour and a half by car, but will take only twelve minutes via hyperloop.""To avoid motion sickness from the high speeds, the pods have no windows, but do offer entertainment and information systems in the armrests."SOURCES: Khaleej Times, Dezeenhttps://www.khaleejtimes.com/news/transport/video-rta-unveils-hyperloop-prototype-in-uae-innovation-month-https://www.dezeen.com/2018/02/26/virgin-unveils-first-prototype-hyperloop-one-passenger-pod/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/28/3557649/3557649_05D7AB991DAF4780B0C98F8356CD5337_180228_3557649_Hyperloop_commuter_pod_unveiled_in_Dubai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/998/628/998628B2A7B24296A0CBF5BC9BCB01CD_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hyperloop one, hyperloop, hyperloop dubai, hyperloop commuter pod, hyperloop pod, virgin hyperloop one, commuter pod, passenger pod, dubai rta]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3557505</guid>
      <title>FIFA mulling VAR for World Cup 2018</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFIFA are likely to use video assistant referees (VAR) during this summer's World Cup, according to Reuters.The technology allows soccer referees and their assistants to review game footage while a match is being played. According to Reuters, it has gained notoriety in Italy's Serie A league where it has caused in-games delays over decisions involving disallowed goals and revoked penalties."The facts are that from almost 1,000 matches which were tested, the accuracy rate of the referees went up from 93 percent to 99 percent," FIFA President Gianni Infantino told Reuters earlier this week. "If we, or I, can do something to make sure that the World Cup is not decided by a referee's mistakes, then I think it's our duty to do it."UEFA boss Aleksander Ceferin said VAR wouldn't feature in the Champions League next season, explaining the technology needed more time to be learned by fans and referees. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of referee pausing game2. Depiction of referee watching screen at side3. Depiction of referee sending someone off4. Depiction of penalty kickVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Reuters, FIFA (YouTube), KNVB, Liverpool Echohttps://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-soccer-fifa/infantino-still-committed-to-var-at-world-cup-idUKKCN1GA1RMhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KmprMLZ0Cichttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qJ7OyOP9muAhttp://www.knvb.nl/downloads/bestand/9844/var-handbook-summaryhttps://www.liverpoolecho.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/var-explained-how-works-its-14215003***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 06:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/02/28/3557505/3557505_1643DF35E4464146A37938DFF89B761B_180228_3557505_FIFA_mulling_VAR_for_World_Cup_2018_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E16/F31/E16F3166974041A288B3EA18B6EF8BDA_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, VAR football technology, FIFA, Video Assistant Referees, What is VAR, VAR explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3558449</guid>
      <title>North Pole thaws in winter amid warming temperatures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists are alarmed at the unusually warm winter in the North Pole and the bizarre cold front that has hit the UK and parts of Europe.The Atlantic reports that Arctic sea ice typically develops a thick layer from late September to early March, with temperatures in the region normally below freezing.This year's Arctic winter, however, is unusually warm. Temperatures have risen to over 36 degrees above normal, and sea ice has started melting.According to The Guardian, a theory known as "warm arctic, cold continents" suggests that as the polar vortex becomes unstable, warm air is taken in and cold air expelled. The North Pole gets hotter as a result, while certain parts of Europe are subjected to unusually frigid weather.Though the theory itself remains debatable, the fact remains that whatever changes happen in the Arctic has a huge impact on the rest of the world.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of a normal Arctic winter2. Depiction of Arctic warming, sea ice melting 3. Depiction of 'warm Arctic, cold continents' theory4. Depiction of cold front in EuropeVOICEOVER (in English): "Arctic sea ice typically develops a thick layer from late September to early March, with temperatures in the region normally below freezing.""This year's Arctic winter, however, is unusually warm. Temperatures have risen to over 36 degrees above normal, and sea ice has started melting.""A theory known as 'warm arctic, cold continents' suggests that as the polar vortex becomes unstable, warm air is taken in and cold air expelled.""The North Pole gets hotter as a result, while certain parts of Europe are subjected to unusually frigid weather."SOURCES: The Guardian, Reuters, CNNhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/feb/27/arctic-warming-scientists-alarmed-by-crazy-temperature-riseshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/27/weather/arctic-temperatures-record-high-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-weather/wacky-weather-makes-arctic-warmer-than-parts-of-europe-idUSKCN1GA2AD***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 10:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/01/3558449/3558449_A116B769474C4A6499000DC130994058_180301_3558449_North_Pole_thaws_in_winter_amid_warming_temperat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1C3/768/1C37681D071D4BC7A69AE25204D9FD1A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Arctic warming, warming Arctic, North Pole warming, Arctic heatwave, Arctic, North Pole, global warming, , climate change, warm Arctic cold continents, europe cold front, snow in Rome]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3558405</guid>
      <title>Study reckons moon came from Earth during synestia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers theorize that the moon was created inside the earth in a new study published this week.The most prominent lunar formation theory holds that the moon was formed when a Mars-sized object named Theia hit the earth 4.6 billion years ago. A cocktail of rock and metal erupted from both celestial bodies, mixing together to birth the moon.New research posits that a collision with something did occur but instead created a giant donut-like spinning mass of vaporized rock called a synestia. Researchers believe the moon was fashioned inside this  potentially over hundreds of years  by atmospheric pressure, extreme heat and rock.Details of the findings were published in the Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Theia hitting early Earth2. Depiction of synestia being formed3. Depiction of moon emerging from synestiaVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets, University of California Davis Newsweek, Nature, Lunar and Planetary Institutehttp://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017JE005333/abstracthttps://www.ucdavis.edu/news/how-moon-formed-inside-vaporized-earth-synestiahttp://www.newsweek.com/moon-formed-moon-formation-inside-earth-origin-theory-spinning-cloud-vaporized-824307https://www.nature.com/articles/nature13539https://www.lpi.usra.edu/exploration/HadeanEarth/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 09:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/01/3558405/3558405_ADF8B92369B54F1090093718B905E57D_180301_3558405_Study_reckons_moon_came_from_Earth_during_synest_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/77C/1DB/77C1DB60A4E045FE98CD63FCF7728E1B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, synestia, what made the moon, moon, synesita animation, lunar research]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
