<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 19:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3773995</guid>
      <title>2D antenna turns wifi signals into e1lectricity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have created a device that can power electronics, wearables, and other devices without the use of batteries or wires, according to MIT News.Researchers from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology created a rectifying antenna, or rectenna, using a thin molybdenum disulphide semiconductor that's only three atoms thick.Electromagnetic waves like Wi-Fi are captured via the device's radio frequency antenna, and then converted into direct current.The rectenna produced 40 microwatts of power when exposed to typical wifi signals of around 150 microwatts, enough to power an LED or silicon chips.According to MIT, early applications for the technology include flexible smartphones and wearable electronics.The device can also reportedly be used to power medical implants or swallowable sensors in place of traditional batteries, which can leak lithium and be lethal to patients.Due to its flexibility, the device can be fabricated to cover large areas. Researchers believe it's possible to develop electronic systems that can wrap around highways, bridges, or office walls.Though the technology has been around for a while, most rectennas are made from rigid materials like silicon or gallium arsenide, according to Science Alert. The MIT team is the first to create a flexible rectenna that can generate a practical amount of electricity.The team's research was published Monday in the journal Nature. They are now reportedly planning to improve efficiency and build more complex systems.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 2D rectenna made with molybdenum disulfide converts wifi signals into direct current2. Rectenna can generate enough power for LED, silicon chips3. Rectenna can be used to power medical implants4. Flexible rectenna can be developed to cover large areasVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology created a rectifying antenna, or rectenna, using a thin molybdenum disulphide semiconductor that's only three atoms thick.""Electromagnetic waves like Wi-Fi are captured via the device's radio frequency antenna, and then converted into direct current.""The rectenna produced 40 microwatts of power when exposed to typical wifi signals of around 150 microwatts, enough to power an LED or silicon chips.""According to MIT, early applications for the technology include flexible smartphones and wearable electronics.""The device can also reportedly be used to power medical implants or swallowable sensors in place of traditional batteries, which can leak lithium and be lethal to patients.""Due to its flexibility, the device can be fabricated to cover large areas. Researchers believe it's possible to develop electronic systems that can wrap around highways, bridges, or office walls."SOURCES: MIT News, The Independent, Science Alerthttps://news.mit.edu/2019/converting-wi-fi-signals-electricity-0128https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/wifi-power-wireless-battery-charging-phone-electricity-generate-a8751156.htmlhttps://www.sciencealert.com/a-new-flexible-device-can-harvest-energy-from-wi-fi-signals-and-turn-it-into-electricity***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 13:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/30/3773995/3773995_F7237111210241A1BB173A441C092D17_190130_3773995_2D_antenna_turns_wifi_signals_into_e1lectricity_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, 2d antenna, rectenna, wifi power, electricity from wifi, MIT, technology, invention, wifi power source, gadget, device, direct current, electric source, power source, electricity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3773593</guid>
      <title>New York's LaGuardia Airport undergoes major renovation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLaGuardia International Airport is being renovated in a push to modernize the aging airport.New York's international airport is being renovated in order to have six concourses and two new arrival and departure halls, the Associated Press reports. It will cover a total of 2.7 million square feet.As much as US$8 billion has been spent to upgrade in an attempt to renovate the New York airport, according to AP.LaGuardia's new Terminal B has already opened in November of last year, complete with 18 new gates, seven of which are expected to open in 2020, according to the New York Post.A new walkway will be used to connect Terminal B to Concourse A, according to AM New York.A new Terminal C is also being built to replace LaGuardia Airport's existing Terminal C and D. It is scheduled to open in 2021.A new rail service connecting LaGuardia International Airport and Manhattan is also expected to open by 2022, according to New York Yimby.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Top shot of the renovated LaGuardia Airport2. Inside Terminal B3. New walkway connecting Terminal B and Concourse A4. Terminal C being flashed blueVOICEOVER (in English): "The Associated Press reports LaGuardia Airport is being renovated in order to have six concourses and two new arrival and departure halls.""It will cover a total of 2.7 million square feet.""LaGuardia's new Terminal B has already opened in November of last year, complete with 18 new gates  seven of which are expected to open in 2020, according to the New York Post.""A new walkway will be used to connect Terminal B to Concourse A, according to AM New York.""A new Terminal C is also being built to replace LaGuardia Airport's existing Terminal C and D." "It is scheduled to open in 2021."SOURCES: New York Yimby, AM New York, NY Post, Associated Presshttps://newyorkyimby.com/2018/07/la-guardia-airports-8-billion-overhaul-making-major-headway.htmlhttps://www.amny.com/transit/laguardia-airport-construction-explained-renovation-plans-timeline-funding-and-more-1.12268455https://nypost.com/2018/11/29/fliers-set-to-get-first-look-at-8b-overhaul-of-laguardia-airport/https://www.apnews.com/53dbb1f10c5f4004894bcd5264858f3c***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 05:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/30/3773593/3773593_B4EED27BB35E4A23B07E542BEFD98E2F_190130_3773593_New_York_s_LaGuardia_Airport_undergoes_major_ren_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, new york, laguardia airport, laguardia airport overhaul, new york airport overhaul, new york laguardia airport renovation, laguardia airport renovation, redesigning laguardia airport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3773494</guid>
      <title>Denmark builds border fence to protect against African swine fever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe BBC reports that Denmark is building a border fence to help protect Danish pigs against the deadly African swine fever.Denmark has started construction on a 70-kilometer long fence along its border with Germany, in an effort to control the migration of wild boars that may be infected with African swine fever.According to the World Organisation for Animal Health, the disease is caused by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family. Symptoms include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen and legs, and diarrhea. In serious cases, it can cause death within 6 to 13 days.The Guardian reports that Denmark's electrified fence will be 1.5 meter tall, and at least 50 centimeters deep to stop boar from burrowing under.According to the BBC, there will be 20 gaps at border crossings and waterways, one gate every kilometer with steps elsewhere for humans, and 20-centimeter openings every 100 meters for small animals.Though African swine fever has not yet been seen in Denmark, the country has over 12 million pigs across 3,000 farms, and pork exports are worth billions of dollars annually.Critics say the fence is not a practical solution, citing gaps at roads due to the E.U.'s open border scheme, and to wild boar populations that can swim across bodies of water.In Germany, the effectiveness of such a structure is also being questioned, since research has shown that the biggest risk of spreading the disease is through contaminated equipment and food.The Danish government is reportedly spending $12 million on the fence, which is expected to be completed later this year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Denmark building fence along border with Germany2. African swine fever virus3. African swine fever symptoms4. Denmark anti-boar border fence features5. Danish pig industry6. Boars can still cross via roads, waterways7. Effectiveness of fence questioned since virus spreads mostly via contaminated equipment, foodVOICEOVER (in English): "Denmark has started construction on a 70-kilometer long fence along its border with Germany, in an effort to control the migration of wild boars that may be infected with African swine fever.""According to the World Organisation for Animal Health, the disease is caused by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family.""Symptoms include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen and legs, and diarrhea. In serious cases, it can cause death within 6 to 13 days.""The Guardian reports that Denmark's electrified fence will be 1.5 meter tall, and at least 50 centimeters deep to stop boar from burrowing under.""According to the BBC, there will be 20 gaps at border crossings and waterways, one gate every kilometer with steps elsewhere for humans, and 20-centimeter openings every 100 meters for small animals.""Though African swine fever has not yet been seen in Denmark, the country has over 12 million pigs across 3,000 farms, and pork exports are worth billions of dollars annually.""Critics say the fence is not a practical solution, citing gaps at roads due to the E.U.'s open border scheme, and to wild boar populations that can swim across bodies of water.""In Germany, the effectiveness of such a structure is also being questioned, since research has shown that the biggest risk of spreading the disease is through contaminated equipment and food."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardian, The Telegraph, World Organisation for Animal Healthhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47027582https://www.theguardian.com/weather/2019/jan/28/denmark-begins-work-on-wall-to-keep-out-wild-boarhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/28/denmark-builds-43-mile-fence-germany-keep-wild-boar/http://www.oie.int/en/animal-health-in-the-world/animal-diseases/african-swine-fever/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 02:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/30/3773494/3773494_9FC2E9E35511422D8A15FA48D147AF75_190130_3773494_Denmark_builds_border_fence_to_protect_against_A_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, african swine fever, border fence, border wall, denmark border fence, denmark fence, anti-pig fence, anti-boar fence, ASF, wild boar, pig disease, wild boar disease]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3773464</guid>
      <title>China has lowest number of births since 1961</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina reported that it had 15.23 million births in 2018, the lowest since 1961 when 11.87 million births were recorded, according to financial services firm Wind Info. According to the Associated Press, citing National Bureau of Statistics data, this puts China's current population at 1.395 billion for 2018. According to Business Insider, when countries fail to have enough children and have an increasing elderly population, the economy usually underperforms. China's one-child policy, carried out from more than 35 years between 1979 and 2015, resulted in an artificially slowed population growth that favored males. This has led to an over abundance of senior citizens with a shrinking young worker base to support them. Beijing is aware of the coming demographics time bomb, but so far has only used marketing and advertising to address falling fertility rates.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China births in 2018 and 1961; current population2. Fewer children, more elderly lead to underperforming economy3. One-child policy consequences4. AdvertisementsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to financial services firm Wind Info, China reported that it had 15.23 million births in 2018, the lowest since 1961 when 11.87 million births were recorded.""According to the Associated Press, citing National Bureau of Statistics data, this puts China's current population at 1.395 billion for 2018." "According to Business Insider, when countries fail to have enough children and have an increasing elderly population, the economy usually underperforms. "China's one-child policy, carried out from more than 35 years between 1979 and 2015, resulted in an artificially slowed population growth that favored males." "This has led to an over abundance of senior citizens with a shrinking young worker base to support them." "Beijing is aware of the coming demographics time bomb, but so far has only used marketing and advertising to address falling fertility rates." SOURCES: CNBC, Business Insiderhttps://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/21/population-growth-china-records-lowest-number-of-births-since-1961.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/china-one-child-policy-demographic-time-bomb-2017-5***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 01:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/30/3773464/3773464_A18C0A0AFC65429FAC91BD72AE124AE3_190130_3773464_China_has_lowest_number_of_births_since_1961_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China birth rate, China lowest birth rate, China population, China demographic time bomb, China One-Child policy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3774627</guid>
      <title>Two hacker groups stole $1 billion from cryptocurrency exchanges, study says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo hacker groups are responsible for a majority of the cybercrime carried out against cryptocurrency exchanges, alleges a new report. Combined, the two groups have stolen roughly $1 billion in cryptocurrency. According to Bitcoin.com, digital surveillance company Chainalysis identified two groups behind many of the hacks in the field in its latest "crypto crime" report.Analysts say on average, each hack from either of the two groups involved around $90 million per incident. Chainalysis says the first hacking group is a "giant, tightly controlled organization" that could be driven in part by non-monetary goals. The second group is smaller, less organized and more brazen, but primarily focused on money. According to the report, at least 50 percent of stolen cryptocurrency were converted into hard currency through some type of conversion service within 112 days of the hacks. Chainalysis said 64.3 percent of the funds were sent to centralized cryptocurrency exchanges, 11.9 percent to peer-to-peer exchanges and the other 23.8 percent used conversion services such as mixing services, bitcoin ATMs and gambling sites. The report found, "exchanges are regularly processing the stolen funds, allowing the hackers to convert the funds to traditional currencies or other cryptocurrencies." This is due to the fact that the stolen funds look like they are coming from the legitimate owners to the exchanges not hacked. It can also be difficult for exchanges to tell if cryptocurrency has been stolen without having specialized investigation software. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two hacker groups stealing crypto from exchanges2. Exchange being hacked 3. Stolen crypto being converted to hard currency4. Services hackers used to convert stolen fundsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new report from digital surveillance company Chainalysis alleges two hacker groups are responsible for a majority of the cybercrime carried out against cryptocurrency exchanges. Combined, the two groups have stolen roughly $1 billion in cryptocurrency." "Analysts say on average, each hack from either of the two groups involved around $90 million per incident." "According to the report, at least 50 percent of stolen cryptocurrency were converted into hard currency through some type of conversion service within 112 days of the hacks." "Chainalysis said 64.3 percent of the funds were sent to centralized cryptocurrency exchanges, 11.9 percent to peer-to-peer exchanges and the other 23.8 percent used conversion services such as mixing services, bitcoin ATMs and gambling sites."SOURCES: Bitcoin.comhttps://news.bitcoin.com/report-two-hacker-groups-stole-1-billion-from-crypto-exchanges/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 11:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/31/3774627/3774627_701121EACD214D0B83629F8BF82FACD3_190131_3774627_Two_hacker_groups_stole__1_billion_from_cryptocu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cryptocurrency, crypto exchange, cryptocurrency hack, cybercrime, hacking groups, hacking digital currency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3774620</guid>
      <title>New sensor could lead to artificial skin with superhuman perception</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new type of sensor developed by researchers could lead to artificial skin that could help burn victims "feel" and help protect workers, according to a paper in Advanced Materials.The skin's ability to sense pressure, heat, cold and vibration is an important safety function. Burn victims, those with prosthetic limbs and others who have lost skin sensitivity can often hurt themselves on accident. According to UConn Today, researchers from the University of Connecticut and University of Toronto wanted to create a sensor that could mimic the sensing abilities of the skin, as well as the ability to detect magnetic fields and sound waves. The scientists made a sensor with a silicone tube wrapped in a copper wire and filled with a solution of iron oxide nanoparticles.An electric current is created when the nanoparticles rub the inside of the silicone tube, which is picked up as a signal from the copper wire. Researchers were able to distinguish between pressure, sound waves and magnetic fields. They were also able to tell the differences between electrical signals caused by walking, running, jumping and swimming. The team hope the sensors will someday be able to help burn victims "feel" again or be used as an early warning system for workers exposed to high magnetic fields. The scientists will now work to see if they can make a functional sensor into a flat configuration more like skin. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sensor can detect touch, magnetic fields and sound waves2. Scientists making sensor in lab3. Sensor's abilities4. Sensors may someday help burn victims and workersVOICEOVER (in English): "According to UConn Today, researchers from the University of Connecticut and University of Toronto wanted to create a sensor that could mimic the sensing abilities of the skin, as well as the ability to detect magnetic fields and sound waves." "The scientists made a sensor with a silicone tube wrapped in a copper wire and filled with a solution of iron oxide nanoparticles.""An electric current is created when the nanoparticles rub the inside of the silicone tube, which is picked up as a signal from the copper wire." "Researchers were able to distinguish between pressure, sound waves and magnetic fields. They were also able to tell the differences between electrical signals caused by walking, running, jumping and swimming." "The team hope the sensors will someday be able to help burn victims 'feel' again or be used as an early warning system for workers exposed to high magnetic fields." SOURCES: Science Daily, University of Connecticut https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/01/190128174554.htmhttps://today.uconn.edu/2019/01/artificial-skin-give-superhuman-perception/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 11:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/31/3774620/3774620_27C815318CC541A5A924CDC2041D3D03_190131_3774620_New_sensor_could_lead_to_artificial_skin_with_su_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, artificial skin, nanoparticles, nanoparticles sensor, iron oxide nanoparticles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3774298</guid>
      <title>Scientists lead mission to explore depths of the Indian Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA group of researchers from a nonprofit research institute called Nekton is leading a  three-year-expedition to explore the Indian Ocean.According to reports from Nekton, the team will leave the coast of Bremerhaven, Germany on January 25 on a diving vessel called the Ocean Zephyr headed to the Seychelles.The Seychelles is an archipelago comprised of 115 islands with an exclusive economic zone that covers roughly 1.4 million square kilometers. The country has committed to protecting 30 percent of its national waters.The team will spend seven weeks mapping the ocean floor, studying underwater life and dropping sensors to depths of 2,000 meters in the waters surrounding the Seychelles. The mission plans to conduct at least 50 first descents in areas around the islands. Their main objective is to gather data that will be used for environmental conservation.The team will be providing live broadcasts of their descents using new subsea communication technologies. The mission's principal scientist, Lucy Woodall, stated: "We expect to discover dozens of species new to science that could be anything from new corals, algae or sponges to larger more charismatic animals like dog-sharks."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Trajectory of first phase of the mission from Germany to the Seychelles2. Geographic location and size of the Seychelles3. Methods of gathering information in the Indian Ocean4. 50 first descents around the islandsVOICEOVER (in English): "A group of researchers from a nonprofit research institute called Nekton is leading a  three-year-expedition to explore the Indian Ocean.""The team will leave the coast of Bremerhaven, Germany on January 25 on a diving vessel called the Ocean Zephyr headed to the Seychelles."The Seychelles is an archipelago comprised of 115 islands with an exclusive economic zone that covers roughly 1.4 million square kilometers. The country has committed to protecting 30 percent of its national waters.""According to Nekton, the team will spend seven weeks mapping the ocean floor, studying underwater life and dropping sensors to depths of 2,000 meters in the waters surrounding the Seychelles.""The mission plans to conduct at least 50 first descents in areas around the islands. Their main objective is to gather data that will be used for environmental conservation."SOURCES: Nekton, AP, Living ithttps://nektonmission.org/missions/mission-ii/overviewhttps://www.ap.org/en-gb/topics/indian-oceanhttps://www.apnews.com/2d6bbd4d97ec48e3b75fcdcc44ff2dfchttp://www.livingit.euronews.com/2019/01/24/the-deep-ocean-is-the-final-frontier***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 05:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/31/3774298/3774298_D829034A66354FEFB0CD837849C7D01C_190131_3774298_Scientists_lead_mission_to_explore_depths_of_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Indian ocean, ocean exploration, seychelles, nexton, ocean exploration mission, deep sea, deep sea exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3774275</guid>
      <title>Royal Caribbean reveals world's longest sea waterslide</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRoyal Caribbean's Navigator of the Seas will have the world's longest waterslide at sea measuring roughly 244 meters in length.Royal Caribbean's Navigator of the Seas vessel is undergoing a $115 million remodeling. This includes the construction of the world's longest waterslide at sea, measuring roughly 244 meters in length.According to Geek, the new slide called "The Blaster" will have the capacity of launching a two-person raft down the slide using five waterjets.A section of the slide protrudes off the edge of the ship and other areas of the tube are transparent giving guests a unique view of the ocean.Opposite to "The Blaster" is another slide called "Riptide." This mat-racer slide also has a transparent part that curves off the side of the cruise ship.The remodeled Navigator of the Seas will be launched again on February 24. It will be setting sail from the coast of Miami to the Bahamas.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Royal Caribbean's Navigator of the Seas size and location of new "The Blaster"slide2. Capacity and technology of "The Blaster"3. Transparent section of "The Blaster"4. Location and transparent section of new "Riptide" slideVOICEOVER (in English): "Royal Caribbean's Navigator of the Seas vessel is undergoing a $115 million remodeling. This includes the construction of the world's longest waterslide at sea measuring roughly 244 meters in length.""According to Geek, the new slide called "The Blaster" will have the capacity of launching a two-person raft down the slide using five waterjets.""A section of the slide protrudes off the edge of the ship and other areas of the tube are transparent giving guests a unique view of the ocean.""Opposite to "The Blaster" is another slide called "Riptide." This mat-racer slide also has a transparent part that curves off the side of the cruise ship."SOURCES: Geek, Royal Caribbean Internationalhttps://www.geek.com/culture/the-worlds-longest-waterslide-at-sea-launches-this-year-and-it-looks-epic-1771658/https://www.royalcaribbean.co.uk/our-ships/navigator-of-the-seas/new-in-2019-makeover/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 05:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/31/3774275/3774275_9D8ADC41207F4DE5AA9983DF57B5C889_190131_3774275_Royal_Caribbean_reveals_world_s_longest_sea_wate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Royal Caribbean international, cruise ship, slide, longest slide, the blaster, the riptide, navigator of the seas, the bahamas, miami, florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3774153</guid>
      <title>Norway plans to build a 'floating tunnel' under the sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Norwegian Public Roads Administration plans to build floating tunnels as part of a coastal highway that would run between Kristiansand and Trondheim, according to the agency's website. It currently takes 21 hours and 7 ferry crossing to travel between these two cities, according to NPR.The new Coastal Highway Route would include bridges as well as submerged floating tunnels that would connect different fjords, CNN reports. It is expected to cut travel time by half.The floating tunnels would be installed around 30 meters under the water, according to CNN.The tunnels would be anchored to the seabed or to pontoons which would float on the surface of the water, CNN reports. This will help in stabilizing the structure. It will then function as an ordinary tunnel, allowing vehicles to drive from one end to the other.If Norway succeeds, this could be the world's first underwater floating tunnel.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of Norway's Coastal Highway Route2. Bridge and a submerged floating tunnel3. Floating tunnel anchored to the seabed and pontoons floating on the surface of the water 4. Vehicles driving through the floating tunnelVOICEOVER (in English): "The Norwegian Public Roads Administration plans to create a Coastal Highway Route that would run between Kristiansand and Trondheim.""CNN reports the new highway would include bridges as well as submerged floating tunnels that would connect different fjords.""It is expected to cut travel time by half.""The floating tunnels would be installed around 30 meters under the water.""The tunnels would be anchored to the seabed or to pontoons which would float on the surface of the water. This will help in stabilizing the structure.""It will then function as an ordinary tunnel, allowing vehicles to drive from one end to the other."SOURCES: CNN, NPR,  The Norwegian Public Roads Administration website, World Economic Forumhttps://edition.cnn.com/style/article/norway-underwater-floating-tunnel-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/2019/01/08/682222168/norway-embarks-on-its-most-ambitious-transport-project-yethttps://www.vegvesen.no/vegprosjekter/ferjefriE39https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2016/07/norway-could-build-the-worlds-first-floating-tunnel***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/31/3774153/3774153_BE9D0D6F8FFA4C3D9F92B645C594ABA3_190131_3774153_Norway_plans_to_build_a__floating_tunnel__under__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, norway, floating tunnel, norway floating tunnel, world's first underwater floating tunnel, norway fjords, floating underwater tunnel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3774904</guid>
      <title>Sonars may be causing some whales to become suicidal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new report suggests that whale's suicidal behavior may be linked to sonar waves. Sonar waves cause major distress for underwater mammals. They are thought to scare them away, but a new report suggests that the effects are deadly.The report suggests suicidal behavior in some beaked whales is linked to exposure to sonar waves. Cuvier's beaked whales are deep divers with bodies capable of withstanding changing pressure. Their metabolism slows down to save oxygen and their organs adapt to avoid decompression sickness.However, according to a report published in the Royal Society Proceedings B Journal, when the whales come into contact with sonar waves emitted by naval patrols, they quickly swim away in fear and confusion. Nitrogen gas bubbles then accumulate in the whales' veins, causing brain hemorrhages and damage to their organs and nervous system, including their spinal cord. This unnatural, quick change in their diving pattern makes the animal accumulate nitrogen.Beaked whales normally dive over 1,000 meters deep for one hour, but when exposed to sonar waves they swim for over two hours at depths of around 3,000 meters.Once disoriented and hurt they tend to beach in nearby coasts. In 2003 a paper pointing out the possible link between sonar and whale deaths led to a 2004 ban on naval exercises around the Canary Islands.Scientists behind the report have an idea for a solution. They suggest placing more moratoriums on mid-frequency sonar activity in regions where large groups of beached whales frequently appear.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cuvier's beaked whales swimming in the ocean2. Cuvier's beaked whales frightened and confused swimming away from the sonar waves3. Effect of decompression sickness and accumulation of nitrogen in whales' bodies4. Cuvier's beaked whales become stranded and beachingVOICEOVER (in English): "Cuvier's beaked whales are deep divers with bodies capable of withstanding changing pressure.""Their metabolism slows down to save oxygen and their organs adapt to avoid decompression sickness.""However, according to a report published in the Royal Society Proceedings B Journal, when the whales come into contact with sonar waves emitted by naval patrols, they quickly swim away in fear and confusion." "Nitrogen gas bubbles then accumulate in the whales' veins, causing brain hemorrhages and damage to their organs and nervous system, including their spinal cord.""This unnatural, quick change in their diving pattern makes the animal accumulate nitrogen.""Beaked whales normally dive over 1,000 meters deep for  one hour, but when exposed to sonar waves they swim for over two hours at depths of around 3,000 meters.""Once disoriented and hurt they tend to beach in nearby coasts."SOURCES: Agence France Presse, Royal Society Proceedings B Journalhttps://www.afp.com/en/news/826/some-whales-sonar-may-provoke-suicidal-behaviour-study-doc-1ct6fy4https://royalsocietypublishing.org/journal/rspb***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 01:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/01/3774904/3774904_0410625855274A69A5F8AB8766509880_190201_3774904_Sonars_may_be_causing_some_whales_to_become_suic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, stranded whales, whale, whale beaching, whale stranding, suicidal whales, sonars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3776805</guid>
      <title>Dubai to build new 550-meter high tower</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDubai has introduced The Burj Jumeirah as the newest addition to its iconic skyline.According to Khaleej Times,  Vice President and Prime Minister of the United Arab Emirates, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, has unveiled plans to build a new tower in the Al Sufouh neighborhood of Dubai.The new building is called, 'The Burj Jumeirah' it will be developed by Dubai Holding, which also created the famous  Burj Al Arab hotel. The Burj Jumeirah is set to be 550 meters tall. The building is shaped like an oval split in two halves. It will be equipped with multiple observation decks and activity centers. The area surrounding the base of the tower will be developed into a commercial zone. The tower will mainly feature houses, hotels and office spaces. Construction will begin immediately with the first phase set to be finished by 2023.The Burj Jumeirah is part of the Downtown Jumeirah project, which includes the development of the area surrounding the new tower.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Burj Jumeirah towering above  the Al Sufouh neighborhood 2. Comparison of The Burj Jumeirah with the Burj Al Arab hotel3. The Burj Jumeirah height and location of its observation deck and commercial zone 4. The Burj Jumeirah's features: housing, hotel spaces and offices.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Khaleej Times,  Vice President and Prime Minister of the United Arab Emirates, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, has unveiled plans to build a new tower in the Al Sufouh neighborhood of Dubai.""The new building is called, 'The Burj Jumeirah' it will be developed by Dubai Holding, which also created the famous  Burj Al Arab hotel." "The Burj Jumeirah is set to be 550 meters tall. The building is shaped like an oval split in two halves. It will be equipped with multiple observation decks and activity centers. The area surrounding the base of the tower will be developed into a commercial zone. ""The tower will mainly feature houses, hotels and office spaces. Construction will begin immediately with the first phase set to be finished by 2023."SOURCES: Khaleej Times, The Nationalhttps://www.khaleejtimes.com/nation/dubai/video-new-550-metre-high-tower-to-come-up-in-dubai-https://www.thenational.ae/uae/burj-jumeirah-dubai-ruler-s-fingerprint-forms-base-of-550-metre-needle-tower-1.820402#9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/04/3776805/3776805_114E63304CFC4C899C931DF3EF7D0849_190204_3776805_Dubai_to_build_new_550_meter_high_tower_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, United Arab Emirates, Dubai, tower, skyline, construction,  Burj Jumeirah]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3776734</guid>
      <title>Pocket-sized device can diagnose infections within minutes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEuroNews reports that a Polish startup has created a mini-lab prototype that can quickly and accurately diagnose infections.SensDx is a pocket-sized diagnostic tool that can determine whether an infection is caused by a bacterium, virus, or fungi, in just four minutes.The device is able to detect sensitive bacteria such as streptococcus pyogenes and haemophilus influenzae, both of which can cause inflammation in the throat.Once a DNA swab is taken from a patient, it's placed in a special buffer with solution and dropped onto the SensDx electrode.A detailed analysis of the infection will then appear on a connected mobile device, laptop, or desktop.According to SensDx's CEO, the device will initially be available only to medical consultation centers for about 100 euros.After two years, it can be given to patients, with data being transferred from home to the doctor's office.According to EuroNews, SensDx has also developed diagnostic kits for animals, which will be similar to the human test kits, but will detect different pathogens.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SensDx can diagnose infection in four minutes2. Examples of sensitive bacteria detectable by SensDx3. How SensDx works4. SensDx test kits for animalsVOICEOVER (in English): "SensDx is a pocket-sized diagnostic tool that can determine whether an infection is caused by a bacterium, virus, or fungi, in just four minutes.""The device is able to detect sensitive bacteria such as streptococcus pyogenes and haemophilus influenzae, both of which can cause inflammation in the throat.""Once a DNA swab is taken from a patient, it's placed in a special buffer with solution and dropped onto the SensDx electrode.""A detailed analysis of the infection will then appear on a connected mobile device, laptop, or desktop.""According to EuroNews, SensDx has also developed diagnostic kits for animals, which will be similar to the human test kits, but will detect different pathogens."SOURCES: SensDx, EuroNews, The First Newshttps://www.sensdx.eu/https://www.euronews.com/2019/01/24/this-pocket-sized-device-can-diagnose-infections-in-4-minuteshttps://www.thefirstnews.com/article/clever-new-mini-lab-will-enable-patients-to-test-themselves-for-illnesses--and-it-can-be-used-on-animals-too-4496***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 08:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/04/3776734/3776734_B3B7BA55FA9844E086C371B56B87E766_190204_3776734_Pocket_sized_device_can_diagnose_infections_with_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sensdx, mini lab, pocket device, pocket lab, pocket diagnostic tool, infections, diagnose infections]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3776705</guid>
      <title>Microplastics found in every marine mammal sampled in UK study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMicroplastics have been found in the digestive tracts of every marine mammal surveyed in a new study of animals washed up on Britain's beaches, according to scientists. According to the BBC, scientists from the University of Exeter and Plymouth Marine Laboratory, or PML, looked at 50 animals, including 10 species of dolphins, seals and whales. According to the Guardian, researchers found that nylon made up more than 60 percent of the microplastics, coming from possible sources like fishing rope and nets, clothing microfibers and toothbrush bristles. Polyethylene terephthalate, or PET, was also widely present in the marine animals studied. According to the scientists, on average, 5.5 plastic particles were discovered in the guts of each animal. According to the BBC, 84 percent of the microplastics found were synthetic fibers, while the remaining was fragments of food packaging and plastic bottles. The results were published in the journal Scientific Reports. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Microplastics discovered in surveyed all marine animals2. Nylon from fishing rope, nets, clothing and toothbrushes made up more than 60 percent of microplastics3. PET plastic was also found in marine animals surveyed4. Majority of microplastics came from synthetic fibers, food packaging and plastic bottlesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, scientists from the University of Exeter and Plymouth Marine Laboratory looked at 50 animals, including 10 species of dolphins, seals and whales and found microplastics in all the animals surveyed." "According to the Guardian, researchers found that nylon made up more than 60 percent of the microplastics, coming from possible sources like fishing rope and nets, clothing microfibers and toothbrush bristles." "Polyethylene terephthalate, or PET, was also widely present in the marine animals studied." "According to the scientists, on average, 5.5 plastic particles were discovered in the guts of each animal.""According to the BBC, 84 percent of the microplastics found were synthetic fibers, while the remaining was fragments of food packaging and plastic bottles." SOURCES: The Guardian, BBChttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/jan/31/microplastics-found-every-marine-mammal-uk-studyhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-scotland-highlands-islands-47078733***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 08:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/04/3776705/3776705_4C33615FC0554BC18F2D103B95CF0187_190204_3776705_Microplastics_found_in_every_marine_mammal_sampl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, microplastics, microplastics pollution, microfiber pollution, plastic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3776695</guid>
      <title>Iran launches gold-backed cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA gold-backed cryptocurrency called the Peyman has been launched in the Islamic Republic of Iran.  According to Iranian English paper Financial Tribune, the Ghoghnoos Company and four banks teamed up to offer the digital currency. The four partner banks are the Parsian Bank, Bank Melli Iran, Bank Pasargad and Bank Mellat. Over-the-counter exchange Iran Fara Bourse is also expected to offer the Peyman, which is the Persian word for covenant. According to a Ghoghnoos director, Peyman will be used to tokenize banks' assets and excess properties. Ghoghnoos has indicated one billion tokens will be available in the initial coin offering. The Peyman is also expected to be available for purchase on Iran Fara Bourse. According to Al Jazeera, the launch of the Peyman comes less than a week after Iran's central bank issued draft cryptocurrency regulations. Iran's central bank also gave the nod to initial coin offerings, cryptocurrency exchanges, bitcoin wallets and cryptocurrency mining. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Peyman is gold-backed cryptocurrency2. Groups involved in Peyman3. Peyman used to tokenize bank assets and properties4. Peyman ICOVOICEOVER (in English): "A gold-backed cryptocurrency called the Peyman has been launched in the Islamic Republic of Iran."  "According to Iranian English paper Financial Tribune, the Ghoghnoos Company and four banks teamed up to offer the digital currency." "Over-the-counter exchange Iran Fara Bourse is also expected to offer the Peyman, which is the Persian word for covenant." "According to a Ghoghnoos director, Peyman will be used to tokenize banks' assets and excess properties." "Ghoghnoos has indicated one billion tokens will be available in the initial coin offering." SOURCES: CCN, Financial Tribune, Al Jazeerahttps://www.ccn.com/iran-launches-gold-backed-cryptocurrency-as-anticipation-for-crypto-rial-grows-to-evade-us-sanctions/https://financialtribune.com/articles/business-and-markets/96476/iran-unveils-gold-backed-cryptocurrencyhttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/01/iran-central-bank-issues-draft-rules-cryptocurrency-190129051653656.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 08:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/04/3776695/3776695_C2FC9334C90D41A68B004A31BD59457F_190204_3776695_Iran_launches_gold_backed_cryptocurrency_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cryptocurrency, Peyman cryptocurrency, Iran cryptocurrency, digital currency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3776574</guid>
      <title>NASA Curiosity Rover will explore other regions of Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Mars Curiosity rover is headed to explore new regions of Mount Sharp.According to NASA's latest update, the Mars Curiosity Rover has left the Vera Rubin Ridge and descended toward a clay region of Mount Sharp, a 5.5 kilometers tall mountain on Mars. The rover will be exploring the mountain's "clay-bearing unit" at the south of the Vera Rubin Ridge. The mission team believes the minerals in this area will help them understand lake formations that contributed to the shape of the lower levels of Mount Sharp.As of December 2018, the Curiosity Rover has drilled and collected nineteen samples of Martian sediments. The latest sample was collected in an area of the Vera Rubin Ridge called Rock Hall.Curiosity first landed on Mars in August 2012 and has since been snapping selfies and collecting data to complete its main mission: finding out if Mars could host microbial life and determine whether or not there ever were forms of life on the Red Planet.New Atlas reports NASA's second rover on the Red Planet, Opportunity, lost contact with its team after a global sand storm blocked out the sun for several days in May 2018. Opportunity is powered by solar power and the lack of sunlight forced the rover to shut down after its batteries were drained.NASA has since tried to contact Opportunity over 600 times using various radio commands to no avail.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mars Curiosity rover moving across Martian terrain2. Mars Curiosity rover in the Vera Rubin Ridge3. Soil composition of Vera Rubin Ridge4. Mars Curiosity rover drilling and extracting soil from the Vera Rubin RidgeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA's latest update, the Mars Curiosity Rover has left the Vera Rubin Ridge and descended toward a clay Region of Mount Sharp, a 5.5 kilometers tall mountain on Mars.""The rover will be exploring the mountain's 'clay-bearing unit' at the south of the Vera Rubin Ridge.""The mission team believes the minerals in this area will help them understand lake formations that contributed to the shape of the lower levels of Mount Sharp.""As of December 2018, the Curiosity Rover has drilled and collected nineteen samples of Martian sediments. The latest sample was collected in an area of the Vera Rubin Ridge called Rock Hall."SOURCES: NASA, New Atlashttps://mars.nasa.gov/news/8405/curiosity-says-farewell-to-mars-vera-rubin-ridge/https://newatlas.com/nasa-opportunity-new-rescue-strategy/58233/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 05:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/04/3776574/3776574_F6784DBF689749EFACC24E26B38597E5_190204_3776574_NASA_Curiosity_Rover_will_explore_other_regions__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mars, rover, mars rover, nasa, nasa curiosity, nasa mission on mars, nasa curiosity rover, curiosity rover]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777613</guid>
      <title>San Francisco rolls out system to track homeless people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSan Francisco has been designing a system over the past two years to track every homeless person in the city, according to the San Francisco Chronicle. The goal of the digital program called ONE System is to collect and sort information in order to tailor housing needs, rehabilitation and other services in order to cut down on costly, wasteful duplication efforts. According to Bloomberg, the $5 million 50-employee pilot program began in August.According to the San Francisco Chronicle, by typing in a homeless person's name, information about every health, housing, jail and counseling program that person has ever been involved in will come up instantly. ONE System was designed by Nevada startup BitFocus Inc., and collects data from 15 city and state agencies, according to Bloomberg.  Participants are asked 17 questions that help determine their individual situation, including time spent on the street, health and vulnerability. The program has so far signed up around 1,000 people, with the goal of registering 2,000 by the end of October. The city's homeless count currently sits at 7,499, according to the San Francisco Chronicle. However, in the five months since the program started, only 20 people have been placed in permanent housing, and 50 more have been helped off the streets through counseling and contact with family and friends. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. ONE System tracking homeless people2. ONE System tracks homeless people's personal information and history3. ONE System collects data from 15 agencies, participants filling out questionnaire4. Homeless people registered in ONE SystemVOICEOVER (in English): "San Francisco has been designing a system over the past two years to track every homeless person in the city." "According to the San Francisco Chronicle, the goal of the digital program called ONE System is to collect and sort information in order to tailor housing needs, rehabilitation and other services in order to cut down on costly, wasteful duplication efforts." "According to the San Francisco Chronicle, by typing in a homeless person's name, information about every health, housing, jail and counseling program that person has ever been involved in will come up instantly." "According to Bloomberg, ONE System was designed by Nevada startup BitFocus Inc., and collects data from 15 city and state agencies."  "Participants are asked 17 questions that help determine their individual situation, including time spent on the street, health and vulnerability." "The program has so far signed up around 1,000 people, with the goal of registering 2,000 by the end of October. According to the San Francisco Chronicle, the city's homeless count currently sits at 7,499." SOURCES: San Francisco Chronicle, Bloomberghttps://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/San-Francisco-rolls-out-long-awaited-system-to-13197944.phphttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-04/one-system-wants-to-track-every-homeless-person-in-san-francisco***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 14:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/06/3777613/3777613_AA41702E8FFD4B69AD201BC18D5A2D84_190206_3777613_San_Francisco_rolls_out_system_to_track_homeless_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, San Francisco homeless, San Francisco ONE System, ONE System, homeless tracking system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777570</guid>
      <title>China using AI in 'Zero Trust' system to spot corruption</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has developed an anti-corruption AI system called "Zero Trust" to help identify corrupt public officials. According to the SCMP, it was developed by the Chinese Academy of Sciences and the Chinese Communist Party's internal control institutions to monitor, evaluate or intervene in the work and personal life of public servants. Zero Trust can cross-reference more than 150 protected databases in central and local governments systems, reports the SCMP. The system is designed to detect property transfers, infrastructure construction, land purchases and house demolitions, according to one researcher involved with the program, according the SCMP. Researchers built the system to detect unusual increases in bank savings, new car purchases or bidding for government contracts under the name of the official or one of his or her family or friends.The system then calculates a probability for those actions to be corrupt and if authorities need to be alerted. According to the SCMP, Zero Trust was only rolled out in 30 counties and cities, but managed to catch 8,721 government officials engaging in embezzlement, abuse of power, misuse of government funds and nepotism. Only some were sentence to jail time, however most were allowed to keep their jobs after receiving a warning or minor punishment. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Zero Trust system can cross-reference more than 150 databases 2. Zero Trust can detect property transfers, infrastructure construction, land purchases and house demolitions3. Zero Trust system can also monitor bank savings, car purchases and government contracts4. The system identified 8,721 instances of corruption VOICEOVER (in English): "China has developed an anti-corruption AI system called "Zero Trust" to help identify corrupt public officials." "Zero Trust can cross-reference more than 150 protected databases in central and local governments systems." "According to a researcher involved with the program, the system is designed to detect property transfers, infrastructure construction, land purchases and house demolitions."  "Researchers built the system to detect unusual increases in bank savings, new car purchases or bidding for government contracts under the name of the official or one of his or her family or friends.""The system then calculates a probability for those actions to be corrupt and if authorities need to be alerted." "According to the SCMP, Zero Trust was only rolled out in 30 counties and cities, but managed to catch 8,721 government officials engaging in embezzlement, abuse of power, misuse of government funds and nepotism."SOURCES: SCMPhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2184857/chinas-corruption-busting-ai-system-zero-trust-being-turned-being***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 12:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/06/3777570/3777570_CB1D731F9C154542BE4D622134972701_190206_3777570_China_using_AI_in__Zero_Trust__system_to_spot_co_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China Zero Trust AI, China corruption, China public official corruption, China AI Zero Trust system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777566</guid>
      <title>China tests new naval railgun</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is testing a new naval gun that uses electromagnetic energy to fire projectiles.CNBC reports that China's newest railgun uses electromagnetic energy to fire rounds and is capable of hitting targets 200 kilometers away traveling at 2.5 kilometers per second. That's seven times the speed of sound.According to CNBC, a missile traveling at that speed would take just 90 seconds to travel from Washington to Philadelphia.Xinhua News reported that China may be mounting the railgun on a Type 055 destroyer. The Type 055 is Asia's largest destroyer to date, measuring 180 meters long and 20 meters wide. It's equipped with anti-missile, anti-ship and anti-submarine weapons. It's equipped to power kinetic energy weapons.CNBC reports that information from a U.S. intelligence report reveals that China is expected to add the weapon to its arsenal in 2025.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Railgun range2. Projectile traveling3. Chinese railgun mounted atop a Type 055 destroyer 4. Type 055 destroyer dimensions and capabilitiesVOICEOVER (in English): "CNBC reports that China's newest railgun uses electromagnetic energy to fire rounds and is capable of hitting targets 200 kilometers away traveling at 2.5 kilometers per second. That's seven times the speed of sound.""According to CNBC, a missile traveling at that speed would take just 90 seconds to travel from Washington to Philadelphia.""Xinhua News reported that China may be mounting the railgun on a Type 055 destroyer." "The Type 055 is Asia's largest destroyer to date, measuring 180 meters long and 20 meters wide.""It's equipped with anti-missile, anti-ship and anti-submarine weapons. It's equipped to power kinetic energy weapons."SOURCES: CNBC, Xinhua News https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/30/china-naval-gun-ready-for-warfare-by-2025-us-intelligence.htmlhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/mil/2018-02/06/c_129806303.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 11:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/06/3777566/3777566_01A2EBCCDA6648FDB7D9F238F03FD89C_190206_3777566_China_tests_new_naval_railgun_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, china weapons, weapons, naval weapons, china military, china railgun, railgun, Type 055 destroyer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777559</guid>
      <title>Genoa bridge to undergo reconstruction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe city of Genoa is ready to start rebuilding five months after the collapse of the 50-year-old Morandi Bridge.The Morandi Bridge collapsed on August 15, 2018. The bridge failure may have been caused by a collapsed stay.According to Italian news site ANSA, the remaining parts of the bridge will be demolished and removed between February 6 and 8.Engineering.com reports that the new bridge will be built with weight bearing columns instead of the A-frame, cable-stayed design of the previous bridge.Renzo Piano is the architect behind the design of the new bridge. He is also the architect behind The Shard in London and the Whitney Museum in New York. Piano is Genoese and has designed the bridge free of charge, calling it an act of 'civic spirit.'The new steel bridge will measure 1,100 meters in length. Its deck will be supported by reinforced concrete beams positioned at 50-meter increments. The bridge is set to be completed in 12 months once construction begins.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. South stay of the Morandi bridge collapses2. Excavators picking up collapsed bridge debris3. Design of the new bridge4. Dimensions of the new bridgeVOICEOVER (in English): "The Morandi Bridge collapsed on August 15, 2018. The bridge failure may have been caused by a collapsed stay.""According to Italian news site ANSA, the remaining parts of the bridge will be demolished and removed between February 6 and 8.""Engineering.com reports that the new bridge will be built with weight bearing columns instead of the A-frame, cable-stayed design of the previous bridge.""The new steel bridge will measure 1,100 meters in length. Its deck will be supported by reinforced concrete beams positioned at 50-meter increments."SOURCES: ANSA, Engineering.comhttp://www.ansa.it/english/news/general_news/2019/01/28/genoa-bridge-demolition-set-to-start_5412681f-0715-4aa8-b3ad-37750453037e.htmlhttps://www.engineering.com/BIM/ArticleID/18231/After-Bridge-Tragedy-Genoa-Selects-a-New-Design.aspx***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 11:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/06/3777559/3777559_8EE4C8C2C9964BC0A1985AD64B8354D9_190206_3777559_Genoa_bridge_to_undergo_reconstruction_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Italy, genoa, bridge, italy genoa bridge, genoa bridge, genoa bridge replaces, genoa bridge demolition, genoa bridge reconstruction, italy bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777519</guid>
      <title>French report finds harmful chemicals in disposable diapers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn investigative report has found traces of harmful chemicals in disposable baby diapers in France.A total of 23 different samples of diapers sold between 2016 and 2018 in France were tested by researchers for toxic chemicals, according to the Safety in Baby Nappies report.As many as 60 different chemicals such as glyphosate, dioxins and PCB-126 were found in the diapers, according to Chemical Watch. Some of these chemicals are banned in the European Union, according to the Guardian.Anses, the French Agency for food, environmental and occupational health and safety, is cited by the Guardian as saying some chemicals, such as perfume, were purposefully added to the diapers.The report did not specify which diaper brands were found to be have toxic chemicals.Diaper manufacturers were quick to react to the report with Pampers saying their diapers are "safe and always have been."Joone responded by saying the report is alarming and explained that the company had previously published toxicology analysis for its products.Reuters quotes French health Minister Agnes Buzyn, as saying there is "no immediate, serious risk for the health of the child, but it is paramount to take precautions."French Environment Minister Francois de Rugy and Finance Minister Bruno Le Maire issued a joint statement urging manufacturers to come up with a plan to remove the toxic chemicals from the diapers in the next 15 days, Reuters reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A diaper and a toxic chemical symbol2. The glyphosate molecule, the dioxin molecule and the PCB-126 molecule3. A waving EU flag and a ban icon4. Perfume being added to the diaperVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Safety in Baby Nappies report, a total of 23 different diaper samples were tested by researchers for toxic chemicals.""According to Chemical Watch, a total of 60 different chemicals such as glyphosate, dioxins, PCB-126 along with others were found in the diapers." "According to the Guardian, some of these chemicals are banned in the European Union.""The Guardian cites Anses, the French agency for food, environmental and occupational health and safety, as saying some of these chemicals, such as perfume, were purposefully added to the diapers."SOURCES: The Guardian, Anses, Reuters, Chemical Watch,  https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/23/france-traces-of-dangerous-chemicals-found-in-disposable-nappieshttps://www.anses.fr/fr/system/files/CONSO2017SA0019Ra.pdfhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-health/toxic-substances-found-in-diapers-in-france-government-agency-idUSKCN1PH0I1https://chemicalwatch.com/73693/french-agency-finds-unsafe-levels-of-chemicals-in-babies-nappies***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 09:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/06/3777519/3777519_7C7AB395A2244C4F93119C8225FB96B8_190206_3777519_French_report_finds_harmful_chemicals_in_disposa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, france, chemicals, disposable diapers, chemicals in diapers, glyphosate, chemicals, disposable diapers health risks,  toxic chemicals diapers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777947</guid>
      <title>Inkjet printed solar panels could revolutionize green energy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAFP reports that a novel processing method has been developed that allows for the production of solar panels at lower temperatures and reduced costs.In 2009, it was discovered that the perovskite class of minerals could be used to make photovoltaic solar cells. But the initial process was complicated, and could only be done on materials like glass that could withstand the extreme heat required.Polish physicist Olga Malinkiewicz eventually found a way to coat flexible foil with perovskites, and later developed an inkjet printing method that required no high heat.The perovskite-coated solar panels are flexible, and can be easily affixed to laptops, cars, drones, spacecrafts, and buildings to allow them to produce electricity, even in the shade or indoors.According to current estimates, a standard 1.3 square meter panel can supply a day's worth of energy to an office workstation. The projected cost of the panel is $57.Malinkiewicz claims the initial cost of the inkjet panels will be comparable to conventional ones.Her company, Saule Technologies, partnered with Swedish construction firm Skanska, which will incorporate the solar cell technology in its projects across the globe.Experts say perovskite technology could "revolutionise access to solar power for all," as it has "the potential to address the world energy poverty."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Perovskite mineral used to form photovoltaic solar cells , limited to glass due to high heat process2. Inkjet printing method for perovskite solar panels 3. Flexible solar panels can be affixed to any surface4. Standard panel can produce a day's worth of energy for an office workstationVOICEOVER (in English): "In 2009, it was discovered that the perovskite class of minerals could be used to form photovoltaic solar cells.""But the initial process was complicated, and could only be done on materials like glass that could withstand the extreme heat required.""Polish physicist Olga Malinkiewicz eventually found a way to coat flexible foil with perovskites, and later developed an inkjet printing method that required no high heat.""The perovskite-coated solar panels are flexible, and can be easily affixed to laptops, cars, drones, spacecrafts, and buildings to allow them to produce electricity, even in the shade or indoors.""According to current estimates, a standard 1.3 square meter panel can supply a day's worth of energy to an office workstation. The projected cost of the panel is $57."SOURCES: AFP-JIJI (Japan Times), Saule Technologieshttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/02/03/world/science-health-world/inkjet-solar-panels-poised-revolutionize-green-energy/#.XFkd3c8za8phttps://www.perovskite-info.com/saule-technologies***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 11:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/07/3777947/3777947_D04C4340785D475CBE4AB4CDBEA96DCE_190207_3777947_Inkjet_printed_solar_panels_could_revolutionize__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, solar energy, solar panels, solar cells, inkjet solar panels, inkjet solar cells, perovskite solar panels, green energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777871</guid>
      <title>Why physicists are interested in the top quark</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to Ohio State University astrophysicist Paul Sutter on Live Science, physicists are interested in studying the mysterious top quark, and it may have to do with its connection to the god particle.According to CERN, quarks are subatomic particles that are the building blocks of matter. There are six types: up, down, charm, strange, top, and bottom.Up and down quarks, which are the most common, and group together to form protons and neutrons. The quarks have fractional charges, which add up to become the positive proton and neutral neutron charges.Charm and strange have a fleeting existence according to Symmetry Magazine, as they're unstable particles that easily decay into conventional particles.The six quarks differ in size and weight, with up and down quarks being the lightest, followed by charm and strange, and then bottom quarks. Top quarks are the largest - about 100 trillion times heavier than up quarks.This wide range in masses is believed to be due to the Higgs field. According to CERN, particles acquire a mass by interacting with this invisible field, whose visible manifestation is the Higgs boson particle. The more a particle interacts, the heavier it is.Experiments at the Large Hadron Collider reveal that the Higgs boson interacts strongly with the top quark.Physicists believe that by studying its coupling with top quarks, more can be learned about the properties of the Higgs boson. It might even lead to the discovery of heavy new-physics particles.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Six types of quarks; up and down quark groupings forming protons and neutrons2. Charm and strange quarks easily decay3. Size and weight comparisons of the six quarks4.  Higgs field and higgs boson believed to give particles mass5. Higgs boson and top quark couplingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CERN, quarks are subatomic particles that are the building blocks of matter. There are six types: up, down, charm, strange, top, and bottom.""Up and down quarks, which are the most common, and group together to form protons and neutrons. The quarks have fractional charges, which add up to become the positive proton and neutral neutron charges.""Charm and strange have a fleeting existence according to Symmetry Magazine, as they're unstable particles that easily decay into conventional particles.""The six quarks differ in size and weight, with up and down quarks being the lightest, followed by charm and strange, and then bottom quarks. Top quarks are the largest - about 100 trillion times heavier than up quarks.""This wide range in masses is believed to be due to the Higgs field. According to CERN, particles acquire a mass by interacting with this invisible field, whose visible manifestation is the Higgs boson particle. The more a particle interacts, the heavier it is.""Experiments at the Large Hadron Collider reveal that the Higgs boson interacts strongly with the top quark.""Physicists believe that by studying its coupling with top quarks, more can be learned about the properties of the Higgs boson."SOURCES: CERN, Live Science, Symmetry Magazinehttps://home.cern/news/press-release/cern/higgs-boson-reveals-its-affinity-top-quarkhttps://home.cern/science/physics/higgs-bosonhttps://home.cern/science/physics/standard-modelhttps://www.livescience.com/64687-why-top-quark-so-heavy.htmlhttps://www.symmetrymagazine.org/article/the-perfect-couple-higgs-and-top-quark-spotted-togetherhttps://www.symmetrymagazine.org/article/may-2009/august-2008-explain-it-in-60-seconds-charm-quark***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/07/3777871/3777871_24B1D9119E9B49E6811AD923A6A73DB4_190207_3777871_Why_physicists_are_interested_in_the_top_quark_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, physics, particle physics, higgs boson, top quark, higgs field, quarks, god particle, subatomic particles, particle collider, new physics, top quark physics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3777805</guid>
      <title>Jenga-like architectural building project planned for Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Dutch firm has been chosen to build a jenga-like building project in northern Germany, according to Inhabitat.Dutch firm MVRDV plans to build a 65,000-square-meter city block called "Koolkiel" in northern Germany. The project would consist of a Jenga-like architecture, reports Inhabitat.The main building's exterior would feature facade panels made from fibre reinforced concrete, according to the company's website.The flexible design of the complex will give the community the freedom to modify the structure's interior and exterior, according to Inhabitat.The project would also be equipped with rooftop solar panels, green roofs and other energy-saving features, Inhabitat reports.The entire complex itself would be a mix of residential and commercial buildings with apartments on top, according to Inhabitat.MVRDV has yet to announce a completion date for the project.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Kool Kiel city block2. The exterior of the main building3. Energy-saving features the building block would have4. The entire city block with a mix of buildingsVOICEOVER (in English): "Dutch firm MVRDV plans to build a 65,000-square-meter city block called 'Koolkiel' in northern Germany. The project would consist of a Jenga-like architecture, reports Inhabitat.""According to the company's website, the main building's exterior would feature facade panels made from fibre reinforced concrete.""Inhabitat reports the project would also be equipped with rooftop solar panels, green roofs and other energy-saving features.""The entire complex itself would be a mix of residential and commercial buildings with apartments on top, according to Inhabitat."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Dezeen, MVRDV, Designboom https://inhabitat.com/mvrdv-designs-solar-powered-koolkiel-with-jenga-like-architecture-in-germany/https://www.dezeen.com/2019/01/29/koolkiel-mvrdv-adaptable-architecture-germany/https://www.mvrdv.nl/projects/378/koolkielhttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/mvrdvs-koolkiel-kiel-germany-01-25-2019/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 06:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/07/3777805/3777805_36D56BCCC6D24C3AB223095295BC3BB5_190207_3777805_Jenga_like_architectural_building_project_planne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, germany, architecture, jenga-like architecture, city block, koolkiel, MVRDV, kiel germany architecture, mvrdv architecture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3778542</guid>
      <title>Research details rat-grown kidneys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers successfully grew kidneys in rats by implanting stem cells from mice. According to a paper published in the journal Nature Communications, researchers selected rat embryos that were genetically modified to not develop kidneys and injected them with stem cells from mice.These embryos were then implanted into the womb of rats that would carry the pregnancy to term. The rats successfully grew kidneys. However, genetically modifying their genes to not grow their own kidneys caused them to lose their sense of smell. Due to this alteration, they did not suckle properly and died shortly after birth. This made it hard for scientists to study the effectiveness of the kidneys they developed.Another concern is that growing organs from another species would eventually lead to organ contamination in the cells of the host."This technology could eventually lead to growing human organs in other animals.However, the paper's research supervisor Masumi Hirabayashi stated that this poses a larger ethical concern. This is because injecting human stem cells into animals could cause them to develop consciousness and reproductive cells.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rat embryo get injected with mice stem cells2. Rat embryo get implanted in wombs of rats3. Rats develop kidneys but lose sense of smell4. Rat organs become contaminated VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a paper published in the journal Nature Communications, researchers selected rat embryos that were genetically modified to not develop kidneys and injected them with stem cells from mice.""These embryos were then implanted into the womb of rats that would carry the pregnancy to term.""The rats successfully grew kidneys. However, genetically modifying their genes to not grow their own kidneys caused them to lose their sense of smell." "Due to this alteration, they did not suckle properly and died shortly after birth. This made it hard for scientists to study the effectiveness of the kidneys they developed.""Another concern is that growing organs from another species would eventually lead to organ contamination in the cells of the host."SOURCES: Nature, Live Sciencehttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-019-08394-9https://www.livescience.com/52526-rarity-of-organ-donations-forcing-patients-to-get-creative.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 15:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/08/3778542/3778542_74EAF2263CF441C0B7544FA2D2BF3987_190208_3778542_Research_details_rat_grown_kidneys_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, rat, stem cells, transplant, organ transplant, organ transplant research, mice, kidney, stem cell transplant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3778533</guid>
      <title>Researchers propose new hypothesis to explain Alzheimer's</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have identified a specific blood-clotting protein that can trigger synaptic damage after leaking into the brain, according to New Atlas. A new study published in the journal Neuron finds the protein fibrinogen can be found in the brains of people with Alzheimer's disease and experimental lab mice. According to New Atlas, scientists found that when fibrinogen enters the brain through blood-brain barrier leaks, it triggers inflammation that can damage neuron synapses. The team found that fibrinogen can cause synaptic damage in the absence of any amyloid plaque build-up. Other studies have proposed that an increasingly permeable blood-brain barrier may allow more toxic amyloid and tau proteins to enter the brain, starting the pathological process that leads to Alzheimer's. This new study could provide an alternative explanation. While tests on animals have been conducted, the findings have yet to lead to human clinical trials. According to the researchers, the type of synaptic damage associated with blood-brain barrier breakdowns could play a role in various neurological conditions. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fibrinogen protein in brain2. Fibrinogen found in people with Alzheimer's and experimental lab mice3. Fibrinogen triggering inflammation that damages neuron synapses4. Fibrinogen can cause synaptic damage in absence of amyloid plaque build-upVOICEOVER (in English): "According to New Atlas, researchers have identified a specific blood-clotting protein that can trigger synaptic damage after leaking into the brain." "A new study published in the journal Neuron finds the protein fibrinogen can be found in the brains of people with Alzheimer's disease and experimental lab mice." "According to New Atlas, scientists found that when fibrinogen enters the brain through blood-brain barrier leaks, it triggers inflammation that can damage neuron synapses." "The team found that fibrinogen can cause synaptic damage in the absence of any amyloid plaque build-up." SOURCES: New Atlashttps://newatlas.com/alzheimers-blood-brain-leak-protein-cognitive-damage/58363/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/08/3778533/3778533_71049FD18E6D4CA9865927E6BB3B8D8D_190208_3778533_Researchers_propose_new_hypothesis_to_explain_Al_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Alzheimer's, Alzheimer's disease, fibrinogen, Alzheimer's fibrinogen]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3778208</guid>
      <title>New findings shed light on Sickle Cell Disease</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has shed light on how silent strokes caused by SCD can affect the body. According to the CDC, Sickle Cell Disease is a disorder that affects hemoglobin, a molecule present in red blood cells in charge of delivering oxygen throughout the body.Blood cells affected by SCD have an irregular crescent shape and also supply a reduced amount of oxygen to the body.A new study published in the American Journal of Hematology studied the effects of limited oxygen and blood flow caused by sickle cell disease. Particularly, its role in silent strokes among sickle cell patients.Silent strokes occur when there has been an interruption of blood flow in an area of the brain that is not vital. However, as they accumulate, they can damage brain function."Using an advanced imaging technique called arterial spin labeling, researchers found that oxygen delivery to regions of the brain where white matter was present was reduced by 35 percent in patients with SCD.Most silent strokes occur in regions of the brain with white matter.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Blood circulating; Comparison between healthy blood cell and SCD blood cell2. Reduced oxygen and blood flow to the brain caused by SCD3. Percentage of  white cells affected by SCD4. Comparison between strokes in grey matter and white matterVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the CDC, Sickle Cell Disease is a disorder that affects hemoglobin, a molecule present in red blood cells in charge of delivering oxygen throughout the body.""Blood cells affected by SCD have an irregular crescent shape and also supply a reduced amount of oxygen to the body.""A new research published in the American Journal of Hematology studied the effects of limited oxygen and blood flow caused by sickle cell disease. Particularly, its role in silent strokes among sickle cell patients.""Silent strokes occur when there has been an interruption of blood flow in an area of the brain that is not vital. However, as they accumulate they can damage brain function.""Using an advanced imaging technique called arterial spin labeling, researchers found that oxygen delivery to regions of the brain where white matter was present was reduced by 35 percent in patients with SCD.""Most silent strokes occur in regions of the brain with white matter.""The results show that the body prioritizes blood flow to grey matter where neurons are present."SOURCES: American Journal Of Hematology, Centers for Disease Control and Preventionhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/ajh.25423https://www.cdc.gov/ncbddd/sicklecell/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 04:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/08/3778208/3778208_99474EF17AB54BE2AFB548FC30671A92_190208_3778208_New_findings_shed_light_on_Sickle_Cell_Disease_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sickle cell disease animation, Research, Sickle Cell Disease, SCD, sickle cell anemia, grey matter, white matter, sickle cell pathophysiology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3778201</guid>
      <title>Startup creates lab-grown protein inspired by Yellowstone Microbes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA NASA-funded start-up is using fermentation technology to create lab-grown protein. According to Bloomberg, biotech start-up Sustainable Bioproducts is trying to replicate behavior from volcanic microbes found in hot springs at Yellowstone National Park to create lab-grown protein.The company has been able to grow protein using fermentation technology. Researchers feed starch and glycerin to the high-protein microbes, which react by multiplying quickly. The resulting protein contains nine key amino acids that are essential for the human diet. The substance can be used to create a meat-like product, mixed to make yogurt or shaped into a plant-based burger patty.According to Food Dive, the NASA-funded company recently received $33 million dollars in Series A funding. Investors include Microsoft's Bill Gates, Amazon's Jeff Bezos, Bloomberg's Michael Bloomberg and Virgin Group's Richard Branson.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Volcanic microbes present in Yellowstone National Park Hot Springs2. Lab-grown protein being fed starch and glycerin3. Lab-grown protein containing key amino-acids4. Foods that could be made with the lab-grown proteinVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Bloomberg, biotech start-up Sustainable Bioproducts is trying to replicate behavior from volcanic microbes found in hot springs at Yellowstone National Park to create lab-grown protein.""The company has been able to grow protein using fermentation technology.""Researchers feed starch and glycerin to the high-protein microbes, which react by multiplying quickly.""The resulting protein contains nine key amino acids that are essential for the human diet.""The substance can be used to create a meat-like product, mixed to make yogurt or shaped into a plant-based burger patty."SOURCES: Sustainable Bioproducts, Bloomberg, Food Dive, Business Insider, Futurism, Food Business Newshttps://www.sustainablebioproducts.com/pressreleases/2019/2/3/sustainable-bioproducts-announces-33-million-series-a-financinghttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-04/do-these-tiny-organisms-hold-the-key-to-lab-grown-foodhttps://www.fooddive.com/news/smokin-hot-volcano-to-table-protein-startup-attracts-33m-from-danone-adm/547635/https://www.businessinsider.com/startup-protein-yellowstone-volcanic-hot-springs-sustainable-bioproducts-2019-1https://futurism.com/the-byte/alt-meat-volcanic-microbeshttps://www.foodbusinessnews.net/articles/13250-danone-adm-invest-in-volcano-to-table-lab-grown-protein-company***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 04:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/08/3778201/3778201_DBB6D620FAE548AEAF17FA9C57A3B516_190208_3778201_Startup_creates_lab_grown_protein_inspired_by_Ye_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, lab grown meat, lab grown protein, meat substitute, protein, plant based, sustainable bioproducts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3779672</guid>
      <title>Honeybees learn how to do simple arithmetic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research published in the journal Science Advances reveals that honeybees are capable of understanding simple math problems.The Australian research team began by teaching 14 honeybees the basic rules of arithmetic. They trained them to enter a Y-shaped maze where they first faced a series of colored geometric shapes.The number and the color of the shapes would vary. If the shapes were blue the bee had to add one unit to the image presented at the entrance. If the shapes were yellow it had to subtract one unit."If they chose the correct answer they would be rewarded with sugar water, if the answer was incorrect they would get a bitter solution called quinine. After 100 trials that took 4-7 hours, the bees had learned a basic concept of addition and subtraction.The bees were able to choose the correct answer between 63 and 72 percent of the time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Honeybees comprehending basic math2. Y-shaped maze used to teach the honeybees arithmetic 3. Explanation of addition and subtraction system4. Honeybee choosing an answer; illustration of reward systemVOICEOVER (in English): "New research published in the journal Science Advances reveals that honeybees are capable of understanding simple math problems.""The Australian research team began by teaching 14 honeybees the basic rules of arithmetic. They trained them to enter a Y-shaped maze where they first faced a series of colored geometric shapes.""The number and the color of the shapes would vary. If the shapes were blue the bee had to add one unit to the image presented at the entrance. If the shapes were yellow it had to subtract one unit.""If they chose the correct answer they would be rewarded with sugar water, if the answer was incorrect they would get a bitter solution called quinine.""After 100 trials that took 4-7 hours, the bees had learned a basic concept of addition and subtraction."SOURCES: Science Advances, RMIT University, Futurismhttp://advances.sciencemag.org/content/5/2/eaav0961https://www.rmit.edu.au/news/all-news/2019/feb/bees-brains-mathshttps://futurism.com/honeybees-math-smart/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/11/3779672/3779672_A75D8968BBC446F0B075B10D1FA876EB_190211_3779672_Honeybees_learn_how_to_do_simple_arithmetic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, RMIT, honeybees, addition, subtraction, australia, research]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3779444</guid>
      <title>Biggest ever surfing lagoon to be built in S. Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpanish firm Wavegarden has started construction on the world's largest surfing lagoon in South Korea. The company is collaborating with Daewon Plus Construction on the project, according to a press release by Wavegarden.The lagoon, called Wavegarden Cove, will be featured on Turtle Island, a manmade island built from land reclaimed from the sea. It will be part of the new Turtle Island attraction which is said to be worth around US$2.4 billion.The lagoon will reportedly be able to produce 1000 ocean-like waves per hour across its different surfing areas. Activities such as kayaking and swimming will also be available.According to a Wavegarden press release, different facilities such as hotels, convention centers and marinas will also be included in the island. Turtle Island is all set to open to the public by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. We see the island and surfing the waves2. We see the Turtle island, first empty and then with the lagoon built3. Activities available at the island4. Different facilities available at the islandVOICEOVER (in English): "Spanish firm Wavegarden has started construction on the world's largest surfing lagoon in Siheung, South Korea.""The lagoon, called Wavegarden Cove, will be featured on Turtle Island, a manmade island built from land reclaimed from the sea.""The lagoon will reportedly be able to produce 1000 ocean-like waves per hour across its different surfing areas.""Activities such as kayaking and swimming will also be available.""According to a Wavegarden press release, different facilities such as hotels, convention centers and marinas will also be included in the island."SOURCES: Wave Garden, New Atlas, https://wavegarden.com/wavegarden-signs-contract-to-build-the-worlds-largest-surfing-lagoon-in-south-korea/https://wavegarden.com/https://newatlas.com/wavegarden-largest-surfing-lagoon/58362/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 05:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/11/3779444/3779444_88FA58B24FDC46B190484CCFAE5E675F_190211_3779444_Biggest_ever_surfing_lagoon_to_be_built_in_S__Ko_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, south korea, surfing lagoon south korea, artificial surf park, wavegarden cove, wavegarden cove south korea, lagoon surfing, man made surfing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3779354</guid>
      <title>Bacteria sacrifice themselves for their colony to survive, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found that bacteria sacrifice themselves to antibiotics in order to preserve their colony.Researchers at California State University and Princeton exposed a colony of E.Coli to a molecule known as LL37, according to the journal E Life.The molecule was slightly modified to give off a green glow that would allow researchers to track its movement.LL37 is a natural antibiotic produced by the skin and some organs in the body to help eliminate foreign bacteria, according to the study.The scientists found that only a tiny amount of E.Coli bacteria were needed to absorb large amounts of LL37. E.Coli cells that consumed the molecule were reportedly killed. However, this allowed the rest of the bacteria colony to keep on growing and spreading.Sattar Taheri-Araghi, a co-senior author of the study said that their findings "have profound implications for the evolution of bacteria."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. E.Coli bacteria and antibiotics2. E.Coli being exposed to molecule LL373. Some of the bacteria consuming the molecule4. The bacteria colony growingVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study has found that bacteria sacrifice themselves to antibiotics in order to preserve the colony.""According to the journal E Life, researchers at California State University and Princeton exposed a colony of E.Coli to a molecule known as LL37.""The molecule was slightly modified to give off a green glow that would allow researchers to track its movement.""E.Coli cells that consumed the molecule were reportedly killed.""However, this allowed the rest of the bacteria colony to keep on growing and spreading."SOURCES: New Atlas, E Life, Princeton University,  https://newatlas.com/bacteria-self-sacrifice-antibiotics/58348/https://elifesciences.org/articles/38174https://www.princeton.edu/news/2019/02/05/dying-bacteria-absorb-antibiotic-allowing-others-survive-and-grow***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 01:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/11/3779354/3779354_4AFD881BF05E4DAEBABF084649D43EC5_190211_3779354_Bacteria_sacrifice_themselves_for_their_colony_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  bacteria, antibiotics, bacteria, antibiotics, bacteria absorb antibiotics, bacteria colony antibiotics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3780080</guid>
      <title>New study finds gut microbiome could be linked to depression</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study of two large groups of Europeans has found several types of gut bacteria are missing in people with depression, according to Science Magazine. The scientists could not say whether the absence is a cause or an effect of the illness, but were able to show that many gut bacteria could produce substances that affect nerve cell function and possibly mood. The results were published in the journal Nature Microbiology. To test the link between the microbiome and depression, Jeroen Raes, a microbiologist at the Catholic University of Leuven in Belgium, and his team looked at 1054 Belgians to assess a "normal" microbiome. Within the group, 173 people had been diagnosed with depression or done poorly on a quality of life survey. The gut microbes of depressed group was then compared to the "normal" group. Two types of bacteria, Coprococcus and Dialister, were absent from the guts of depressed participants. The team then looked at the microbiomes of 1064 Dutch participants and also found the same two species were missing in people who were depressed. It is still unclear how the gut microbiome affects the brain. One possible avenue is through the vagus nerve, which connects the gut and the brain. But with more studies, scientists hope the microbiome-brain connection could eventually lead to novel therapies for treating depression.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Participants in study from Belgium and Holland2. Belgium participants3. Depressed participants were found to be lacking in two gut bacteria4. Microbiome-brain connection could lead to new depression treatmentsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study of two large groups of Europeans has found several types of gut bacteria are missing in people with depression." "To test the link between the microbiome and depression, Jeroen Raes, a microbiologist at the Catholic University of Leuven in Belgium, and his team looked at 1054 Belgians to assess a 'normal' microbiome." "Within the group, 173 people had been diagnosed with depression or done poorly on a quality of life survey. The gut microbes of depressed group was then compared to the 'normal' group." "Two types of bacteria, Coprococcus and Dialister, were absent from the guts of depressed participants." "The team then looked at the microbiomes of 1064 Dutch participants and also found the same two species were missing in people who were depressed." "But with more studies, scientists hope the microbiome-brain connection could eventually lead to novel therapies for treating depression."    SOURCES: Science Magazinehttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/02/evidence-mounts-gut-bacteria-can-influence-mood-prevent-depression***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 08:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/12/3780080/3780080_68F33B72A34B4E828412CED6D37383A4_190212_3780080_New_study_finds_gut_microbiome_could_be_linked_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, gut microbiome, gut microbes, gut bacteria, gut depression, microbiome depression, coprococcus, dialister]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3779989</guid>
      <title>Japan's 2020 Olympic medals are made from recycled electronics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan is preparing for next year's Olympics by asking the public to donate electronic devices they no longer use, according to New Atlas.Japan's Organizing Committee for the 2020 Olympics has been collecting used smartphones, digital cameras and laptops since April 2018 to convert the devices' metals into medals.Recycle centers were set up across the country, resulting in more than 47,000 tons of electronic devices being collected, according to New Atlas.Information from the official Tokyo 2020 website notes that the committee has already met its target goal for bronze medals  2,700 kg. Around 28.4 kg of the targeted 30.3 kg has been extracted for the gold medal. While 3,500 kg of the targeted 4,100 kg of silver has been extracted from the recycled waste. The committee expects to meet the targets next month. The Tokyo 2020 Olympic medal designs will be unveiled this summer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Olympic logo, electronic devices and one olympic medal2. A bronze metal and a vertical measurement bar3. A gold metal, a silver metal and two pie charts4. A gold, silver and bronze olympic medalsVOICEOVER (in English): "Japan's Organizing Committee for the 2020 Olympics has been collecting used smartphones, digital cameras and laptops since April 2018 to convert the devices' metals into medals.""Information from the official Tokyo 2020 website notes that the committee has already met its target goal for bronze medals  2,700 kg.""Around 28.4 kg of the targeted 30.3 kg has been extracted for the gold medal." "While 3,500 kg of the targeted 4,100 kg of silver has been extracted from the recycled waste.""The committee expects to meet the targets next month."SOURCES: New Atlas, Tokyo Olympics 2020 website, The Japan Times, The Japan News, https://newatlas.com/tokyo-2020-olympic-medals-electronic-waste/58399/https://tokyo2020.org/en/news/notice/20190208-03.htmlhttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/02/08/national/tokyo-olympics-course-meet-target-using-recycled-metal-medals/#.XGDbdIiFNjUhttp://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0005534530***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 06:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/12/3779989/3779989_3E9F2AB6395047B3B1BACF9D77F3F72E_190212_3779989_Japan_s_2020_Olympic_medals_are_made_from_recycl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan olympics, japan 2020 olympic medals, olympic medals japan, olympic medals recycled waste, olympic medals recycled waste, tokyo olympics recycled medals, recycled e-waste medals, recycled e-waste medals japan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3779863</guid>
      <title>Hayabusa-2 spacecraft gets set for asteroid sampling mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan's Hayabusa 2 spacecraft is scheduled to collect rock samples from the asteroid Ryugu on February 22.The spacecraft will fire a 5 gram projectile made of metal tantalum onto the asteroid's surface while touching down, according to the BBC.The particles that fly up will then be collected by the spacecraft's sampler horn as Hayabusa 2 descends onto the asteroid's surface.The scientists involved believe the samples will provide insight into the evolution and origin of the Earth as Ryugu is believed to be an ancient asteroid.Hayabusa 2 had previously deployed two rovers that explored Ryugu's surface. They sent back images and data of the asteroid to Earth.The spacecraft is expected to return to Earth with the samples in 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Hayabusa-2 spacecraft, the asteroid and rock samples2. The process for the spacecraft to land on the asteroid3. The spacecraft collecting samples4. Rovers hopping on the asteroid, and sending data and photos to Earth5. The Hayabusa-2 traveling back to Earth VOICEOVER (in English): "Japan's Hayabusa 2 spacecraft is scheduled to collect rock samples from the asteroid Ryugu on February 22.""According to the BBC, the spacecraft will fire a 5 gram projectile made of metal tantalum onto the asteroid's surface while touching down.""The particles that fly up will then be collected by the spacecraft's sampler horn as Hayabusa 2 descends onto the asteroid's surface.""It had previously deployed two rovers that explored Ryugu's surface. They sent back images and data of the asteroid to Earth.""The spacecraft is expected to return to Earth with the samples in 2020."SOURCES: BBC, JAXA, The Planetary Society, https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47159214http://www.hayabusa2.jaxa.jp/enjoy/material/http://www.planetary.org/blogs/jason-davis/hayabusa2-updates-sample-collection.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/12/3779863/3779863_EF5277E73C2F482B8D3BA20883F40F55_190212_3779863_Hayabusa_2_spacecraft_gets_set_for_asteroid_samp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan, japan asteroid mission, hayabusa-2, jaxa, jaxa spacecraft, ryugu asteroid, asteroid ryugu sample, ryugu sample return, japanese spacecraft asteroid, Ryugu asteroid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3780902</guid>
      <title>UK to send new aircraft carrier to Pacific on first mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe UK's new aircraft carrier will be deployed to the Pacific on its first mission, in a show of "hard power" and "lethality" meant to support the country's global interests.In a speech at the Royal United Services Institute, British Defence Minister Gavin Williamson said the HMS Queen Elizabeth aircraft carrier will go to the Mediterranean, the Middle East, and the Pacific region on its first operational mission.CNN reports that the 65,000-tonne HMS Queen Elizabeth was commissioned in 2017 and has a ski-jump flight deck. It's expected to be the centerpiece of the British Navy once it enters service in 2020.British and American F-35 fighter jets will reportedly be embedded in the air wing of the carrier, which Williamson says will enhance "the reach and lethality of our forces" while reinforcing the U.S. as a close partner.Williamson's speech came on the same day the U.S. sailed two Navy warships near the Mischief Reef in the Spratlys to challenge Beijing's territorial claims.This prompted Chinese foreign ministry to issue a sharp rebuke telling the U.S. to stop "provocative actions" that violate China's sovereignty.The South China Morning Post reports that Britain has repeatedly stated intentions to increase activity abroad, especially in the Asia-Pacific region, with plans to build a military base in either Singapore or Brunei.During his recent speech, Williamson also mentioned a plan to develop a squadron of network-enabled drones that can confuse and overwhelm enemy air defences.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. HMS Queen Elizabeth to go on first operational mission in Mediterranean, Middle East, Pacific2. HMS Queen Elizabeth features3. UK and US F-35 fighter jets on the carrier4. Two U.S. navy warships sailing near Mischief Reef5. Future British naval base in Brunei or Singapore6. Squadron of drones capable of confusing and overwhelming enemy air defenseVOICEOVER (in English): "In a speech at the Royal United Services Institute, British Defence Minister Gavin Williamson said the HMS Queen Elizabeth aircraft carrier will go to the Mediterranean, the Middle East, and the Pacific region on its first operational mission.""Commissioned in 2017, the HMS Queen Elizabeth weighs 65,000 tonnes and has a ski-jump flight deck. It's expected to be the centerpiece of the British Navy once it enters service in 2020.""British and American F-35 fighter jets will reportedly be embedded in the air wing of the carrier, which Williamson says will enhance 'the reach and lethality of our forces' while reinforcing the U.S. as a close partner.""Williamson's speech came on the same day the U.S. sailed two Navy warships near the Mischief Reef in the Spratlys to challenge Beijing's territorial claims.""This prompted Chinese foreign ministry to issue a sharp rebuke telling the U.S. to stop 'provocative actions' that violate China's sovereignty.""The South China Morning Post reports that Britain has repeatedly stated intentions to increase activity abroad, especially in the Asia-Pacific region, with plans to build a naval base in either Singapore or Brunei.""During his recent speech, Williamson also mentioned a plan to develop a squadron of network-enabled drones that can confuse and overwhelm enemy air defences."SOURCES: UK Ministry of Defence, CNN, South China Morning Posthttps://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/defence-in-global-britainhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/02/12/asia/britain-defense-aircraft-carrier-pacific-intl/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/02/10/politics/us-ships-south-china-sea/index.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/2185746/britain-urges-west-be-ready-flex-military-muscle-pacific***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 16:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/14/3780902/3780902_1947DC9E363B430995D35BE4A4905D1E_190214_3780902_UK_to_send_new_aircraft_carrier_to_Pacific_on_fi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, aircraft carrier, HMS Queen Elizabeth, UK aircraft carrier, Pacific mission, British navy, British fleet, British military]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3780611</guid>
      <title>Report estimates one-third of Himalayan glaciers will disappear by 2100</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOne-third of Himalayas glaciers will melt off by 2100 and a recent report shows not even immediate climate change actions can save them.Glaciers in the Hindu Kush-Himalaya region span eight countries and are an important geo-ecological asset. They are the origin of 10 major river basins and sustain the lives of 1.65 billion people. "A new report called The Hindu Kush-Himalaya Assessment predicts that 36 percent of the glaciers located in the Himalayan and Hindu Kush range will be gone by 2100 even if carbon emissions are slashed to zero by 2050.Even if the global rise in temperature is limited to 2 degrees Celsius, 50 percent of the glaciers would disappear by 2100. The report predicts that in 2050 and 2060 river flow will increase possibly causing glacial lake outburst floods in surrounding communities.The Hindu Kush Himalayan range has already lost roughly 15 percent of its ice since the 1970s.Sherab Lama, a Nepalese Buddhist monk told NPR people that from his village are scared saying, "They say, 'I don't know what will happen after two to three generations.' They are very worried. I am very worried."  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Geographic location of Hindu Kush-Himalaya region2. Reduction of 36 percent of Himalayan glaciers3. Reduction of 50 percent of the Himalayan glaciers 4. River flow increase in the Hindu Kush-Himalaya regionVOICEOVER (in English): "Glaciers in the Hindu Kush-Himalaya region span eight countries and are an important geo-ecological asset. They are the origin of 10 major river basins and sustain the lives of 1.65 billion people.""A new report called The Hindu Kush-Himalaya Assessment predicts that 36 percent of the glaciers located in the Himalayan and Hindu Kush range will be gone by 2100 even if carbon emissions are slashed to zero by 2050.""Even if the global rise in temperature is limited to two degrees Celsius, 50 percent of the glaciers would disappear by 2100.""The report predicts that in 2050 and 2060 river flow will increase possibly causing glacial lake outburst floods in surrounding communities."SOURCES: The Hindu Kush Himalaya Assessment, The Guardian, NPR, The Conversationhttps://link.springer.com/content/pdf/10.1007%2F978-3-319-92288-1.pdfhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/feb/04/a-third-of-himalayan-ice-cap-doomed-finds-shocking-reporthttps://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2019/02/05/691578203/report-global-warming-could-melt-at-least-a-third-of-himalayan-glaciershttps://theconversation.com/melting-himalayan-glaciers-a-big-drop-in-a-bucket-thats-already-full-111345***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 07:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/13/3780611/3780611_81D4C4BB15DC48C1AD025C28149426A3_190213_3780611_Report_estimates_one_third_of_Himalayan_glaciers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, himalayas, Hindu Kush Himalaya, climate change, global warming, himalayan glaciers, ice melt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3780496</guid>
      <title>How Trump can bypass Congress to build the wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPresident Donald Trump has hinted that he might declare a state of emergency to bypass Congress and get funding for his wall, just days before the February 15 deadline.The Atlantic reports that under the National Emergencies Act of 1976, President Trump can declare a national emergency along the southern border, and have access to specific powers that Congress has already codified by law.A U.S. government official told CNN, "the administration could pull: $681 million from Treasury forfeiture funds, $3.6 billion in military construction, $3 billion in Pentagon civil works funds, and $200 million in Department of Homeland Security funds."So funds originally intended for projects like military housing or civil infrastructure repair would now be reallocated for wall construction. According to Vox, Trump could also unlock a $20 million immigration emergency fund that's meant to be used by states to feed and house migrants.CNN reports that if the emergency declaration is made, the Army Corps of Engineers would then be deployed to build the wall.Private property on which some portions of the wall will be built can be seized by the administration since it will be for public use. Internal White House documents reviewed by CNN indicates that "environmental reviews can be skipped, and Homeland Security can use waivers to bypass contracting laws."Congress can override the declaration with a simple majority vote, but if the President were to veto, they will need a supermajority or two-thirds vote in both chambers to override it.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Trump declares state of emergency on southern border2. Funds re-allocated for construction of border wall3. Army Corps of Engineers deployed to build the wall4. How Congress can override President's declarationVOICEOVER (in English): "The Atlantic reports that under the National Emergencies Act of 1976, President Trump can declare a national emergency along the southern border, and have access to specific powers that Congress has already codified by law.""A U.S. government official told CNN, "the administration could pull: $681 million from Treasury forfeiture funds, $3.6 billion in military construction, $3 billion in Pentagon civil works funds, and $200 million in Department of Homeland Security funds.""So funds originally intended for projects like military housing or civil infrastructure repair would now be reallocated for wall construction.""CNN reports that if the emergency declaration is made, the Army Corps of Engineers would then be deployed to build the wall.""Congress can override the declaration with a simple majority vote, but if the President were to veto, they will need a supermajority or two-thirds vote in both chambers to override it."SOURCES: CNN, The Atlantic, Voxhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/01/24/politics/trump-border-wall-emergency-draft/index.htmlhttp://www.tucsonnewsnow.com/2019/02/12/what-happens-if-trump-declares-national-emergency-build-wall/https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/01/presidential-emergency-powers/576418/https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2019/1/8/18172749/trump-national-emergency-government-shutdown-wall***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 04:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/13/3780496/3780496_C0E017434F9E45809101E2118F00B807_190213_3780496_How_Trump_can_bypass_Congress_to_build_the_wall_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump, Donald Trump, national emergency, state of emergency, trump wall, border wall, trump border wall, government shutdown, wall funding]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3780405</guid>
      <title>New technology can match a person's face to their body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Japanese company has developed a system that would be able to identify a person even if they aren't directly facing the camera, according to New Atlas.NEC has announced an recognition technology that would be able to analyze a person's entire body, rather than just their face.Developers used deep learning techniques and body shape and clothing analysis to create a system called 'Person Re-identification Technology," according to New Atlas.NEC says the system had accuracy rates of up to 90 percent during testing.The AI-powered recognition technology would be able to identify people even if their back or their side is facing the camera, according to the company's press release.The system could also be used to track a person moving from one place to another, even if their faces aren't clearly visible.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Male man being scanned2. Deep learning techniques on the face and scan effect on the body3. The technology recognizing a person from their back and their side4. The camera tracking a person as he movesVOICEOVER (in English): "NEC has announced an recognition technology that would be able to analyze a person's entire body, rather than just their face.""According to New Atlas, developers used deep learning techniques and body shape and clothing analysis to create a system called 'Person Re-identification Technology.'""NEC says the system had accuracy rates of up to 90 percent during testing.""According to the company's press release, the AI-powered recognition technology would be able to identify people even if their back or their side is facing the camera.""The system could also be used to track a person moving from one place to another, even if their faces aren't clearly visible."SOURCES: NEC press release, New Atlas, Find Biometrics https://www.newswiretoday.com/news/169250/NEC-Technology-Recognizes-People-Based-on-Partial-Images/https://newatlas.com/nec-partial-facial-recognition-tech/58398/https://findbiometrics.com/nec-tech-matches-faces-bodies-enhancing-surveillance-502084/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/13/3780405/3780405_46C7190B8C2F4FCE85E038C3F7DEA703_190213_3780405_New_technology_can_match_a_person_s_face_to_thei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan, ai technology, facial recognition, NEC ,ai technology deep learning, ai face recognition, Person Re-identification Technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3780402</guid>
      <title>Exercise could help prevent Alzheimer&#x2019;s</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHormone released during exercise could help prevent Alzheimers, reports Medical Xpress.A new study published in the journal Nature Medicine shows that a hormone released during exercise called irisin helps regrow brain cells and protect the brain from developing Alzheimers. Irisin production is reduced in Alzheimers patients.The team studied the effects of irisin on mice. Results showed mice that swam almost every day for five weeks did not suffer memory impairment even though they were being infused with beta-amyloid.According to Alzheimers Association, accumulation of beta-amyloid protein is one of the possible causes of Alzheimers disease.However, mice who swam every day but had irisin blocked in their systems did not experience any improvements and did not perform better in memory tests than beta-amyloid-infused mice that had not exercised.Researchers hope this new finding can help them develop a pharmaceutical form of irisin that could help elderly patients that have difficulties exercising prevent symptoms of dementia or treat Alzheimers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Irisin helps brain function and prevents memory loss2. Irisin in mice infused with beta-amyloid3. Mice get irisin blocked4. Pharmaceutical form of irisinVOICEOVER (in English): A new study published in the journal Nature Medicine shows that a hormone released during exercise called irisin helps regrow brain cells and protect the brain from developing Alzheimers. Irisin production is reduced in Alzheimers patients.The team studied the effects of irisin on mice. Results showed mice that swam almost every day for five weeks did not suffer memory impairment even though they were being infused with beta-amyloid.According to Alzheimers Association, accumulation of beta-amyloid protein is one of the possible causes of Alzheimers disease.However mice who swam every day but had irisin blocked in their systems did not experience any improvements and did not perform better in memory tests than beta-amyloid-infused mice that had not exercised.Researchers hope this new finding can help them develop a pharmaceutical form of irisin that could help elderly patients that have difficulties exercising prevent symptoms of dementia or treat Alzheimers.SOURCES: Nature Medicine, Medical Xpresshttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-018-0275-4https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-02-alzheimer.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/13/3780402/3780402_60742AC1C77C4F97A6B176FE3E5EEBE9_190213_3780402_New_technology_can_match_a_person_s_face_to_thei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,animation,3D,graphics,Next Animation,Next Media,feature,sidebar,video,explainer,image,illustration,graphic,Alzheimers,Alzheimers disease,beta amyloid,irisin,memory loss,dementia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3781374</guid>
      <title>Sleep helps reduce inflammation and fight atherosclerosis in mice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in the journal Nature has found that getting adequate sleep can help by reducing inflammation in the body and fighting against atherosclerosis. According to Live Science, the study found that fragmented sleep in mice affects levels of a certain hormone, which then increases production of inflammatory cells in the bone marrow. This inflammation plays a role in the development of atherosclerosis. Atherosclerosis is a condition where plaques made up of fat, cholesterol, calcium and other substances build up inside arteries.  The new study looked at mice that were genetically prone to atherosclerosis. Some of the mice were allowed to get adequate sleep, while another group's sleep was frequently interrupted by a "sweep bar" that automatically swept across the bottom of the cage. The scientists found the sleep-deprived mice had larger arterial plaques and higher levels of inflammation in their blood vessels compared with the sleep-sufficient mice. Researchers also discovered sleep-deprived mice had lower levels of the hormone hypocretin, which led to an increase in the levels of the signalling protein CSF1. This in turn increased production of inflammatory white blood cells in the bone marrow and accelerated atherosclerosis. The team found that by restoring hypocretin levels in the mice reduced atherosclerosis. According to study senior author Filip Swirski, of the Massachusetts General Hospital Center for Systems Biology, "we have discovered that sleep helps regulate the production of inflammatory cells and the health of blood vessels and that, conversely, sleep disruption breaks down control of inflammatory cell production, leading to more inflammation and heart disease."  The next step will be for researchers to see if the results can be replicated in humans.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New study findings2. Mice split into sufficient sleep and sleep-deprived groups3. Sleep-deprived mice had more plaques and higher inflammation than sleep-sufficient mice4. Study resultsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the journal Nature, fragmented sleep in mice affects levels of a certain hormone, which then increases production of inflammatory cells in bone marrow. This inflammation plays a role in the development of atherosclerosis." "The new study looked at mice that were genetically prone to atherosclerosis. Some of the mice were allowed to get adequate sleep, while another group's sleep was frequently interrupted by a 'sweep bar' that automatically swept across the bottom of the cage." "The scientists found the sleep-deprived mice had larger arterial plaques and higher levels of inflammation in their blood vessels compared with the sleep-sufficient mice." "Researchers also discovered sleep-deprived mice had lower levels of the hormone hypocretin, which led to an increase in the levels of the signalling protein CSF1, which in turn increased production of inflammatory white blood cells in the bone marrow and accelerated atherosclerosis." SOURCES: Live Science, Naturehttps://www.livescience.com/64761-sleep-heart-disease.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-0948-2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 12:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/14/3781374/3781374_EB054F7413FE4B3A84E5B36E38B009F5_190214_3781374_Sleep_helps_reduce_inflammation_and_fight_athero_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, adequate sleep, sleep inflammation, sleep atherosclerosis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3781367</guid>
      <title>NASA spots 22-mile-wide crater beneath Greenland ice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have discovered what may be another massive crater below Greenland's ice sheets, NASA announced on Monday. According to Space.com, the suspected crater is around 22 miles or 36 kilometers wide, but has not been definitively identified yet as an impact crater. According the NBC News, this comes just months after other scientists discovered a 19-mile-wide impact crater under the Hiawatha glacier. Joe MacGregor, a glaciologist at NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center, is a co-author of the paper published in the journal Geophysical Research Letters, which describes the find. He was also on the team that found the Hiawatha crater.  After the finding the Hiawatha crater, MacGregor and his team analyzed topographic maps and satellite imagery to see if there might be other craters in the area. That's when they discovered the second bowl-shaped feature 114 miles southeast of the Hiawatha crater. According to NBC, the presence was confirmed using Operation IceBridge data, an ongoing NASA mission which uses planes to map changes in ice in the polar regions. In order for researchers to determine if this second structure is actually an impact crater, scientists will need to conduct more field work or obtain core samples to confirm the discovery. According to NBC, the team says they are unsure how old the structure is, but they estimated it was formed 100,000 to 100 million years ago.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location and size of 2nd possible impact crater2. Hiawatha glacier impact crater3. Researchers analyzing topographic maps and satellite imagery4. Researchers conducting field work and taking core samplesVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA announced on Monday that researchers have discovered what may be another massive crater below Greenland's ice sheets." "According to Space.com, the suspected crater is around 22 miles or 36 kilometers wide, but has not been definitively identified yet as an impact crater." "According the NBC News, this comes just months after other scientists discovered a 19-mile-wide impact crater under the Hiawatha glacier."  "After the finding the Hiawatha crater, the team analyzed topographic maps and satellite imagery to see if there might be other craters in the area." "That's when they discovered the second bowl-shaped feature 114 miles southeast of the Hiawatha crater." "In order for researchers to determine if this second structure is actually an impact crater, scientists will need to conduct more field work or obtain core samples to confirm the discovery." SOURCES: Space.com, NBC Newshttps://www.space.com/second-possible-crater-impact-beneath-greenland.htmlhttps://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/another-immense-crater-may-have-been-found-deep-under-greenland-ncna970191***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 12:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/14/3781367/3781367_01E473CD293E4B8BA48AD3740B36E41D_190214_3781367_NASA_spots_22_mile_wide_crater_beneath_Greenland_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Greenland, Greenland crater, Greenland impact crater, Hiawatha crater, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3781152</guid>
      <title>Rising temperatures could change the ocean's color, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe oceans are expected to become bluer and greener by the end of the end of this century, according to a study published in Nature Communications.Researchers from MIT and the University of Southampton noted that phytoplankton at the surface of the sea absorbs and reflects the sunlight. This gives the ocean its current bluish-green hue.Rising temperatures and acidity will cause phytoplankton in the water to decrease in number, essentially changing the color of the ocean as less sunlight is absorbed.The study explains that parts of the ocean will gradually turn a deep blue in color while others gradually turn darker green over the next 80 years.However, this change probably won't be visible to the naked eye, lead author of the study, Dr. Stephanie Dutkiewicz, told the BBC.The researchers were experimenting on the assumption that ocean temperatures would have risen by 3 degrees Celsius by 2100.Weather patterns such as El Nino or La Nina could also change the color of the ocean, according to a press release by MIT.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The ocean turning a dark shade of blue and green2. Phytoplankton and sun rays bouncing off the water3. Phytoplankton decreasing in number, causing the color of the ocean to change4. Part of the ocean turning deep blue while another part of the ocean turns deep green in colorVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study in published in Nature Communications, the oceans are expected to become bluer and greener by the end of the 21st Century.""Researchers from MIT and the University of Southampton noted that phytoplankton at the surface of the sea absorbs and reflects the sunlight. "This gives the ocean its current bluish-green hue." "However, rising temperatures and acidity will cause phytoplankton in the water to decrease in number, essentially changing the color of the ocean as less sunlight is absorbed.""The study explains that parts of the ocean will gradually turn a deep blue in color while others gradually turn darker green over the next 80 years.""However, this change probably won't be visible to the naked eye, lead author of the study, Dr. Stephanie Dutkiewicz, told the BBC."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Nature Communications, Gizmodo, New Atlas, MIT News, BBC News, CNN,    https://inhabitat.com/climate-change-to-change-the-color-of-the-oceans-over-the-next-80-years/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-019-08457-xhttps://earther.gizmodo.com/climate-change-is-causing-earths-oceans-to-change-color-1832327766https://newatlas.com/climate-change-ocean-color-century-global-warming/58336/http://news.mit.edu/2019/study-ocean-color-change-phytoplankton-climate-0204https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47092201https://edition.cnn.com/2019/02/04/world/climate-change-ocean-color-study/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 07:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/14/3781152/3781152_F67E7995CA5649D3B06DAFD5B1EAB38F_190214_3781152_Rising_temperatures_could_change_the_ocean_s_col_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, climate change, oceans, ocean color, ocean color change, color of the ocean is changing due to climate change, effect of climate change on oceans, ocean climate change, phytoplankton, rising temperatures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3781143</guid>
      <title>Study says North Korea poses less nuclear threat to U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study by Stanford University's Center for International Security and Cooperation reports that North Korea continues to build nuclear weapons.Open-source satellite images featured in a report by Stanford University's Center for International Security and Cooperation show that North Korea has not stopped production of nuclear weapons.Reuters reports that spent nuclear fuel generated at Yongbyon, North Korea's main nuclear plant, appears to have been reprocessed in May 2018.Researchers believe North Korea may have also produced 5 to 8 kilograms of weapons-grade plutonium. The report estimates that North Korea may have created an additional 5 to 7 nuclear weapons using plutonium and highly enriched uranium.Experts who participated in the study told Reuters that they believe North Korea doesn't have the capacity to reach the U.S. However, neighboring countries such as Japan and South Korea are still in danger.North Korea has stopped conducting nuclear tests. In 2018, the country did not flight test missiles of any range.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 3D rendition of satellite imagery of North Korean nuclear production2. Spent fuel and weapons-grade plutonium produced in Yongbyon3. Increase of North Korea nuclear weapons4. North Korean missiles capable of reaching Asia, but not USVOICEOVER (in English): "Open-source satellite images featured in a report by Stanford University's Center for International Security and Cooperation show that  North Korea has not stopped production of nuclear weapons.""Reuters reports that spent nuclear fuel generated at Yongbyon, North Korea's main nuclear plant, appears to have been reprocessed in May 2018.""Researchers believe North Korea may have also produced 5 to 8 kilograms of weapons-grade plutonium.""The report estimates that North Korea may have created an additional 5 to 7 nuclear weapons using plutonium and highly enriched uranium.""Experts who participated in the study told Reuters that they believe North Korea doesn't have the capacity to reach the U.S. However, neighboring countries such as Japan and South Korea are still in danger.""North Korea has stopped conducting nuclear tests. In 2018, the country did not flight test missiles of any range."SOURCES: Reuters, Stanford Center for International Security and Cooperation https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa-nuclear-study/north-korea-may-have-made-more-nuclear-bombs-but-threat-reduced-study-idUSKCN1Q10ELhttps://cisac.fsi.stanford.edu/content/dprk-history-2018-update***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/14/3781143/3781143_E4C4040EF28540E99528A407E1033730_190214_3781143_Study_says_North_Korea_poses_less_nuclear_threat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, north korea missile base, north korea missile, denuclearization, nuclear missile, north korea, missile base, north korea nuclear weapons, nuclear weapons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3781810</guid>
      <title>Elroy Air's self-flying drones could soon be used to deliver cargo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSan Francisco-based startup, Elroy Air, is developing an autonomous drone that could be used to haul heavy cargo as early as next year, according to the company's website.The company has already raised US$9.2 million from investors to build the aircraft called "Chaparral," Forbes reports.Its new self-flying drone will be able to carry 225 kg of cargo and fly 500 kilometers while in the air, according to Elroy Air's website.The drone is said to use a grasping mechanism to automatically pick up and release cargo pods.The aircraft will use six electric rotors for vertical take-offs and landings, Forbes reports.A hybrid-electric powertrain system will be used to power the self-flying drone. This will allow fewer pollutants to be scattered in the air, according to the company's website.Its website explains that the drone could also be used in humanitarian ways, such as to carry life saving supplies to disaster relief areas.The drone will undergo testing this year and is expected to be put into service by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The self-flying drone appears and is in the air2. The drone picking up then releasing the cargo pod3. The aircraft taking off and landing vertically4. The drone flying in the skyVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Elroy Air's website, its new self-flying drone will be able to carry 225 kg of cargo and fly 500 kilometers while in the air.""The drone is said to use a grasping mechanism to automatically pick up and release cargo pods.""Forbes reports the aircraft will use six electric rotors for vertical take-offs and landings.""A hybrid-electric powertrain system will be used to power the self-flying drone." "According to the company's website, this will allow fewer pollutants to be scattered in the air."SOURCES: Wired, Futurism, Elroy Air, Venture Beat, Forbes, Elroy Air Press release, https://www.wired.com/story/elroy-cargo-drone-chaparral/https://futurism.com/the-byte/giant-cargo-drone-elroy-airhttp://www.elroyair.com/https://venturebeat.com/2019/02/13/elroy-air-raises-9-2-million-for-delivery-drones-that-can-carry-up-to-500-pounds/https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2019/02/13/before-amazon-drops-packages-on-your-house-from-the-air-drones-may-start-to-transform-bulk-air-cargo/#694132e872fahttps://medium.com/@communications_71131/how-autonomous-air-cargo-can-expand-the-reach-of-expedited-logistics-33a98e98118c***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 09:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/15/3781810/3781810_379090A1AE4449D89CAD19CCD79630BC_190215_3781810_Elroy_Air_s_self_flying_drones_could_soon_be_use_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, drones, self flying drones, cargo, elroy air, elroy air drone,  drone delivery, drone helicopter, drone cargo delivery, drone cargo plane, cargo drone elroy air]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3781789</guid>
      <title>Spain may have to hold third election after budget is rejected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpain Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez might have to call for a third general election in less than four years after his budget was rejected by right-wing parties.Pedro Sanchez came to power in mid-2018 after ousting then prime minister Mariano Rajoy with the support of Catalan separatist lawmakers. Sanchez's Spanish Socialist Workers' Party needed their support to expel Rajoy as they only hold 84 of the 350 seats in Congress.According to The New York Times, this time around Catalan pro-independence parties rejected Sanchez's government budget plan and sided with the People's Party and the center-right Citizen's party. The budget was rejected 191 to 158 with one abstention.The shift in alliance comes after Catalan pro-independence parties made it clear that support for the budget would only come if independence talks were held. However, Sanchez's government sustains that, according to Spain's constitution, the country must remain united. Spain is divided into 17 autonomous regions. Catalonia is one of the wealthiest of them. According to CNBC, it accounts for roughly 20 percent of the country's GDP.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pedro Sanchez ousts Mariano Rajoy with the support of Catalan separatist lawmakers.2. Spanish Socialist Workers' Party hold 84 of the 350 seats in Congress3. Spanish political parties; Budget rejected 191 to 158 with one abstention4. Catalan pro-independenceVOICEOVER (in English): "Pedro Sanchez came to power in mid-2018 after ousting then prime minister Mariano Rajoy with the support of Catalan separatist lawmakers.""Sanchez's Spanish Socialist Workers' Party needed their support to expel Rajoy as they only hold 84 of the 350 seats in Congress.""According to The New York Times, this time around Catalan pro-independence parties rejected Sanchez's government budget plan and sided with the People's Party and the center-right Citizen's party.""The budget was rejected 191 to 158 with one abstention.""The shift in alliance comes after Catalan pro-independence parties made it clear that support for the budget would only come if independence talks were held." "However, Sanchez's government sustains that, according to Spain's constitution, the country must remain united." SOURCES: The New York Times, The Guardian, The Financial Times, Deutsche Welle, CNBC https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/13/world/europe/spain-election-vote.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/feb/13/spanish-pm-pedro-sanchez-snap-general-election-budgethttps://www.ft.com/content/45554e38-2f88-11e9-8744-e7016697f225https://www.dw.com/en/spanish-pm-calls-emergency-meeting-after-budget-rejected/a-47488641https://www.cnbc.com/2017/09/21/heres-how-bad-economically-a-spain-catalonia-split-could-really-be.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 09:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/15/3781789/3781789_322CD2A2F4154570A17B1D296A02C194_190215_3781789_Spain_may_have_to_hold_third_election_after_budg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, spain elections, spain budget, spanish government, Catalan independence, pedro sanchez, spanish socialist workers party, catalan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783486</guid>
      <title>Turkish authorities believe Khashoggi's remains may have been burned</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTurkey's state-run news agency Anadolu quoted a recent police report that states that Khashoggi's remains may have been burned in the Saudi consulate in Istanbul.The report states that the consulate has two wells and a gas and wood furnace that could reach over 1,000 degrees Celsius. This furnace could have been used to destroy traces of Khashoggi's DNA.Police also revealed that the hit squad had ordered 32 pieces of raw meat from a restaurant to the consulate after killing Khashoggi.The report also suggests that Khashoggi's fiancee could have been the second victim of the killing if the hit squad had been informed that she was waiting outside.Turkish authorities know that one of the members of the hit squad is Lieutenant Colonel Salah Mohammed A. Tubaigy, a forensic expert from the Saudi Interior Ministry.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Khashoggi attacked by Saudi operatives2. Khashoggi at Suadi consulate in Istanbul3. Khashoggi entering Saudi consulate in Istanbul;Khashoggi leaves phones with fiancee4.Khashoggi met inside consulate by Maher Mutreb 5.Khashoggi suffocated by Saudi operatives6.Depiction of saw used to dismember Khashoggi7.Khashoggi fiancee waiting outside consulate8.Khashoggi remains reportedly may have been burned9.Wood furnace and well at Saudi consulate; Destruction of DNA evidence10.32 pieces of raw meat ordered by operatives11.Khashoggi fiancee reportedly could have been attackedVOICEOVER (in English): "Washington Post journalist and Saudi dissident, Jamal Khashoggi, was killed by a Saudi hit squad on October 2." "He had arrived at the country's consulate in Istanbul to retrieve documents he needed in order to marry his Turkish fiance, Hatice Cengiz.""Khashoggi was last seen in CCTV footage as he entered the consulate at about 13:14 local time. He left both his phones with his fiancee instructing her to call for help if he didn't return.""Upon entering he encountered Saudi intelligence officer Maher Mutreb, who told the journalist, 'You are coming back,' according to a CNN source who read the transcript of an audio recording of Khashoggi's death.""This is when the hit squad is thought to have seized Khashoggi and suffocated him by putting a plastic bag over his head. Khashoggi's final words were, 'I can't breathe.'""The transcript then goes on to describe the sound of a saw assumed to be used for his dismemberment. Khashoggi's last gasps and screams can be heard at the same time.""During this time Khashoggi's fiancee was still waiting outside the consulate. She stayed until 1:00 am and came back the following day after he still hadn't returned.""Turkey's state-run news agency Anadolu quoted a recent police report that states that Khashoggi's remains may have been burned in the Saudi consulate in Istanbul.""The report states that the consulate has two wells and a gas and wood furnace that could reach over 1,000 degrees Celsius. This furnace could have been used to destroy traces of Khashoggi's DNA.""Police also revealed that the hit squad had ordered 32 pieces of raw meat from a restaurant to the consulate after killing Khashoggi.""The report also suggests that Khashoggi's fiancee could have been the second victim of the killing if the hit squad had been informed that she was waiting outside."SOURCES: Anadolu, CNN https://www.aa.com.tr/en/jamal-khashoggi/police-report-reveals-new-details-on-khashoggi-killing/1393298https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/09/middleeast/jamal-khashoggi-last-words-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/19/3783486/3783486_849418DA20FC42FB9F926F7864CEFE40_190219_3783486_Turkish_authorities_believe_Khashoggi_s_remains__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Jamal Khashoggi, Khashoggi, last words, final words, Khashoggi last words, Saudi consulate Istanbul, Khashoggi audio recording, Khashoggi transcript, Saudi journalist, Saudi dissident, MBS, Saudi crown prince, Mohammed bin Salman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783427</guid>
      <title>Aurora gunman opens fire on coworkers after being terminated from job</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA man opened fire on his coworkers after losing his job at an Illinois manufacturing plant, using a gun he was carrying illegally.The Chicago Tribune reports that while at a termination meeting at the Henry Pratt Co. in Aurora, Illinois, Gary Martin pulled out a handgun to shoot and kill the three people in the room with him.Martin then went on a gun rampage inside the office, shooting dead two coworkers just outside the meeting room and injuring another.According to CNN, the 45-year-old gunman shot and wounded five of the first police officers who arrived on the scene, before fleeing into the sprawling manufacturing plant.Aurora police Deputy Chief Keefe Jackson said over 200 to 300 officers from 35 agencies were deployed to the scene to hunt for the suspect and help rescue victims.The police found Martin in a back machine shop an hour later. He opened fire on the officers, who fired back, killing him.According to the Chicago Tribune, Martin had been carrying the gun illegally. Police said he bought the handgun in 2014 after getting an Illinois firearm owner's identification card.A background check failed to turn up a felony aggravated assault charge in Mississippi 25 years earlier, which would've disqualified him from legally owning a gun.But it wasn't until Martin applied for a concealed carry permit that his conviction was flagged and his firearm owner's ID card revoked. According to CNN, he was instructed to voluntarily relinquish his gun, but never did.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman shoots and kills co-workers during termination meeting2. Gunman opens fire inside office, killing two more and injuring one3. Gunman shoots and wounds five responding officers4. Gunman killed in shootout with policeVOICEOVER (in English): "The Chicago Tribune reports that while at a termination meeting at the Henry Pratt Co. in Aurora, Illinois, Gary Martin pulled out a handgun to shoot and kill the three people in the room with him.""Martin then went on a gun rampage inside the office, shooting dead two coworkers just outside the meeting room and injuring another.""According to CNN, the 45-year-old gunman shot and wounded five of the first police officers who arrived on the scene, before fleeing into the sprawling manufacturing plant.""The police found Martin in a back machine shop an hour later. He opened fire on the officers, who fired back, killing him."SOURCES: Chicago Tribune, CNNhttps://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/aurora-beacon-news/news/ct-met-aurora-illinois-shooting-update-20190216-story.html#nt=storygalleryhttps://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/aurora-beacon-news/news/ct-met-cb-aurora-illinois-shooting-updates-20190216-story.htmlhttps://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/aurora-beacon-news/news/ct-abn-aurora-warehouse-shooting-timeline-st-0217-story.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/02/17/us/aurora-shooting-termination/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 16:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/19/3783427/3783427_3C300D15317F43E98CE3F5D09917C385_190219_3783427_Aurora_gunman_opens_fire_on_coworkers_after_bein_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, aurora shooting, henry pratt shooting, aurora gunman, mass shooting, gun laws, gun control, gun rampage, shooting rampage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783174</guid>
      <title>No agreement yet in US-China trade talks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. and China have not yet an accord in crucial trade talks, reports The South China Morning Post. Beijing and Washington continue to disagree on matters such as equal market access and protection of intellectual property during trade talks.According to Business Insider, both sides are seeking to lower tariffs and ease trade tensions.Anonymous sources told The New York Times, the U.S. wants to create a process that will increase taxes on Chinese products if its American exports continue to rise.If a trade deal isn't locked in by March 1, the US will raise taxes from 10 to 25 percent on US$200 billion worth of Chinese products, Business Insider reports.US President Donald Trump is considering pushing the deadline back by 60 days, Bloomberg reports.The South China Morning Post reports the talks are currently being conducted by US trade representative Robert E. Lighthizer, US treasury secretary Steven Mnuchin and Chinese Vice-Premier Liu He.If they can't reach an agreement, President Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping might have to hold a meeting to hash out a deal.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A Chinese flag, the US flag, along with a market access icon and an intellectual property icon2. What the both sides are seeking3. Chinese products and a vertical bar graph4. US flag and two calendar iconsVOICEOVER (in English): "The South China Morning Post reports that China and the US continue to disagree on  matters such as equal market access and protection of intellectual property.""According to Business Insider, both sides are seeking to lower tariffs and ease trade tensions.""Business Insider reports that if a trade deal isn't locked in by March 1, the US will raise taxes from 10 to 25 percent on US$200 billion worth of Chinese products.""Bloomberg reports US President Donald Trump is considering pushing the deadline back by 60 days."SOURCES: The South China Morning Post, Business Insider, Bloomberg, CNBC, The Washington Post, The New York Times, https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/2186228/trade-war-talks-china-and-us-said-be-far-apart-frameworkhttps://www.businessinsider.com/trump-china-trade-war-negotiations-tariffs-march-1-deadline-2019-2https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-14/u-s-china-trade-teams-said-to-be-far-apart-on-reform-demandshttps://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/14/us-china-trade-deal-may-not-be-the-catalyst.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/in-pursuing-a-trade-deal-the-us-may-be-asking-china-to-do-the-unthinkable/2019/02/14/2cdf9ad6-3067-11e9-ac6c-14eea99d5e24_story.html?noredirect=on&utm_term=.26332b7d4ec0https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/12/business/us-china-trade-talks.html?action=click&module=Top%20Stories&pgtype=Homepage***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 08:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/18/3783174/3783174_C1973DAFA95A4924A06D536E3EA7A4A7_190218_3783174_No_agreement_yet_in_US_China_trade_talks_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, usa, china, trade talks, us china trade talks, us china trade, us china relations, us china trade war,China vs usa, trade war china and the usa trade war china news, trade war china and the united states]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783135</guid>
      <title>JP Morgan to launch first bank-backed cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJP Morgan is creating its own cryptocurrency, and is becoming the first major U.S. bank to do so.According to CNBC, the nation's largest bank, JP Morgan Chase, announced on Thursday that it would be launching its own cryptocurrency called the JPM coin, which has a fixed value redeemable for $1.The coin is designed to be used by big institutional customers such as corporations, banks, and broker-dealers rather than individuals.According to the bank's head of blockchain projects, the digital token is meant to speed up international payments, which traditionally take a day or more to settle via wire transfer. It can also be used for securities transactions and treasury services.When clients want to move dollars on the bank's Quorum blockchain system, money in their accounts is converted to JPM coins.According to Fox Business, 'the tokens are transferred and instantaneously redeemed' for the equivalent amount of dollars.The New York Times reports that JP Morgan hopes to increase the coin's versatility, perhaps expanding in the future to represent currencies other than the dollar.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. JP Morgan cryptocurrency coin fixed to a single U.S. dollar2. JPM coin used only by major JP Morgan institutional clients3. JPM coin used to speed up international payments, securities transactions, treasury service4. How JPM coin worksVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNBC, JP Morgan Chase announced it would be launching its own cryptocurrency called the JPM coin, which has a fixed value redeemable for $1.""The coin is designed to be used by big institutional customers such as corporations, banks, and broker-dealers rather than individuals.""According to the bank's head of blockchain projects, the digital token is meant to speed up international payments, which traditionally take a day or more to settle via wire transfer. It can also be used for securities transactions and treasury services."When clients want to move dollars on the bank's Quorum blockchain system, money in their accounts is converted to JPM coins.""According to Fox Business, 'the tokens are transferred and instantaneously redeemed' for the equivalent amount of dollars."SOURCES: CNBC, New York Times, Fox Businesshttps://www.cnbc.com/amp/2019/02/13/jp-morgan-is-rolling-out-the-first-us-bank-backed-cryptocurrency-to-transform-payments--.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/14/business/dealbook/jpmorgan-cryptocurrency-bitcoin.htmlhttps://www.foxbusiness.com/features/jpmorgan-set-to-roll-out-the-first-bank-backed-cryptocurrency***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 07:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/18/3783135/3783135_121C87945D374E20ACFA5EAE2A39250A_190218_3783135_JP_Morgan_to_launch_first_bank_backed_cryptocurr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cryptocurrency, blockchain, digital tokens, bank cryptocurrency, JP Morgan, JP Morgan chase, JPM coin, JP Morgan coin, JP Morgan cryptocurrency, Quorum]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783037</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show two interconnected volcanoes in Indonesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that the two volcanoes may actually be connected via the same plumbing system.A team of scientists were monitoring volcanic activity at the Agung volcano to find out what caused its sudden eruption in 2017, according to a study published in the journal Nature Communications.Using satellite technology by the European Space Agency, researchers from the University of Bristol were able to map out ground motion between the Agung volcano and the neighboring volcano Batur.Juliet Biggs, who lead the study, explained in a University of Bristol press release that this could indicate movement of fresh magma underneath the volcano.Fabien Albino, a researcher involved with the study, is quoted as saying in the same press release that they noticed the magma "must be moving sideways" as well as moving upwards vertically as earthquake activity was noticed upto 5 km away from the summit.He added that the study provides geophysical evidence that shows that Mount Agung and Mount Batur may actually have a connected plumbing system.Albino went on to explain the study has important implications for predicting volcano eruptions and could also be used to explain two volcanic explosions taking place at the same time.Mount Agung suddenly erupted in November of 2017 after remaining dormant for 50 years."Bali's main airport was closed down while thousands of residents were forced to evacuate, CNN reported at the time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Agung volcano erupting2. Ground motion between Agung volcano and Batur volcano3. Cross section of Agung volcano with magma moving sideways4. Cross section of Agung volcano and Batur volcano, showing they are connectedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the journal Nature Communications, a team of scientists were monitoring volcanic activity at the Agung volcano to find out what caused its sudden eruption in 2017.""Using satellite technology by the European Space Agency, researchers from the University of Bristol were able to map out ground motion between the Agung volcano and the neighboring volcano Batur.""Juliet Biggs, who lead the study, explained in a University of Bristol press release that this could indicate movement of fresh magma underneath the volcano.""Fabien Albino, a researcher involved with the study, is quoted as saying in the same press release that they noticed the magma 'must be moving sideways' as well as moving upwards vertically as earthquake activity was noticed upto 5 km away from the summit.""He added that the study provides geophysical evidence that shows that Mount Agung and Mount Batur may actually have a connected plumbing system."SOURCES: Nature Communications,Earth.com ,Phys.org, University of Bristolhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-019-08564-9https://www.earth.com/news/neighboring-volcanoes-connected-bali/https://phys.org/news/2019-02-satellite-images-reveal-interconnected-plumbing.htmlhttp://www.bristol.ac.uk/news/2019/february/bali-volcano-satellite-images-.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 03:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/18/3783037/3783037_39A54526F6144A78ACA26A1A3CC64B97_190218_3783037_Satellite_images_show_two_interconnected_volcano_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  bali, indonesia, volcanoes, bali volcanoes connected, bali volcano eruption, mount agung eruption, interconnected volcanoes indonesia, volcano plumbing system, volcano magma flow]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783921</guid>
      <title>Big Ben-sized asteroid to skim past Earth on February 19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA large asteroid traveling through space at tens of thousands of miles per hour is going to pass by our planet on Tuesday.NASA's asteroid trackers have been monitoring asteroid 2013 MD8 since its discovery in 2013. The space rock measures between 128 to 282 feet, making it nearly as tall as London's Big Ben.Asteroid 2013 MD8 is classified as a Near Earth Object. These are asteroids and comets composed of water ice and embedded dust particles, which are nudged by gravitational attraction into a trajectory that allows them to cut into Earth's orbit.NASA announced that the asteroid will pass Earth on February 19, at 12:55 p.m. Eastern Standard Time, while traveling at a speed of 30,418 miles per hour.At its closest, 2013 MD8 will be 0.0387 astronomical units from Earth, or roughly 15.1 lunar distances.According to NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory, the space rock's next close approach to Earth won't be until January 28, 2022.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid 2013 MD8 nearly as tall as Big Ben2. Description of Near Earth Objects3. Asteroid 2013 MD8 trajectory and speed4. Asteroid's closest distance to EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's asteroid trackers have been monitoring asteroid 2013 MD8 since its discovery in 2013. The space rock measures between 128 to 282 feet, making it nearly as tall as London's Big Ben.""Asteroid 2013 MD8 is classified as a Near Earth Object. These are asteroids and comets composed of water ice and embedded dust particles, which are nudged by gravitational attraction into a trajectory that allows them to cut into Earth's orbit.""NASA announced that the asteroid will pass Earth on February 19, at 12:55 p.m. Eastern Standard Time, while traveling at a speed of 30,418 miles per hour.""At its closest, 2013 MD8 will be 0.0387 astronomical units from Earth, or roughly 15.1 lunar distances."SOURCES: NASAhttps://solarsystem.nasa.gov/news/849/moon-missive/https://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?sstr=2013%20MD8;old=0;orb=1;cov=0;log=0;cad=1#cadhttps://cneos.jpl.nasa.gov/about/basics.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 13:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/19/3783921/3783921_DBFEDD9791604EA1B80617FF27C42117_190219_3783921_Big_Ben_sized_asteroid_to_skim_past_Earth_on_Feb_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, asteroid, asteroid flyby, giant asteroid, big ben sized asteroid, 2013 md8, near earth object, close asteroid encounter, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783837</guid>
      <title>Boeing to build robot submersibles for U.S. Navy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBoeing has been awarded a US$43 million contract by the U.S. Navy to build unmanned robot submarines, according to the US Department of Defense.The company will build four Orca Extra Large Unmanned Undersea Vehicles. According to U.S. Naval Institute News, the submarine will measure 51-feet in length. The vehicle will be capable of sailing up to 6,500 nautical miles. Its design is based on Boeing's Echo Voyager unmanned submarine.The vehicle will include payload bay measuring 34-feet in width. This will have a volume of 2,000 cubic feet, New Atlas reports. The diesel-electric Orca will have depth sensors and an inertial navigation system, according to Popular Mechanics.The submersible is expected to be autonomous and could remain submerged for months.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boeing logo, US Navy logo and the Orca submarine2. Length of the Orca submarine 3. Flash blue on the payload bay of the Orca submarine4. Depth sensors and the submarine sailing by itself under the sea VOICEOVER (in English): "Boeing has been awarded a US$43 million contract by the U.S. Navy.""According to the US Department of Defense, the company will build four Orca Extra Large Unmanned Undersea Vehicles.""According to U.S. Naval Institute News, the submarine will measure 51-feet in length. "The vehicle will be capable of sailing up to 6,500 nautical miles.""Its design is based on Boeing's Echo Voyager unmanned submarine.""New Atlas reports the vehicle will include payload bay measuring 34-feet in width. This will have a volume of 2,000 cubic feet.""According to Popular Mechanics, the diesel-electric Orca will have depth sensors and an inertial navigation system."SOURCES: US Department of Defense, US Naval Institute News, New Atlashttps://dod.defense.gov/News/Contracts/Contract-View/Article/1757113/https://news.usni.org/2019/02/13/41119?fbclid=IwAR1w0dY9toVPxKXodqMLeRFer_8I_jU4p7NqWgym2XO81WggqxbbqvaWwH0https://newatlas.com/boeing-contractoorca-robotic-subs/58505/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 11:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/19/3783837/3783837_DE23006F93F843F1884013DA4FFE49B9_190219_3783837_Boeing_to_build_robot_submersibles_for_U_S__Navy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Boeing, orca, US navy, Orca Extra Large Unmanned Undersea Vehicles, submarines, unmanned submarines, autonomous navigation system, unmanned underwater vehicles, robotic submarines, navy orca, navy orca uuv, navy orca program, us navy orca]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3783529</guid>
      <title>China plans to build a solar power station in space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has ambitious plans to build the first ever solar power station in space.China's Science and Technology Daily reports the country is planning to build a solar power station that would orbit the earth at a distance of 36,000 kilometers.The newspaper quotes Li Ming, vice-president of The China Academy of Space Technology, as saying in 2017 that China has the potential to become the first country to build a solar power station with practical value in space if it continues to increase development at its current speed.Pang Zhihao, a researcher from the China Academy of Space Technology, told the newspaper the solar station would be able to draw energy from the sun without any interference from earth's atmosphere.Pang said the orbital power plant would be able to provide a stable supply of energy back to earth up to 99 percent of the time, at six times the intensity of regular solar farms.The scientists are expected to build a small to medium-sized solar power station and launch it to the stratosphere between 2021 and 2025, according to Science and Technology Daily.Pang said the team is also contemplating whether to use robots and 3D printing technology to build the power station in space, as its weight could exceed 1,000 tonnes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The solar power station in space2. The solar station absorbing sun rays3. The solar station beaming solar energy back to earth4. Medium-sized solar power station and a calendarVOICEOVER (in English): "China's Science and Technology Daily reports the country is planning to build a solar power station that would orbit the earth at a distance of 36,000 kilometers.""Pang Zhihao, a researcher from the China Academy of Space Technology, told the newspaper the solar station would be able to draw energy from the sun without any interference from earth's atmosphere.""Pang said the orbital power plant would be able to provide a stable supply of energy back to earth up to 99 percent of the time, at six times the intensity of regular solar farms.""According to Science and Technology Daily, the scientists are expected to build a small to medium-sized solar power station and launch it to the stratosphere between 2021 and 2025."SOURCES: Science & Technology Daily, Sydney Morning Herald, http://www.stdaily.com/index/kejixinwen/2019-02/14/content_750019.shtmlhttp://www.stdaily.com/zhuanti01/tjyzsc/2019-01/25/content_748479.shtmlhttp://stdaily.com/index/kejixinwen/2017-11/01/content_590295.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 02:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/19/3783529/3783529_36D49DF55E704851B871EB335F8A6A7F_190219_3783529_China_plans_to_build_a_solar_power_station_in_sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, space, solar power station, renewable energy, solar power, green technology, solar power station in space, solar energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3784503</guid>
      <title>Scientists decode great white shark genome</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA research team has mapped the great white shark's genome and found the keys to many of its special adaptations. The great white shark's genome contains large amounts of information. They have 41 pairs of chromosomes while humans only have 23.The results were published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences. These showed that a set of genes involved in wound healing and another set involved with blood clotting had evolved significantly among sharks, allowing them to recover from injuries much faster than other organisms.Findings also showed that great whites have genetic adaptations that help them preserve a stable genome. The same genes that are involved in genome stability also have the ability to fight cancer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. White shark genome; comparison of number of chromosomes between white shark and humans2. Special white shark genes that allow them to heal more quickly3. White shark genome stability4. White shark genome resistant to cancerVOICEOVER (in English): "The great white shark's genome contains large amounts of information. They have 41 pairs of chromosomes while humans only have 23.""A research team mapped the great white shark's genome and found the keys to many of its special adaptations.""The results of the study were published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences." "These showed that a set of genes involved in wound healing and another set involved with blood clotting had evolved significantly among sharks, allowing them to recover from injuries much faster than other organisms.""Findings also showed that great whites have genetic adaptations that help them preserve a stable genome." "The same genes that are involved in genome stability also have the ability to fight cancer."SOURCES: Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, CNET, WiRED, Digital Trends, One Green Planet  https://www.pnas.org/content/early/2019/02/13/1819778116https://www.cnet.com/news/the-great-white-sharks-genetic-healing-powers-have-been-decoded/https://www.wired.com/story/dun-dun-duun-duuun-the-great-white-shark-genome-is-here/https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/great-white-shark-genome/http://www.onegreenplanet.org/animalsandnature/7-alarming-facts-about-the-shark-fin-trade/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 13:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/20/3784503/3784503_B445E842971742CAABBBB8AD414EE03B_190220_3784503_Scientists_decode_great_white_shark_genome_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, white shark, shark, genome, genetics, white shark genetics, white shark genome, white shark genetics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3784337</guid>
      <title>Scientists find neurons can send signals wirelessly to each other</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch published in the Journal of Physiology details a newly found form of neural communication in which neurons that are not connected can send signals to each other.According to the study, the new type of neural communication is able to move from a neuron in one section of the brain to another. Scientists from Case Western Reserve University were testing brain waves in hippocampal slices taken from the brains of decapitated mice. According to the study, researchers found that an electrical field was generated at a gradual recurring interval in their sampled brain tissue. This activated nearby cells.The electric field was also found to stimulate neurons even if there was a gap in the brain tissue.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Brain and a spark jumping from one neuron to another2. Mouse, brain waves going rough hippocampal slices from the mouse3. An electric field forming, and a few cells becoming activated as a result4. The electric field stimulate neuronsVOICEOVER (in English): "New research details a newly found form of neural communication which is able to move from a neuron in one section of the brain to another.""Scientists from Case Western Reserve University were testing brain waves in hippocampal slices taken from the brains of decapitated mice.""According to the study, published in the Journal of Physiology, researchers found that an electrical field was generated at a gradual recurring interval in their sampled brain tissue. "This activated nearby cells.""The electric field was also found to stimulate neurons even if there was a gap in the brain tissue."SOURCES:Science Alert, Case Western Reserve University, The Journal of Physiology,  https://www.sciencealert.com/neuroscientists-say-they-ve-found-an-entirely-new-form-of-neural-communicationhttps://thedaily.case.edu/discovering-a-new-form-of-communication-in-the-brain/https://physoc.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1113/JP276904***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 08:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/20/3784337/3784337_9730D7F064354BE69954217A98384692_190220_3784337_Scientists_find_neurons_can_send_signals_wireles_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, neuroscience, brain, neural communication, hippocampus, human brain, human brain neural network, brain neural communication, neurons, science, neurons leaping wirelessly, new form of communication in the brain]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3785153</guid>
      <title>Japanese utility makes first contact with Fukushima melted fuel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLast week, a probe touched melted nuclear debris in the damaged second reactor at the Fukushima nuclear plant for the first time in almost eight years since the disaster, according to Tokyo Electric Power Company.  The purpose of the mission was to determine how solid the melted fuel is and whether it could be transported away from the site, according to The Asahi Shimbun.  The robotic probe designed by Toshiba weighs about 1 kilogram and is fitted with 3-centimeter-long claws. It can extend 15 meters and lift pieces up to 8 centimeters in diameter, that weigh up to 2 kilograms. The probe is also equipped with a dosimeter and a camera.According to TEPCO, workers manually inserted the probe through a crack in the side of the No. 2 reactor's containment vessel.  Workers then remotely operated the probe from a building close to the No. 2 reactor building.The probe lifted pebble-like nuclear fuel debris at five spots and failed to pick up debris in one area. The probe also touched melted fuel on the workers scaffold below the reactor's pressure vessel. The retrieval process will start in earnest at one of the reactors in 2021, according to a joint central government and TEPCO plan. According to Bloomberg, full decommissioning of the Fukushima plant is expected to take 30 or 40 years.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Fukushima plant and Toshiba probe2. Toshiba probe3. Probe being inserted and probe control room4. Probe touching melted fuel VOICEOVER (in English): "According to TEPCO, last week, a probe touched melted nuclear debris in the damaged second reactor at the Fukushima nuclear plant for the first time in almost eight years since the disaster."  "According to The Asahi Shimbun.The purpose of the mission was to determine how solid the melted fuel is and whether it could be transported away from the site."  "The robotic probe designed by Toshiba weighs about 1 kilogram and is fitted with 3-centimeter-long claws. It can extend 15 meters and lift pieces up to 8 centimeters in diameter, that weigh up to 2 kilograms. The probe is also equipped with a dosimeter and a camera." "According to TEPCO, workers manually inserted the probe through a crack in the side of the No. 2 reactor's containment vessel."  "Workers then remotely operated the probe from a building close to the No. 2 reactor building.""The probe lifted pebble-like nuclear fuel debris at five spots and failed to pick up debris in one area. The probe also touched melted fuel on the workers scaffold below the reactor's pressure vessel." SOURCES: The Asahi Shimbun, Bloomberg, Ars Technicahttp://www.asahi.com/ajw/articles/photo/AS20190214003286.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-11/next-up-for-fukushima-clean-up-what-does-melted-fuel-feel-like?srnd=premiumhttps://arstechnica.com/science/2019/02/japanese-utility-makes-first-contact-with-melted-fukushima-fuel/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 12:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/21/3785153/3785153_90E32CF7CBFF40FCA6EB28CFEB6F940A_190221_3785153_Japanese_utility_makes_first_contact_with_Fukush_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Fukushima, Fukushima Reactor 2, Fukushima melted fuel, Fukushima Toshiba probe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3785083</guid>
      <title>Effects of U.S. sanctions on Venezuela</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVenezuela's economic struggles worsen as the U.S. lays even more sanctions on the country.What began as social upheaval after the death of Hugo Chavez and the presidency of his hand-picked successor Nicolas Maduro has spiralled into one of the world's largest humanitarian crises.According to the U.S. Department of State, in March of 2015 Obama had issued an executive order to implement the act. So far, under this act, the Department of the Treasury has sanctioned 65 individuals, six during the Obama administration and 58 during Trump's.In addition to targeted sanctions against individuals and companies, the Trump administration has imposed additional economic sanctions.Venezuela is currently experiencing unprecedented levels of poverty, with almost 90 percent of its population living below the poverty line, according to data from ENCOVI, Venezuela's official survey on quality of life.According to data from ENCOVI, 64.3 percent of families in the country have lost roughly 11.4 kilograms or 25 pounds, and 63.2 percent of adults said they skipped a meal to provide food to their children. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Obama and Trump impose sanctions on individuals in Venezuela2. Trump restricts Venezuelan access to U.S. debt and equity markets3. Venezuela's cryptocurrency4.Trump administration announces sanctions against PDVSA5. Venezuela oil production plummetingVOICEOVER (in English): "In December of 2014, Obama signed The Venezuela Defense of Human Rights and Civil Society Act. This act is mainly directed towards Venezuelan officials who participated in human rights abuses.""According to the U.S. Department of State, in March of 2015 Obama had issued an executive order to implement the act. So far, under this act, the Department of the Treasury has sanctioned 65 individuals, six during the Obama administration and 58 during Trump's.""In addition to targeted sanctions against individuals and companies, the Trump administration has imposed additional economic sanctions.""In 2017, Trump restricted Venezuelan access to U.S. debt and equity markets. This sanction had a few exceptions, among them transactions for new debt by CITGO, which is owned by PDVSA, the Venezuelan state-owned oil and natural gas company.""In February of 2018, Maduro's government created a cryptocurrency called 'Petro' in an effort to evade sanctions. One month later the U.S. enacted yet another sanction, this time prohibiting transactions involving Venezuelan digital currency." "On January 28, the Trump administration announced yet another sanction, this time against PDVSA, forcing Venezuela to find new ways to dilute its crude oil and look for new customers." "During the announcement, National Security Advisor John Bolton said $7 billion in assets would be frozen and the company would lose roughly $11 billion dollars in export proceeds in the coming year.""This sanction is an extremely heavy blow to Venezuela as its oil production continues to plummet from 2.4 million barrels per day in 2015 to 1.34 million in 2018, according to a report by Rystad Energy."SOURCES: ENCOVI, United Nations Human Rights, U.S. Department of State, Rystad Energyhttps://encovi.ucab.edu.ve/https://bit.ly/2BNdRDshttps://www.state.gov/e/eb/tfs/spi/venezuela/https://bit.ly/2CCza8ghttps://bit.ly/2Sqou9P***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 10:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/21/3785083/3785083_FD39DB573E624C2D8E24434CD6F30C56_190221_3785083_Effects_of_U_S__sanctions_on_Venezuela_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, us venezuela sanctions, venezuela sanctions, sanctions, venezuela economy, juan guaido, trump, donald trump, maduro, nicolas maduro, guaido, poverty, venezuela cryptocurrency, venezuela petro cryptocurrency, venezuela petro issuance, digital currency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3785075</guid>
      <title>Neptune's new moon Hippocamp may have broken off from a larger moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of astronomers using NASA's Hubble Space telescope have shed light on the mysterious moon around Neptune.According to a press release from the SETI Institute, a tiny moon discovered orbiting Neptune in 2013 has now been named Hippocamp. It is one of the planet's seven inner moons, and the newest of its 14 known moons.Naming conventions for the Neptune system require something out of Greco-Roman undersea mythology. In Greek mythology, Hippocamp is a half fish, half horse creature. It's related to Hippocampus, which is the scientific name for the seahorse, and the name of a major component of the human brain that's seahorse-shaped.Hippocamp measures about 34 kilometers across, and is 1/1000th the mass of Proteus, which at 418 kilometers across is Neptune's largest inner satellite.The small moon was observed to be orbiting unusually close to Proteus, even though such a large moon should have gravitationally swept it aside and cleared its orbital path.In a paper published in the journal Nature, SETI researchers hypothesized that Hippocamp is a fragment of Proteus that broke off following a collision with a comet billions of years ago.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hippocamp one of Neptune's seven inner moons2. Hippocamp size compared to Proteus and other inner moons3. Hippocamp orbiting closely with Proteus4. Hippocamp may have broken off from Proteus after a comet collisionVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the SETI Institute, a tiny moon discovered orbiting Neptune in 2013 has now been named Hippocamp. It is one of the planet's seven inner moons, and the newest of its 14 known moons.""Hippocamp measures about 34 kilometers across, and is 1/1000th the mass of the Proteus, which at 418 kilometers across is Neptune's largest inner satellite.""The small moon was observed to be orbiting unusually close to Proteus, even though such a large moon should have gravitationally swept it aside and cleared its orbital path.""In a paper published in the journal Nature, SETI researchers hypothesized that Hippocamp is a fragment of Proteus that broke off following a collision with a comet billions of years ago."SOURCES: SETI Institute, Naturehttps://www.seti.org/press-release/tiny-neptune-moon-spotted-hubble-may-have-broken-largerhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-0909-9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 10:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/21/3785075/3785075_5D6510725A7A4B29BD52966E94E408B0_190221_3785075_Neptune_s_new_moon_Hippocamp_may_have_broken_off_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Neptune, Neptune moon, Hippocamp, moons of Neptune, moons, Hubble Space Telescope, new moon, Proteus, comet collision]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3784865</guid>
      <title>ESA unveils plans to explore binary asteroid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA and the European Space Agency are joining forces to research an asteroid system.The ESA's Hera spacecraft will be the first to explore an asteroid system named 65803 Didymos. According to the space agency, Didymos measures 780 meters across. The asteroid system, is its orbiting moonlet "Didymoon" which is only 160 meters in width.According to an ESA news release, the Hera spacecraft will research the crater formed by the DART experiment in 2026. It collect data pertaining to the shape and dimensions of the DART crater, as well as surface samples. Hera will also use thermal imaging technology to examine the asteroid's structure. If the mission is successful, this moonlet will be the smallest asteroid ever visited by any spacecraft.Prior to that, NASA will conduct its first planetary defense mission. According to the space agency, the Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART, will crash into the surface of Didymoon in 2022. NASA is aiming to change the speed and direction of the asteroid system with this test.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Hera spacecraft and the planetary system2. The size of the two asteroids3. NASA's planetary defense mission4. Representation of the spacecraft using its onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system to detect the asteroid 5. Representation of the spacecraft crashing into the asteroid6. Hera researching the hole formed by DART7.Hera scanning the asteroidsVOICEOVER (in English): "The ESA's Hera spacecraft will be the first to explore an asteroid system named 65803 Didymos.""According to the space agency, Didymos measures 780 meters across.""Accompanying the asteroid system, is its orbiting moonlet 'Didymoon' which is only 160 meters in width.""If the mission is successful, this moonlet will be the smallest asteroid ever visited by any spacecraft.""Prior to all of this, NASA will conduct its first planetary defense mission."  "According to the space agency, the Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART, will crash into the surface of Didymoon in 2022. "NASA is aiming to change the speed and direction of the asteroid system with this test.""According to an ESA news release, the Hera spacecraft will research the crater formed by the DART experiment in 2026.""It collect data pertaining to the shape and dimensions of the DART crater, as well as surface samples." "Hera will also use thermal imaging technology to examine the asteroid's structure." SOURCES: NASA, ESA https://www.nasa.gov/planetarydefense/darthttp://dart.jhuapl.edu/News-and-Resources/18-05389_DART_NASA-Compliant_FS-v9.pdfhttp://www.esa.int/Our_Activities/Space_Engineering_Technology/Hera/ESA_plans_mission_to_smallest_asteroid_ever_visitedhttps://www.esa.int/Our_Activities/Space_Engineering_Technology/Hera/Target_asteroid***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 06:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/21/3784865/3784865_5D259760CAD54F48A1301A9FDB83BE98_190221_3784865_ESA_unveils_plans_to_explore_binary_asteroid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, esa, nasa, hera mission, asteroid, binary asteroid system, didymoon, planetary defense system, NASA, DART, hera mission esa,  Didymos asteroid, Didymoon, asteroid defense, asteroid system, didymos, asteroid impact mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3784801</guid>
      <title>Chinese social credit system bans millions from taking trains, flying</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMillions of Chinese citizens have now been banned from traveling by air or train as the government continues to expand its social credit system, the South China Morning Post reports.China is rolling out a social credit system that assigns "personal trustworthiness points" to its citizens as a way to monitoring the public and businesses.Credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, character traits, behavior, preferences and interpersonal relationships are all considered when assigning a credit score, according to Reuters.Trustworthy individuals are to be provided with more access to society, while individuals who are blacklisted will be severely restricted, Reuters reports.An official blacklist released by China's National Enterprise Credit Information Publicity System has also banned more than 3.59 million Chinese businesses in 2018 from accessing financial markets, issuing corporate bonds or taking part in land auctions.About 17.46 million people were not allowed to purchase airline tickets, while 5.47 million weren't allowed to buy tickets for high-speed trains, according to the blacklist.The South China Morning Post cites the blacklist as saying individuals and business were punished for behaviors such as failing to repay loans, false or misleading advertising, or defrauding customers.China plans to fully implement its social credit system by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Subway riders with social credit score2. Citizens given an individual score based on several factors3. Trustworthy individuals and blacklisted individuals 4. China, airplane and high-speed train5. Chinese flag, financial market icon, corporate bond icon and land auction icon6. Airplane with airline ticket, high speed train with tickets7. Behaviors individuals and companies were punished forVOICEOVER (in English): "China is rolling out a social credit system that assigns 'personal trustworthiness points' to its citizens as a way to monitoring the public and businesses.""According to Reuters, credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, character traits, behavior, preferences and interpersonal relationships are all considered when assigning a credit score.""Trustworthy individuals are to be provided with more access to society, while individuals who are blacklisted will be severely restricted.""The South China Morning Post reports millions of Chinese citizens have now been banned from traveling by air or train as the government continues to expand its social credit system.""An official blacklist released by China's National Enterprise Credit Information Publicity System has also banned more than 3.59 million Chinese businesses in 2018 from accessing financial markets, issuing corporate bonds or taking part in land auctions.""According to the report, about 17.46 million people were not allowed to purchase airline tickets, while 5.47 million weren't allowed to buy tickets for high-speed trains.""The South China Morning Post cites the report as saying individuals and business were punished for behaviors such as failing to repay loans, false or misleading advertising, or defrauding customers."SOURCES: The South China Morning Post, Xinhua, Reuters, National Enterprise Credit Information Publicity System, https://www.scmp.com/economy/china-economy/article/2186606/chinas-social-credit-system-shows-its-teeth-banning-millionshttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-11/21/c_137622527.htmhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-society-points/beijing-pioneering-citizens-points-system-critics-brand-orwellian-idUSKCN1NP0FThttp://www.gsxt.gov.cn/%7B3E5A916C593C60E1B5483B5E0A4FDCE914FA6E3A5FB1F40BC0A5FEA5C8A5C0374337433743A59A094966-1550647243824%7D***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 04:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/21/3784801/3784801_068A266F995D4126913B26472A9B209C_190221_3784801_Chinese_social_credit_system_bans_millions_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, social credit system, China Social Credit System, china surveillance system, china surveillance, chinese social credit system, surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3785716</guid>
      <title>Futuristic vertical farm would grow food in the middle of the city</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrench design company Studio NAB has come up with the idea of creating a large vertical farm called the Superfarm to promote sustainable living.The Superfarm would be six stories tall, with its topmost layer containing solar panels and wind turbines to produce renewable energy, according to its website.Level 2 would feature an open terrace with plants such as ginseng, spirulina and aloe vera cultures.Levels 3 and 4 would be dedicated to insect breeding and algae cultures.The fifth floor would farm aquatic creatures such as trout and tilapia and young plant cultures, while the sixth story would contain a greenhouse that would include plants such as acai berries and goji berries.Each floor would have a specific purpose and would work in unison with other floors to create a viable ecosystem.The goal of the Superfarm is to "recreate an ecosystem in an urban environment,"according to Studio NAB's website.This would allow customers to connect directly with product makers and have easier access to farms.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Superfarm2. The length of the Superfarm, solar panels and wind turbines3. Level 2,3 and 4 of the Superfarm4. Level 5 and 6 of the SuperfarmVOICEOVER (in English): "French design company Studio NAB has come up with the idea of creating a large vertical farm called the Superfarm to promote sustainable living.""According to its website, the Superfarm would be six stories tall, with its topmost layer containing solar panels and wind turbines to produce renewable energy.""Level 2 would feature an open terrace with plants such as ginseng, spirulina and aloe vera cultures.""Levels 3 and 4 would be dedicated to insect breeding and algae cultures.""The fifth floor would farm aquatic creatures such as trout and tilapia and young plant cultures,""while the sixth story would contain a greenhouse that would include plants such as acai berries and goji berries.""Each floor would have a specific purpose and would work in unison with other floors to create a viable ecosystem."SOURCES: Inhabitat, Studio NAB, Building Design Construction, DesignBoom https://inhabitat.com/superfarm-design-envisions-an-urban-vertical-farm-that-is-energy-self-sufficient/?variation=chttps://www.studionab.fr/https://www.studionab.fr/superfarmhttps://www.bdcnetwork.com/studio-nab%E2%80%99s-superfarm-project-creates-entire-ecosystem-urban-environmenthttps://www.designboom.com/architecture/studio-nab-superfarm-urban-vertical-farm-concept-02-13-2019/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 10:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/22/3785716/3785716_F786011CA08C4D54B9C87615CCB216C4_190222_3785716_Futuristic_vertical_farm_would_grow_food_in_the__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, superfarm, urban vertical farming,  studio NAB france, vertical farm, futuristic vertical farming, self sufficient vertical farm, superfarm urban vertical farm, ecosystem, sustainable ecosystem]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3785664</guid>
      <title>China using DNA to track Muslim Uighurs in Xinjiang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese authorities in Xinjiang are collecting DNA samples along with other biometric data from all residents in the region between the ages of 12 and 65, according to Human Rights Watch. According to the New York Times, China is trying to force the country's predominantly Muslim Uighurs to become more subservient to the party. The government has detained up to a million people in "re-education" camps. According to Fortune, part of the surveillance effort is to collect biometric data such as iris scans, fingerprints, voice scans, and DNA.  According to the New York Times, human right groups and Uighur activists say a comprehensive DNA database could be used to chase down Uighurs who resist conforming to the campaign. To improve their DNA tracking and testing capabilities, China's police purchased genetic sequencing equipment from Massachusetts biotechnology firm Thermo Fisher Scientific. Chinese authorities also used genetic material from people around the world that was provided by prominent Yale University geneticist, Kenneth Kidd, to compare to Uighur DNA. According to the New York Times, on Wednesday, Thermo Fisher said it would no longer sell its equipment in Xinjiang. According to Dr. Kidd, he was unaware how his material and expertise were being used. He said he thought Chinese scientists were acting within scientific norms that require informed consent by DNA donors. According to China's official news agency Xinhua nearly 36 million people in Xinjiang took part in the program called "Physicals for All" from 2016 to 2017.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Uighurs in Xinjiang having DNA collected2. Biometric data collected by CCP3. China used Thermo Fisher Scientific machine and Yale geneticist data4. Thermo Fisher Scientific to stop selling machine in Xinjiang, Yale geneticist unaware how his material was being usedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Human Rights Watch, Chinese authorities in Xinjiang are collecting DNA samples along with other biometric data from all residents in the region between the ages of 12 and 65." "According to the New York Times, part of the surveillance effort is to collect biometric data such as iris scans, fingerprints, voice scans, and DNA."  "To improve their DNA tracking and testing capabilities, China's police purchased genetic sequencing equipment from Massachusetts biotechnology firm Thermo Fisher Scientific." "Chinese authorities also used genetic material from people around the world that was provided by prominent Yale University geneticist, Kenneth Kidd, to compare to Uighur DNA." "According to the New York Times, on Wednesday, Thermo Fisher said it would no longer sell its equipment in Xinjiang. "According to Dr. Kidd, he was unaware how his material and expertise were being used. He said he thought Chinese scientists were acting within scientific norms that require informed consent by DNA donors." SOURCES: New York Times, Wall Street Journal, Fortune, Human Rights Watchhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/21/business/china-xinjiang-uighur-dna-thermo-fisher.htmlhttps://www.wsj.com/articles/thermo-fisher-to-stop-sales-of-genetic-sequencers-to-chinas-xinjiang-region-11550694620http://fortune.com/2019/02/21/thermo-fisher-xinjiang-china-uighurs/https://www.hrw.org/news/2017/12/13/china-minority-region-collects-dna-millions***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/22/3785664/3785664_3DC65A38193747FD9E6332A11EA56A28_190222_3785664_China_using_DNA_to_track_Muslim_Uighurs_in_Xinji_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, China, China Muslims, China Uighur, China collecting DNA, China collecting DNA Xinjiang, Muslim Uighurs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3785478</guid>
      <title>Earth atmosphere reaches twice the distance of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from ESA and NASA show the real size of Earth's geocorona.New observations from a study by the European Space Agency and NASA show that Earth's geocorona, an atmospheric layer made of hydrogen atoms, reaches up to 630,000 kilometers or 391,000 miles away. That is the equivalent of 50 times the Earth's diameter and double the distance to the Moon.According to the paper published in AGU's Journal of Geophysical Research, the team made these observations using an instrument mounted on a satellite called the Solar and Heliospheric Observatory, or SOHO.The SOHO orbits some 1.5 million kilometers from Earth towards the Sun and mainly studies Earth's interactions with the Sun. It is equipped with a remote tool called Solar Wind Anisotropies, or SWAN. The SWAN is capable of detecting hydrogen signatures in the outer layer of Earth's atmosphere by using an absorption cell.These new findings could help researchers look for watery planets with similar atmospheres outside of our solar system.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Size of Earth's geocorona2. NASA/ESA['s Solar and Heliospheric Observatory3. SOHO orbiting the sun4. SOHO detecting hydrogen signatures from EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "New observations from a study by the European Space Agency and NASA show that Earth's geocorona, an atmospheric layer made of hydrogen atoms, reaches up to 630,000 kilometers or 391,000 miles away." "That is the equivalent of 50 times the Earth's diameter and double the distance to the Moon.""According to the paper published in AGU's Journal of Geophysical Research, the team made these observations using an instrument mounted on a satellite called the Solar and Heliospheric Observatory, or SOHO.""The SOHO orbits some 1.5 million kilometers from Earth towards the Sun and mainly studies Earth's interactions with the Sun." "It is equipped with a remote tool called Solar Wind Anisotropies, or SWAN. The SWAN is capable of detecting hydrogen signatures in the outer layer of Earth's atmosphere by using an absorption cell."SOURCES: European Space Agency, AGUhttp://sci.esa.int/soho/61130-earth-at1 moon viewmosphere-stretches-out-to-the-moon-and-beyond/https://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1029/2018JA026136***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 05:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/22/3785478/3785478_2DF22EE93E624F8B9CA217FC6ACB9D09_190222_3785478_Earth_atmosphere_reaches_twice_the_distance_of_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, earth, nasa, esa, geocorona, SOHO, SWAN, European space agency, Solar Wind Anisotropies, solar and Heliospheric Observatory, atmosphere]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3785967</guid>
      <title>Russia and U.S. fight to deliver aid to Venezuela</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. and Russia rush to deliver aid to Venezuela in an attempt to further their political agendas.Over the past weeks, U.S. trucks carrying aid have arrived at the Colombia-Venezuela border at the request of Juan Guaido, who has been recognized by the U.S. and Canada among others as interim President of Venezuela.According to NPR, the aid has since been rejected by Maduro's government who has blocked the main border bridge with trucks. Maduro claims the aid is an attempt by the U.S. to intervene in local politics.AP reports that last Wednesday Russian shipments of aid had arrived in Venezuela under the protection of the World Health Organization. According to El Periodico, Nicolas Maduro confirmed the delivery of 300 tons of medical aid from Russia.Puerto Rico and Brazil have announced that they too will be sending supplies to Venezuela with Puerto Rico promising 250 tons of aid. None have addressed how they will deliver the supplies.Meanwhile, the U.N. has criticized this stand-off. U.N. spokesman Stephane Dujarric told reporters in New York, "humanitarian action needs to be independent of political, military or other objectives."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. delivers aid to Venezuela 2. U.S. aid gets blocked by Maduro's government3. Maduro's government accepts Russian aid4. Puerto Rico and Brazil join the list of countries trying to send aid to VenezuelaVOICEOVER (in English): "Over the past weeks, U.S. trucks carrying aid have arrived at the Colombia-Venezuela border at the request of Juan Guaido who has been recognized by the U.S. and Canada among others as interim president of Venezuela.""According to NPR, the aid has since been rejected by Maduro's government who has blocked the main border bridge with trucks. Maduro claims this aid is yet another attempt for the U.S. to intervene in local politics.""AP reports that last Wednesday Russian shipments of aid had arrived in Venezuela under the protection of the World Health Organization. According to El Periodico, Nicolas Maduro confirmed the delivery of 300 tons of medical aid from Russia.""Puerto Rico and Brazil have announced that they too will be sending supplies to Venezuela with Puerto Rico promising 250 tons of aid. None have addressed how they will deliver the supplies."SOURCES: ENCOVI, NPR, El Periodico, Associated Presshttps://www.ucab.edu.ve/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/02/ENCOVI-2017-presentaci%C3%B3n-para-difundir-.pdfhttps://www.npr.org/2019/02/16/695154567/u-s-masses-aid-along-venezuelan-border-as-some-humanitarian-groups-warn-of-riskshttps://www.elperiodico.com/es/internacional/20190219/ayuda-humanitaria-rusia-llega-venezuela-7311550https://www.apnews.com/2e1ace0158ac40189acd90c36962cbe7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/23/3785967/3785967_2487E54910454685896FBC91679DB66F_190223_3785967_Russia_and_U_S__fight_to_deliver_aid_to_Venezuel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  venezuela, venezuela president, venezuela opposition, interim president, nicolas maduro, juan guaido, venezuela oil, venezuela oil, oil revenue, us venezuela sanctions, venezuela sanctions, sanctions, venezuela economy, juan guaido, trump, donald trump, maduro, nicolas maduro, guaido, poverty, venezuela aid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3787109</guid>
      <title>Airline seats equipped with cameras pointed at passengers sparks security concerns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSome planes operated by American Airlines, United Airlines and Singapore Airlines have cameras preinstalled in seat-back entertainment systems. According to Buzzfeed News, a passenger on a Singapore flight posted a photo of his seat-back display with the camera on Feb. 17.  According to the Associated Press, American, United and Singapore all said last Friday that they have never activated the cameras and have no plans to use them. According to an American Airlines spokesman, entertainment system companies have been installing the cameras to offer future options like seat-to-seat conferencing.  American's seat-back entertainment systems are manufactured by Panasonic, while Singapore uses Panasonic and Thales, according to airline representatives. American Airlines spokesman Ross Feinstein said cameras are in premium economy seats on 82 Boeing 777 and Airbus A330-200 planes. Singapore spokesman James Boyd said cameras are on 84 Airbus A350s, Airbus A380s and Boeing 777s and 787s. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Some American Airlines, United Airlines and Singapore Airlines have cameras in seat-back entertainment systems2. Singapore Airlines passenger taking picture of seat-back camera, airlines saying cameras have not and will not be activated3. Cameras were installed for future options like seat-to-seat conferencing4. Passengers sitting in seats with cameras installedVOICEOVER (in English): "Some planes operated by American Airlines, United Airlines and Singapore Airlines have cameras preinstalled in seat-back entertainment systems." "According to Buzzfeed News, a passenger on a Singapore flight posted a photo of his seat-back display with the camera on Feb. 17."  "According to the Associated Press, American, United and Singapore all said last Friday that they have never activated the cameras and have no plans to use them." "According to an American Airlines spokesman, entertainment system companies have been installing the cameras to offer future options like seat-to-seat conferencing."  "American Airlines spokesman Ross Feinstein said cameras are in premium economy seats on 82 Boeing 777 and Airbus A330-200 planes." "Singapore spokesman James Boyd said cameras are on 84 Airbus A350s, Airbus A380s and Boeing 777s and 787s." SOURCES: Buzzfeed News, The Verge, Associated Presshttps://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/nicolenguyen/american-airlines-planes-entertainment-system-camerashttps://www.theverge.com/2019/2/22/18235979/camera-airplane-inflight-entertainment-american-singapore-airlines-privacyhttps://www.marketwatch.com/story/airline-seats-now-equipped-with-cameras-aimed-at-passengers-2019-02-23***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/25/3787109/3787109_388E7414EAEB4E64BCA1D34A56B5BAA7_190225_3787109_Airline_seats_equipped_with_cameras_pointed_at_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, airline seat cameras, seat-back entertainment cameras, American Airlines, United Airlines, Singapore Airlines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3786902</guid>
      <title>Gene-editing may have impacted brains of Chinese twins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from UCLA has shown that removing the gene CCR5, could potentially be linked to enhancing one's ability to learn and form memories.Last year, in November, a Chinese scientist allegedly used CRISPR, a gene-editing tool, to create the world's first gene-edited babies. He Jiankui said he altered the babies' DNA to remove a gene called CCR5, according to a Associated Press report from the time. This would make the twin baby girls immune to HIV. New research, published in the journal Cell, people who lack CCR5 were found to have better cognition and were also found to recover faster from strokes. The researchers tested their theory on mice. They altered the DNA of the mice to remove CCR5. This was found to enhance animals' intelligence.According to MIT Technology Review, the scientists connected their findings to the Chinese twins. Researcher Alconi J.Silva explained the gene-modification performed on them "likely" affected their brains. "The simplest interpretation is that those mutations will probably have an impact on cognitive function in the twins," Silva explained, according to MIT Technology Review.Follow up studies about CCR5 are already taking place at UCLA, with participants being given Maraviroc, an HIV treatment , to see if it improves cognition.  Silva said that altering CCR5 was found to have big effects. Silva added that we "are not ready" for the consequences we could potentially face for mutating DNA.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Altering the DNA with CRISPR, HIV virus2. DNA strand and twin baby girls3. DNA strand, brain4. Mouse, DNA strand being edited5. A male avatar, cognition icon and brain flashing red6. Another male avatar taking MaravirocVOICEOVER (in English): "Last year, in November, a Chinese scientist allegedly used CRISPR, a gene-editing tool, to create the world's first gene-edited babies.""According to an Associated Press report from the time, He Jiankui, said he altered the babies' DNA to remove a gene called CCR5." ""This would make the twin baby girls immune to HIV." "New research from UCLA has shown that removing the gene CCR5, could potentially be linked to enhancing one's ability to learn and form memories.""The researchers tested their theory on mice." "They altered the DNA of the mice to remove CCR5. This was found to enhance the animals' intelligence.""According to a new study published in the journal Cell, people who lack CCR5 were found to have better cognition...""...and were also found to recover faster from strokes.""Follow up studies about CCR5 are already taking place at UCLA, with participants being given Maraviroc, an HIV treatment, to see if it improves cognition."SOURCES: The Associated Press, Cell, MIT Technology Review, https://www.apnews.com/4997bb7aa36c45449b488e19ac83e86dhttps://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(19)30107-2https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612997/the-crispr-twins-had-their-brains-altered/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 07:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/25/3786902/3786902_D9BE8BDB60CB499385F8801B1F1F2C66_190225_3786902_Gene_editing_may_have_impacted_brains_of_Chinese_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, crispr babies, crispr china, crispr gene editing, gene edited babies china, CRISPR, gene-editing, editing DNA, CRISPR-cas9, altering human DNA, china crispr human, crispr twins china, gene edited twins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3787706</guid>
      <title>Lunar Library containing record of human civilization sent to the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA small disc containing the records of human civilization is being sent to the moon in order to preserve it for billions of years.CNET reports that when the Beresheet lunar lander was launched on SpaceX's Falcon 9 rocket Thursday, it was carrying a disc encoded with a 30-million-page archive of human history and civilization, dubbed the Lunar Library.Created by the Arch Mission Foundation, the Lunar Library is a DVD-sized archive composed of 25 nickel film discs that are each only 40 microns thick.According to the foundation, the first four layers contain over 60,000 analog images of documents, photos, books, and illustrations that can be seen with a low-powered microscope. Letters on these layers are the size of a bacillus bacterium.The 21 digital layers beneath are encoded with 200 GB of information, as well as images, audio, video, and software.""This includes a complete copy of the English-language Wikipedia and the PanLex datasets, which is a linguistic key to 5,000 languages.The AMF had previously placed a test archive on Elon Musk's Tesla Roadster that was launched to Mars orbit aboard a Falcon Heavy rocket.According to CNET, there's also a solid-state copy of Wikipedia on a cubesat from SpaceChain that's currently in low-Earth orbit.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Beresheet lunar lander carrying Lunar Library 2. Lunar Library disc composed of 25 nickel film discs3. Four analog layers4. Twenty-one digital layersVOICEOVER (in English): "CNET reports that when the Beresheet lunar lander was launched on SpaceX's Falcon 9 rocket Thursday, it was carrying a disc encoded with a 30-million-page archive of human history and civilization, dubbed the Lunar Library.""Created by the Arch Mission Foundation, the Lunar Library is a DVD-sized archive composed of 25 nickel film discs that are each only 40 microns thick.""According to the foundation, the first four layers contain over 60,000 analog images of documents, photos, books, and illustrations that can be seen with a low-powered microscope. Letters on these layers are the size of a bacillus bacterium.""The 21 digital layers beneath are encoded with 200 GB of information, images, audio, video and software.""This includes a complete copy of the English-language Wikipedia and the PanLex datasets, which is a linguistic key to 5,000 languages."SOURCES: Arch Mission Foundation, CNEThttps://www.archmission.org/spaceilhttps://www.dropbox.com/s/uuhj4a4u2djldub/Overview%20of%20the%20Lunar%20Library.pdf?dl=0https://www.cnet.com/news/backup-of-humanity-on-its-way-to-the-moon-aboard-israeli-lander/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 12:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/26/3787706/3787706_B970B79D7A234149B338744B2E8EE20A_190226_3787706_Lunar_Library_containing_record_of_human_civiliz_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, lunar library, record of human civilization, arch mission foundation, AMF, Beresheet, lunar lander, Falcon 9 rocket, SpaceX, Falcon Heavy, Tesla Roadster]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3787630</guid>
      <title>Russian company develops 'suicide drones'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANKalashnikov, the company behind the AK-47, has created a suicide drone.The drone, called KYB-UAV, is 4-feet wide, according to Intelligent Aerospace. Citing a Russian language Kalashnikov news release, the Washington Post reports that the device can fly at a speed of 130 kilometers per hour for 30 minutes.The drone can also carry a payload of explosives weighing up to 3 kg of while flying. Intelligent Aerospace reports that the device can be sent to its target via payload targeting image or by manually inputting the coordinates.The National Interest also quotes a Kalashnikov news release as saying that the drone, "is designed to destroy remote ground targets."The Russian-made drone would be low-priced and widely available, The Washington Post reports.The drone was shown last week at the 2019 International Defence Exhibition and Conference in Abu Dhabi.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Width of the drone2. The drone flying in the sky3. The drone carrying an explosive4. The drone releasing the explosiveVOICEOVER (in English): "The drone, called KYB-UAV, is 4-feet wide according to Intelligent Aerospace.""Citing a Russian language Kalashnikov news release, the Washington Post reports that the device can fly at a speed of 130 kilometers per hour for 30 minutes.""The drone can also carry a payload of explosives weighing up to 3 kg while flying.""Intelligent Aerospace reports that the device can be sent to its target via payload targeting image or by manually inputting the coordinates.""The National Interest also quotes a Kalashnikov news release as saying that the drone, quote "is designed to destroy remote ground targets". End quote."SOURCES: The Washington Post, Kalashnikov's News Statement, National Interest website, https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2019/02/23/kalashnikov-assault-rifle-changed-world-now-theres-kalashnikov-kamikaze-drone/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.81b006dd6749https://kalashnikovgroup.ru/press-center/news/kontsern_-kalashnikov-_razrabotal_vysokotochnyy_udarnyy_bespilotnyy_kompleks_-kub-blahttps://nationalinterest.org/blog/buzz/company-makes-ak-47-now-building-suicide-drones-44937***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 10:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/26/3787630/3787630_4DD706782E9545B9A948A38B8EEC0EB9_190226_3787630_Russian_company_develops__suicide_drones__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, russia, kalashnikov drone, drone, military drone, kalashnikov concern, intelligent weapons, suicide drones, russian suicide drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3787620</guid>
      <title>Climate change could cause low level clouds over oceans to disappear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIf the levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere continue to rise, according to a new study, stratocumulus clouds may disappear and Earth's temperatures to climb sharply. According to the study, stratocumulus clouds cover 20 percent of tropical oceans and critically affect Earth's energy balance by reflecting 30-60 percent of shortwave radiation back into space. Researchers from the California Institute of Technology ran detailed simulations of cloud formation and the effects solar radiation had on them. Their results were published in the journal Nature. Scientists modeled a small patch of sky using a supercomputer to run simulations, and found that if carbon dioxide levels reach about 1,200 parts per million, or ppm, in the atmosphere, stratocumulus clouds break up.Currently, atmospheric carbon dioxide is around 410 ppm, however if the current trend of releasing more CO2 into the atmosphere continues at this pace, the Earth could reach 1,200 ppm in 100 to 150 years.  The resulting loss of stratocumulus clouds could lead to an increase in temperature of 14 degrees Fahrenheit (8 degrees Celsius).  More research will need to be carried out as the data from the study has not yet been replicated. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Stratocumulus clouds disappearing over oceans as temperatures rise2. Stratocumulus clouds covering oceans and reflecting solar radiation3. Study simulation4. If CO2 levels continue to rise, startocumulus clouds could be gone in 100 to 150 years, increasing temperaturesVOICEOVER (in English): "If the levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere continue to rise, according to a new study, stratocumulus clouds may disappear and Earth's temperatures to climb sharply." "According to the study published in the journal Nature, stratocumulus clouds cover 20 percent of tropical oceans and critically affect Earth's energy balance by reflecting 30-60 percent of shortwave radiation back into space." "Researchers from the California Institute of Technology ran detailed simulations of cloud formation and the effects solar radiation had on them." "Scientists modeled a small patch of sky using a supercomputer to run simulations, and found that if carbon dioxide levels reach about 1,200 parts per million, or ppm, in the atmosphere, stratocumulus clouds break up.""Currently, atmospheric carbon dioxide is around 410 ppm, however if the current trend of releasing more CO2 into the atmosphere continues at this pace, the Earth could reach 1,200 ppm in 100 to 150 years."  "The resulting loss of stratocumulus clouds could lead to an increase in temperature of 14 degrees Fahrenheit."  SOURCES: USA Today, Techcrunch, Naturehttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/02/25/global-warming-could-zap-earths-clouds-bake-us-even-more/2980788002/https://techcrunch.com/2019/02/25/climate-change-kills-off-clouds-over-the-ocean-in-new-simulation/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41561-019-0310-1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 10:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/26/3787620/3787620_9C027FCC0E6146C998FC0BA6F7EE12DD_190226_3787620_Climate_change_could_cause_low_level_clouds_over_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, climate change, global warming, CO2 levels, carbon dioxide, climate change cloud cover]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3787526</guid>
      <title>New luxury apartment high rise being built in Melbourne</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new 100-floor luxury high rise complex is being built in Melbourne.  The new residential tower is called 'Australia 108' and once it's complete will be 319 meters tall and feature a total of 1,105 apartments.According to Design Build Network, the core is made of concrete and its frame is designed with mega-column and mega-frames. Roughly 2,500 tons of glass will be used in the building's facade.The luxurious residential building will also have a special amenity zone on the 70th and 71st floors called 'The Starburst' which will include two infinity pools, a gym, and private dining rooms.The first stage of the construction was completed in May 2018. It included the construction of the first 40 levels and 491 apartments. The final stage will be finished by 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Australia 108 height and number of apartments it will feature2. Material used in the Australia 1083. Special luxury zone featured in the Australia 1084. Construction stagesVOICEOVER (in English): "A residential tower called 'Australia 108' is being built in Melbourne, Australia. Once it is finalized it will measure 319 meters and feature a total of 1,105 apartments.""According to Design Build Network, the core is made of concrete and its frame is designed with mega-column and mega-frames. Roughly 2,500 tons of glass will be used in the building's facade.""The luxurious residential building will also have a special amenity zone on the 70th and 71st floors called 'The Starburst' which will include two infinity pools, a gym and private dining rooms.""The first stage of the construction was completed in May 2018. It included the construction of the first 40 levels and 491 apartments. The final stage will be finished by 2020."SOURCES: Design Build Network, Domainhttps://www.designbuild-network.com/projects/australia-108-residential-tower/https://www.domain.com.au/news/australia-108-penthouse-sale-smashes-national-price-record-20150408-1mg23h/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 08:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/26/3787526/3787526_4ED94B2C9075457EB17968F33810C53F_190226_3787526_New_luxury_apartment_high_rise_being_built_in_Me_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, melbourne, australia, building, infrastructure, luxury housing, luxury, Australia 108]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3787404</guid>
      <title>Kim Jong Un sets off on long train trip to Vietnam for Trump summit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korean leader Kim Jong Un set off on a train trip to Vietnam on Saturday to attend a summit with the U.S.According to the BBC, Kim Jong Un and Donald Trump will meet in Hanoi for the second US-North Korea summit, where they are expected to continue denuclearization talks.Russia's TASS news agency, citing a North Korean diplomatic source, said Kim left Pyongyang in an armored train at 5 p.m. on February 23.Reuters reports that two witnesses in Dandong spotted the train crossing from North Korea into China via the Yalu river bridge at around 9:30 p.m.Kim's 21-car train bears a striking resemblance to the armored train his late father Kim Jong Il used to visit allies in China and Russia. According to the Chosun Ilbo, the locomotive contains a conference room, an audience chamber, and bedrooms, and is fitted with satellite phone connections and a flat screen TV.While a plane ride would take only a few hours, the New York Times reports that Kim's journey by rail can take as long as two days.The train is expected to stop at the Vietnamese border station of Dong Dang, where the North Korean leader will disembark and travel the remaining 170 kilometers to Hanoi by car.The summit is scheduled for Wednesday and Thursday, with three sources confirming to Reuters that the preferred location is the Government Guesthouse in central Hanoi.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Donald Trump, Kim Jong Un meeting in Hanoi to discuss denuclearization2. Kim Jong Un's armored train leaving Pyongyang, crossing into China3. 21-car train may be same one used by Kim Jong Il to visit Russia, China4. Facilities, equipment inside the train5. Train route from Pyongyang to Dong Dang, Vietnam6. Kim Jong Un disembarks at Dong Dang station, goes to Hanoi by carVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, Kim Jong Un and Donald Trump will meet in Hanoi for the second US-North Korea summit, where they are expected to continue denuclearization talks.""Russia's TASS news agency, citing a North Korean diplomatic source, said Kim left Pyongyang in an armored train at 5 p.m. on February 23.""Reuters reports that two witnesses in Dandong spotted the train crossing from North Korea into China via the Yalu river bridge at around 9:30 p.m.""Kim's 21-car train bears a striking resemblance to the armored train his late father Kim Jong Il used to visit allies in China and Russia.""According to the Chosun Ilbo, the locomotive contains a conference room, an audience chamber and bedrooms, and is outfitted with satellite phone connections and a flat screen TV.""While a plane ride only takes a few hours, the New York Times reports that Kim's journey by rail can take as long as two days.""The train is expected to stop at the Vietnamese border station of Dong Dang, where the North Korean leader will disembark and go the remaining 170 kilometers to Hanoi by car."SOURCES: Reuters, New York Times, BBC, Chosun Ilbohttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa/north-koreas-kim-sets-off-by-train-to-vietnam-for-summit-with-trump-report-idUSKCN1QC053https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/24/world/asia/north-korea-kim-jong-un-china-train.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-47328334http://english.chosun.com/site/data/html_dir/2009/11/09/2009110900406.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 05:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/26/3787404/3787404_6B615E53B5264ACABB4619A0DA42EDE4_190226_3787404_Kim_Jong_Un_sets_off_on_long_train_trip_to_Vietn_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump, Donald Trump, Kim Jong Un, Kim Trump summit, Trump Kim summit, US North Korea summit, US North Korea talks, denuclearization, denuclearization talks, Vietnam summit, Hanoi summit, North Korea, armored train, train trip]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788257</guid>
      <title>China testing out 'gait-recognition' technology</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese authorities are testing a new system that analyzes people's gait when they walk.  According to the South China Morning Post, Chinese police are testing a new technology called 'gait recognition' that analyzes live videos and stores data of how a person walks.The system was developed by Watrix, a Chinese artificial intelligence start-up. They claim the program can detect someone's walk from 50 meters away regardless of whether they are facing the camera.It does this by creating silhouettes of people in videos and studying their body contour, their arm movement while walking, whether they have a toe-in or a toe-out gait, among other elements. All these components allow them to identify each person's unique 'walking style.' Authorities in the Chinese cities of Beijing, Shanghai, and Chongqing are among the cities that have already tried the product. The newest version of the program is able to analyze live camera feeds of megacities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman is scanned as she is walking2. People walking on street are detected and scanned by Watrix3. Elements that Watrix analyzes from individual's walks4. Cities testing the programsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the South China Morning Post, Chinese police are testing a new technology called 'gait recognition' that analyzes live videos and stores data of how a person walks.""The system was developed by Watrix, a Chinese artificial intelligence start-up." "They claim the program can detect someone's walk from 50 meters away regardless of whether they are facing the camera.""It does this by creating silhouettes of people in videos and studying their body contour, their arm movement while walking, whether they have a toe-in or a toe-out gait, among other elements." "All these components allow them to identify each person's unique 'walking style.'""Authorities in the Chinese cities of Beijing, Shanghai, and Chongqing are among the cities that have already tried the product." "The newest version of the program is able to analyze live camera feeds of megacities."SOURCES: South China Morning Posthttps://www.scmp.com/tech/start-ups/article/2187600/chinese-police-surveillance-gets-boost-ai-start-watrix-technology-can***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 09:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/27/3788257/3788257_BB54D3435B3E4593BC58EF702AAFF2E2_190227_3788257_China_testing_out__gait_recognition__technology_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, surveillance, surveillance state, china surveillance, police state, china surveillance system, total surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788083</guid>
      <title>Iceberg twice the size of New York City will break-off from Antarctica</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA satellite images show two cracks running across the  Antarctic Brunt Ice Shelf which could break off into a 1,700 kilometer-iceberg. Images taken by NASA show a northward expanding crevice, named Chasm 1 by the British Antarctic Survey, stretching across the Antarctic Brunt Ice Shelf and a smaller crevice called Halloween crack, inching closer to the edge of the ice shelf. The two cracks are just 4 kilometers or 2.5 miles from each other. When these two rifts meet, an iceberg twice the size of New York City will break off of the shelf. NASA predicts the resulting mass of the iceberg could cover 1,700 kilometers or 660 square miles. This would make it the largest iceberg to break away from the Brunt Ice Shelf in over a century.According to the Natural Environment Research Council, this phenomenon is called iceberg calving. Calving occurs when large portions of ice break off from glaciers or the margins of ice shelves.Data from the Natural Environment Research Council show that these shifts have forced British researchers working at the Halley Research Station to relocate. There have been six Halley stations built so far.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of two cracks on the Antarctic Brunt Ice Shelf  2. Estimated size of the iceberg that will break off from the Antarctic Brunt Ice Shelf 3. Iceberg calving4. Location of Halley Research Station on the Antarctic Brunt Ice Shelf  VOICEOVER (in English): "Images taken by NASA show a northward expanding crevice, named Chasm 1 by the British Antarctic Survey, stretching across the Antarctic Brunt Ice Shelf and a smaller crevice called Halloween crack, inching closer to the edge of the ice shelf." "The two cracks are just 4 kilometers or 2.5 miles from each other." "When these two rifts meet, an iceberg twice the size of New York City will break off of the shelf.""NASA predicts the resulting mass of the iceberg could cover 1,700 kilometers or 660 square miles.""This would make it the largest iceberg to break away from the Brunt Ice Shelf in over a century.""According to the Natural Environment Research Council, this phenomenon is called iceberg calving. "Calving occurs when large portions of ice break off from glaciers or the margins of ice shelves.""Data from the Natural Environment Research Council show that these shifts have forced British researchers working at the Halley Research Station to relocate." "There have been six Halley stations built so far."SOURCES: NASA, British Antarctic Surveyhttps://earthobservatory.nasa.gov/images/144563/countdown-to-calving-at-brunt-ice-shelf?utm_source=TWITTER&utm_medium=NASA&utm_campaign=NASASocial&linkId=63995852https://www.bas.ac.uk/about/about-bas/our-history/british-research-stations-and-refuges/halley-z/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 06:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/27/3788083/3788083_1FC1B569F19C4895A9C9006534F6934E_190227_3788083_Iceberg_twice_the_size_of_New_York_City_will_bre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, iceberg, Antarctica, calving, Antarctic Brunt Ice Shelf, Chasm 1, Halloween crack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788878</guid>
      <title>India, Pakistan claim to down each other's jets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIndia and Pakistan have both said they shot down each other's fighter jets on Wednesday. Reuters reports both countries have ordered airstrikes over the last two days, the first time in history the two nations have done so, while ground forces have exchanged fire in more than a dozen locations. According to Reuters, tensions rose on Tuesday when India launched an airstrike in Pakistan territory on what it said was a militant training base. Reuters reports that a senior Indian government source said 300 militants were killed in the strike, while Pakistan says no one died. According to CNN, Pakistan says its air force shot down two Indian fighter jets in the disputed border region of Kashmir.India confirmed the loss of one plane and said it shot down a Pakistani jet as it responded to the incident. The Pakistan government's official Twitter account posted a video of the man it claimed was an Indian pilot who had been shot down. According to CNN, India and Pakistan both control parts of Kashmir, but each claims the region in full. Countries from around the world have called on both nuclear-armed nations to show restraint.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. India and Pakistan both claim to have downed each other's fighter jets2. Both countries have ordered airstrikes and artillery strikes3. India airstrike on training base in Pakistan territory4. Pakistan claims to have downed 2 Indian jets, while India claims to have downed 1 Pakistan jetVOICEOVER (in English): "India and Pakistan have both said they shot down each other's fighter jets on Wednesday." "Reuters reports both countries have ordered airstrikes over the last two days, the first time in history the two nations have done so, while ground forces have exchanged fire in more than a dozen locations." "According to Reuters, tensions rose on Tuesday when India launched an airstrike in Pakistan territory on what it said was a militant training base." "Reuters reports that a senior Indian government source said 300 militants were killed in the strike, while Pakistan says no one died." "According to CNN, Pakistan says its air force shot down two Indian fighter jets in the disputed border region of Kashmir.""India confirmed the loss of one plane and said it shot down a Pakistani jet as it responded to the incident." SOURCES: Reuters, CNN https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir-idUSKCN1QG0IRhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/02/27/india/india-pakistan-strikes-escalation-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/28/3788878/3788878_0A8E3067061A463EA1D7AD3C1664B585_190228_3788878_India__Pakistan_claim_to_down_each_other_s_jets_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, India, Pakistan, Kashmir, India Pakistan airstrikes, India Pakistan tensions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788864</guid>
      <title>Dozens missing  after gold mine collapses in Indonesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least 43 people are trapped inside an illegal gold mine in Sulawesi, Indonesia.According to the Indonesian National Disaster Mitigation Agency, a landslide has trapped roughly 43 people inside an illegal gold mine in the Bolaang Mongondow region of North Sulawesi, Indonesia.Local authorities say the landslide happened on Tuesday at  9:00 p.m. local time causing the mine's supportive beams and planks to collapse.According to national disaster agency spokesman Sutopo Purwo Nugroho to Reuters, rescuers have found at least 3 dead bodies and rescued 14 miners.Conditions near the mine remain dangerous forcing local authorities and rescue teams to use simple tools such as spades and ropes to search for survivors.Small scale gold-mining is illegal but local authorities fail to report them and often overlook the practice. Accidents are a common occurrence in these mines due to the lack of regulation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of illegal gold mine2. Landslide causes the goldmine to collapse; beams and planks break3. Rescuers find 4 bodies and rescue 144. Rescuers use simple tools due to unstable conditionsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Indonesian National Disaster Mitigation Agency, a landslide has trapped roughly 43 people inside an illegal gold mine in the Bolaang Mongondow region of North Sulawesi, Indonesia.""Local authorities say the landslide happened on Tuesday at  9:00 p.m. local time causing the mine's supportive beams and planks to collapse.""According to national disaster agency spokesman Sutopo Purwo Nugroho to Reuters, rescuers have found at least 3 dead bodies and rescued 14 miners.""Conditions near the mine remain dangerous forcing local authorities and rescue teams to use simple tools such as spades and ropes to search for survivors."SOURCES: Reuters, South China Morning Posthttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-mine-collapse/indonesia-says-scores-missing-after-illegal-gold-mine-collapses-idUSKCN1QG02Mhttps://www.scmp.com/news/asia/southeast-asia/article/2187844/indonesia-says-t-three-killed-another-60-feared-buried***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/28/3788864/3788864_1D830DB5C63F429AA725CECAB0276B31_190228_3788864_Dozens_missing__after_gold_mine_collapses_in_Ind_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, indonesia, sulawesi, mine collapse, gold mine collapse, landslide, landslide indonesia, landslide, gold mine, illegal mine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788862</guid>
      <title>First CRISPR human trial approved outside of China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe FDA has given approval to two pharmaceutical companies to begin a human gene-editing trial.A joint clinical trial led by CRISPR Therapeutics and Vertex will use gene editing to target sickle cell disease and beta-thalassemia. This will be the first confirmed CRISPR gene editing clinical trial to take place outside of China.According to a CRISPR Therapeutics news release, the gene-editing therapy, called CTX001, will be used to modify a patient's stem cells to increase hemoglobin levels in red blood cells.The first trial of gene-editing will be tested on two patients, with each being administered a single dose of CTX001. The patients will be monitored to see when the edited cells start producing mature blood cells, according to the news release.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Editing a DNA strand, sickle cell disease and beta-thalassemia cells2. A Chinese map with an arrow2. A petri dish with stem cells, edited stem cell, red blood cells, vertical bar3. Two male avatar being injected with CTX0014. A blood stream with red blood cellsVOICEOVER (in English): "A joint clinical trial led by CRISPR Therapeutics and Vertex will use gene editing to target sickle cell disease and beta-thalassemia.""This will be the first confirmed CRISPR gene editing clinical trial to take place outside of China.""According to a CRISPR Therapeutics news release, the gene-editing therapy, called CTX001, will be used to modify a patient's stem cells to increase hemoglobin levels in red blood cells.""The first trial of gene-editing will be tested on two patients, with each being administered a single dose of CTX001.""The patients will be monitored to see when the edited cells start producing mature blood cells, according to the news release."SOURCES: New Atlas, CRISPR therapeutics news release, Vantage, Drug Development Technology, Bio Pharma Dive, MedCity News, https://newatlas.com/crispr-trial-underway-vertex-gene-therapy/58643/http://ir.crisprtx.com/news-releases/news-release-details/crispr-therapeutics-and-vertex-announce-progress-clinicalhttp://www.evaluate.com/vantage/articles/news/corporate-strategy/vertex-and-crispr-ante-gene-therapy-chasehttps://www.drugdevelopment-technology.com/news/crispr-vertex-gene-editing-therapy-trial/https://www.biopharmadive.com/news/in-gene-editing-milestone-first-patient-treated-in-vertex-crispr-therapeu/549127/https://medcitynews.com/2019/02/vertex-crispr-therapeutics-infuse-first-patient-in-crispr-cas9-based-gene-therapy-study/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/28/3788862/3788862_EC0A5CC2F6214953B1192B29124AAD2B_190228_3788862_First_CRISPR_human_trial_approved_outside_of_Chi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, crispr gene editing, 
CRISPR, CRISPR technology, gene-editing, DNA, editing DNA, CRISPR-cas9, altering human DNA, crispr human, CRISPR therapy, CRISPR gene editing clinical trial]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788853</guid>
      <title>Central Park Tower to be the tallest residential building in the world</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANReal estate development firm Extell is giving New York City a newly designed tower on West 57th Street.The Guardian reports that a 472 meter high skyscraper called Central Park Tower is being built right next to New York City's Central Park. The tower is designed by architecture firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill.A 472 meter high skyscraper called Central Park Tower is being built right next to New York City's Central Park, according to DesignBoom.The building features luxury apartments with glass windows where residents of the tower can get a "million dollar view" of NYC's Central Park, according to Archinect.An exclusive club called the Central Park Club will also be located within the skyscraper, according to a news release by the architectural firm.The club will include amenities such as an 18 meter swimming pool, a resident's billiard's lounge and a sauna and steam room.If everything goes according to plan, Central Park Tower will be the tallest residential building the world once it has opened.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Central Park Tower, Central Park2. Luxury apartment inside the tower3. Central Park Club4. Amenities included in the towerVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that a 472 meter high skyscraper called Central Park Tower is being built right next to New York City's Central Park. The tower is designed by architecture firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill.""The building features luxury apartments with glass windows where residents of the tower can get a 'million dollar view' of NYC's Central Park, according to Archinect.""An exclusive club called the Central Park Club will also be located within the skyscraper, according to a news release by the architectural firm.""The club will include amenities such as an 18 meter swimming pool, a resident's billiard's lounge and a sauna and steam room."SOURCES: Central Park Tower, Design Boom, Archinect News, The Guardian, https://centralparktower.com/https://www.designboom.com/architecture/central-park-tower-worlds-tallest-residential-building-new-york-10-16-2018/https://archinect.com/news/article/150091140/new-renderings-of-central-park-tower-aka-nordstrom-tower-aka-217-west-57th-streethttps://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/feb/05/super-tall-super-skinny-super-expensive-the-pencil-towers-of-new-yorks-super-rich***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/28/3788853/3788853_D060B8E86C70453795CFF3E3EB351930_190228_3788853_Central_Park_Tower_to_be_the_tallest_residential_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, architecture, central park tower, skyscrapers, US skyscrapers, architecture new york, central park tower construction, central park tower apartments, central park tower 2019, nyc architecture, central park tower nyc, skyscrapers new york, skyscrapers nyc, tallest residential building]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788737</guid>
      <title>New NASA telescope could locate thousands of exoplanets, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Wide Field Infrared Survey Telescope, or WFIRST, is a future flagship mission planned to make new observations about our universe, according to a new study published in The Astrophysical Journal.The two main objectives of the spacecraft is to study dark energy and to locate exoplanets by using gravitational microlensing."The new telescope will have the ability to map out different galaxies 100 times faster than the Hubble Space Telescope, according to a news release by The Ohio State University.WFIRST will also continuously look at 100 million stars at the center of the Milky Way galaxy and analyze the light to determine if there are any exoplanets out there.According to the university's news release, the telescope could discover as many as 1,400 new planets outside our solar system.Ohio State University quotes Matthew Penny, lead author of the study, as saying, the telescope's infrared light allows the device to "see through dust that lies in the plane of the Milky Way in between us and the galactic center..''The WFIRST mission is currently in its planning stages and is planned to launch in the middle of 2020, following NASA's James Webb Space Telescope.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. WFIRST telescope, the universe2. Dark energy, exoplanets, and the telescope3. The telescope scanning the universe4. Stars in the Milky Way galaxy and exoplanetsVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's newest space telescope, called The Wide Field Infrared Survey Telescope or WFIRST, is a future flagship mission planned to make new observations about our universe, according to a new study published in The Astrophysical Journal.""WFIRST has two main objectives: to study dark energy and to locate exoplanets by using gravitational microlensing.""According to a news release by The Ohio State University, the new telescope will have the ability to map out different galaxies 100 times faster than the Hubble Space Telescope.""WFIRST will also continuously look at 100 million stars at the center of the Milky Way galaxy and analyze the light to determine if there are any exoplanets out there.""According to the university's news release, the telescope could discover as many as 1,400 new planets outside our solar system."SOURCES: News Atlas, Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, The Ohio State University, Forbes, NASA,   https://newatlas.com/future-nasa-telescope-wfirst-1400-new-exoplanets/58649/https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/1538-4365/aafb69/metahttps://news.osu.edu/new-nasa-mission-could-find-more-than-1000-planets/https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2019/02/26/the-nasa-space-telescope-the-trump-administration-tried-to-kill-will-find-1400-new-planets/#5119f45e406ehttps://www.nasa.gov/wfirst***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 06:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/02/28/3788737/3788737_7497FB3F475349D7A8C38B2AD00288D0_190228_3788737_New_NASA_telescope_could_locate_thousands_of_exo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, nasa, telescope, exoplanets, wide field infrared survey telescope, dark energy, exoplanet nasa, gravitational microlensing, microlensing exoplanets, microlensing event, milky way, WFIRST telescope]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789619</guid>
      <title>Defunct Russian 1970s Venus probe could crash to Earth this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA failed 1970s Russian Venus probe which has been trapped in Earth orbit could crash back into the planet this year. According to Space.com, the Kosmos 482 Venus probe was launched on March 31, 1972, but due to a rocket malfunction, failed to escape Earth's orbit. A large portion of the failed spacecraft still remains in orbit today as space junk, but according to experts could fall back to Earth this year.According to Don Mitchell, who studies Soviet space history talking to Space.com, when the Cosmos 482 mission failed, a heavy frame of tanks and equipment were jettisoned from the probe and burned up in Earth's atmosphere. However, the Kosmos 482 Venus entry capsule is still adrift, orbiting the Earth every 112 minutes. The lander mass is 1,091 pounds (495 kilograms) and is equipped with significant thermal protection. According to satellite watcher Thomas Dorman talking to Space.com, the failed probe could fall back to Earth late this year or mid next year. According to Space.com, previous estimates had the probe falling between 2023 and 2025.     RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rocket launching carrying Kosmos 482 probe2. Kosmos 482 in space3. Kosmos 482 orbiting Earth4. Kosmos 482 falling back to EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Space.com, the Kosmos 482 Venus probe was launched on March 31, 1972, but due to a rocket malfunction, failed to escape Earth's orbit." "A large portion of the failed spacecraft still remains in orbit today as space junk, but according to experts could fall back to Earth this year.""According to Don Mitchell, who studies Soviet space history talking to Space.com, when the Cosmos 482 mission failed, a heavy frame of tanks and equipment were jettisoned from the probe and burned up in Earth's atmosphere." "However, the Kosmos 482 Venus entry capsule is still adrift, orbiting the Earth every 112 minutes. The lander mass is 1,091 pounds and is equipped with significant thermal protection." "According to satellite watcher Thomas Dorman talking to Space.com, the failed probe could fall back to Earth this year or mid next year." "According to Space.com, previous estimates had the probe falling between 2023 and 2025."     SOURCES: Space.comhttps://www.space.com/failed-soviet-venus-spacecraft-falls-to-earth-soon.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 13:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/01/3789619/3789619_DEBEC320856640B5A28925D9D1403643_190301_3789619_Defunct_Russian_1970s_Venus_probe_could_crash_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Russia Kosmos 482, Kosmos 482 probe, Venus Kosmos 482 probe, failed Russian Kosmos 482 probe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789603</guid>
      <title>How the Democratic party will stage its primary debates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Democratic National Committee has announced that it has limited the number of presidential debate participants to 20 candidates. The debates will be held in June and July on two separate consecutive nights depending on the number of candidates that qualify.The Associated Press reports that candidates will qualify for the debate if they earn at least 1 percent support in three separate national or early primary state polls conducted from January 1 to two weeks before the debate.They can also qualify if they receive campaign donations from 65,000 people across 20 different states, with a minimum of 200 unique donors per state.Candidates will be assigned randomly to the two stages regardless of each candidates polling percentages.Efforts for a fairer and less poll-driven selection process for the nominees comes after voters in the 2016 elections felt the DNC was biased against the then outsider Senator Bernie Sanders.These claims stemmed mainly from allegations by former DNC chair Donna Brazile. In her book 'Hacks: The Inside Story of the Break-ins and Breakdowns that Put Donald Trump in the White House' Brazile accuses Hillary Clinton of rigging the primary elections in her favor by signing a joint fundraising agreement with the DNC and the Hillary Victory Fund.The exact dates and locations for the debates are yet to be confirmed, however, the DNC announced that NBC, MSNBC and Telemundo will broadcast the June debates on back-to-back nights, and CNN will broadcast the July debate on back-to-back nights. There will be a total of 12 debates. ________________RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Democratic National Committee limits first debates to 20 candidates2. Candidates qualify if they earn at least 1 percent support in national or early state polls 3. Candidates qualify depending on number of donations they receive4. Candidates are assigned randomly to one of two stagesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Democratic National Committee has announced that it has limited the number of presidential debate participants to 20 candidates." "The debates will be held in June and July on two separate consecutive nights depending on the number of candidates that qualify." "The Associated Press reports that candidates will qualify for the debate if they earn at least 1 percent support in three separate national or early primary state polls conducted from January 1 to two weeks before the debate.""They can also qualify if they receive campaign donations from 65,000 people across 20 different states, with a minimum of 200 unique donors per state.""Candidates will be assigned randomly to the two stages regardless of each candidates polling percentages."SOURCES: Associated Press, Politico, Voxhttps://www.apnews.com/03172a56519d4b9f8404bbb2e6be3742https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/14/dnc-fundraising-polling-early-debates-1170182https://www.vox.com/2019/2/14/18225341/dnc-tom-perez-debates-2020-president***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 13:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/01/3789603/3789603_A78970F9D5904B84B37D404551EE2D1C_190301_3789603_How_the_Democratic_party_will_stage_its_primary__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Democratic, Democrats, DNC, Democratic National Committee, Donald trump, 2020, 2020 elections, democratic debates, democratic primary]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789587</guid>
      <title>Iceland announces new quotas for whaling practices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIceland's government has announced it will be allowing whaling companies to kill more than 2,000 whales over the next five years.According to the Animal Welfare Institute Iceland has had a bumpy relationship with the International Whaling Commission after it imposed a moratorium on commercial whaling back in 1986.Iceland withdrew from the IWC but came back in 2002 and continued to hunt whales under a special permit that allowed them to kill protected species under the guise that it was being done for scientific purposes.Now, the Icelandic government is allowing whale hunters to kill over 2,000 whales per year over the next five years.The Associated Press reports that the Icelandic government has announced that whaling will be permitted for at least another five years.Iceland's Fisheries and Agriculture Minister Kristjan Thor Juliusson announced that whalers would be allowed to harpoon 209 fin whales and 217 minke whales every year until 2023.The World Wildlife Fund lists fin whales as an endangered species.Iceland has four harpoon-equipped vessels. According to the Directorate of Fisheries, in 2018, they hunted 5 minke whales and 145 fin whales.According to the University of Iceland, whaling is profitable for the country, bringing in roughly $11.8 million per year between 2009 and 2017.However, the AP reports that politicians are increasingly opposing whaling practices as they believe it damages the country's image and affects tourism which is a growing industry in the country. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Whaling in Iceland2. Species that will be allowed to be whaled3. Iceland's harpoon vessels4. Iceland's whaling industry and tourism industry VOICEOVER (in English):  "Associated Press reports that the Icelandic government has announced that whaling will be permitted for at least another five years.""Iceland's Fisheries and Agriculture Minister Kristjan Thor Juliusson announced that whalers would be allowed to harpoon 209 fin whales and 217 minke whales every year until 2023.""The World Wildlife Fund lists fin whales as an endangered species.""Iceland has four harpoon-equipped vessels. According to the Directorate of Fisheries, in 2018, they hunted 5 minke whales and 145 fin whales.""According to the University of Iceland, whaling is profitable for the country, bringing in roughly $11.8 million per year between 2009 and 2017.""However, the AP reports that politicians are increasingly opposing whaling practices as they believe it damages the country's image and affects tourism which is a growing industry in the country. "SOURCES: Associated Presshttps://www.apnews.com/f99a7c00cbfe443a8a67e9281f7218b7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 13:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/03/01/3789587/3789587_65DCDD98C4C94D059133608C2EFB5626_190301_3789587_Iceland_announces_new_quotas_for_whaling_practic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, whaling, commercial whaling, IWC, international whaling committee, iceland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
