<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3667275</guid>
      <title>Japan debuts mobile mosque to welcome Muslim visitors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Tokyo-based company is planning to launch a mobile mosque ahead of the 2020 Summer Olympics, reports Japan Today.The moving mosque takes the form of a large white and blue truck that expands into a place of worship.The back of the truck is able to flip open to reveal an entrance. The width of the truck would then double as the side of the truck slides out.A 48-square-meter room inside the truck should accommodate about 50 people at a time.Outdoor taps and a washing area would also be included in the mosque to allow worshippers to cleanse themselves before prayer.Yasuharu Inoue, the CEO of the project, said they want to share the idea of "omotenashi" or Japanese hospitality, with Muslim people.Inoue also said he hopes the mobile  mosque will help Muslim visitors feel at home as it would be able to travel to different Olympic venues if necessary.Inoue said he was inspired to create a mobile mosque after a trip to Qatar a few years ago.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the truck which would be used as a mobile mosque. 2. Showing the truck opening up to reveal an entrance and the slides opening up to expand the space.3. Showing the inside of the mobile mosque with people praying.4. Showing a tap and cleansing area in the mobile mosque.VOICEOVER (in English): "The moving mosque takes the form of a large white and blue truck that expands into a place of worship.""The back of the truck is able to flip open to reveal an entrance. The width of the truck would then double as the side of the truck slides out.""A 48-square-meter room inside the truck should accommodate about 50 people at a time." "Outdoor taps and a washing area would also be included in the mosque to allow worshippers to cleanse themselves before prayer."SOURCES: ABC News, Japan Today, Japan Times,https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/tokyo-company-debuts-mobile-mosque-ahead-2020-olympics-56803111https://japantoday.com/category/national/tokyo-company-debuts-mobile-mosque-ahead-of-2020-olympicshttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2018/07/29/national/company-unveils-mobile-mosque-welcome-muslims-visiting-japan/#.W2JxgIiFNjU***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 16:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/03/3667275/3667275_AF95FF95871F47209B65DC029DC03924_180803_3667275_Japan_debuts_mobile_mosque_to_welcome_Muslim_vis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/8A6/8B2/8A68B26F554D4927A19BC451F25E1B6B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Japan, Muslims, Mosque, Mobile Mosque, Japan Olympics 2020, worship]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666663</guid>
      <title>Man's limbs amputated after contracting deadly infection from dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA man's arms and legs were amputated after his dog's saliva caused a blood infection in his body, reports The Washington Post.Greg Manteufel suffered from sepsis, or blood poisoning, from the bacteria called Capnocytophaga canimorsus after it entered his bloodstream from his dog's saliva.His wife was quick to rush him to the hospital after he went into septic shock, reports Milwaukee Patch.Apparently the sepsis caused Manteufel to develop multiple blood spots which looked like bruises on his chest, face and the rest of his body.The doctors then tried to stop the infection from spreading with antibiotics. However, that blocked blood flow and caused some tissue and muscles to die.According to The Washington Post, the doctors then amputated his legs from the knee down, as well as his hands.Dr. Dilvia Munoz-Price, an infectious disease specialist, noted that Manteufel had contracted a rare infection and "more than 99 percent of people … will never have this issue ..."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the bacteria Capnocytophaga canimorsus entering the bloodstream.2. Showing blood spots appearing on the body because of the bacteria.3. Showing antibiotics entering the bloodstream and trying to stop the infection but that causes blockage and results in dead tissue and muscles.4. Showing his hands and legs below the knee disappearing to indicate amputation.VOICEOVER (in English): "Greg Manteufel suffered from sepsis, or blood poisoning from the bacteria called Capnocytophaga canimorsus after it entered his bloodstream from his dog's saliva.""Apparently the sepsis caused Manteufel to develop multiple blood spots which looked like bruises on his chest, face and the rest of his body.""The doctors then tried to stop the infection from spreading with antibiotics. However, that blocked blood flow and caused some tissue and muscles to die.""According to The Washington Post, the doctors then amputated his legs from the knee down, as well as his hands."SOURCES: The Washington Post, WRAL, NBC Chicago, WHNT News, The Epoch Timeshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2018/07/31/the-shocking-reason-that-this-mans-legs-and-hands-were-amputated-a-dogs-saliva/?utm_term=.357f6b5a7f55https://www.wral.com/bacteria-in-dog-saliva-causes-wisconsin-man-to-lose-both-legs-/17739232/https://www.nbcchicago.com/news/local/Mans-Limbs-Amputated-After-Bacteria-Linked-to-Dog-Saliva-Causes-Infection-489670431.htmlhttps://whnt.com/2018/07/31/hit-him-with-a-vengeance-mans-limbs-amputated-after-dog-lick-leads-to-blood-infection/?utm_campaign=trueAnthem:+Trending+Content&utm_content=5b609dcf04d301037c261207&utm_medium=trueAnthem&utm_source=twitterhttps://patch.com/wisconsin/milwaukee/dog-licks-wisconsin-man-his-legs-hands-had-be-amputatedhttps://www.theepochtimes.com/wisconsin-man-48-loses-limbs-from-dog-saliva-that-led-to-rare-infection_2610430.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 02:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/02/3666663/3666663_B554DE8E8342413C83961104AA4698B2_180802_3666663_Man_s_limbs_amputated_after_contracting_deadly_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/982/939/98293983ECE4498C9F49B51E64ED96B0_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, dog, saliva, infection, sepsis, septic shock, antibiotics, blood spots, blood infection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667765</guid>
      <title>NASA study shows terraforming Mars may not be possible</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study from NASA shows that it may not be possible to make Mars habitable for humans using current technology.According to the research conducted by NASA, there isn't enough carbon dioxide on Mars required to create an Earth-like atmosphere.Mars does have carbon dioxide in its rocks and polar ice caps, reports Space.com.However, even if all the carbon dioxide was released, it wouldn't be enough to raise the atmospheric pressure to 1 bar which is necessary for the temperatures at the pole to be above the melting point of water.Elon Musk does not agree with the scientists, and tweeted, "there's a massive amount of CO2 on Mars absorbed into soil that'd be released upon heating."The scientists said even if carbon dioxide from the soil were to be released, it would require the entire planet of Mars to be heated 100 meters below the surface which could take up to 10,000 years.They did agree that the released carbon dioxide could raise the atmospheric pressure, however it wouldn't be enough to warm up the atmosphere.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing Mars atmosphere and how there isn't enough carbon dioxide in the atmosphere.2. Showing some carbon dioxide in rocks and polar ice caps on Mars.3. Showing the temperature increasing on Mars because of the carbon dioxide, but it still isn't enough raise the atmospheric pressure.4. Showing the carbon dioxide molecule and fire icon to depict the heating of mars below the surface.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the research conducted by NASA, there isn't enough carbon dioxide on Mars to trap the heat and gases required to create an Earth-like atmosphere""Space.com reports Mars does have carbon dioxide in its rocks and polar ice caps.""However, even if all the carbon dioxide was released, it wouldn't be enough to raise the atmospheric pressure to 1 bar which is necessary for the temperatures at the pole to be above the melting point of water.""Scientists say even if carbon dioxide from the soil were to be released, it would require the entire planet of Mars to be heated 100 meters below the surface which could take upto 10,000 years."SOURCES: Quartz, Space.com, USA Today, Terraforming Mars Studyhttps://qz.com/1345912/nasa-says-nobody-not-even-elon-musk-can-terraform-mars/https://www.space.com/41318-we-cant-terraform-mars.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/science/2018/08/01/mars-terraform-nasa-elon-musk/878404002/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-018-0529-6.epdf?referrer_access_token=scg0V_-ispWfmHNvG7wlCNRgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0OEVA2jqQmP7EVNMm-ws-AKYR2p87cXLV6olBUe4T9qryYzexS8whoNqSaEtg93yWzaaBiEyjPhRFw2h6hoW4uesoTfx1ZzJVbGGjn3GOwQShwL4RS_7miKTVIPzk_gtLtSypy_PwDpA2jgdD8lTNFZBSe4Pdx4-SfA7Maky51jpwZdfnLcxhQX7z2zxjME0vmhb-SRuuin-dPlRYftvkIWcJT59YpAtDms_Nn7DAjhxw%3D%3D&tracking_referrer=www.usatoday.com***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 09:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/03/3667765/3667765_6E315235A2BD4DE1AC0506E68090BA1D_180803_3667765_NASA_study_shows_terraforming_Mars_may_not_be_po_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/73E/DF9/73EDF9C593544BABBBAEC62B0ACA4EC6_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,Mars, Space, NASA, terraforming Mars, carbon dioxide, habitable, atmosphere, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667717</guid>
      <title>China plans to bring an asteroid down to Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA group of Chinese scientists are planning to capture a small asteroid near Earth to study it for its resources. So far, the scientists have targeted an asteroid which is 6.4 meters in diameter and weighs several hundred tons, reports Xinhua.Li Ming Tao, a researcher involved with the project, said they aim to "turn asteroids with a potential threat to Earth into usable resources."The Chinese scientists plan to send a spacecraft with a huge bag which would wrap around a small asteroid and push it to Earth.The spacecraft would then unfold a heat shield which would "reduce the velocity of the asteroid" from 12.5 kilometers per second to 140 meters per second when it enters Earth's atmosphere.The scientists plan to study the asteroid and may choose to mine it for its resources.The asteroids may contain traces of history about the origins of the solar system and the origin of water and life on our planet, Xinhua reports.The team plans to launch the asteroid catcher by 2029 and bring back an asteroid by 2034.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the asteroid the scientists want to capture in space along with its dimensions.2. Showing how the aircraft will catch the asteroid with a bag.3. Showing how the scientists plan to shield the asteroid as it enters Earth's atmosphere.4. Showing what the scientists plan to do with the asteroid in Earth.VOICEOVER (in English): "Xinhua reports a group of Chinese scientists are planning to capture a small asteroid near Earth to study it for its resources. So far, the scientists have targeted an asteroid which is 6.4 meters in diameter and weighs several hundred tons.""The Chinese scientists plan to send a spacecraft with a huge bag which would wrap around a small asteroid and push it to Earth.""The spacecraft would then unfold a heat shield which would 'reduce the velocity of the asteroid' from 12.5 km per second to 140 meter per second when it enters Earth's atmosphere.""The scientists plan to study the asteroid and may choose to mine it for its resources."SOURCES: Outer Places, Extreme Tech, Tech Times, Business Recorder, Xinhua https://www.outerplaces.com/science/item/18727-china-lasso-asteroid-mininghttps://www.extremetech.com/extreme/274388-chinese-scientists-want-to-capture-a-small-asteroid-and-land-it-on-earthhttps://www.techtimes.com/articles/232692/20180726/china-plans-to-capture-an-asteroid-and-bring-it-down-to-earth.htmhttps://www.brecorder.com/2018/07/27/430720/china-plans-to-catch-asteroids-and-bring-them-down-to-earth/http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-07/23/c_137342866.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 08:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/03/3667717/3667717_0C482154B39D406E8D421E920C237A6B_180803_3667717_China_plans_to_bring_an_asteroid_down_to_Earth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/916/504/9165044AF889409EBBED5776E0FB802D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, China, scientists, asteroids, spacecraft, mining asteroids, heat shield, space, minerals, spaceship, exploring space, resources]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667408</guid>
      <title>Puppeteer fungus hijacks flies, brings them to gruesome end</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have identified a fungal pathogen that hijacks hapless fruit flies and puppeteers them to their death.According to new research from UC Berkeley, when the fungus known as entomophthora muscae infects fruit flies, it infiltrates the nervous system early on.The host insect remains seemingly unaffected while the fungus feeds off its fat stores, but begins acting abnormally once the pathogen invades and destroys its organs.Eventually, the fly is forced to climb to an elevated spot, where the fungus grows out of its proboscis and sticks to the surface it's on, cementing it in place.The fly is then made to raise its wings to a 90-degree angle before dying, allowing new spores to be ejected from its exposed abdomen to infect new hosts.The existence of the fungus, whose scientific name means "destroyer of insects", has been known for over a hundred years. Similar pathogens exists that hijack ants and aphids, but scientists have yet to figure out how exactly how.The Berkeley researchers are especially curious about how the puppet-master fungus gets the fly to override survival instincts and climb to its death, and are now focusing their efforts to uncover the answer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of fungus infiltrating fly's nervous system2. Depiction of fungus invading organs, causing fly to act abnormally3. Depiction of fly climbing to a high spot, cemented in place by fungus4. Depiction of fly dying with wings at 90 degrees, spores bursting out of abdomenVOICEOVER (in English): "New UC Berkeley research has found that when the entomophthora muscae fungus infects fruit flies, it infiltrates the nervous system early on.""The insect is relatively unaffected while the fungus feeds off its fat stores, but begins acting abnormally once the pathogen invades and destroys its organs.""Eventually, the fly is forced to climb to an elevated spot, where the fungus grows out of its proboscis and sticks to the surface it's on, cementing it in place.""The fly is made to raise its wings to a 90-degree angle before dying, allowing new spores to be ejected from its exposed abdomen to infect new hosts."SOURCES: University of California Berkeleyhttp://news.berkeley.edu/story_jump/flies-meet-gruesome-end-under-influence-of-puppeteer-fungus/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/03/3667408/3667408_A01D3D2DAC224E988223F3FBF8D9A015_180803_3667408_Puppeteer_fungus_hijacks_flies__brings_them_to_g_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/72B/425/72B425F92DC64DCE8E2CA318F292D2EF_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, fly, zombie fly, fungus, puppeteer fungus, mind control fungus, spores, Entomophthora muscae, fruit flies, destroyer of insects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669722</guid>
      <title>How scientists have transplanted a lab-grown lung into a pig</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in Science Translational Medicine describes how scientists have successfully transplanted a bioengineered lung into a pig.Scientists created lung scaffolds by taking a lung from another pig and bathing it in a solution of sugar and protein.This leaves a skeleton of the lungs, stripping it of all the blood and living cells.The lung scaffolds are then treated with growth factor-filled hydrogels and nanoparticles which would prepare it to receive cells from the pig where the lung was going to be transplanted to.The cells were left in the lung scaffolds for 30 days where it prepared a brand new lung.The researchers noticed the pigs which received the bioengineered lung managed to grow blood vessel networks by two weeks.Researchers involved in the project said the same process could be used for human transplants five to ten years from now.This successful operation means organ donor shortages could become a thing of the past.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the lung scaffold is prepared2. The skeleton of the lung3. The lung scaffold being prepared to receive cells from a new pig4. The lung growing blood vesselsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists created lung scaffolds by taking a lung from another pig and bathing it in a solution of sugar and protein.""This leaves a skeleton of the lungs, stripping it of all the blood and living cells.""The lung scaffolds are then treated with growth factor-filled hydrogels and nanoparticles which would prepare it to receive cells from the pig where the lung was going to be transplanted to.""The researchers noticed the pigs which received the bioengineered lung managed to grow blood vessel networks by two weeks."SOURCES: Digital Trends, Science Translational Medicine, New Atlas, Quartzhttps://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/lab-grown-lung-transplanted-pigs/http://stm.sciencemag.org/content/10/452/eaao3926https://newatlas.com/bioengineered-lungs-transplanted-pigs/55738/https://qz.com/1346000/scientists-successfully-transplanted-lab-grown-lungs-into-pigs/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 11:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/06/3669722/3669722_3B415C548A7B44B3AF04DF8BB97B7A80_180806_3669722_How_scientists_have_transplanted_a_lab_grown_lun_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DD6/5F6/DD65F64DB9D44D529F3DC5687D39BB98_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, science, medical breakthrough, bioengineering, lab-grown lungs, lung transplant, pigs, lung scaffold]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669714</guid>
      <title>Powerful 6.9 magnitude earthquake kills dozens in Indonesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRescue and evacuation operations are underway after several Indonesian islands were rocked by a deadly earthquake and strong aftershocks.Reuters reports that Indonesia's holiday island of Lombok was hit by a magnitude 6.9 earthquake around 6:46 p.m. on Sunday. According to the USGS, the quake had a depth of 31 kilometers and was felt in neighboring Bali.The powerful tremors triggered panic across the islands, as people fled homes and  buildings and ran onto the streets. At least 91 people have been confirmed dead, most of them killed by falling rubble in northern and western Lombok. Hundreds more are reportedly injured.The earthquake triggered an initial tsunami alert warning of waves up to half a meter, though this was later cancelled.It's the second to occur in Lombok in a week, after a 6.4 quake that shook the island on July 29 claimed 17 victims.More than 120 aftershocks, some ranging in magnitude from 4.3 to 5.4, were recorded following the massive quake. The death toll is also expected to rise as more news trickles in from the hardest-hit parts of the island.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of 6.9 magnitude quake hitting Lombok and being felt in Bali2. Depiction of people fleeing homes and buildings3. Depiction of death toll, number of injured4. Depiction of tsunami warningVOICEOVER (in English): "Indonesia's Lombok island was hit by a magnitude 6.9 earthquake around 6:46 p.m. on Sunday. The quake had a depth of 31 kilometers and was felt in neighboring Bali.""The powerful tremors triggered panic across the islands, as people fled homes and  buildings and ran onto the streets.""At least 91 people have been confirmed dead, most of them killed by falling rubble in northern and western Lombok. Hundreds more are reportedly injured.""The earthquake triggered an initial tsunami alert warning of waves up to half a meter, though this was later cancelled."SOURCES: Reuters, Jakarta Post, USGShttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-quake/powerful-quake-kills-82-on-indonesias-lombok-tourists-flee-idUSKBN1KR07Fhttp://www.thejakartapost.com/news/2018/08/06/indonesia-quake-kills-82-leaves-hundreds-wounded.htmlhttps://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us1000g3ub#origin***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 11:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/06/3669714/3669714_4AABBE59F3A74C0EA5CCD2C5C7DFE99F_180806_3669714_Powerful_6_9_magnitude_earthquake_kills_dozens_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C87/95A/C8795A0DFEB24D8391B2C1B1CA32FB19_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, earthquake, indonesia earthquake, lombok, bali, tsunami warning, quake, magnitude 7 earthquake, powerful quake, disaster, ring of fire, pacific ring of fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669687</guid>
      <title>Some bacteria have become resistant to hand sanitizers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that certain germs are becoming more and more resistant to hand sanitizers.Alcohol-based disinfectants are widely used to eliminate germs, and have proven effective against reducing infections like those caused by the staphylococcus bacteria, CNN reports.But a recent study published in Science Translational Medicine noticed a rise enterococcal infections, suggesting that the bacteria that causes it may have developed a tolerance to alcohol.Alcohol is believed to kill bacteria by dissolving their cellular membrane, so it was thought that germs and viruses were unable to adapt to it.Researchers analyzed 139 types of bacteria from 1997 to 2015 and found that on average, those taken after 2009 tolerated alcohol more than pre- 2004 strains.Further testing showed that the alcohol-tolerant bacteria appeared in the guts of mice even after their cages were cleaned with sanitizing wipes.Currently, the enterococcus bacteria can only be killed with a 70% alcohol solution, according to NPR, though It's unclear if the bacteria will mutate to tolerate higher concentrations, or even build total resistance.The study authors say this doesn't mean people should give up hand sanitizers altogether, but there's a strong indication washing with soap and water is still the best way to eliminate germs."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of alcohol eliminating hand germs2. Depiction of alcohol-tolerant enterococcus bacteria3. Depiction of long-term bacteria analysis4. Depiction of bacteria testing on miceVOICEOVER (in English): "Alcohol-based disinfectants are widely used to eliminate germs, and have proven effective against reducing infections like those caused by the staphylococcus bacteria.""But a recent study noticed a rise enterococcal infections, suggesting that the bacteria that causes it may have developed a tolerance to alcohol.""Researchers analyzed 139 types of bacteria from 1997 to 2015 and found that on average, those taken after 2009 tolerated alcohol more than pre- 2004 strains.""Further testing showed that the alcohol-tolerant bacteria appeared in the guts of mice even after their cages were cleaned with sanitizing wipes."SOURCES: CNN, NPRhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/02/health/hand-sanitizer-bacteria-resistance-study/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2018/08/02/635017716/some-bacteria-are-becoming-more-tolerant-of-hand-sanitizers-study-finds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 10:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/06/3669687/3669687_2DDB74C489A24863B9A91A84B3BBE512_180806_3669687_Some_bacteria_have_become_resistant_to_hand_sani_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/AB3/D97/AB3D97896E574B7EA6D49C23CABA1F8D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, hand sanitizer, bacteria, sanitizers, totoo alcohol, alcohol resistant bacteria, superbugs, germs, hand germs, hand washing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669508</guid>
      <title>Study finds plastic exposed to the sun emit greenhouse gases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in PLOS One shows that plastic releases greenhouses gases when exposed to the sun.The study found that some of the commonly-used plastics release methane and ethylene one they are exposed to sunlight.Dr. Sarah-Jeanne Royer, lead author of the study, said they originally set out to measure methane produced by organisms in seawater when she realized that most of the methane was being emitted from the plastic bottles in the sea, reports EcoWatch.Dr. Royer and her team tested plastics such as polycarbonate, polypropylene, polystyrene, and low-density polyethylene along with others found in food packaging, textiles, and other plastic goods. When plastic is exposed to light from the sun, it breaks down, which exposes more plastic area to the sun, resulting in greater gas emissions.One of the plastics, low-density polyethylene, was found to continue emitting gases even in the dark, after it had it had been exposed to the sun.The study found plastic bags, which is the most commonly used and discarded plastic in the world, emitted the largest amount of greenhouse gases.In a press release by the University of Hawaii, Dr. Royer and her team is now working to "constrain the overall greenhouse gas emissions from plastics."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of methane and ethylene being emitted from plastic bottle on the beach.2. Depiction of different plastics and where they are found.3. Depiction of how light from the sun causes plastic to degrade and release greenhouse gases.4. Depiction of how low-density polyethylene continues to emit greenhouse gases in the dark after expose to the sun.VOICEOVER (in English): "The study found that some of the commonly-used plastics release methane and ethylene one they are exposed to sunlight.""Dr. Royer and her team tested plastics such as polycarbonate, polypropylene, polystyrene, and low-density polyethylene along with others found in food packaging, textiles, and other plastic goods. ""When plastic is exposed to light from the sun, it breaks down, which exposes more plastic area to the sun, resulting in greater gas emissions.""One of the plastics, low-density polyethylene, was found to continue emitting gases even in the dark, after it had it had been exposed to the sun."SOURCES: EcoWatch, Production of methane and ethylene from plastic in the environment Study, Hawaii Press release, The BBC https://www.ecowatch.com/plastic-waste-could-contribute-to-climate-change-2592101036.htmlhttp://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0200574http://www.hawaii.edu/news/article.php?aId=9407https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-45043989***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 07:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/06/3669508/3669508_BFE1363045AA41338FA08083DC4F08F3_180806_3669508_Study_finds_plastic_exposed_to_the_sun_emit_gree_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/AD4/CD6/AD4CD682B2FF4E838B57A16386288684_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Study, Hawaii, plastic, methane, greenhouse gases, Sun, global warming, climate change, greenhouse gas emissions, ethylene]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3670426</guid>
      <title>Venezuela arrests six over failed assassination attempt on president</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVenezuela claims it has identified the mastermind and accomplices behind a failed attempt on the president's life.CNN reports that Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro survived an alleged assassination attempt on Saturday after a drone exploded near where he was delivering a speech.Footage of the event show him looking up mid-speech as a loud bang is heard off-screen. Soldiers are then seen breaking formation and scattering. Though the president escaped unscathed, seven members of the national guard were reportedly injured by the blast.According to Venezuela's Interior Minister Nestor Reverol, assailants used two DJI M600 drones, each carrying a kilogram of C4 explosives. One drone was set to detonate above Maduro, the other in front of him.The Venezuelan military electronically knocked one of the drones off-course and caused it to detonate away from the target area. The second drone ended up crashing into an apartment building two blocks away from the event.Six people were detained and later charged in connection with the attack after authorities examined materials and electronic devices in their possession.The Madura administration accused the far right of trying to kill him, alleging that they conspired with Colombian President Juan Manuel Santos and Venezuelans in Miami.Critics say no evidence has been presented to back the government's claims. According to the Times of London, some have even speculated the attack may have been staged to let the president take action against his opponents.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of failed assassination attempt2. Depiction of explosive-laden drones3. Depiction of drone being knocked off-course by signal jammer4. Depiction of second drone crashing into apartment building5. Depiction of suspects being arrestedVOICEOVER (in English): "Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro survived an alleged assassination attempt on Saturday, after a drone exploded near where he was delivering a speech.""According to Venezuela's interior minister, assailants used two DJI M600 drones, each carrying a kilogram of C4 explosives. One drone was set to detonate above Maduro, the other in front of him.""The Venezuelan military electronically knocked one of the drones off-course and caused it to detonate away from the target area. ""The second drone ended up crashing into an apartment building two blocks away from the event.""Six people were detained and later charged in connection with the attack after authorities examined materials and electronic devices in their possession."SOURCES: CNN, USA Today, The Timeshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/06/americas/venezuela-maduro-apparent-assassination-attempt/index.htmlhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/08/06/venezuela-drone-attack-nicolas-maduro-assassination-attempt-what-happened/913096002/https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/assassination-plot-not-staged-maduro-insists-s7c25c02b***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/07/3670426/3670426_35C4F7B5C9BD4F528A0781F6B27C5667_180807_3670426_Venezuela_arrests_six_over_failed_assassination__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/510/ACB/510ACBD1EFE04AC08E0AB4CF63F6E629_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, venezuela, president, nicolas maduro, maduro, assassination, assassination attempt, explosion, drone explosion, drone attack, far right, DJI M600 drone, drone signal jammer, venezuela politics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671073</guid>
      <title>Study shows microbes in our gut can impact our ability to gain or lose weight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in Mayo Clinic Proceedings shows certain types of bacteria in our gut may influence weight loss and weight gain.Researchers from the Mayo Clinic in Rochester, Minnesota found that those who were successful in losing weight had an abundance of a bacteria called Phascolarctobacterium in their gut, while those who weren't had an abundance of bacteria named Dialister.  Gut bacteria is important as it breaks down food parts we can't normally digest. When this occurs, the bacteria creates "extra calories" for our body to digest, which results in a calorie boost.The study was conducted with 26 participants who were overweight and obese, and going through lifestyle changes.The participants were tracked for three months, during which they had to follow a low-calorie diet and were encouraged to walk 10,000 steps a day.The team of researchers collected fecal samples from the participants to find out which bacteria their body's digestive system contained.Purna Kashyap, a researcher involved in the study, explained to NPR that "people who lost at least 5 percent of their body weight had a different gut bacteria compared to those who did not lose 5 percent of their body weight."The bacteria Phascolarctobacterium had previously been associated with weight gain in a study involving obese rats.The Mayo researchers said their study suggests Phascolarctobacterium may increase the effects of lifestyle and dietary changes on weight loss. However, Kashyap added that there might be other types of bacteria that may influence dieting as well.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the Phascolarctobacterium bacteria and the Dialister which were found in the digestive tract.2. Depiction of bacteria found in the gut breaking down food.3. Showing three calendar icons to represent three months and then showing a step counter to show the participants had to walk 10,000 steps a day.4. Depiction of the percentage of weight some of the participants lost and the bacteria that was found in their digestive tract.VOICEOVER (in English): "A study by researchers from the Mayo Clinic found that those who were successful in losing weight had an abundance of a bacteria called Phascolarctobacterium in their gut, while those who were not had an abundance of bacteria named Dialister.""Gut bacteria breaks down food parts we can't normally digest. When this occurs, the bacteria creates 'extra calories' for our body to digest, which results in a calorie boost.""The participants were tracked for three months, during which they had to follow a low-calorie diet and were encouraged to walk 10,000 steps a day.""A researcher involved in the study told NPR that 'people who lost at least 5 percent of their body weight had a different gut bacteria compared to those who did not lose 5 percent of their body weight.'"SOURCES: NPR, Mayo Clinic Proceedings, Fortune, Washington Times,https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/08/06/635362706/diet-hit-a-snag-your-gut-bacteria-may-be-partly-to-blamehttps://www.mayoclinicproceedings.org/article/S0025-6196(18)30148-4/abstracthttp://fortune.com/2018/08/06/weight-loss-diet-gut-bacteria/https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/6/gut-bacteria-factor-weight-loss-study/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 09:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/08/3671073/3671073_499B9DF08B4543349B11B050EC6A0314_180808_3671073_Study_shows_microbes_in_our_gut_can_impact_our_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1FC/45C/1FC45C8589634C43A46C9DF594203DCD_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,Study, US, bacteria, microbes, guts, gut bacteria, Phascolarctobacterium bacteria, Dialister bacteria, types of bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671003</guid>
      <title>Canine influenza is on the rise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe number of canine influenza confirmed cases in Michigan has risen to 49 since mid-July, reports WNDU.According to AVMA, dogs can get canine influenza after being exposed to the H3N8 or H3N2 virus.It is a respiratory infection which can be caused by sniffing or licking dogs who have the virus or by sharing food and water with those dogs.Sick dogs who are coughing or sneezing may also pass on the virus to healthy dogs.Dogs may also be exposed to the virus by humans whose clothings or skin have been contaminated with the it.Michigan Department of Agriculture & Rural Development mentioned in a news release, symptoms may include fever, discharge from the eyes or nose, and coughing along with lethargic behavior."However, canine influenza can also be prevented with a vaccine.James Averill, Michigan's state veterinarian, told Michigan Live, "It's important that dog owners work with their veterinarians to protect their dogs."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the H3N8 and the H3N2 virus.2. Depiction of how the dog may receive the virus, which then enters the lungs.3. Depiction of some of the symptoms the dog may have such as discharge from the eyes and nose.4. Depiction of the dog receiving a vaccine to prevent canine influenza.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to AVMA, Dogs can get canine influenza after being exposed to the H3N8 or H3N2 virus.""It is a respiratory infection which can be caused by sniffing or licking dogs who have the virus or by sharing food and water with those dogs.""Michigan Department of Agriculture & Rural Development mentioned in a news release, symptoms may include fever, discharge from the eyes or nose, and coughing along with lethargic behavior.""However, canine influenza can also be prevented with a vaccine."SOURCES: Michigan Live, WNDU,  Michigan Department of Agriculture & Rural Development(MDARD), American Veterinary Medical Association(AVMA)https://www.mlive.com/news/index.ssf/2018/08/canine_influenza_cases_spike_a.htmlhttp://www.wndu.com/content/news/How-to-tell-if-your-dog-has-dog-flu-490019961.htmlhttps://www.michigan.gov/mdard/0,4610,7-125-48096---,00.htmlhttps://www.avma.org/KB/Resources/FAQs/Pages/Control-of-Canine-Influenza-in-Dogs.aspx***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 08:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/08/3671003/3671003_F7C57E229B0A46C0B621F0EF345D236E_180808_3671003_Canine_influenza_is_on_the_rise_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1C5/836/1C58368ED7C94C989CBF3A33CAD14837_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, US, dog, canine influenza, dog flu, highly contagious, respiratory infection, virus, coughing, symptoms, disease]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671934</guid>
      <title>Scientists say climate policies may not be enough to undo damage caused by wildfires</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe amount of carbon being spewed out into the atmosphere may completely undo what climate policies have helped to prevent over the years, reports CAL Matters.The scientists involved in the study say when wildfires burn, only 15 percent of the carbon is released at the time.However, the remainder of the carbon continues to be released as the trees decay over the years and decades.According to the scientists, the carbon that continues to be released would contain more harmful compounds than the original forest fire.The study also warns that future fires that take place over previously burned land would make things even worse.In the wake of these natural disasters, we may be forced to find new solutions or face even greater disasters in the future, reports The Guardian. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the forest, with a fire icon and carbon dioxide molecule to represent the release of only 15% carbon at the time of a wildfire. 2. Showing the aftermath of the fire with most of the forest burning down 3. The burned trees release more carbon dioxide gradually.4. Showing a previously burned land catching on fire.VOICEOVER (in English): "The scientists involved in the study say when wildfires burn, only 15 percent of the carbon is released at the time.""However, the remainder of the carbon continues to be released as the trees decay over the years and decades.""According to the scientists, the carbon that continues to be released would contain more harmful compounds than the original forest fire.""The study also warns that future fires that take place over previously burned land would make things even worse."SOURCES: CAL Matters, Tech Crunch, Drought, Tree Mortality, and Wildfire in Forests Adapted to Frequent Fire research paper, The Guardian, CBS SF Bay Area https://calmatters.org/articles/as-california-burns-climate-goals-may-go-up-in-smoke-even-after-the-flames-are-out/https://techcrunch.com/2018/08/08/as-california-burns-climate-goals-may-go-up-in-smoke-even-after-the-flames-are-out/https://nature.berkeley.edu/stephenslab/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Stephens-et-al.-Fire-Tree-Mortality-BioSci-2018.pdfhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/aug/07/california-wildfires-megafires-future-climate-changehttps://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/californias-fire-season-hotter-nights/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 13:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/09/3671934/3671934_34CE258DD14F41B5823EA624EF34F4C7_180809_3671934_Scientists_say_climate_policies_may_not_be_enoug_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/28B/FFB/28BFFBF299284657AA79F47C10FF3FA2_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, wildfires, California wildfires, climate change, climate policies, fires, forest fires, flames, carbon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671922</guid>
      <title>Scientists say Earth is at risk of becoming "hothouse"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America says Earth is approaching "hothouse" conditions if global temperatures rise more than 2 degrees Celsius.Scientists also stated that once temperatures hit the tipping point, where Earth's natural systems will be triggered, this will further increase global warming.Right now, the earth's forests, land and other natural systems work to absorb around 4.5 billion tonnes of carbon, to prevent carbon from ending up in the atmosphere.However, if temperatures continue to warm the planet, these natural systems may end up releasing more carbon than they take in.In the report, the researchers warn rising temperatures could also lead to rising sea levels up to 60 meters from today's shorelines.Some places would become uninhabitable if the earth continues to get warmer and warmer.However, the researchers ended on an optimistic note, saying this catastrophe could be avoided if action is taken immediately to change how we are impacting Earth's natural systems.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the rising temperatures affecting Earth.2. Depiction of the forest working to absorb carbon dioxide3. Depiction of rising temperature affecting sea levels.4. Depiction of parts of the world becoming uninhabitable due to climate change.VOICEOVER (in English): "A study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America says Earth is approaching 'hothouse' conditions if global temperatures rise more than 2°C.""Right now, the Earth's forests, land and other natural systems work to absorb around 4.5 billion tonnes of carbon, to prevent carbon from ending up in the atmosphere.""In the report the researchers warn rising temperatures could also lead to rising sea levels upto 60 meters from today's shorelines.""Some places would become uninhabitable if the earth continues to get warmer and warmer."SOURCES: Fox News, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America,  Stockholm University Study, The BBC, The Guardian, CNN http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/08/07/hothouse-earth-scientists-believe-planet-could-soon-cross-threshold-leading-to-warmer-temps-and-sea-rise.htmlhttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/07/31/1810141115http://www.stockholmresilience.org/research/research-news/2018-08-06-planet-at-risk-of-heading-towards-hothouse-earth-state.htmlhttps://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-45084144https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/aug/06/domino-effect-of-climate-events-could-push-earth-into-a-hothouse-statehttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/07/health/hothouse-earth-warming-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 13:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/09/3671922/3671922_409C498A15094C92B99578FFDD13BB3F_180809_3671922_Scientists_say_Earth_is_at_risk_of_becoming__hot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9FC/9DA/9FC9DA1B20024334B6F0345459B7C305_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Earth, global warming, climate change, study, planet earth, rising temperatures, carbon dioxide, atmosphere, global temperatures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671484</guid>
      <title>China claims it has carried out successful hypersonic aircraft test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina says it has tested out a new hypersonic aircraft, The Starry Sky-2 , which could one day be used to carry nuclear missiles, reports The South China Morning Post.According to reports from Xinhua, the aircraft is a hypersonic experimental waverider vehicle.The hypersonic aircraft has a flatter, wedge-shaped fuselage and was launched by a multistage rocket into space in northwest China.The aircraft, which is still at the experimental stage, can ride on shock waves it generates.The China Academy of Aerospace Aerodynamics released a statement saying the Starry Sky-2 can travel at least five to six times the speed of sound."The academy also released pictures and videos of the test on WeChat, showing the aircraft twisting and turning. The aircraft then landed in a designated target zone.Zhou Chenming, a Beijing-based military analyst, told the South China Morning Post the aircraft may also have other military applications, adding there are still three to five years before the technology can be weaponized.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the hypersonic aircraft and the launching of the aircraft.2. We see the aircraft continuing to soar into space. 3. Showing the aircraft twisting and turning in space.4. We see the aircraft going towards the ground.VOICEOVER (in English): "The hypersonic aircraft has a flatter, wedge-shaped fuselage and was launched by a multistage rocket into space in northwest China.""The China Academy of Aerospace Aerodynamics released a statement saying The Starry Sky-2 can travel at least five to six times the speed of sound.""The academy also released pictures and videos of the test on WeChat, showing the aircraft twisting and turning. ""The aircraft then landed in a designated target zone."SOURCES: CNN, WeChat press release, South China Morning Post, Defence Blog, Asia Times, Xinhua Nethttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/07/china/china-hypersonic-aircraft-intl/index.html?no-st=1533692596https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?subscene=23&__biz=MzI3MDA2NDI2MQ==&mid=2650740091&idx=1&sn=8c2545c20c672d7f52d97fd560abe48c&chksm=f2dd7a91c5aaf38700ba3d259a68661b738e8303f0e4f36b6bee01f770c7e95ceb31ff1b050e&scene=7#rdhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2158524/chinas-hypersonic-aircraft-starry-sky-2-could-be-used#commentshttps://defence-blog.com/aviation/china-successfully-test-fire-hypersonic-aircraft.htmlhttp://www.atimes.com/article/china-tests-its-hypersonic-wave-rider-aircraft/http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-08/06/c_137370948.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 02:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/09/3671484/3671484_CCEB977C8497440381F3748FFCDF4D65_180809_3671484_China_claims_it_has_carried_out_successful_hyper_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/E57/5AF/E575AF05825740EE9A686A1D6CDC80C1_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,China, aircraft, hypersonic aircraft, Aerospace technology, rocket, Starry Sky-2, flight test, aerospace industry, launch, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3672464</guid>
      <title>Men who wear boxers have higher sperm count</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that men looking to boost their sperm count may want to swap their briefs for boxers.According to a new study led by the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health,  semen and blood samples were collected from 656 men seeking treatment at a fertility center with their partners. The men were also asked what the type of underwear they wore the last three months.Researchers found that while the subjects produced similar amounts of ejaculation fluid, boxer-wearers had 25% higher sperm concentration, 17% higher total sperm count, and better motility compared to those who wore jockeys or briefs.Brief wearers' blood had more follicle-stimulating hormones, which are released by the pituitary gland and associated with sperm production. This suggests the gland may have been boosting hormone production to compensate for lower sperm numbers.The Guardian reports that previous studies have found scrotal temperature to affect spermatogenesis, and that wearing loose-fitting underwear is better than tighter undergarments at keeping it cool.But while the new study shows a link between type of underwear and fertility, more research is needed to account for other factors and establish clear causality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of researchers surveying underwear types, collecting samples from men 2. Depiction of better sperm count, concentration, motility in men wearing boxers3. Depiction of higher FSH levels in men wearing briefs4. Depiction of scrotal temperature potentially affecting sperm productionVOICEOVER (in English): "A Harvard study collected semen and blood samples from men seeking treatment at a fertility center with their partners, and surveyed the type of underwear they wore.""Researchers found boxer-wearers had 25% higher sperm concentration, 17% higher total sperm count, and better motility compared to those who wore jockeys or briefs.""Brief wearers' blood had more follicle-stimulating hormones associated with sperm production, which suggests the pituitary gland was working to compensate for lower sperm numbers.""Previous studies have found that scrotal temperature affects spermatogenesis, and that wearing loose-fitting underwear is better than tighter undergarments at keeping it cool."SOURCES: Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health, The Guardian, USA Todayhttps://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2018-08/htcs-bob080618.phphttps://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/aug/08/wearing-boxer-shorts-boosts-sperm-count-scientists-sayhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/08/08/boxers-briefs-choice-sperm-count-study/937220002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/10/3672464/3672464_4DFE6D1B25404D618BB6FE7560121BEF_180810_3672464_Men_who_wear_boxers_have_higher_sperm_count_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FF7/A55/FF7A55F596044408B7E35257741F411F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, sperm, sperm count, boxers vs briefs, boxer shorts, boxers or briefs, sperm concentration, sperm motility, swimmers, male reproduction, male fertility]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674166</guid>
      <title>NASA launches Parker solar probe on mission to 'touch the sun'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has sent a probe to fly closer to the sun's surface than any man-made object has ever gone.Unlike other space missions, the Parker solar probe will have a long and complex orbit, since it's much more difficult to get to the sun, according to NASA.The earth travels 67,000 miles per hour in a sideways motion relative to the sun to avoid being pulled in by its strong gravitational forces. As such, any object travelling to the sun must cancel that motion.NASA's Parker solar probe must drop 53,000 miles per hour of sideways speed. In addition to being launched by the powerful Delta IV Heavy rocket, it will perform seven Venus flybys over a seven-year period, relying on the planet's gravity to draw its orbit closer to the sun.The probe is then set to fly through the heated solar atmosphere called the corona, to understand and be able to predict the behavior of solar winds.If all goes according to plan, the Parker solar probe will make its first close pass at the sun in November.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Earth's sideways motion relative to the sun2. Depiction of solar probe launch atop Delta Heavy IV rocket3. Depiction of probe's trajectory and Venus flybys4. Depiction of probe studying solar windsVOICEOVER (in English): "The earth travels 67,000 miles per hour in a sideways motion relative to the sun to avoid being pulled into it. So any object travelling to the sun must cancel that motion.""NASA's Parker solar probe must drop 53,000 miles per hour of sideways speed. In addition to being launched by the powerful Delta IV Heavy rocket, it will perform seven Venus flybys over a seven-year period, relying on the planet's gravity to draw its orbit closer to the sun.""The probe is then set to fly through the heated solar atmosphere called the corona, to understand and be able to predict the behavior of solar winds."SOURCES: NASA, United Launch Alliance, CBShttps://svs.gsfc.nasa.gov/13017https://www.ulalaunch.com/missions/delta-iv-parker-solar-probehttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/parker-solar-probe-cleared-for-launch-mission-to-touch-the-sun-nasa/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 08:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/13/3674166/3674166_7169A248C8DE499191D5C1543DC499C3_180813_3674166_NASA_launches_Parker_solar_probe_on_mission_to___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/5BF/4EE/5BF4EE8B851D477CA94E64F4C03E1C9C_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, NASA, solar probe, sun mission, parker solar probe, solar mission, rocket launch, delta heavy rocket, touch the sun, NASA mission, solar winds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674934</guid>
      <title>Ford Motor Credit claiming massive Reagor-Dykes Auto Group fraud</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFord Motor Credit filed more documents with the bankruptcy court last Friday claiming Reagor-Dykes Auto Group misrepresented sales-reporting data to Ford Credit. Ford claims this could be one of the largest floor-plan financing frauds in U.S. history, according to KCBD. Ford believes Reagor-Dykes was stretching out the time it was using to pay off vehicles it sold to customers. During a Ford Credit investigation, they discovered the auto group was selling vehicles on average of 55 days before reporting the car sales to Ford Credit. The documents also claims Reagor-Dykes fraudulently obtained double-flooring from Ford Credit, reported KCBD. Double-flooring is an illegal practice where a single vehicle is used as collateral for more than one loan. Ford Credit also says Reagor-Dykes secured inventory financing for vehicles it had already sold. By listing the vehicles as current inventory, Reagor-Dykes was then able to obtain additional financing. According to Ford, Reagor-Dykes "squandered more than $41 million on the current management's watch  through either their own fraud or gross mismanagement."  According to KCBD, Ford Credit filed the documents requesting the court appoint a trustee to recover and preserve assets for the liquidation of Reagor-Dykes and provide payment to creditors. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Reagor-Dykes misrepresenting sales-reporting data to Ford Credit2. Reagor-Dykes was selling vehicles on average of 55 days before reporting the car sales to Ford Credit3. Reagor-Dykes obtaining double-flooring from Ford Credit4. Reagor-Dykes obtaining financing for cars already soldVOICEOVER (in English): "Ford Motor Credit filed more documents with the bankruptcy court claiming Reagor-Dykes Auto Group misrepresented sales-reporting data to Ford Credit."  "According to KCBD, during a Ford Credit investigation, they discovered the auto group was selling vehicles on average of 55 days before reporting the car sales to Ford Credit." "The documents also claims Reagor-Dykes fraudulently obtained double-flooring from Ford Credit, reported KCBD. Double-flooring is an illegal practice where a single vehicle is used as collateral for more than one loan." "Ford Credit also says Reagor-Dykes secured inventory financing for vehicles it had already sold. By listing the vehicles as current inventory, Reagor-Dykes was then able to obtain additional financing." SOURCES: KCBDhttp://www.kcbd.com/story/38858910/ford-this-may-be-one-of-the-largest-frauds-in-the-history-of-the-united-states***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/14/3674934/3674934_5220CEB235DF471BB81069E539955607_180814_3674934_Ford_Motor_Credit_claiming_massive_Reagor_Dykes__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/8B9/D8F/8B9D8FA993CE48C3B284626D17090AAC_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Ford Credit, Reagor-Dykes Auto Group, Ford Reagor-Dykes, double flooring, Ford]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674770</guid>
      <title>Man at New Mexico compound was training kids to commit school shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe search for a missing boy led police to a remote New Mexico property, where they found something even more horrifying.CNN reports that 4-year-old Abdul-Ghani Wahhaj went missing in late November, and is believed to have been kidnapped by his father, Siraj Wahhaj.On Friday, authorities raided a makeshift compound near Amalia, New Mexico with no running water or electricity, and rescued 11 emaciated children aged 1 to 15.They found Siraj Wahhaj armed with an AR-15, revolver, four pistols, and ammunition, and arrested him and his accomplices, a man and three women.Court documents allege that Wahhaj was giving the children weapons training, and preparing them to commit future school shootings.The remains of a young boy were later found at the site, but authorities have yet to determine if the body is Wahhaj's missing son.The five suspects were charged with 11 counts of felony child abuse, and have pleaded not guilty.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of children rescued from New Mexico compound2. Depiction of suspects arrested at New Mexico compound3. Depiction of children being trained to commit school shootings4. Depiction of human remains found on siteVOICEOVER (in English): "On Friday, authorities raided a makeshift compound near Amalia, New Mexico with no running water or electricity, and rescued 11 emaciated children aged 1 to 15.""They found Siraj Wahhaj armed with an AR-15, revolver, four pistols, and ammunition, and arrested him and his accomplices, a man and three women.""Court documents allege that Wahhaj was giving the children weapons training, and preparing them to commit future school shootings.""The remains of a young boy were later found at the site, but authorities have yet to determine if the body is Wahhaj's missing son."SOURCES: ABC, CNBC, CNN, Albuquerque Journalhttps://abcnews.go.com/US/man-found-11-children-filthy-mexico-compound-training/story?id=57114702https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/08/man-training-kids-for-school-shooting-court-documents-say.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/09/us/new-mexico-compound-children/index.htmlhttps://www.abqjournal.com/1206057/officials-childs-body-found-at-taos-county-compound.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 06:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/14/3674770/3674770_3335F92E66E845808E35A38040AB681A_180814_3674770_Man_at_New_Mexico_compound_was_training_kids_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A84/F89/A84F8939986C49988E406AC457512939_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, new mexico compound, muslim, extremist, extremist muslim, missing boy, school shooting, weapons training, siraj wahhaj, kidnapped boy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674645</guid>
      <title>Rare mega-shark teeth discovered at Australian beach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA jawful of sharp, serrated teeth provides rare evidence of a similarly ferocious mega-shark that once stalked the ancient waters down under.According to a press release from Museums Victoria, amateur fossil enthusiast Philip Mullaly discovered a set of sharp teeth sticking out of a boulder on Australia's Jan Juc coast. He contacted Museums Victoria, and further exploration revealed several more.The teeth belonged to the Great Narrow Jagged-Toothed Shark, which grew to over nine meters long  twice the size of a Great White.The prehistoric predator lived approximately 25 million years ago and are believed to have preyed on small whales and penguins.Shark skeletons are mostly made of cartilage, which doesn't fossilize well. Only single teeth and bits of vertebra are usually found, so multiple sets from a single shark is a rare find.Apart from the mega-shark, teeth from several Sixgill sharks were also uncovered, leading the team to believe a school of the bottom-feeding Sixgills may have feasted on the mega-shark's carcass.The fossilized teeth collection is with Museums Victoria, and will be on public display for six months.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of shark teeth found on Australian coast2. Depiction of Great Narrow Jagged-Toothed shark3. Depiction of shark preying on whale4. Depiction of fossilized shark partsVOICEOVER (in English): "After an amateur fossil enthusiast discovered a set of sharp teeth sticking out of a boulder on Australia's Jan Juc coast, further exploration revealed several more.""The teeth belonged to the Great Narrow Jagged-Toothed Shark, which grew to over nine meters long  twice the size of a Great White.""The prehistoric predator lived approximately 25 million years ago and are believed to have preyed on small whales and penguins.""Shark skeletons are mostly made of cartilage, which doesn't fossilize well. Only single teeth and bits of vertebra are usually found, so multiple sets from a single shark is a rare find.SOURCES: Museums Victoria, New York Timeshttps://museumsvictoria.com.au/media-releases/victorian-fossil-find-uncovers-prehistoric-leftovers-of-colossal-shark-feast/https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/09/science/sharks-fossils-australia.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 03:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/14/3674645/3674645_D33C8290E05743B3B9268219CF63C1F8_180814_3674645_Rare_mega_shark_teeth_discovered_at_Australian_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/74F/80F/74F80FF99565465E88A5F5ADE97E7C4C_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, mega shark, prehistoric shark, shark teeth, shark teeth, great narrow jagged-toothed shark, megalodon, shark fossil, jan juc, museums victoria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674625</guid>
      <title>Study finds stomach viruses cluster together to become more deadly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in Cell Host & Microbe found that different stomach viruses tend to be more contagious when the virus particles cluster together.The scientists conducted the study by analyzing stool samples from patients who had rotavirus or norovirus.They found out that stomach virus such as norovirus and rotavirus cluster together to form "packs" of up to 40 viruses.The virus clusters  called vesicles  are then covered in a protective membrane. The virus inside the clusters are also quick to replicate inside the membrane to form more virus particles.According to the study, the protective membrane protects the virus clusters from being noticed by the immune system.As the vesicles pass through the immune system and into the intestine, it quickly separates and infects one single cell with multiple viruses.In the study, scientists found that mice infected with clustered viruses became more ill compared to those that were infected with a single virus.The researchers noted as there are currently no vaccine to treat the vesicles, treatments to target the clusters, instead of individual virus particles, would need to be developed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Showing the two stomach viruses Norovirus and rotavirus. 2. We show the virus clustering together and being covered by a protective membrane.3. We see the virus multiplying inside the protective membrane.4. We see the clustered virus entering the body's intestine and attacking a single cell with multiple viruses.VOICEOVER (in English): "Stomach virus such as norovirus and rotavirus cluster together to form 'packs' of up to 40 viruses.""The virus clusters  called vesicles  are then covered in a protective membrane." "The virus inside the clusters are also quick to replicate inside the membrane to form more virus particles.According to the study, the protective membrane protects the virus clusters from being noticed by the immune system." "As the vesicles enter pass through the immune system and into the intestine, it quickly separates and infects one single cell with multiple viruses."SOURCES:NPR, Cell Host & Microbe, THE BBC, Science News, ResearchGate,  National Institutes of Health,  Medical Xpresshttps://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2018/08/09/637015778/scientists-discover-the-secret-weapon-of-stomach-viruseshttps://www.cell.com/cell-host-microbe/fulltext/S1931-3128(18)30376-7?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS1931312818303767%3Fshowall%3Dtruehttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-45114842https://www.sciencenews.org/article/nasty-stomach-viruses-can-travel-packshttps://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/traveling-together-in-packets-is-what-makes-some-viruses-so-infectioushttps://www.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/nih-researchers-discover-highly-infectious-vehicle-transmission-viruses-among-humanshttps://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-08-highly-infectious-vehicle-virus-transmission.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/14/3674625/3674625_86FE73B7A6CE4005BEDE7D14B84987E2_180814_3674625_Study_finds_stomach_viruses_cluster_together_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/B3F/BA1/B3FBA146EF0E489B833678789F3BFE60_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, science, stomach viruses, rotavirus, norovirus, stomach illness, vaccine, antiviral drugs, virus clusters, virus, individual viruses, virus infections, vesicles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3675377</guid>
      <title>Increase in number of La Crosse Encephalitis infection cases in U.S. children</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A woman is making the plight of her 6-year-old son public as a warning to other parents after he contracted La Crosse encephalitis from a mosquito bite, reports USA Today.In a post on social media, LoriAnne Surrett talks about how Noah, her son, had to spend six weeks at the hospital to fight the virus.A person contracts La Crosse encephalitis when they are bitten by an infected mosquito. The virus can cause inflammation of the brain as fluids build up. According to the CDC, symptoms usually take up to one to two weeks to show up and may include fever and headaches. In more severe cases, symptoms may also include nausea, vomiting, even seizures. The CDC says the most effective way to reduce the chance of being infected with the virus is to use insect repellents which contain DEET, Picaridin or other similar ingredients.The CDC also says there is no specific treatment for La Crosse encephalitis as antibiotics aren’t effective against the virus.However if the illness is severe, it may be treated with supportive therapy, IV fluids along with respiratory support, which is how Noah was treated.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/18/08/15/3675376/3675376_DF183B87491545A792F63FC81C0CFCA3_180815_3675376_Increase_in_number_of_La_Crosse_Encephalitis_inf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/1D0/2F2/1D02F2877CE54687884AC71E44D591DA_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,Education,Educational,virus,mosquito bite,La Crosse encephalitis,inflammation of brain,infected mosquito,insect repellents,DEET,Picaridin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676506</guid>
      <title>Study finds vaping can damage immune system cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVaping can harm important immune system cells, according to a new study. Researchers from the University of Birmingham found e-cigarette vapor disabled vital immune cells in the lungs and increased inflammation, the BBC reported. The small scale study was led by Professor David Thickett, and the results published in the online journal Thorax. The experiment used a mechanical procedure to mimic vaping, using lung tissue samples from eight non-smokers. Scientists found the vapor caused inflammation and negatively affected alveolar macrophages, cells that remove harmful dust particles, bacteria and allergens. Changes in the lung tissue occurred over 48 hours, however the group advise that further research is needed to understand long-term health complications from vaping. Thickett said while e-cigarettes may be safer than traditional cigarettes, they could still be harmful if used long-term. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Person vaping with an e-cigarette2. Lung tissue samples being taken from a non-smoker3. Vapor can negatively affect alveolar macrophages, which remove dust, bacteria and allergens4. Changes in lung tissue occurred over 48 hoursVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the University of Birmingham found e-cigarette vapor disabled vital immune cells in the lungs and increased inflammation.""The experiment used a mechanical procedure to mimic vaping, using lung tissue samples from eight non-smokers." "Scientists found the vapor caused inflammation and negatively affected alveolar macrophages, cells that remove harmful dust particles, bacteria and allergens." "Changes in the lung tissue occurred over 48 hours, however the group advise that further research is needed to understand long-term health complications from vaping." SOURCES: BBC https://www.bbc.com/news/health-45170756***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/16/3676506/3676506_8818F9BAD4D64930884AE006E8458AEB_180816_3676506_Study_finds_vaping_can_damage_immune_system_cell_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/7BF/D5E/7BFD5E677E1649B8872B01A73CCBF3D5_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, vaping, vaping immune system, e-cigarettes, vaping health risks, e-cigs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677345</guid>
      <title>Measles cases on the rise across the country</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to the CDC, there has been an increase of measles cases this year.Measles includes symptoms such as high fever, red eyes, and a rash that begins on the face.The CDC says the virus is contagious as it stays in the airspace when someone with measles has coughed or sneezed. Ninety percent of the people who are not immune to the virus will likely become infected.They also recommend getting the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine to prevent outbreaks.Measles is especially unsafe for children under the age of 5 or adults over the age of 20.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Person getting measles spots and measles cases chart 2. Measles symptoms3. Measles virus spreading into the air from sneezing4. MMR vaccine and someone receiving vaccinationVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the CDC, there has been an increase of measles cases this year.""Measles includes symptoms such as high fever, red eyes, and a rash that begins on the face.""The CDC says the virus is contagious as it stays in the airspace when someone with measles has coughed or sneezed. Ninety percent of the people who aren't immune to the virus will likely become infected.""They also recommend getting the measles, mumps, and rubella vaccine to prevent outbreaks."SOURCES: AL.com. ABC, CDC, Fox News, NOLA, Fox 59, The Economisthttps://www.al.com/news/index.ssf/2018/08/measles_outbreak_hits_21_state.htmlhttps://abc11.com/health/cdc-monitoring-measles-cases-in-21-states-including-north-carolina-/3957136/https://www.cdc.gov/measles/cases-outbreaks.htmlhttp://www.foxnews.com/health/2018/08/15/measles-reported-in-21-states-d-c-so-far-this-year-cdc-says.htmlhttps://www.nola.com/health/index.ssf/2018/08/measles_louisiana_health.htmlhttps://fox59.com/2018/08/15/measles-outbreak-hits-more-than-100-people-in-21-states-including-indiana/https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2018/08/15/what-populists-and-anti-vaxxers-have-in-common***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 12:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/17/3677345/3677345_CE9806A258F8423F85264815463674B7_180817_3677345_Measles_cases_on_the_rise_across_the_country_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/5B7/7A5/5B77A5B7D4CF455E88B0C6F5942E6543_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Measles, Measles outbreak, vaccination, measles symptoms, Virus,  MMR vaccine, measles vaccine, measles virus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677272</guid>
      <title>Woman's lost contact lens found embedded in eyelid after 28 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDecades after losing her contact lens, a woman finally found it embedded in her eyelid 28 years later.CNN reports that a 42-year-old British woman noticed a slight swelling over her left eye that became large and painful in a span of six months, prompting her to see a specialist.Doctors conducted an MRI and discovered a small 6-millimeter cyst embedded in her eyelid.When the cyst was surgically removed, it broke open to reveal a hard contact lens inside, even though the patient had not worn any for 28 years.Her mother later recalled that the woman got hit in the left eye with a shuttlecock as a teen. The rigid contact she was wearing was assumed lost, but had apparently remained in her eyelid for 28 years.It's still unknown why the swelling and inflammation happened nearly three decades after the incident. The woman's left eyelid had been droopy for a long time, but had no other symptoms indicative of a trapped contact lens. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Slight swelling  above eye growing into painful lump2. MRI scan revealing cyst on eyelid3. Hard contact lens being found inside cyst4. Contact lens being stuck in eyelid after badminton accidentVOICEOVER (in English): "A 42-year-old British woman noticed a slight swelling over her left eye that became large and painful in a span of six months, prompting her to see a specialist.""Doctors conducted an MRI and discovered a small 6-millimeter cyst embedded in her eyelid.""When the cyst was surgically removed, it broke open to reveal a hard contact lens inside, even though the patient had not worn any for 28 years.""Her mother later recalled that the woman got hit in the left eye with a shuttlecock as a teen. The rigid contact she was wearing was assumed lost, but had apparently stayed in the eyelid for 28 years."SOURCES: CNN, BMJ Case Reportshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/15/health/contact-lens-eyelid-study/index.htmlhttp://casereports.bmj.com/content/2018/bcr-2018-225767.fullv***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 11:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/17/3677272/3677272_110F6E17D0274E08AA4D96615AB935F8_180817_3677272_Woman_s_lost_contact_lens_found_embedded_in_eyel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/4AF/B8F/4AFB8FB0671C465AB4FA78900D67504A_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  contact lens, lost contact lens, cyst, eye cyst, swollen eyelid, droopy eyelid, contact lens in eye, contact lens mishap]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677182</guid>
      <title>'Zombie gene' protects elephants from cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANElephants rarely get cancer, and scientists may have finally figured out why.According to research from the University of Chicago, over 17 percent of people worldwide die from cancer, compared to less than 5 percent for elephants, even though they have 100 times as many potentially cancerous cells.One reason for this is they have over 20 copies of the tumor suppressor gene p53 that stops DNA damage from turning into cancer, while humans and other animals only have one.Because the cells died as soon as damage was detected, there is zero risk of them ever becoming cancerous.The study found that p53 can also trigger an inactive pseudogene in elephants called LIF6 to come back to life. When cell damage is detected by p53, it activates the LIF6 gene, which in turn produces a protein that pokes holes in the target mitochondria and causes it to die.This genetic resistance to cancer is not just seen in elephants. Smaller critters like naked mole rats and grey squirrels also have mechanisms that keep them tumor-free.By studying how these animals' genes work, scientists are hoping to figure out how to prevent or treat cancer in humans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cancer mortality rates in humans and elephants2. Elephants having more copies of tumor suppressor gene p533. p53 reanimating inactive LIF6 pseudogene4. LIF6 gene triggering cell deathVOICEOVER (in English): "Over 17 percent of people worldwide die from cancer, compared to less than 5 percent for elephants, even though they have 100 times as many potentially cancerous cells.""One reason for this is they have over 20 copies of the tumor suppressor gene p53 that stops DNA damage from turning into cancer, while humans and other animals only have one.""A University of Chicago study found that p53 can also trigger an inactive pseudogene in elephants called LIF6 to come back to life.""When cell damage is detected by p53, it activates the LIF6 gene, which in turn produces a protein that pokes holes in the target mitochondria and causes it to die."SOURCES: University of Chicago, CNNhttps://news.uchicago.edu/story/zombie-gene-protects-elephants-against-cancerhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/14/health/elephant-cancer-zombie-genetics-study/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 10:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/17/3677182/3677182_DFB07011812240D4A4D1DE09B3DCDBA2_180817_3677182__Zombie_gene__protects_elephants_from_cancer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/13D/6C6/13D6C6EA3B304D47A6EE5D1949C38730_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, elephants, cancer, cancer research, zombie gene, why elephants don't have cancer, cancer mortality, tumor suppressor gene, p53, lif6]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676937</guid>
      <title>Blue light from digital devices damages eye cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research shows blue light from smartphones and tablets may be negatively affecting vision.Fortune reports that digital devices like phones or tablets are constantly exposing us to blue light, which cannot be blocked or reflected by the eye's cornea or lens.Photoreceptor cells in the retina rely on molecules called retinal to sense light and trigger the firing of signals to the brain. Simply put, it's what allows people to see.But a new study from the University of Toledo has found that exposing retinal to blue light causes a toxic reaction that kills photoreceptor cells, which are incapable of regenerating.When introduced into other cell types, the retinal molecule produced the same deadly reaction when exposed to blue light, but not with yellow, green, or red light.Alpha tocopherol, a form of vitamin E, was found to reduce cell damage. But as vitamin levels decrease with age, prolonged blue light exposure may lead to macular degeneration, a leading cause of blindness.Researchers advise wearing glasses that filter out UV and blue light to serve as eye protection, and to avoid looking at devices in the dark.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Blue light exposure from digital devices2. How photoreceptors and retinal work3. Blue light triggering toxicity in retinal4. Alpha tocopherol reducing photoreceptor cell damageVOICEOVER (in English): "Digital devices like phones or tablets are constantly exposing us to blue light, which cannot be blocked or reflected by the eye's cornea or lens.""Photoreceptor cells in the retina rely on molecules called retinal to sense light and trigger the firing of signals to the brain. Simply put, it's what allows people to see.""But a new study from the University of Toledo has found that exposing retinal to blue light causes a toxic reaction that kills photoreceptor cells, which are incapable of regenerating.""Alpha tocopherol, a form of vitamin E, was found to reduce cell damage. But as vitamin levels decrease with age, prolonged blue light exposure may lead to macular degeneration, a leading cause of blindness."SOURCES: University of Toledo, Forbeshttps://utnews.utoledo.edu/index.php/08_08_2018/ut-chemists-discover-how-blue-light-speeds-blindnesshttps://www.forbes.com/sites/fionamcmillan/2018/08/11/how-blue-light-damages-cells-in-your-eyes/#495d424c384b***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 06:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/17/3676937/3676937_E561790A2BBC42E189CD979F7C0831B0_180817_3676937_Blue_light_from_digital_devices_damages_eye_cell_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/563/C76/563C76AB858B49A4B0785E936089F68E_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, blue light, blindness, vision, blinding, blue light exposure, macular degeneration, digital devices, blue light filter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3678832</guid>
      <title>Woman who fell off cruise ship rescued after floating for 10 hours</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA British woman on a cruise ship in the Adriatic Sea fell into the water approximately 60 miles off the coast of Croatia and reportedly spent 10 hours treading water before being rescued. The 46-year-old, who some local media identified as Kay Longstaff, said, "I fell off the back of the Norwegian Star and I was in the water for 10 hours, so these wonderful guys rescued me," in an interview with Croatia's state television network HRT. According to the Washington Post, she declined to tell reporters how she fell off the cruise ship. The cruise company is expected to examine closed-circuit camera footage in order to determine the events leading up to the incident. The company said the woman went overboard as the ship was headed to Venice. The ship was stopped and a search mounted after crew realized someone had fallen overboard. Croatian navy and coast guard were also alerted. The navy used a PC-9 aircraft and a patrol boat. Kay was spotted around 9:40 p.m. in the sea and rescued five minutes later.  She was taken to a hospital in Pula, Croatia and is in stable condition.According to the Guardian, the incident is under investigation and the British embassy in Croatia has been informed. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Norwegian Star traveling to Venice2. Kay treading water for 10 hours3. Norwegian Star, Croatian navy and coast guard searching for Kay4. Kay being rescued from waterVOICEOVER (in English): "A British woman on a cruise ship in the Adriatic Sea fell into the water approximately 60 miles off the coast of Croatia as the ship was on its way to Venice and was rescued after almost half a day at sea." "The 46-year-old, who identified herself as Kay to local media, said she fell off the back of the Norwegian Star and then managed to stay afloat for 10 hours."  "After crew realized someone had fallen overboard, the ship was stopped and a search mounted. Croatian navy and coast guard were also alerted. The navy used a PC-9 aircraft and a patrol boat in the search."  "Kay was spotted around 9:40 p.m. in the sea and rescued five minutes later. She was taken to a hospital in Pula, Croatia and is in stable condition."SOURCES: Washington Post, Guardianhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2018/08/19/woman-says-she-fell-off-cruise-ship-spent-hours-adriatic-sea-before-she-was-rescued/?utm_term=.6361b36ebc32https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/19/british-woman-rescued-10-hours-adriatic-sea-cruise-ship-fall***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 12:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/20/3678832/3678832_94823A51DC744B7EABD584375FAB5AE9_180820_3678832_Woman_who_fell_off_cruise_ship_rescued_after_flo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/537/FEB/537FEB79C8EA4182AE2F71A6C4E51D22_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, woman falls off cruise ship, woman survives 10 hours at sea, cruise ship, cruise ship fall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679249</guid>
      <title>Eating certain vegetables can help prevent colon cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research from the Francis Crick Institute and Imperial College London is offering concrete evidence that eating certain veggies can not only keep the bowels healthy  it also protects from cancer.According to the study published in the journal Immunity, aryl hydrocarbon receptor or AhR is a protein that acts as an environmental sensor, protecting the gut from inflammatory responses to the bacteria that live in it.Scientists studied mice that couldn't produce AhR, finding that they developed gut inflammation, which progressed to colon cancer.The key to stimulating AhR is I3C or indole-3-carbinol, which is produced when vegetables from the Brassica genus like cabbage, broccoli, or kale, is digested.Mice that were fed a diet rich in I3C didn't develop inflammation or cancer. Those with cancer that were switched to the diet also ended up with fewer, more benign tumors.The team now wants to see if the veggies have the same effect on people. They're hoping to do further experiments in organoids made from biopsies of the human gut, and eventually go on to human trials.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of AhR protecting the gut from inflammation2. Depiction of mice with no AhR developing colon cancer3. Depiction of indole-3-carbinol found in vegetables of the Brassica genus4. Depiction of I3C rich diet reducing inflammation, cancerVOICEOVER (in English): "Aryl hydrocarbon receptor or AhR is a protein that acts as an environmental sensor, protecting the gut from inflammatory responses to the bacteria that live in it.""Scientists at the Francis Crick Institute and Imperial College London studied mice that couldn't produce AhR, finding that they developed gut inflammation, which progressed to colon cancer.""The key to stimulating AhR is I3C or indole-3-carbinol, which is produced when vegetables from the Brassica genus like cabbage, broccoli, or kale, is digested."Mice that were fed a diet rich in I3C didn't develop inflammation or cancer. Those with cancer that were switched to the diet also ended up with fewer, more benign tumors.SOURCES: Imperial College London, BBChttps://www.imperial.ac.uk/news/187692/broccoli-cabbage-kale-protect-against-colon/https://www.bbc.com/news/health-45171651***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 05:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/21/3679249/3679249_B16A420FF96F452C8025D8E2F347334D_180821_3679249_Eating_certain_vegetables_can_help_prevent_colon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/78B/FC0/78BFC00D630D44B7A0C3EFCFD80BB260_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, cancer, cancer research, anti cancer, cancer cure, cancer prevention, colon cancer, cabbage, vegetables, bowel cancer, superfood, healthy food]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679216</guid>
      <title>Flushing disposable contact lenses is adding to plastics pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study by Arizona State University found that people discarding their disposable contacts by flushing them could be contributing to plastics pollution. In the U.S., approximately 45 million people wear contacts. The study found around 15 to 20 percent of wearers don't dispose of their old lenses in waste containers, and instead flush them down toilets or sinks.    The study, presented at the National Meeting and Exposition of the American Chemical Society, estimates between 1.8 to 3.4 billion lenses get flushed per year, equaling 20 to 23 metric tons plastics waste. Because the contact lenses are made with stronger plastics, they do not break down when exposed to microbes while going through a sewage treatment plant.Researchers found that the old contacts instead become smaller pieces and are prevalent in wastewater sludge after sewage treatment. The sludge is then deposited on land where lenses can then be washed into lakes and rivers where they are then by fish, birds or other animals.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People flushing disposable lenses down the toilet2. Disposable contacts making it through a sewage treatment plant3. The lenses can be washed into lakes and rivers where they are consumed by wildlife4. People flushing disposable contactsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study by Arizona State University found that people flushing their disposable contacts could be contributing to plastics pollution. Of the around 45 million Americans who wear contacts, 15 to 20 percent discard their old lenses by flushing them down the toilet or sink." "Because the contact lenses are made with stronger plastics, they do not break down when exposed to microbes at a sewage treatment plant. Researchers found that the old contacts instead become smaller pieces and are prevalent in wastewater sludge after sewage treatment." "The sludge is then deposited on land where lenses can then be washed into lakes and rivers where they are consumed by fish, birds or other animals."   "The study, presented at the National Meeting and Exposition of the American Chemical Society, estimates between 1.8 - 3.4 billion lenses get flushed per year, equaling 20 - 23 metric tons plastics waste." SOURCES: Arizona State University, USA Today, BBChttps://asunow.asu.edu/20180819-discoveries-asu-scientists-1st-nationwide-study-environmental-costs-contact-lenseshttps://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2018/08/19/flushing-your-contact-lenses-down-drain-adding-plastic-waste-oceans/1020256002/https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-45222865***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 04:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/21/3679216/3679216_F4EC5341488846F1985CB270AAFB43EC_180821_3679216_Flushing_disposable_contact_lenses_is_adding_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/E29/0B1/E290B1283A9C441BAA6345C17E090AF8_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, disposable contacts, plastics pollution, microplastics, flushing disposable contacts, contact lenses]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679937</guid>
      <title>Large magma reservoir discovered beneath Long Valley supervolcano</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found a huge cache of magma hidden underneath one of the largest supervolcanoes in the world.Forbes reports that California's Long Valley supervolcano erupted some 760,000 years ago, spewing out hot ash, lava, and toxic gas for 6 days that resulted in the formation of a massive caldera.Since 1978, a gradual uplift has been observed in the caldera center, likely from magma flowing into a chamber below the supervolcano.Using seismic tomography, researchers from the USGS California Volcano Observatory were able to show a more detailed view of the subsurface, which they published in the journal Geology.They discovered that the reservoir beneath the supervolcano contained 240 cubic miles of semi-molten magma, 27% of which was in a liquid state.An eruption would require at least 50% of the magma to be liquid, so there is no immediate threat. However, when Long Valley does eventually erupt, it's likely going to be a massive catastrophe similar to the one from hundreds of thousands of years ago.Since scientists aren't be sure how magma is distributed within the reservoir, normal eruptions are also a possibility, so they're keeping a close eye on the caldera.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Long Valley supervolcano eruption 760,000 years ago2. Depiction of Long Valley caldera dome growing3. Depiction of seismic tomography revealing magma reservoir4. Depiction of 240 cubic miles of magma under Long Valley, with 27% in liquid formVOICEOVER (in English): "California's Long Valley supervolcano erupted some 760,000 years ago, spewing out hot ash, lava, and toxic gas for 6 days that resulted in the formation of a massive caldera.""Since 1978, a gradual uplift has been observed in the caldera center, likely from magma flowing into a chamber below the supervolcano.""Using seismic tomography, researchers from the USGS California Volcano Observatory were able to show a more detailed view of the subsurface.""They discovered that the reservoir beneath the supervolcano contained 240 cubic miles of semi-molten magma, 27% of which was in a liquid state."SOURCES: Geological Society of America, Forbeshttps://gsw.silverchair-cdn.com/gsw/Content_public/Journal/geology/PAP/10.1130_G45094.1/1/g45094.pdf?Expires=2147483647&Signature=lhUjQuLGQV5d7Wt~5G8~AAZvPOgi~PIxTs5SGeLDVct5H1nrX0t5iYr9LEoUA3dDR6s4hk5MumhOdJZGFcLiRhTlAAWDp~3IRR-jvrhLN7FqCR~svEHju~1bdKwYfpH2luSUh2SnIDzM0ppT~udf6dXr9mPsBX4x5GSuHL2mSPJsuj4qGy1z8ibC1qg5PzpM81f1wdrQ-ZndI7FI4uy45IF2wAobpcMLtFNeZWJUDmdbpQk8AQgm~-P1ca8PAK0k~kJx6-eL7jlo1N7tSWJhKxn6uzZl~gGFlW-pku2D0LoG5m1OtQSIJ-AcK6aFOiuyTETm0tpP-r4vHe8ZND4~WQ__&Key-Pair-Id=APKAIE5G5CRDK6RD3PGAhttps://www.forbes.com/sites/trevornace/2018/08/16/a-massive-240-cubic-miles-of-magma-was-just-discovered-beneath-californias-supervolcano/#48dc7bfe6cb9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 06:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/22/3679937/3679937_8EBF78A997B84BB68DAD675814BEC55D_180822_3679937_Large_magma_reservoir_discovered_beneath_Long_Va_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/2B3/460/2B3460AA53524FB09477FF461771DE6E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, supervolcano, volcano, magma, magma cache, magma reservoir, long valley supervolcano, long valley caldera, california supervolcano, volcanic eruption, lava, hot lava, pyroclastic flows]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679899</guid>
      <title>Minds social network moves to Ethereum, launches own token</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMinds, a blockchain based social network, has launched its own token to reward users for using the website in addition to moving the its network to Ethereum.According to Heavy.com, Minds is an encrypted, open-source Facebook clone that claims to focus on free speech.  Users on Mind.com will earn tokens for contributing to the site, according to Heavy.com. Tokens can also be purchased on the site. In addition, users will also be able to promote posts using tokens. Minds users can also use the tokens to tip channels or to pay for subscriptions.  Minds CEO Bill Ottman says the platform receives 500,000 daily pages views and has 1.25 million registered users. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Minds is releasing its own token and moving system to Ethereum2. Minds user getting rewarded tokens, user purchasing tokens3. Minds tokens can be used to promote, tip and subscribe on the network4. Minds page views and registered usersVOICEOVER (in English): "Minds, a blockchain based, encrypted, open-source Facebook clone that claims to focus on free speech has released its own token in addition to moving the entire network to Ethereum ahead of its official launch."    "According to Heavy.com, users on Mind.com will earn tokens for contributing to the site. Tokens can also be purchased on the site." "In addition, users will also be able to promote posts using tokens. Minds users can also use the tokens to tip channels or to pay for subscriptions."  "Minds CEO Bill Ottman says the platform receives 500,000 daily pages views and has 1.25 million registered users." SOURCES: Heavy, Coindeskhttps://heavy.com/tech/2018/08/minds-token/https://www.coindesk.com/blockchain-social-network-minds-is-migrating-to-ethereum-for-launch/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 05:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/22/3679899/3679899_EEB7866744D8405187058E92059D37F5_180822_3679899_Minds_social_network_moves_to_Ethereum__launches_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/980/314/980314B1324C4E0AA6DD00B6A5C920B6_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, cryptocurrency, digital currency, social media network, Minds social network, Ethereum]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679893</guid>
      <title>Using electric chopsticks to encourage healthy eating</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a study published in Food Research International, a team of scientists have designed cutlery which could help to alter the taste of food and help to cut down on the amount of salt we consume. Human beings have the tendency to eat a lot of salt because it makes food taste good, even though too much salt isn't good for the body, reports IEEE Spectrum.Nimesha Ranasinghe, assistant professor at the University of Maine and director of the Multisensory Interactive Media Lab, came up with the idea of using utensils such as chopsticks and soup bowls to transmit the salty flavor to the tongue.Ranasinghe said he experimented with the amplitude, the frequency and with the placement of electrodes on different utensils.He designed a pair of chopsticks with electrodes embedded in the tips of the chopstick which would send taste sensations to the tongue once turned on.Ranasinghe said recent research shows all the regions of the tongue can detect all five taste senses, reports IEEE Spectrum.He told Newsweek the technology would be able to simulate different flavors such as sourness, saltiness, and bitterness with around 70 percent accuracy.The scientist has also experimented with different objects such as flavor-enhancing water bottles, straws, spoons, and even an Internet-connected cocktail glass aka a "vocktail."He admits the technology is still in its beginning stages, however he has hope that " ... one day virtual flavors will burst onto the tongue … "RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A pair of electric chopsticks as well as an electric soup bowl.2. The electric chopstick and how it works.3. The taste buds scattered around the tongue.4. Percentage of how accurately the product works.VOICEOVER (in English): "Nimesha Ranasinghe came up with the idea of using utensils such as chopsticks and soup bowls to transmit the salty flavor to the tongue.""He designed a pair of chopsticks with electrodes embedded in the tips of the chopstick which would send taste sensations to the tongue once turned on.""IEEE Spectrum reports Ranasinghe said recent research shows all the regions of the tongue can detect all five taste senses.""He told Newsweek the technology would be able to simulate different flavors such as sourness, saltiness, and bitterness with around 70 percent accuracy."SOURCES: Spectrum IEEE, Sciencedirect, Telegraph, Newsweek, Smithsonian.com, Digital Trends, The Sunhttps://spectrum.ieee.org/the-human-os/biomedical/devices/hacking-the-flavor-of-food-with-electric-chopsticks-and-soup-bowlshttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0963996918303983https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/12/want-make-takeaways-healthy-give-electric-shock-experts-say/https://www.newsweek.com/chopsticks-make-food-salty-shooting-electricity-tongue-developed-scientists-1070122https://www.smithsonianmag.com/innovation/using-electric-currents-to-fool-ourselves-into-tasting-something-were-not-180970005/https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/smart-chopsticks-zap-your-tongue/https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6989887/electric-cutlery-fight-obesity/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/22/3679893/3679893_0609FE56708440619DBA0151CCE92243_180822_3679893_Using_electric_chopsticks_to_encourage_healthy_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9B6/6D1/9B66D18CB21749A28C7AB2BEDFBE6F40_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, food, food flavors, electric chopsticks, electric taste augmentation, electrodes, simulated flavors, technology, taste sensation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681946</guid>
      <title>Iran found spreading misinformation online</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook released a statement saying they have removed hundreds of accounts and pages after they were found spreading misinformation on the social networking site.Facebook says FireEye, a cybersecurity firm, alerted them about the Iranian accounts and pages.The Iranian efforts date back to 2011 and involved Facebook and Instagram.It eventually expanded to Twitter and Youtube as well, reports The Washington Post.Facebook says it removed a total of 652 pages, accounts, and groups which were linked to Iran.Facebook claims some of the accounts were linked to Iran's state-owned media.Apparently, the fake Iranian accounts used Facebook to organize events and purchase ads on the website.The accounts included themes such as "anti-Saudi, anti-Israeli, and pro-Palestinians." They also seemed to advocate policies that were favorable to Iran.Twitter said it had removed 284 accounts for "coordinated manipulation," saying the accounts appeared to have originated from Iran.According to reports from The Independent, the fake accounts were found to target users specifically in the US, UK, Latin America and the Middle East.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. We see the Iranian flag as well as different websites such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and Youtube.2. We see the homepage on Facebook, 652 was written to represent the amount of pages removed. 3. A depiction of how the Iranians spread information online through purchasing ads and creating events.4. We see a Twitter page, 284 was written to represent the amount of pages removed on the website. VOICEOVER (in English): "The Washington Post reports the Iranian efforts to spread misinformation date back to 2011 and involved Facebook and Instagram.It eventually expanded to Twitter and Youtube as well.""Facebook says it removed a total of 652 pages, accounts, and groups which were linked to Iran.""Apparently, the fake Iranian accounts used Facebook to organize events and purchase ads on the website.""Twitter said it had removed 284 accounts for 'coordinated manipulation,' saying the accounts appeared to have originated from Iran."SOURCES: The Independent, The Washington Post, Newsroom Facebook, Reuters, CNN, Bloomberghttps://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/facebook-twitter-google-misinformation-campaign-latest-iran-russia-a8502146.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2018/08/21/russian-iran-created-facebook-pages-groups-accounts-mislead-users-around-world-company-says/?utm_term=.835e90c2b4dbhttps://newsroom.fb.com/news/2018/08/more-coordinated-inauthentic-behavior/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-russia-usa/facebook-twitter-dismantle-disinformation-campaigns-tied-to-iran-and-russia-idUSKCN1L62FDhttps://money.cnn.com/2018/08/21/technology/facebook-disinformation-iran-russia/index.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-08-21/facebook-says-it-removed-influence-campaigns-from-iran-russia***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/24/3681946/3681946_B1ABED85F2E54C2CBDD7070388BAED9C_180824_3681946_Iran_found_spreading_misinformation_online_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/583/03B/58303B754A6F4348B9C6499538FED2D8_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Iran, misinformation, global misinformation operation, Iranian influence, disinformation, disinformation campaigns, social media, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Youtube, fake accounts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681693</guid>
      <title>Facebook to rate its users based on trustworthiness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook has started giving scores based on trustworthiness of users on the social media site.According to The Washington Post,  Facebook has developed the ratings system over the past year and would be used to assign users a score from zero to one.Facebook has not disclosed what criteria they use to determine a user's scores, or whether the scores are used in any other way.Facebook claims the system was created in an effort to combat fake news.Facebook has given the option to allow users to report or flag problematic content on the site.However, they have discovered that some people were falsely reporting content just because they didn't agree with it.A spokeswoman from Facebook told The BBC, they are doing this to ensure the "fight against misinformation is as effective as possible."Users apparently have no way of knowing what their rating is, at least for now.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Facebook logo and a vertical bar graph showing user scores.2. The Facebook homepage appears and different posts on the social media site are shown along with an example of "fake news."3. The process of reporting a story on Facebook is shown.4. Showing different content that were reported on the site.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Washington Post,  Facebook has developed the ratings system over the past year and would be used to assign users a score from zero to one.""Facebook claims the system was created in an effort to combat fake news.""Facebook has given the option to allow users to report or flag problematic content on the site.""However, they have discovered that some people were falsely reporting content just because they didn't agree with it."SOURCES: The Washington Post, The BBC, Reuters, CNET, The Verge, https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2018/08/21/facebook-is-rating-trustworthiness-its-users-scale-zero-one/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.c9627d4f2445https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-45257894https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-ratings/facebook-moves-to-rate-users-on-trustworthiness-report-idUSKCN1L61IMhttps://www.cnet.com/au/news/facebook-is-reportedly-rating-your-trustworthiness/https://www.theverge.com/2018/8/21/17763886/facebook-trust-ratings-fake-news-reporting-score***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 07:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/24/3681693/3681693_A32F61E8B5F741D2B6B972F1785B0C7F_180824_3681693_Facebook_to_rate_its_users_based_on_trustworthin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/EC5/377/EC5377F5570A4DD199118C9F49093C98_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Facebook, facebook users, rating users, social media, ratings system, misinformation, content, scores, surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681498</guid>
      <title>Heat shield installed on the Orion Spacecraft</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to reports from NASA, an uncrewed Orion spacecraft will be launched during the Exploration Mission-1, beginning a three week trip to space.NASA's Orion spacecraft is 16.5 feet in diameter, one of the largest of its kind.The base structure of the heat shield has titanium truss covered with layers of carbon fiber material known as composite substrate.Large blocks of Avcoat, an ablative material, were then bonded onto the shield's surface.Avcoat has been used in the past in Apollo's heat shields and the Orion Exploration Flight Test-1. However, this time blocks were used instead of the usual injecting method.The Orion spacecraft would be taken 40,000 miles beyond the moon and back to Earth.As the spacecraft re enters Earth's atmosphere, it would need to withstand temperatures of upto 5,000 degrees Fahrenheit. This is when the ablative material will wear away, and prevent heat from being transferred to the rest of the spacecraft.The NASA engineers plan to monitor how the Orion performs in outer space and if it works well, it may soon carry astronauts into space destinations such as the Moon and Mars.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The heatshield of the Orion Spacecraft is shown, as well as its base.2. Avcoat blocks being added onto the heatshield of the Orion Spacecraft.3. The Orion Spacecraft is seen travelling in space with the heat shield.4. The Spacecraft is seen entering Earth's atmosphere.VOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Orion spacecraft is 16.5 feet in diameter, one of the largest of its kind.The base structure of the heat shield has titanium truss covered with layers of carbon fiber material known as composite substrate.""Large blocks of Avcoat, an ablative material, were then bonded onto the shield's surface.""The Orion spacecraft would be taken 40,000 miles beyond the moon and back to Earth.""As the spacecraft re enters Earth's atmosphere, it would need to withstand temperatures of up to 5,000 degrees Fahrenheit. This is when the ablative material will wear away, and prevent heat from being transferred to the rest of the spacecraft."SOURCES: Space Coast Daily, NASA, Phys.orghttp://spacecoastdaily.com/2018/08/heat-shield-install-at-kennedy-space-center-brings-orion-spacecraft-closer-to-space/https://www.nasa.gov/feature/heat-shield-install-brings-orion-spacecraft-closer-to-spacehttps://phys.org/news/2013-12-shield-nasa-orion-spacecraft-kennedy.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 02:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/24/3681498/3681498_26FE5D91FEA34C64AEA3D799FE801561_180824_3681498_Heat_shield_installed_on_the_Orion_Spacecraft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/2A2/968/2A29689155D04B1CBF7BB9952B8DFFE5_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Space, Outer space, NASA, heat shield,spacecraft, Orion Spacecraft, NASA Orion Spacecraft, Orion NASA, astronauts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683640</guid>
      <title>Chagas disease spread by bite of a kissing bug on the rise in the US</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a statement from the American Heart Association, Chagas disease has been spreading from Central and South America to the U.S.Chagas disease is spread by a bug called the Triatomine bug, also known as the kissing bug, which carries a parasite called Trypanosoma cruzi.According to the CDC, the kissing bug gets infected by biting an infected animal or person.After getting infected, the bug carries the parasite in its feces.The infected bug then bites humans around the eyes or mouth, breaking into the skin.Initial symptoms of Chagas disease include fever, body aches, headaches, rashes etc, however the American Heart Association released a warning saying around 60- 70 percent of people do not develop any symptoms of the disease.According to the CDC, the infection may result in cardiac complications or intestinal complications for some.The disease can only be treated with anti-trypanosomal medication.It also does not spread from person to person or contact with animals.The American Heart Association released a statement to increase global awareness of the disease in hopes of detecting the disease at an early stage.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Triatomine bug is shown along with the parasite Trypanosoma cruzi.2. The infected bug biting the eyes and lips.3. Symptoms of Chagas disease.4. Anti-trypanosomal medication to treat the disease is shown.VOICEOVER (in English): "Chagas disease is spread by a bug called the Triatomine bug, also known as the kissing bug, which carries a parasite called Trypanosoma cruzi.""The infected bug then bites humans around the eyes or mouth, breaking into the skin.""Initial symptoms of Chagas disease include fever, body aches, headaches, rashes etc, however the American Heart Association released a warning saying around 60- 70 percent of people do not develop any symptoms of the disease.""The disease can only be treated with anti-trypanosomal medication."SOURCES: ABC News, CDC, American Heart Association, Forbes, Fox News,https://abcnews.go.com/Health/small-bugs-big-problems-insects-bite-lead-heart/story?id=57411091https://www.cdc.gov/parasites/chagas/gen_info/detailed.htmlhttps://newsroom.heart.org/news/chagas-disease-caused-by-a-parasite-has-spread-outside-of-latin-america-and-carries-a-high-risk-of-heart-disease?preview=1484https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/08/24/kissing-bugs-how-you-can-get-heart-disease-from-a-bite/#71f3f48752adhttp://www.foxnews.com/health/2018/08/24/blood-sucking-kissing-bugs-spreading-dangerous-parasitic-disease-in-us-health-officials-warn.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 13:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683640/3683640_48F97DD17B6F49E2ACD54376ACD0F2C5_180827_3683640_Chagas_disease_spread_by_bite_of_a_kissing_bug_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/AD0/EFA/AD0EFAC5EDE9473EB8BDEF4B0D03677A_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Kissing bug disease, Triatomine bug, Chagas disease, Chagas disease symptoms, disease, Trypanosoma cruzi parasite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683547</guid>
      <title>What is glioblastoma, the brain cancer that killed John McCain?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArizona Senator John McCain died Saturday from an aggressive form of brain cancer, glioblastoma. According to the American Brain Tumor Association, glioblastomas are brain tumors that appear in astrocytes, star-shaped cells that make up the supportive tissue of the brain. Glioblastomas are highly malignant and reproduce rapidly, and are supported by a large network of blood vessels in the brain. They rarely spread to other parts of the body. They are usually found in the cerebral hemispheres of the brain, but can appear anywhere in the brain or spinal cord. According to Popular Science, symptoms can range from general neurologic symptoms, such as headaches or seizures, to specific areas of the brain, like speech difficulty, weakness on one side of the body, or double vision.Glioblastoma is normally diagnosed through brain imagery and then surgery. Treatment includes surgery to remove as much of the tumor as possible, then radiation and chemotherapy.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Glioblastoma tumor2. Cross section of glioblastoma tumor3. Glioblastoma symptoms4. Glioblastoma treatmentVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the American Brain Tumor Association, glioblastomas are brain tumors that appear in astrocytes, star-shaped cells that make up the supportive tissue of the brain.""Glioblastomas are highly malignant and reproduce rapidly, and are supported by a large network of blood vessels. They are usually found in the cerebral hemispheres of the brain, but can appear anywhere in the brain or spinal cord." "According to Popular Science, symptoms can range from general neurologic symptoms, such as headaches or seizures, to specific areas of the brain, like speech difficulty, weakness on one side of the body, or double vision.""Glioblastoma is normally diagnosed through brain imagery and then surgery. Treatment includes surgery to remove as much of the tumor as possible, then radiation and chemotherapy."  SOURCES: Popular Science, ABC 7, American Brain Tumor Associationhttps://www.popsci.com/what-is-glioblastomahttps://abc7chicago.com/health/glioblastoma-more-about-the-brain-cancer-that-afflicted-john-mccain/4050146/https://www.abta.org/tumor_types/glioblastoma-gbm/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 11:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683547/3683547_EE27B27DB71449BC80C33AF8B75A3BFA_180827_3683547_What_is_glioblastoma__the_brain_cancer_that_kill_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/57C/C45/57CC452D28AB45D49569772907B06B45_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, brain cancer, brain tumor, glioblastoma, Senator John McCain]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683369</guid>
      <title>NASA launches laser to scan Earth's polar ice caps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA says it plans to launch an advanced laser instrument which would be used to monitor our planet's melting polar ice.NASA's new laser  Ice, Cloud and land Elevation Satellite-2 (ICESat-2)  would have the ability to collect more than 250 times the height measurements of polar ice compared to its predecessor.The laser also uses a new system called Advanced Topographic Laser Altimeter System (ATLAS), which would enable it send six beams of green light to the ground and to fire 10,000 times each second.The laser would also have the ability to measure ice on Greenland and Antarctica "within the width of a pencil," by capturing 60,000 measurements each second.It would also be able to time how long it takes for light photons in the green light to travel to and from Earth.NASA says ICESat-2 will get a more detailed view of the ice surface as it circles the Earth from pole to pole, measuring ice heights along the way four times a year.NASA says the mission is scheduled to last for three years and hopes this new technology will bring about new data about our planet's melting ice and how its changing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The ICESat-2 laser is shown, it is also shown collecting height measurements of ice caps.2. The ICESat-2 laser is shown shooting green beams.3. The ICESat-2 laser is shown in space measuring ice in Greenland and Antarctica.4. The ICESat-2 laser is shown in space measuring ice in the polar caps in a detailed way.VOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's new laser, ICESat-2, would have the ability to collect more than 250 times the height measurements of polar ice compared to its predecessor.""The laser also uses a new system called ATLAS, which would enable it send six beams of green light to the ground and to fire 10,000 times each second." "The laser would also have the ability to measure ice on Greenland and Antarctica 'within the width of a pencil,' by capturing 60,000 measurements each second." "NASA says ICESat-2 will get a more detailed view of the ice surface as it circles the Earth from pole to pole, measuring ice heights along the way four times a year."SOURCES: NASA, Space, Phys.org https://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-launching-advanced-laser-to-measure-earth-s-changing-icehttps://www.space.com/41596-nasa-icesat2-earth-ice-satellite-september-launch.htmlhttps://phys.org/news/2018-08-nasa-advanced-laser-earth-ice.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 07:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683369/3683369_5F4F435A177B4249832616BA2BC67157_180827_3683369_NASA_launches_laser_to_scan_Earth_s_polar_ice_ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FAE/EAE/FAEEAE53646E45929D52E6F8592E8239_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  NASA, space laser, ice, polar caps, antarctica, greenland, ICESat-2, ATLAS, Earth, melting ice caps, polar ice, polar ice caps melting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683343</guid>
      <title>Stratolaunch unveils new rocket lineup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe makers of the world's largest plane have recently unveiled exactly how it plans to deploy satellites into orbit.According to a Stratolaunch Systems press release, its planned lineup of launch vehicles includes the Pegasus rocket, two medium-lift rockets, and a space plane.The small-payload Pegasus XL has a 370-kilogram capacity for either single or triple configuration.The Medium Launch Vehicle, or MLV, has a capacity of 3,400 kilograms. A three-core variant called the MLV-Heavy is being developed to carry nearly twice as much.The reusable space plane, codenamed 'Black Ice', is presently just a design study. It's meant to carry cargo to and from Earth, though a follow-on variant will be crew-capable.Rather than blasting off a launchpad, the rockets will be tethered to a massive twin-fuselage carrier, which boasts a wingspan of 385 feet. Once the plane gets to an altitude of 35,000 feet, the rockets drop and blast off into orbit.So far, the main aircraft carrier has done a taxi test, but has yet to go up in the air. It will also need to be tested and fitted for the rockets.Assuming everything goes smoothly for Stratolaunch, the first Pegasus rocket is set to launch by 2020, followed by the MLV in 2022.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Stratolaunch rocket lineup2. Depiction of Pegasus XL3. Depiction of MLV and MLV-H4. Depiction of reusable space plane5. Depiction of rocket tethered to plane belly6.Depiction of rocket dropped at 35,000 feetVOICEOVER (in English): "Stratolaunch's planned lineup of launch vehicles includes the Pegasus rocket, two medium-lift rockets, and a space plane.""The small-payload Pegasus XL has a 370-kilogram capacity for either single or triple configuration.""The Medium Launch Vehicle, or MLV, has a capacity of 3,400 kilograms. A three-core variant called the MLV-Heavy is being developed to carry nearly twice as much.""The reusable space plane, codenamed 'Black Ice', is presently just a design study. It's meant to carry cargo to and from Earth, though a follow-on variant will be crew-capable."SOURCES: Stratolaunch, Spacehttps://www.stratolaunch.com/2018/08/20/stratolaunch-announces-new-launch-vehicles/https://www.space.com/41548-stratolaunch-rocket-family-space-plane-revealed.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 07:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683343/3683343_B95729CF408D43A8BB0687B0D49E98DC_180827_3683343_Stratolaunch_unveils_new_rocket_lineup_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/079/C07/079C07A14FAE49219C0B3B9241DED43F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, stratolaunch, world's biggest plane, world's largest plane, rocket, launch vehicle, air launch, space orbit, rocket fleet, launch vehicle, pegasus xl, mlv, mlv-h, space plane, black ice]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683290</guid>
      <title>Electron-ion collider project could reveal atomic nuclei mysteries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. National Academies of Sciences, Engineering and Medicine has endorsed the development of a multi-million-dollar particle accelerator project.According to MIT News, the electron-ion collider will consist of two intersecting accelerators  one blasting a beam of electrons and the other a beam of protons or ions to nearly the speed of light.The beams are made to collide at intersecting points, which are surrounded by detectors to record the resulting interaction.Each collision generates virtual photons, particles of light that penetrate through the proton or nucleus to tease out the structure within, including the distribution of quarks and gluons.The proposed machine would be able to help physicists understand where the mass of a proton comes from, how it gets its spin, and how gluons work.Science Magazine reports that two facilities have submitted proposals to host the EIC. Brookhaven National Laboratory in Upton, New York has a proton accelerator, but no electron ring, while the Jefferson Lab in Newport News, Virginia has the electron accelerator, but will need a proton ring.The Department of Energy is currently building a $730 million facility for rare isotope beams and may not be able to fund the proposed collider until after 2020. So for now, the two labs are collaborating on research and development.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of intersecting accelerators blasting beams of electrons and ions2. Depiction of electrons and ions colliding at intersection points3. Depiction of collision teasing out internal structure 4. Depiction of two different proposals to assemble electron-ion colliderVOICEOVER (in English): "The electron-ion collider will consist of two intersecting accelerators  one blasting a beam of electrons and the other a beam of protons or ions to nearly the speed of light.""The beams are made to collide at intersecting points, which are surrounded by detectors to record the resulting interaction.""Each collision generates virtual photons, particles of light that penetrate through the proton or nucleus to tease out the structure within, including the distribution of quarks and gluons.""Two facilities have submitted proposals to host the EIC. Brookhaven National Laboratory has a proton accelerator, but no electron ring, while Jefferson Lab has the electron accelerator, but will need a proton ring."SOURCES: MIT News, Science Magazine, Jefferson Lab, Brookhaven National Laboratoryhttp://news.mit.edu/2018/3q-richard-milner-new-us-particle-accelerator-0724http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/07/scientists-endorse-billion-dollar-collider-look-inside-protons-and-neutronshttps://www.jlab.org/jleic/https://www.bnl.gov/eic/erhic.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 05:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683290/3683290_51F78B9311624171B23E2663F04F2562_180827_3683290_Electron_ion_collider_project_could_reveal_atomi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BED/E8B/BEDE8B645A304AE999A409C76B85074A_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, electron ion collider, EIC, particle accelerator, electron beam, protons, proton parts, electrons, proton mass, spin, physics, nuclear physics, jefferson lab, brookhaven national laboratory]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683279</guid>
      <title>Ancient Neanderthal-Denisovan hybrid discovered in Siberian cave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found concrete evidence of interbreeding between different species of early humans.In 2012, a bone fragment from a teenage girl who died some 90,000 years ago was recovered from the Denisova cave in Siberia's Altai Mountains, according to a new study published in Nature.Analysis of the genome conducted at the Max Planck Institute for Evolutionary Anthropology revealed that the girl was a hybrid  her mother was a Neanderthal while her father was Denisovan.Denisovans are a hominin group distinct from Neanderthals and modern humans. Only a few of their bone fragments have been found, so their appearance and behavior remain a mystery.Researchers did find that this particular Denisovan had some Neanderthal ancestry, while the mother was genetically closer to Neanderthals in western Europe than to one who had lived in the cave earlier.Scientists knew from looking at the genetic patterns of ancient humans and homo sapiens that the different groups mated with each other, but the findings mark the first time a first-generation offspring of these pairings has been found.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of bone shard belonging to ancient teenage girl found in Siberian cave2. Depiction of girl's half-Neanderthal, half-Denisovan lineage3. Depiction of Denisovans4. Depiction of Neanderthal mother and Denisovan father's ancestryVOICEOVER (in English): "In 2012, a bone fragment from a teenage girl who died some 90,000 years ago was recovered from the Denisova cave in Siberia's Altai Mountains.""Analysis of the genome reveals that the girl was a hybrid  her mother was a Neanderthal while her father was Denisovan.""Denisovans are a hominin group distinct from Neanderthals and modern humans. Only a few of their bone fragments have been found, so their appearance and behavior remain a mystery.""Researchers did find that this particular Denisovan had some Neanderthal ancestry, while the mother was genetically closer to Neanderthals in western Europe than to one who had lived in the cave earlier."SOURCES: Nature, Max Planck Institute for Evolutionary Anthropologyhttps://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-06004-0https://www.mpg.de/12208106/neandertals-denisovans-daughter***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 05:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683279/3683279_397684C92CD94E5D8D7B4F591BB8D8A8_180827_3683279_Ancient_Neanderthal_Denisovan_hybrid_discovered__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/ACB/555/ACB55571B7BA4A6089E34B1600723731_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, human hybrid, ancient human, interbreeding, neanderthal, denisovan, neanderthal denisovan hybrid, denisova cave, ancient teen]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683257</guid>
      <title>Rare flesh-eating sexually transmitted disease found in UK</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA rare sexually transmitted disease which causes the genitals to break out into flesh eating ulcers has been found in the UK for the first time, reports The Lancashire Post.The STI is called Donovanosis, and is usually found in tropical regions such as southeast India, Guyana and New Guinea.The infection usually occurs in the genital area, however it could also appear around the nose, mouth, and chest.If a person goes without treatment, the ulcers could increase in size.Shamir Patel, a pharmacist,  told Liverpool Echo, that antibiotics could potentially be used to treat the disease.He said the STI is a "rare and nasty condition" which causes lesions and skin disintegration as the flesh basically eats itself and "literally rot away."However, he said the disease is going untreated in the early stages due to to it being so uncommon in the UK.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The disease Donovanosis appears and the areas where it usually is found is shown on a map.2. The area where the infection usually occurs is shown.3. The ulcers are shown and the infection increasing in size.4. Antibiotics are shown treating the infection.VOICEOVER (in English): "The STI is called Donovanosis, and is usually found in tropical regions such as southeast India, Guyana and New Guinea.""The infection usually occurs in the genital area, however it could also appear around the nose, mouth, and chest.""If a person goes without treatment, the ulcers could increase in size.""Shamir Patel, a pharmacist,  told Liverpool Echo, that antibiotics could potentially be used to treat the disease."SOURCES: Somersetlive, Liverpool Echo, Lancashire Post, https://www.somersetlive.co.uk/news/somerset-news/flesh-eating-sti-causes-flesh-1925934https://www.liverpoolecho.co.uk/news/liverpool-news/rare-sti-causes-flesh-eating-15055923?_ga=2.148268983.1422363005.1535077975-982006934.1528784145https://www.lep.co.uk/news/health/rare-sti-which-causes-genitals-to-erupt-into-flesh-eating-ulcers-diagnosed-in-southport-1-9313588***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 04:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683257/3683257_3552FCEE35B2432C80E8A1F600293643_180827_3683257_Rare_flesh_eating_sexually_transmitted_disease_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/692/E30/692E3009BBD94D4482C9A832ABE989D8_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, STI, STD, ulcers, flesh-eating ulcers, UK, STD symptoms, sexually transmitted disease, disease, genitals, infection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683174</guid>
      <title>Drug tunnel found under former fast food restaurant between Arizona and Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAuthorities in Arizona discovered a nearly 600-foot long drug tunnel running between a former fast food restaurant and a private residence in Mexico. According to KGUN, suspect Jesus Ivan Lopez Garcia was pulled over on August 13 after police saw him loading several plastic containers into a trailer outside of an old Kentucky Fried Chicken restaurant. Lopez was found to be in possession of 239 packages of various narcotics, including 261 pounds of methamphetamine, 14 pounds of cocaine, 30 pounds of white heroin, 13.7 bounds of brown heroin and 6.8 pounds of fentanyl. Police say the total street value of the drugs was over $1 million.    After obtaining a search warrant, agents searched Lopez's home and the old KFC and found the entrance to the tunnel in the kitchen of the former fast food restaurant. Homeland Security Investigations told KYMA, the tunnel was 22 feet deep, 5 feet tall and 3 feet wide. It extended 590 feet underground to a home across the border in San Luis Rio Colorado, Mexico where it came up to a trap door underneath a bed.   Garcia is now facing federal charges which include conspiracy to possess with intent to distribute methamphetamine and cocaine.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Drug containers being loaded into trailer  2. The suspect was in possession of 239 packages of narcotics3. The entrance of the drug tunnel4.  A cross section of the drug tunnelVOICEOVER (in English): "According to KGUN, suspect Jesus Ivan Lopez Garcia was pulled over on August 13 after police saw him loading several plastic containers into a trailer outside of an old Kentucky Fried Chicken restaurant." "Lopez was found to be in possession of 239 packages of various narcotics, including 261 pounds of methamphetamine, 14 pounds of cocaine, 30 pounds of white heroin, 13.7 bounds of brown heroin and 6.8 pounds of fentanyl. Police estimated the street value of the drugs at over $1 million." "After obtaining a search warrant, agents searched Lopez's home and the old KFC and found the entrance to the tunnel in the kitchen of the former fast food restaurant." "Homeland Security Investigations told KYMA, the tunnel was 22 feet deep, 5 feet tall and 3 feet wide. It extended 590 feet underground to a home across the border in San Luis Rio Colorado, Mexico where it came up to a trap door underneath a bed." SOURCES: CNN, BBC, KYMA https://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/23/us/drug-tunnel-arizona-mexico-trnd/index.html?utm_term=link&utm_source=fbCNNi&utm_content=2018-08-23T22%3A00%3A12&utm_medium=socialhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-45291978https://www.kyma.com/news/top-stories/agents-find-drug-tunnel-after-significant-drug-bust/784599445***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/27/3683174/3683174_225193E779F342D48B942555A500E627_180827_3683174_Drug_tunnel_found_under_former_fast_food_restaur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C47/646/C47646E13CFB4AC6996A561B35511B99_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, drug tunnel, US Mexico border, tunnel US Mexico border, drug tunnel Arizona Mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684107</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy re-launches 2nd Fleet in response to Russian military expansion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Navy has officially reactivated the Cold War-era Second Fleet in response to increased Russian military expansion. The fleet was originally set up in the beginning of the Cold War, with the main objective of supporting NATO against the Soviet Union. According to Politico, the move comes amid a recent surge in Russian submarine activity in the Atlantic.According to CNN, NATO and U.S. officials have said that Russian naval activity is at its highest since the end of the Cold War. The 2nd Fleet located in Norfolk, Virginia, which was deactivated in 2011, will be assigned ships, aircraft and Marine landing forces that can be deployed along the East Coast and in the North Atlantic. Vice Adm. Andrew "Woody" Lewis, who took command of the new headquarters last Friday, said he and his staff will "aggressively and quickly rebuild this command into an operational warfighting organization. According to CNN, officials say the Atlantic fleet will work with naval units like Naval Forces Europe and the Fourth and Sixth Fleets while focusing on joint, integrated training and operations in "high-end of naval warfare." The fleet will once again support NATO and the NATO Joint Force Command for the Atlantic which will be located in Norfolk as well. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of 2nd Fleet headquarters in Virginia2. Russian submarine traveling underwater3. 2nd Fleet will be assigned ships, aircraft and Marine landing forces4. 2nd Fleet will work with Naval Forces Europe, 4th Fleet and 6th FleetVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Navy has officially reactivated the Cold War-era Second Fleet in Norfolk, Virginia in response to increased Russian military expansion." "According to Politico, the move comes amid a recent surge in Russian submarine activity in the Atlantic, as well as overall Russian military expansion." "The 2nd Fleet located in Norfolk, Virginia, which was deactivated in 2011, will be assigned ships, aircraft and Marine landing forces that can be deployed along the East Coast and in the North Atlantic." "According to CNN, officials say the Atlantic fleet will work with naval units like Naval Forces Europe and the Fourth and Sixth Fleets while focusing on joint, integrated training and operations in "high-end of naval warfare."" SOURCES: Politico, CNNhttps://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/24/navy-atlantic-fleet-russia-751660https://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/24/politics/us-navy-fleet-russia/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 09:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/28/3684107/3684107_F7ADC2ACEC4B4E54B71DD2506C869A24_180828_3684107_U_S__Navy_re_launches_2nd_Fleet_in_response_to_R_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/022/DA6/022DA670A3154E7590BAD58BCCF05F8C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, US Navy, US Navy re-launches, 2nd Fleet, Atlantic 2nd Fleet, US Navy 2nd Fleet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683892</guid>
      <title>Earth's magnetic field can flip faster than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found evidence that Earth's magnetic poles have shifted rapidly once before, and could lead to a global catastrophe should it happen again.Forbes reports that the earth is surrounded by a magnetic field that shields the planet's surface from charged particles constantly being emitted by the sun.This field can switch directions  a phenomenon known as geomagnetic reversal. It is believed to unfold slowly over thousands of years, with the last full reversal occurring 780,000 years agoAccording to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Science, research teams from Taiwan and China analyzed a Sanxing Cave stalagmite that grew over a 16,000-year period. Variations in the rock's magnetic minerals revealed a huge polarity shift 98,000 years ago that occurred in just 144 years.Previous studies have suggested that the magnetic field could weaken by about 90% during a reversal, which will greatly impact power grids and modern electronics.Unfortunately, pole shifts can't be predicted, and we can only hope it happens far enough in the future to when humanity has come up with certain technologies to avoid significant damage.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of magnetic field shielding Earth from solar particles2. Depiction of geomagnetic reversal3. Depiction of stalagmite analysis revealing fast pole switch4. Depiction of consequences of Earth's pole reversalVOICEOVER (in English): "The Earth is surrounded by a magnetic field that shields the planet's surface from charged particles constantly being emitted by the sun.""This field can switch directions  a phenomenon known as geomagnetic reversal. It's believed to unfold slowly over thousands of years, with the last full reversal occurring 780,000 years ago.""A new study analyzed a Chinese stalagmite that grew over a 16,000-year period. Variations in the rock's magnetic minerals revealed a huge polarity shift 98,000 years ago that occurred in just 144 years.""Previous studies have suggested that the magnetic field could weaken by about 90% during a reversal, which will greatly impact power grids and modern electronics."SOURCES: Forbes, PNAS, Science Alerthttps://www.forbes.com/sites/davidbressan/2018/08/23/earths-magnetic-field-could-flip-much-faster-than-previously-thought/#3f61daa0438chttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/08/14/1720404115https://www.sciencealert.com/earth-geomagnetic-polarity-excursion-rapid-reversal-ancient-past***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/28/3683892/3683892_F4C2582DD59F4AD7BF68FB7AA100B161_180828_3683892_Earth_s_magnetic_field_can_flip_faster_than_prev_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/0A3/A22/0A3A221CA7164C28B64D4593A6A840F0_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, magnetic field, earth magnetic field, magnetic poles, Earth magnetic poles, geomagnetic reversal, pole reversal, pole switch, pole flip, magnetic reversal, magnetic switch]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684929</guid>
      <title>Russia and China set for massive military drills</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRussia, China and Mongolia will this year take part in a large, joint military operation dubbed "Vostok-2018".According to the Moscow Times, Russia is sending 300,000 military personnel as well as 1,000 aircraft and two naval fleets to the exercise. China is sending 3,200 troops, along with aircraft, and 900 pieces of military hardware, reports Xinhua. Mongolia's contribution to the event is unknown, according to the BBC.Xinhua reports that the Chinese and Russian cooperation in the event is being hailed as proof of expanded ties between the two countries.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of countries involved2. Depiction of Russia involvement3. Further depiction of Russia involvement4. Depiction of Chinese and Mongolian involvementVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: The Moscow Times, Xinuha, TASS, BBChttps://themoscowtimes.com/news/300000-troops-participate-largest-war-games-since-1981-62690http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2018-08/29/c_137426179.htmhttp://tass.com/defense/1018951https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-45330161***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 10:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/29/3684929/3684929_7D25047040EA4BDCBAE1BA9780504FF7_180829_3684929_Russia_and_China_set_for_massive_military_drills_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/E51/F90/E51F902803CE435AB39C59F0B8A8E474_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Russia, China, Mongolia, Navy, Aircraft, air force, Vostok 2018, East 2018, military, east asia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684718</guid>
      <title>New weight-loss pill might help in the fight against obesity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in the New England Journal of Medicine has found promising results for a weight-loss drug in the U.S.Researchers say lorcaserin, also known under the trade name of Belviq in the U.S., [a][b]is the first drug for weight-loss that does not increase the risk of heart issues.Half of the 12,000 participants in the study were given lorcaserin, which is designed to suppress appetite, while the other half were given a placebo.The drug is supposed to be taken twice a day and will would stimulate brain chemicals to bring about a feeling of fullness.However, the researchers noted that side effects such as headaches and nausea may also be caused by the drug.After 40 months, the study found that the participants prescribed lorcaserin were three times more likely to lose 5 to 10 percent of their body weight compared to those taking a placebo.  However, according an editorial published in the New England Journal of Medicine, patients are advised to use the drugs on a "cautious basis" based on their needs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lorcaserin is shown in a bottle, along with a depiction of the drug being deemed safe for the heart.2. Two of the lorcaserin drugs as well as the brain getting stimulated are shown.3. Side effects of lorcaserin are shown.4. A depiction of the drug being ingested and a chart showing the body weight reducing by five to ten percent.VOICEOVER (in English): "The researchers involved claim lorcaserin, which is known under the trade name of Belviq in the U.S., is the first drug for weight-loss deemed safe for the heart.""The drug is supposed to be taken twice a day and will would stimulate brain chemicals to bring about a feeling of fullness.""However, the researchers noted that side effects such as headaches and nausea may also be caused by the drug.""After 40 months, the study found that the participants who were prescribed lorcaserin were three times more likely to lose 5 to 10 percent of their body weight compared to those taking a placebo."  SOURCES: The Guardian, The New England Journal of Medicine, The BBC, Reuters, The Atlanta Journal-Constitution, Associated Presshttps://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/aug/27/weight-loss-drug-belviq-not-linked-to-heart-problems-finds-studyhttps://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1808721https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45319393https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-belviq-safety/weight-loss-drug-lorcaserin-found-safe-in-large-study-idUSKCN1LC2C1https://www.ajc.com/news/health-med-fit-science/this-weight-loss-drug-the-first-succeed-without-heart-risks-study-finds/cFh0YIJSs4bfuMpEsnxpPN/https://apnews.com/5bcf5229e462469cb150cdb67c9c9beb/Weight-loss-drug-Belviq-seems-safe-for-heart,-study-finds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 06:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/29/3684718/3684718_7B121E3D56BC4DD1AECD781A7FDB8542_180829_3684718_New_weight_loss_pill_might_help_in_the_fight_aga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BAE/FA4/BAEFA41739E4498992F32874CCB99547_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, US, study, weight-loss pills, drugs, medicine,lorcaserin, Belviq, obesity, obesity epidemic, fighting obesity,  placebo, stimulate brain chemicals, body weight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684710</guid>
      <title>America's 'Space Force'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. military is exploring how to take its operations into space.According to a U.S. Department of Defence document, military officials are exploring four components for a proposed Space Force. One of these is a Space Development Agency for primarily research and development.The next would be a Space Operation Force. According to the DOD, this would "develop, field and integrate space capabilities into multi-domain warfighting".Thirdly the U.S. government would explore a Services and Support component for logistical and administrative purposes. The fourth component the DoD are looking at is a U.S. Space Command to lead conflict operations in space. According to Defense One, the creation of a new military branch would need congressional approval but some of it could be delivered by a restructuring of the DoD.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of scientists developing new space technology2. Depiction of military officials coordinating space operations3. Depiction of a astronaut servicing a space-based facility4. Depiction of a space command operations centerVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a U.S. Department of Defence document, military officials are exploring four components for a proposed Space Force.""One of these is a Space Development Agency for primarily research and development.""The next would be a Space Operation Force.""According to the DOD, this would "develop, field and integrate space capabilities into multi-domain warfighting"." "Thirdly the U.S. government would explore a Services and Support component for logistical and administrative purposes.""The fourth component the DoD are looking at is a U.S. Space Command to lead conflict operations in space." SOURCES: U.S. Department of Defense, Defense One, National Geographic, Planetary Societyhttps://media.defense.gov/2018/Aug/09/2001952764/-1/-1/1/ORGANIZATIONAL-MANAGEMENT-STRUCTURE-DOD-NATIONAL-SECURITY-SPACE-COMPONENTS.PDFhttps://www.defenseone.com/politics/2018/07/pentagon-create-space-force/150157/https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/06/space-force-trump-legal-military-role-satellites-science/http://www.planetary.org/blogs/casey-dreier/2018/0823-space-force-explainer.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 06:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/29/3684710/3684710_2D01F5BC0807484A81C12486FB07EAE1_180829_3684710_America_s__Space_Force__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A66/7C5/A667C58490AF4D79A7104FD0BB0940BD_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, space force news, us space force news, space force, space corps, space defense, science and technology, pentagon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684623</guid>
      <title>China accused of predatory lending to smaller, developing countries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has been accused of leveraging massive loans to smaller, developing countries in order to take over assets and construct military bases in said countries. In a practice referred to as "debt-trap diplomacy" or "debt colonialism," huge loans are given to countries that will be unable to repay, forcing smaller countries to give up major concessions when the loans default, according to The Center for Global Development.  Countries like Pakistan, Djibouti, Fiji, Montenegro, Maldives, Kyrgyzstan and Laos all owe China large amounts of money. Last year, Sri Lanka owed more that $1 billion in debts to China, so it was forced to hand over a port to Chinese government-owned business on a 99-year lease. Infrastructure loans to build roads and ports linked to the "Belt and Road" initiative to have led to countries owing millions or billions in debt, often accounting for large percentages of the countries' GDP.China may be looking to leverage its debt in the Pacific in order to increase its military footprint in the South Pacific, The Times reports.In April, China informed Vanuatu it had intentions of building a military base. According to the Sun, Vanuatu owes $246 million to China.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nine smaller countries that owe China massive loans 2. China making loan to country that defaults and has to surrender assets and territory3. Belt and Road initiative has led countries to owe China money4. Chinese military portVOICEOVER (in English): "China has been accused of leveraging massive loans to smaller, developing countries in order to take over assets and construct military bases in said countries." "According to The Center for Global Development, in a practice referred to as "debt-trap diplomacy" or "debt colonialism," huge loans are given to countries that will be unable to repay, forcing smaller countries to surrender assets and territory when the loans default.  "Infrastructure loans to build roads and ports linked to the "Belt and Road" initiative to have led to countries owing millions or billions in debt, often accounting for large percentages of the countries' GDP.""According to The Times, China may be looking to leverage its debt in the Pacific in order to increase its military footprint in the South Pacific. In April, China informed Vanuatu it had intentions of building a military base. According to the Sun, Vanuatu owes $246 million to China."  SOURCES: Center for Global Development, The Times, Lowy Institute for International Policyhttps://www.cgdev.org/article/chinas-debt-trap-diplomacy-along-belt-and-road-wirehttps://www.cgdev.org/sites/default/files/examining-debt-implications-belt-and-road-initiative-policy-perspective.pdfhttps://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/world/australia-fears-chinese-influence-in-pacific-as-tonga-admits-debt-distress-mxzc9j9frhttps://chineseaidmap.lowyinstitute.org/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 04:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/29/3684623/3684623_E2B8A168B317472093010A3180900622_180829_3684623_China_accused_of_predatory_lending_to_smaller__d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9DC/BA4/9DCBA44389574645BF8FEE00FE8E3B60_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, China debt, China debt-trap diplomacy, debt colonialism, Belt and Road initiative]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684609</guid>
      <title>Remains of 4,000-year-old lost city in China discovered</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArcheologists have discovered the remains of a 4,000-year-old lost city on a ridge above China's Tuwei River.  Researchers found a massive step pyramid that is at least 230 feet high and stretches 59 acres at its base and published the results in the journal Antiquity, according to Live Science. According to archeologists, a city flourished around the pyramid for five centuries, and at one point encompassed an area of 988 acres. Researchers have named the city "Shimao." The pyramid was built out of a loess hill, and had 11 steps tapering as they ascend. It was guarded by an inner and outer wall. According to the researchers, atop the pyramid "were extensive palaces built of rammed earth, with wooden pillars and roofing tiles, a gigantic water reservoir, and domestic remains related to daily life." The researchers believe the ruling class lived on top of the pyramid, where artisanal or industrial crafts were produced. The remains of several human sacrifices were also discovered at Shimao.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. City ruins in this side of a hill2. The pyramid at the center of the lost city3. Aerial view of Shimao with inner and outer wall4. City ruinsVOICEOVER (in English): "Archeologists have discovered the remains of a 4,000-year-old lost city on a ridge above China's Tuwei River that flourished from 2300 B.C. to 1800 B.C and at one point encompassed an area of 988 acres." "Researchers found a massive step pyramid that is at least 230 feet high and stretches 59 acres at its base and published the results in the journal Antiquity. Researchers have named the city "Shimao."""The pyramid was built out of a loess hill, and had 11 steps tapering as they ascend. It was guarded by an inner and outer wall." "According to the researchers, atop the pyramid "were extensive palaces built of rammed earth, with wooden pillars and roofing tiles, a gigantic water reservoir, and domestic remains related to daily life."" SOURCES: MSN, Live Science, Journal Antiquityhttps://www.msn.com/en-ph/news/world/remains-of-4000-year-old-lost-city-with-230-foot-tall-pyramid-and-pits-filled-with-human-skulls-from-mass-sacrifices-discovered-in-china/ar-BBMqaNx?li=BBr8Mknhttps://www.livescience.com/63406-massive-shimao-pyramid-unearthed-china.htmlhttps://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/antiquity/article/when-peripheries-were-centres-a-preliminary-study-of-the-shimaocentred-polity-in-the-loess-highland-china/EA48B7FEF5512D41D615DC3480DE0DDC***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 04:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/29/3684609/3684609_CAEB6C0F35294E638E8BB2D9C2234BA7_180829_3684609_Remains_of_4_000_year_old_lost_city_in_China_dis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/4B8/DAB/4B8DABE77E7F43448E049CCC1956849A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, China lost city, China lost city discovered, China lost pyramid discovered, China Shimao lost city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3686486</guid>
      <title>Hot, humid weather can prevent body from cooling down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWith 17 states in the eastern U.S. under heat advisories, the hot temperatures along with the high humidity could be a health concern for some.According to Popular Science, when temperatures are high and the air is humid, the mechanisms the body has to cool down are not as effective.  Heat energy moves from warmer to cooler places. When outside temperature is cooler, heat leaves the body. But when outside temperatures are higher, heat can't escape as well. In high humidity, the air is full of moisture, so sweat takes longer to evaporate.As the body tries to cool down, blood is sent to the surface of the skin in order to radiate off heat. This pulls water out of the bloodstream and puts them into the sweat glands.Because of dehydration, less blood is available to transport oxygen to the brain and other internal organs. Circulation is encumbered as well because the blood has less water.    If those conditions maintain and fluids are not replenished, there is a risk of heat exhaustion. If someone appears to be confused, or starts to show other neurological symptoms, that is a sign of heat stroke.  Young children and older people are at higher risk for heat-related illnesses. It's important to stay properly hydrated in hot, humid weather. Wear loose-fitting and lightweight clothing. If possible, avoid direct sunlight. Avoid alcoholic and caffeinated drinks, which are dehydrating.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Body losing heat in colder temperature, loosing less heat in hot, humid temperature2. Sweating in high humidity, body radiating heat3. Less blood available for brain and internal organs, circulation slowing4. Heat exhaustion and heat strokeVOICEOVER (in English): "When temperatures are high and the air is humid, the mechanisms the body has to cool down are not as effective. When the outside temperature is cooler, heat leaves the body. But when outside temperatures are higher, heat doesn't escape as well." "In high humidity, the air is full of moisture, so sweat takes longer to evaporate.As the body tries to cool down, blood is sent to the surface of the skin in order to radiate off heat. This pulls water out of the bloodstream and puts them into the sweat glands.""Less blood is available to transport oxygen to the brain and other internal organs. Circulation is encumbered as well because the blood has less water."    "If those conditions maintain and fluids are not replenished, there is a risk of heat exhaustion. If someone appears to be confused, or starts to show other neurological symptoms, that is a sign of heat stroke."SOURCES: Popular Sciencehttps://www.popsci.com/hot-humid-weather-dangerous-health***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 12:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/31/3686486/3686486_1581D76E9EB7488CA14997EAC83C794D_180831_3686486_Hot__humid_weather_can_prevent_body_from_cooling_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A34/CB4/A34CB4A5337544908CAEC1C0809C2834_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, hot temperature, heat wave, high humidity, heat exhaustion, heat stroke]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3686015</guid>
      <title>North Korea's high speed rail hopes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea is exploring the possibility of a bullet train system, reports Reuters.Pyongyang is hoping to create a high-speed rail network between its cities and across national borders, according to Reuters.The news agency reports that a senior North Korean official told the French Senate earlier this year they'd like to cooperate with French companies to build the railway.According to Reuters, when reporters visited the demolition of the Punggye-ri nuclear test site in June the journey took them 12 hours on North Korea's current railroads. South Korea's high speed rail could have made the journey in just 2 and a half hours.Reuters reports a project like this could be a potential money-spinner but that nuclear-related sanctions on business with the North could pose a challenge.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of North Korea and bullet train2. Depiction of bullet train3. Depiction of speed difference between regular DPRK train and South Korean bullet train4. Depiction of project and nuclear sanctionsVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Reutershttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-southkorea-railroad-analys/korea-detente-revives-north-korean-leaders-bullet-train-dreams-idUSKCN1LE2TOhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles-southkorea/south-korea-welcomes-norths-decision-to-let-reporters-visit-nuclear-site-idUSKCN1IO022***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 03:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/08/31/3686015/3686015_F22FD39A351441649A55EB10CC4BD30D_180831_3686015_North_Korea_s_high_speed_rail_hopes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C3C/B77/C3CB77F4CA31462AB90D25906BF97A97_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, high speed rail, north, korea, HSR, Asia trains, bullet trains, transportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
