<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3687977</guid>
      <title>Mysterious 'ghost ship' found off the coast of Myanmar</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOfficials are investigating a ship that was found drifting off the coast of Myanmar, reports Fox News.The "ghost ship" was discovered by fishermen about 11 kilometers off the coast off Yangon, Myanmar.Officials say the empty cargo ship, named Sam Rataulangi PB 1600, was being towed by a tugboat, called Independence, to a ship-breaking factory in Bangladesh.In a Facebook post, the Yangon police said the ship had an Indonesian flag. The vessel was also reported to be more than 177 meters long, according to the Marine Traffic website.According to AFP, the bad weather caused the cables attached to the ship broke as the ship neared the Yangon River. This is when the crew decided to abandon the ship.Myanmar Navy officials decided to use coastal radar records to track down the approximate location of the two vessels, Fox News reports.Officials involved in the case are still investigating further, as the ship's last recorded location was reportedly off the coast of Taiwan before appearing in Myanmar waters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. An empty cargo ship is shown being towed in the sea to Bangladesh2. The design of the ship, with the Indonesian flag, is shown here, along with its size.3. The cables attached to the cargo ship and tugboat break apart, and the ship has being stranded.4. The coastal radar being used to find the approximate location of the two vessels.VOICEOVER (in English): "Officials say the empty cargo ship was being towed by a tugboat to a ship-breaking factory in Bangladesh.""In a Facebook post, the Yangon police said the ship had an Indonesian flag. According to the Marine Traffic website, the vessel was also reported to be more than 177 meters long.""According to AFP, bad weather caused the cables attached to the ship to break as the ship neared the Yangon River. This is when the crew decided to abandon the ship.""Fox News reports Myanmar Navy officials decided to use coastal radar records to track down the approximate location of the two vessels."SOURCES: Fox News, France 24, Marine Traffic, Sky News, Eleven Myanmar, Myanmar Times, The BBC, http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/09/02/ghost-ship-found-drifting-off-coast-burma-navy-solves-mystery.htmlhttps://www.france24.com/en/20180901-ghost-ship-myanmar-waters-earlier-towed-indonesian-manned-vessel-navyhttps://www.marinetraffic.com/en/ais/details/ships/shipid:702959/mmsi:525003026/imo:9151981/vessel:SAM_RATULANGI_PB_1600https://news.sky.com/story/mystery-of-myanmar-ghost-ship-solved-11487693http://www.elevenmyanmar.com/local/14847https://www.mmtimes.com/news/ghost-ship-runs-aground-thongwa.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-45377707***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 10:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/03/3687977/3687977_F731491FB25242EE84EAB7C2E4E28FD7_180903_3687977_Mysterious__ghost_ship__found_off_the_coast_of_M_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/821/245/821245B1385742A98E958DBA9BC7C8B1_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,Myanmar, Yangon police,  ship, cargo ship, ghost ship, mystery ghost ship, Myanmar coast, cargo ship, seas tugboat, coastal radar records, Sam Rataulangi PB 1600 freighter, vessels, ships, fishermen]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3687729</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover 85 miles of deep-sea coral reef off Atlantic Coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers on board the research vessel (RV) Atlantis have discovered a deep-sea coral reef about 160 miles off the coast of Charleston, South Carolina. According to HuffPost, a human-operated submersible named Alvin was deployed from the RV Atlantis, and its cameras discovered enormous cold-water coral populations about 0.5 miles below the ocean surface.Scientists used Alvin to explore the reef and collect coral samples on Aug. 23 and Aug. 24. The team found large amounts of Lophelia pertusa, a branching, whitish coral found in cold waters. According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), L. pertusa can survive in deep-seas by using stinging tentacles to stun its prey and guide food into its stomach.  The corals found by the Atlantis were located about 16 miles to the northwest of corals found earlier in the summer by the NOAA RV Okeanos Explorer. The coral-covered area explored by the Okeanos and the Atlantis run for an estimated 85 miles, layered with massive, rocky piles of dead coral likely accumulated over many thousands of years, according to expedition lead scientist Erik Cordes, reported HuffPost.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. RV Atlantis lowering the ALVIN submersible into the water2. Alvin submersible locating coral on ocean floor3. Alvin submersible collecting coral samples4. Alvin submersible taking more coral samplesVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers on board the research vessel Atlantis have discovered a deep-sea coral reef about 160 miles off the coast of Charleston, South Carolina." "According to the HuffPost, by deploying a human-operated submersible named Alvin from the RV Atlantis, cameras discovered enormous cold-water coral populations about 0.5 miles below the ocean surface." "Scientists used Alvin to explore the reef and collect coral samples on Aug. 23 and Aug. 24, and found large amounts of Lophelia pertusa, a branching, whitish coral found in cold waters." "The corals found by the Atlantis were located about 16 miles to the northwest of corals found earlier in the summer by the NOAA RV Okeanos Explorer. The coral-covered area explored by the Okeanos and the Atlantis run for an estimated 85 miles."SOURCES: HuffPost, Live Sciencehttps://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/scientists-discover-giant-deep-sea-coral-reef-off-atlantic-coast_us_5b81c298e4b0cd327dfd415ehttps://www.livescience.com/63442-new-coral-reef-found.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 04:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/03/3687729/3687729_A53761C0BA3D4C43BAED9CF944ED6E97_180903_3687729_Scientists_discover_85_miles_of_deep_sea_coral_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/92A/F7D/92AF7D73AEB746CE8963D021F4129849_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, coral reef, deep-sea coral reef, RV Atlantis, Lophelia pertusa, coral]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3687713</guid>
      <title>Study finds warm water trapped under the Arctic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a study published in Science Advances, there is warm water trapped under the surface of the Arctic seas that could significantly melt sea ice in the Arctic.The researchers used old data from ships and new data from probes installed in the Arctic waters to calculate the "heat content."The warm water beneath the Arctic Sea is accumulating rapidly around 50 meters below the Arctic Ocean.As the sea ice started to melt, the water was exposed to the sun, and heated up.The Arctic winds then sent the warmer waters to the north, which is where they are trapped beneath the ice pack at present.Warm water is typically lighter than cold water, causing it to float. According to the CBC, the warm water doesn't float in the Arctic because its saltiness makes it sink. Instead, the colder, fresh water sits near the sea ice.However, the researchers warn the trapped hot water has the potential to "come to the surface" and "impact the ice."The researchers explain this could happen if the waters become so warm, they stop sinking and begin mixing with the cold, fresh water near the sea ice.The Arctic is already warning at twice the rate of the global average, this would only exacerbate the dire situation in the polar region.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The area where the warm water is accumulating is shown.2. The process of how the water got heated up.3. Depiction of the warm waters being sent to the north of the Arctic.4. Depiction of the warm water coming to the surface and impacting the Arctic ice.VOICEOVER (in English): "Warm water beneath the Arctic Sea is accumulating rapidly around 50 meters below the Arctic Ocean.""As the sea ice melts, the water exposed to the sun heats up.""The Arctic winds then send the warmer waters to the north, which is where they remain trapped beneath the ice pack.""However, the researchers warn the trapped hot water has the potential to 'come to the surface' and 'impact the ice.'"SOURCES: New Scientist, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation(CBC), Digital Journal, The Independent, Phys.org, Science Advances study,https://www.newscientist.com/article/2178160-a-warm-water-time-bomb-could-spell-disaster-for-arctic-sea-ice/https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/north/sea-ice-warm-layer-1.4803195http://www.digitaljournal.com/tech-and-science/science/warm-water-under-canada-basin-could-cause-significant-ice-melt/article/530693https://www.independent.co.uk/environment/arctic-sea-ice-melting-warm-water-trapped-polar-canada-yale-university-perfect-a8513176.htmlhttps://phys.org/news/2018-08-archived-deep-arctic-interior.htmlhttp://advances.sciencemag.org/content/4/8/eaat6773***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 04:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/03/3687713/3687713_998131B84FDA49E5877398BF5B6D68B4_180903_3687713_Study_finds_warm_water_trapped_under_the_Arctic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/952/955/9529557C36D64BE5B44EBBC38592F240_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, The Arctic, arctic sea ice, arctic sea ice melting, warm water, warm water in the arctic, global warming, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3688719</guid>
      <title>Dozens of elephant carcasses found near Botswana wildlife sanctuary</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe carcasses of 87 elephants have been found near the Okavango Delta wildlife sanctuary in Botswana, where it appears the animals were killed for their tusks, reports The BBC.Elephants Without Borders, a conservation nonprofit organization, discovered the dead elephants while conducting an aerial survey.The report says the poachers tried to hide the massacre by concealing the carcasses with drying bushes.The organization believes the carcasses were poached as the skulls of the elephants were chopped off, presumably to remove the tusks.Botswana has the largest elephant population in the world, and in the midst of its anti-poaching unit being disarmed, poachers have begun to breach its borders.According to data from the Great Elephant Census, a third of the elephants in Africa are estimated to have been killed in the last decade alone.The organization claims the incident is the largest scale of poaching deaths ever seen in Africa.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A helicopter looking down and discovering the carcasses of the elephants.2. Depiction of the carcasses being concealed by drying bushes.3. The elephant is shown without a head, as the tusks were removed.4. The map of Africa is shown, along with an elephant icon and a vertical bar chart.VOICEOVER (in English): "Elephants Without Borders, a conservation nonprofit organization, discovered the dead elephants while conducting an aerial survey.""The report says the poachers tried to hide the massacre by concealing the carcasses with drying bushes.""The organization believes the carcasses were poached as the skulls of the elephants were chopped off, presumably to remove the tusks.""According to data from the Great Elephant Census, a third of the elephants in Africa are estimated to have been killed in the last decade alone."SOURCES: NPR, The BBC, Great Elephant Census, Elephants Without Borders, The South African,https://www.npr.org/2018/09/03/644340279/nearly-90-elephants-found-dead-near-botswana-sanctuary-killed-by-poachershttps://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-africa-45396394http://www.greatelephantcensus.com/http://elephantswithoutborders.org/https://www.thesouthafrican.com/poaching-almost-90-elephants-dead-in-biggest-ever-slaughter-in-africa/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 10:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/04/3688719/3688719_7A5AEA214F4B47EE9059C3E3B7C13836_180904_3688719_Dozens_of_elephant_carcasses_found_near_Botswana_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/3B6/0C8/3B60C805E90D4E88A483A39EC832E3F9_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Botswana,elephants, elephant carcasses, wildlife sanctuary, Africa, poaching, wild animals, tusks, ivory, hunting,elephant poaching in Africa, elephant poaching news, elephant poaching 2018, elephant poaching videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3688416</guid>
      <title>Ocean cleanup plans to clean up 90% of ocean garbage patch by 2040</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Ocean Cleanup, a nonprofit organization, has launched a beta cleanup system to collect plastic from the oceans, reports Forbes.According to the organization, there are about 1.8 trillion pieces of plastic on the surface of the Great Pacific Garbage Patch, which is located between Hawaii and California.The organization has come up with a cleanup system, called System 001,which consists of a 600-meter-long floater and a 3-meter-deep skirt to prevent the plastic in the ocean from flowing over it.System 001 would also take advantage of natural forces such as the wind, ocean currents and waves to propel the system forward and form a U-shape naturally to concentrate plastic in the center.The cleanup system is also fitted with solar powered-lights, cameras, sensors, satellite antenna along with anti-collision systems.A support vessel would come by periodically to take out the plastic gathered by the cleanup system, which would then be recycled and turned into products.This is just the first fleet; the organization eventually plans to launch 60 more fleets in an year or two.Some researchers worry the system might be harmful for marine life and could trap sea creatures as well, reports Business Insider.Meanwhile, others worry plastic parts in the ocean might be deeper underwater than the device can reach, and claim it might be a much more complex task to remove such pollutants.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the floater blocking plastic.2. The floater is shown turn change into a U-shape to concentrate the plastic in the middle.3. Different items the floater is fitted with.4. A vessel is seen taking away the plastic gathered by the floater.VOICEOVER (in English): "The organization has come up with a cleanup system that consists of a 600-meter-long floater and a 3-meter-deep skirt to prevent the plastic in the ocean from flowing over it.""The system would also take advantage of natural forces such as the wind, ocean currents and waves to propel the system forward and form a U-shape naturally to concentrate plastic in the center.""The cleanup system is also fitted with solar powered-lights, cameras, sensors, satellite antenna along with anti-collision systems.""A support vessel would come by periodically to take out the plastic gathered by the cleanup system, which would then be recycled and turned into products."SOURCES: Forbes, Big Think, Business Insider, Plastic News, The Ocean Cleanuphttps://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffkart/2018/08/28/the-ocean-cleanup-is-starting-aims-to-cut-garbage-patch-by-90-by-2040/#4983bb17253ehttps://bigthink.com/stephen-johnson/great-pacific-garbage-patch-the-ocean-cleanup-project-set-to-launch-full-scale-test-in-septemberhttps://www.businessinsider.com/boyan-slat-ocean-cleanup-launch-into-pacific-on-september-8-2018-7http://www.plasticsnews.com/article/20180803/NEWS/180809954/ocean-cleanup-uses-plastics-to-remove-plastics-litter-from-the-pacifichttps://www.theoceancleanup.com/technology/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 04:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/04/3688416/3688416_EFBE8D1A895A42FAAA4600D4FB792C05_180904_3688416_Ocean_cleanup_plans_to_clean_up_90__of_ocean_gar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F70/6E3/F706E3AD98074E75807462FC5B4D8DF3_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, ocean, ocean cleanup, garbage patch, floater, plastic, plastic in ocean, beta cleanup system, plastic pollution, polluted oceans, technology, marine life, going green]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3688399</guid>
      <title>Microwaves suspected cause of US diplomatic staff headaches</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch into brain injuries suffered by U.S. diplomatic staff has been linked to suspected energy attacks on embassy workers in China and Cuba.The brain can perceive microwaves as sounds in a phenomenon known as the Frey effect. Over time, targeted microwave energy could induce head injury.A microwave weapon, according to the New York Times, could look like a satellite dish and may be handheld or fixed to a variety of transportation. Citing research, the New York Times reports that U.S. diplomatic staff in Cuba experienced intense high-pitched sounds inside their hotel rooms and homes. University of Pennsylvania brain expert Douglas Smith told CNN the injuries are like "like a concussion, but without a concussion" as patients had no previous head trauma.A senior U.S. administration official told CNN authorities suspect the injuries were caused by microwave beams, but added that they have no solid evidence.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of brain "hearing" microwaves2. Depiction of dish and transportation3. Depiction of worker and suspected microwave energy attack4. Depiction of man suffering headache with no causeVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: New York Times, Journal of the American Medical Association, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/01/science/sonic-attack-cuba-microwave.htmlhttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2673168?widget=personalizedcontent&previousarticle=2673164https://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/02/health/cuba-china-state-department-microwaves-sonic-attacks/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 04:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/04/3688399/3688399_2ECDC7BF48624900B1A4AA41F2558845_180904_3688399_Microwaves_suspected_cause_of_US_diplomatic_staf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BEA/7E9/BEA7E92EC1E548728B0E3E6FC7E58EE5_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  microwave energy, microwave, science and technology, medical, ear, brain, how sound travels, headaches, migraine, USA, Cuba, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3689255</guid>
      <title>Study finds airport security trays contains more viruses than toilets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study published in the BioMed Central Infectious Diseases journal found that plastic airport security trays carry viruses that could cause respiratory infections.The researchers involved in the study took swab samples of different plastic trays at the Helsinki Airport three times during flu season in 2016.Four out of eight security tray samples were found contaminated with rhinovirus or adenovirus, both of which cause cold-like symptoms.The plastic trays were found to contain the highest frequency of respiratory viruses as the trays were recycled quite often and contained different items such as shoes, laptops among other things.The study also found the viruses on 10% of the surface area tested such as shop payment terminals, staircase rails, as well as passport-checking counters.The researchers encouraged people to minimize the spread of viruses by hand-washing and coughing into their sleeves.The researchers also said the airports should offer hand sanitizers to travelers as well as cleaning and disinfecting the security trays more often.The scientists involved in the study warned that airports could spread disease and create a potential risk-zone.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The airport security bin is shown with a swab sample.2. Depiction of four out of eight trays were found contaminated with rhinovirus or adenovirus.3. Ways to minimize the spread of viruses.4. Other ways to prevent the spread of viruses.VOICEOVER (in English): "The researchers involved in the study took swab samples of different plastic trays at the Helsinki Airport, three times during flu season in 2016.""Four out of eight security tray samples were then found contaminated with rhinovirus or adenovirus, both of which cause cold-like symptoms.""The researchers encouraged people to minimize the spread of viruses by hand-washing and coughing into their sleeves.""The researchers also said the airports should offer hand sanitizers to travelers as well as cleaning and disinfecting the security trays more often."SOURCES: BioMed Central Infectious Diseases journal, The Washington Post, The Guardian, The Oregonianhttps://bmcinfectdis.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12879-018-3150-5https://www.washingtonpost.com/transportation/2018/09/04/those-airport-security-bins-carry-more-germs-than-toilets-scientists-say/?utm_term=.9c534a9ebe05https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/04/airport-security-trays-carry-more-viruses-than-toilet-surfaces-scientists-findhttps://www.oregonlive.com/today/index.ssf/2018/09/airport_security_bins_carry_mo.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/05/3689255/3689255_D7EFE808F21D43B3A2B0305E1082B810_180905_3689255_Study_finds_airport_security_trays_contains_more_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F1D/9D7/F1D9D787AAAC4A7185EE40AD77EA2189_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Airport, airport security, security, airport security trays, security bins, plastic trays, virus, respiratory viruses, contagious, study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3689213</guid>
      <title>Argentina announces austerity measures as peso continues to slide</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANArgentina has announced new austerity measures in a bid to stem its current currency crisis, ahead of receiving a $50 billion loan from the International Monetary Fund.  In a televised address, President Mauricio Macri said the country could no longer keep spending more than it earned.Argentina will slash spending and raise export taxes in order to tackle its budget deficit, The Guardian reports.The president announced taxes on grain exports and other products and said the nation will abolish about half of the government's ministries. The administration did not say which ministries would be closed or merged, the BBC reports.Argentina is the largest exporter of soy meal and soy oil and is also a major producer of corn, wheat and raw soybeans.Starting on January 1, those exports will be taxed four pesos for every dollar in value, while processed products will be taxed three pesos for every dollar in value.  The export taxes will be lifted once the economy has stabilized.  Argentina's goal is to achieve a budget surplus of 1 percent of GDP by 2020.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Argentina is planning to cut spending and raise export taxes2. Certain exports will be taxed and half the government ministries closed3. Argentina exports soy meal, soy oil, corn, wheat and soybeans4. Exports will be taxed at different ratesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports Argentina has announced new austerity measures that will slash spending and raise export taxes to tackle its budget deficit amid its current currency crisis."   "President Mauricio Macri announced taxes on grain exports and other products and said the nation will abolish about half of the government's ministries." "Argentina is the largest exporter of soy meal and soy oil, and is also a major producer of corn, wheat and raw soybeans.""Starting on January 1, those exports will be taxed four pesos for every dollar in value, while processed products will be taxed three pesos for every dollar in value. The export taxes will be lifted once the economy has stabilized."  SOURCES: BBC, The Guardianhttps://www.bbc.com/news/business-45392362https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/argentina-austerity-peso-crisis-macri***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/05/3689213/3689213_68D7BE583BB34607912A3B0DC80D9F0E_180905_3689213_Argentina_announces_austerity_measures_as_peso_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/7B9/783/7B97834D664F4250BF5EDC0AA9F787CC_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Argentina, Argentina peso crisis, Argentina currency crisis, Argentina austerity measures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3690196</guid>
      <title>Mysterious leak in the International Space Station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRussian officials have discovered a tiny leak at the International Space Station and believe it may have been caused by a human.The hole was discovered after Russian ground operators registered a dip in pressure levels in the space station, reports NPR.This led the crew to discover a hole, about two millimeters in diameter, on the inner wall of a Russian spacecraft attached to the International Space Station."The crew was then immediately instructed by ground operators to seal the hole with tape. They later used an epoxy-based sealant. This temporarily stopped oxygen from leaking from the cabin.No one onboard was in danger as a result of the leak.Originally the authorities suspected the hole could have been caused by a meteorite. However, they ruled out the possibility after traces of a drill sliding was discovered along the surface.According to the Russian News Agency, the Russian officials involved said they will find the person responsible for the accident and find out if it was on purpose or by accident.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The International Space Station is shown along with a vertical bar graph showing a drop in pressure levels.2. The hole is shown inside the space station.3. Ways the hole were sealed.4. A meteorite is shown along with drill marks.VOICEOVER (in English): "NPR reports the hole was discovered after Russian ground operators registered a dip in pressure levels in the space station.""This led the crew to discover a hole, about two millimeters in diameter, on the inner wall of a Russian spacecraft attached to the International Space Station.""The crew was then immediately instructed by ground operators to seal the hole with tape, and later used an epoxy-based sealant.""Originally the authorities suspected the hole could have been caused by a meteorite. However, they ruled out the possibility after traces of a drill sliding was discovered along the surface."SOURCES: NPR, The Washington Post, The Independent, Reuters, Russian News Agencyhttps://www.npr.org/2018/09/05/644820679/who-caused-the-mysterious-leak-at-the-international-space-stationhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2018/09/05/russia-claims-that-someone-may-have-sabotaged-international-space-station/?utm_term=.3c6c7db5e7dehttps://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/nasa-iss-hole-man-made-international-space-station-roscosmos-human-a8522036.htmlhttps://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-russia-spacestation/russia-weighs-possibility-of-deliberate-act-in-space-station-damage-idUKKCN1LL363http://tass.com/science/1019791***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 13:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/06/3690196/3690196_65FA7FC98B7B4C9C97C267B88BD0EBB8_180906_3690196_Mysterious_leak_in_the_International_Space_Stati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/456/B8B/456B8B9E88FE4671BA9E3CCD36757520_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Space, International Space Station, spacecraft, spacecraft, leak, hole in international space station, mystery leak, mystery leak in space, drilling marks, drill, meteorite,cabin, sealant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3690189</guid>
      <title>How poison was smuggled inside Britain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBritish Prime Minister Theresa May has outlined how two Russian suspects smuggled Novichok poison into the UK as part of an assassination plot.May told British lawmakers Wednesday how Russian nationals traveled to the UK using the aliases Alexander Petrov and Ruslan Boshirov. Both have been charged in the attempted murders of ex-Russian spy Sergei Skirpal, and two others.The men managed are believed to have smuggled Novichok inside a perfume bottle, then traveled to the UK where authorities suspected the hatched the assassination plot.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of suspects' route to Britain2. Depiction of hotel room3. Depiction of how substance got onto door4. Depiction of suspects returning to RussiaVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: UK Government, Bloomberg, BBC https://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/pm-statement-on-the-salisbury-investigation-5-september-2018https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-09-05/planes-trains-and-fake-perfume-how-novichok-arrived-in-britainhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-45421445***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 13:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/06/3690189/3690189_08E7EF0960DF478887391AD9DDD56C24_180906_3690189_How_poison_was_smuggled_inside_Britain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/756/72E/75672E829C94416A9D9AAC83BE019D4E_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, britain, russia, parliament, sergei skirpal, chemicals, chemical, travel, Uk and Russia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3690093</guid>
      <title>Researchers using synthetic bacteria to cure disease</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have reached an important milestone in synthetic biology by carrying out successful trials on a group of volunteers in order to help treat people who suffer from phenylketonuria.The genetically engineered probiotic developed by Synlogic could become the first synthetic biology-based medical treatment to be approved by the Food and Drug Administration, according the New York Times. People who suffer from phenylketonuria, or PKU, must avoid dietary protein in foods like meat and cheese, because their bodies cannot break down the amino acid phenylalanine, or Phe. The study, published on August 13 in Nature Biotechnology, showed that the probiotic can significantly lower Phe levels in both mouse models of PKU and in healthy monkeys, according to The Scientist. The treatment is called SYNB1618 and is a modified version of the probiotic Escherichia coli Nissle. Researchers say treatment with SYNB1618 is a two-step process. The first step is to get patients' blood Phe under control. The second step is to relax the diet and slowly add natural protein into their diet. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People with PKU must avoid protein because their bodies cannot breakdown Phe2. Human trials testing the genetically engineered probiotic3. SYNB1618 is a modified version of the probiotic Escherichia coli Nissle4. SYNB1618 is a two-step processVOICEOVER (in English): "People who suffer from phenylketonuria, or PKU, must avoid dietary protein in foods like meat and cheese, because their bodies cannot break down the amino acid phenylalanine, or Phe." "According to the New York Times, researchers at Synlogic have now carried out successful human trials using a genetically engineered probiotic in order to help treat people with PKU.""The treatment is called SYNB1618 and is a modified version of the probiotic Escherichia coli Nissle." "Researchers say treatment with SYNB1618 is a two-step process. The first step is to get patients' blood Phe under control. The second step is to relax the diet and slowly add natural protein into their diet." SOURCES: New York Times, The Scientisthttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/04/health/synthetic-biology-pku.htmlhttps://www.the-scientist.com/news-opinion/synthetic-bacteria-help-treat-phenylketonuria-in-mice-64656***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 11:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/06/3690093/3690093_EE6833ACA87B4F5F9B6304919B6B3A2D_180906_3690093_Researchers_using_synthetic_bacteria_to_cure_dis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/509/F1B/509F1BC4E88847F08ACCEFD04E0D7F77_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, synthetic biology, genetically modified bacterium, modified probiotic, phenylketonuria, phenylalanine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3690863</guid>
      <title>What causes 'black hair' on your tongue?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA 55-year-old woman developed a case of black hairy tongue after taking an antibiotic for an infected wound.The case was published by Dr. Yasir Hamad, an assistant professor in the Department of Medicine at the Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, in the New England Journal of Medicine on Wednesday, according to CNN. The condition refers to when papillae on the tongue grow longer than normal and turn black. Papillae are normally less than a millimeter long, but can grow to between 12 and 18 millimeters in length in patients suffering from the condition. The blackening occurs as the growing papillae trap microscopic food particles that allow bacteria and other microbes to flourish on the tongue. Black hairy tongue is an uncommon and harmless side effect of some drugs, but can also be caused by smoking, bad oral hygiene and some medical conditions. In this case, the woman was taking minocycline to treat a wound infection from a car accident. Within a week, her tongue turned black, she started feeling nauseous and developed a foul taste in her mouth. Four weeks after doctors changed her medication, her tongue turned back to its normal color.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman developing black hairy tongue after taking antibiotic2. Normal papillae growing and turning black3. Blackening occurring from trapped food particles and other causes of the condition4. Woman's tongue turning back to normal colorVOICEOVER (in English): "A 55-year-old woman developed a case of black hairy tongue after taking an antibiotic for an infected wound. The condition refers to when papillae on the tongue grow longer than normal and turn black." "Papillae are normally less than a millimeter long, but can grow to between 12 and 18 millimeters in length in patients suffering from the condition." "The blackening occurs as the growing papillae trap microscopic food particles that allow bacteria and other microbes to flourish on the tongue. It is an uncommon and harmless side effect of some drugs, but can also be caused by smoking, bad oral hygiene and some medical conditions." "In this case, four weeks after doctors changed the woman's medication, her tongue turned back to its normal color."   SOURCES: CNNhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/05/health/black-hairy-tongue-study/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 10:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/07/3690863/3690863_9060C7CCA84E4E9FAA730E613D994A17_180907_3690863_What_causes__black_hair__on_your_tongue__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C43/910/C43910DCA0BD48D8B6C6CA4E2A9E155C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, black hairy tongue, black hair on tongue, papillae, black hairy tongue symptoms, black hairy tongue causes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3692492</guid>
      <title>Red tide hits Tampa Bay</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANToxic algae has wiped out droves of south west Florida's marine life.According to the National Ocean and Atmospheric Administration, red tide algal blooms can produce neurotoxins which are lethal to fish. The algae is deadly to birds, turtles, manatees and dolphins.A red tide bloom 150 miles long was observed last month in South West Florida. It reportedly reached the Tampa Bay area over the weekend. It can also cause hypoxia to fish via oxygen depletion in water. Red tide can be harmful to humans if the neurotoxins become airborne, or by eating infected shellfish. Symptoms of infection can include coughing and irritated eyes, although individuals with respiratory conditions may suffer more serious problems.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of impact on fish2. Depiction of red tide in Florida3. Depiction of impact on oxygen4. Depiction of impact on human healthVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the National Ocean and Atmospheric Administration, red tide algal blooms can produce neurotoxins which are lethal to fish.""The algae is also deadly to birds, turtles, manatees and dolphins.""A red tide bloom 150 miles long was observed last month in South West Florida. It reportedly reached the Tampa Bay area over the weekend." "The algae can also cause hypoxia to fish via oxygen depletion in water.""Red tide can be harmful to humans if the neurotoxins become airborne, or by eating infected shellfish."SOURCES: Tampa Bay Times, NOAA, Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commissionhttps://www.tampabay.com/news/Red-Tide-arrives-in-Pinellas-killing-hundreds-of-thousands-of-fish_171618836https://oceanservice.noaa.gov/news/redtide-florida/http://myfwc.com/redtidestatus***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 11:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/10/3692492/3692492_7C0DD0286B3A48BC8BCF46386F7BE947_180910_3692492_Red_tide_hits_Tampa_Bay_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C1D/C8E/C1DC8ED6F95C45BD8BA7D9B5BEB61DCA_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, red tide, red tide florida, red tide florida 2018, science, technology, toxic algae, red tide algae, science explained, tampa bay]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3692357</guid>
      <title>Installing massive wind and solar farms across the Sahara could affect weather</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists say installing massive wind and solar farms across the Sahara Desert could affect the weather. According to a paper published in the journal Science, the wind turbines could help to double the amount of rain in the region.The researchers say the wind turbines would work to mix warmer air from above and cooler air from below to create a "feedback loop" which would increase precipitation and vegetation growth.The large solar panel farms would absorb a larger percentage of the sunlight in the area, leading to cooler temperatures.The researchers also believe, the energy generated from the wind and solar farms could meet global energy demands.According to the author of the study, the plan "could help agriculture, economic development and social well-being in the Sahara … and other nearby regions."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sahara Desert with a wind and solar farms2. Wind turbines doubling the amount of rain3. Wind turbines mixing warmer and cooler air4. Solar panels reflecting sunlight and reducing temperatureVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists say installing massive wind and solar farms across the Sahara Desert could affect the weather." "According to a paper published in the journal Science, the wind turbines could help to double the amount of rain in the region.""The researchers say the wind turbines would work to mix warmer air from above and cooler air from below to create a 'feedback loop' which would increase precipitation and vegetation growth.""The large solar panel farms would absorb a larger percentage of the sunlight in the area, leading to cooler temperatures."SOURCES: The BBC, Tech Times, Science, The  Independent, NPRhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-45435593https://www.techtimes.com/articles/234154/20180909/building-large-wind-and-solar-farms-in-the-sahara-could-help-green-the-desert-says-study.htmhttp://science.sciencemag.org/content/361/6406/1019https://www.independent.co.uk/environment/wind-solar-power-sahara-desert-green-climate-change-renewable-energy-a8526361.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2018/09/09/645539064/so-maybe-stopping-the-sahara-from-expanding-isn-t-an-impossible-dream***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 09:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/10/3692357/3692357_A227C7A7D3524C949B451B0EFFD3C206_180910_3692357_Installing_massive_wind_and_solar_farms_across_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/542/8DE/5428DE2969934203B5A49CE069AB2D35_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  study, science, wind farms, solar farms, the Sahara desert,solar panels, wind turbines, weather green the Sahara, sunlight, vegetation, agriculture, rain, transforming the Sahara]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3692334</guid>
      <title>Selfie wrist injuries on the rise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a study in the Irish Medical Journal, a selfie wrist often occurs when the distal radius is accidently fractured.The researchers found that people often compromise their sense of space when their trying to take the perfect selfie, leading people to concentrate on their smartphones rather than their surroundings.In more extreme cases, the injury could lead to trauma and or hospitalization.In the study, the researchers noted the importance of educating society of the risks associated with taking selfies in order to reduce selfie-related injuries.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The distal radius is shown in the wrist.2. A woman is shown trying to take a selfie.3. A woman is shown to be so distracted taking a selfie that she bumps into the tree.4. The woman is shown being hospitalized.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study in the Irish Medical Journal, a selfie wrist often occurs when the distal radius is accidently fractured.""The researchers found that people often compromise their sense of space when their trying to take a selfie...""... leading people to concentrate on their smartphones rather than their surroundings.""In more extreme cases, the injury could lead to trauma and or hospitalization."SOURCES: Irish Medical Journal, Irish Examiner, The Journal.ie, The Irish Timeshttp://imj.ie/the-selfie-wrist-selfie-induced-trauma/https://www.irishexaminer.com/ireland/doctors-warn-of-selfie-wrist-injuries-452340.htmlhttp://www.thejournal.ie/selfie-arm-breaks-irish-medical-journal-3440834-Jun2017/https://www.irishtimes.com/news/health/selfie-induced-injuries-leaving-some-snap-unhappy-1.3117229***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/10/3692334/3692334_7DCB311250E94A32867B40C875072EF6_180910_3692334_Selfie_wrist_injuries_on_the_rise_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/F51/C2F/F51C2F51CEF84EB4869BE60B881F2E6E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Selfie wrist, selfie, snapping selfies, dangerous, doctor, wrist, wrist injury, selfie-induced wrist injuries, distal radius, smartphones, social media, injured wrists]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3692323</guid>
      <title>How to avoid and treat head lice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIn the United States alone head lice causes around six to 12 million infestations a year in children between the ages of three and 11. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, head lice is primarily spread by direct contact with the hair of an infected person. The most common way to get head lice is through head-to-head contact at places like school, home and outdoor sports or camp activities. Lice can also be spread when sharing personal care items like combs, brushes, towels and hats. According to the CDC, head lice should be treated with a pediculicide, a medication that kills head lice, that has an ovicidal effect meant to kill head lice eggs.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lice can cause infestations in children between 3 and 112. Lice is commonly contracted through head-to-head contact at places like school, home, outdoor sports or camp activities3. Lice can also be spread through person care items4. Lice can be treated with pediculicide medicationsVOICEOVER (in English): "In the U.S. alone, head lice causes around 6 to 12 million infestations a year in children between the ages of 3 and 11. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, head lice is primarily spread by direct contact with the hair of an infected person." "The most common way to get head lice is through head-to-head contact at places like school, home and outdoor sports or camp activities." "Lice can also be spread when sharing personal care items like combs, brushes, towels and hats." "According to the CDC, head lice should be treated with a pediculicide, a medication that kills head lice, that has an ovicidal effect meant to kill head lice eggs."   SOURCES: Advance Healthcare Network, CDChttp://nursing.advanceweb.com/avoiding-dealing-with-head-lice/https://www.cdc.gov/parasites/lice/head/epi.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/parasites/lice/head/treatment.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 07:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/10/3692323/3692323_4F7BC559C60345CEA1723CA93AA778C5_180910_3692323_How_to_avoid_and_treat_head_lice_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/629/203/629203BEC3064F168988034E74B11EB4_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, head lice, head lice outbreak, lice, lice prevention, lice treatment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3692846</guid>
      <title>Japanese researchers design space elevator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of researchers from Shizuoka University plan to develop a miniature "space elevator" to connect Earth and the International Space Station with a cable.According to The Mainichi Shimbun, researchers plan to develop an approximately 10-meter-long high-strength steel cable, with carbon nanotube being considered to be used as the primary material.They also plan to release a pair of satellites that would connect with the cable, and would measure around 10 centimeters on each side.The space elevator would be made up of six oval-shaped cars, which would be about 18 meters long and 7.2 meters wide.A camera would also be attached to the satellites which would record the elevator as it moves in space.The researchers expect the elevator to travel up to 200 kilometers per hour and carry people as well as cargo shipments into space by 2050.However, the researchers worry there might be problems such as the elevator colliding with space debris, meteorites or even the transmission of electricity from earth to space.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The steel cable is shown going into space along with carbon nanotube.2. Two satellites which would be connected to the space elevator.3. The oval-shaped elevator car to be used is depicted here.4. Cameras on the satellite recording the elevator's movement.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to The Mainichi, the researchers plan to develop an approximately 10-meter-long high-strength steel cable, with carbon nanotube being considered to be used as the primary material.""They also plan to release a pair of satellites that would connect with the cable, and would measure around 10 centimeters on each side.""The space elevator would be made up of six oval-shaped cars, which would be about 18 meters long and 7.2 meters wide.""A camera would also be attached to the satellites which would record the elevator as it moves in space."SOURCES: Phys.org, CNet,The Mainichi, Express, Japan Today, https://phys.org/news/2018-09-japan-mini-space-elevator.htmlhttps://www.cnet.com/news/japan-to-conduct-first-test-as-part-of-space-elevator-project/https://mainichi.jp/english/articles/20180826/p2a/00m/0na/005000chttps://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1012949/japan-space-elevator-platform-shizuoka-university-latesthttps://japantoday.com/category/tech/going-up%21-japan-to-test-mini-space-elevator***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 05:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/11/3692846/3692846_35DB32C75B2E48EE92C8EB73D9FF7A1B_180911_3692846_Japanese_researchers_design_space_elevator_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/0DE/3C4/0DE3C41254074067A1742018CD2A8522_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Japan, Space, Space elevator, future, future travel, traveling in space, technology, outer space, Earth, International Space Station, cable, satellites]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3693781</guid>
      <title>Unique surgery allows cancer patient to dance again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA young cancer survivor is still able to dance thanks to an innovative surgery. Delaney Unger, 12, was diagnosed with osteosarcoma of the left knee in 2016, which would require chemotherapy and amputation of her knee, according to CNN. Because of the location of her Unger's cancer, doctors were able to perform a rare procedure called a rotationplasty. During a 13-hour surgery in April of 2017, she had her left knee completely amputated. Surgeons then took Unger's ankle and foot, rotated them 180 degrees and attached them to the stump of her thigh, according to Newsday. This allowed her ankle to function as a knee. In October of 2017, Unger, who is now cancer free, received a prosthetic which fits over the backward-oriented foot and extends up the thigh. The prosthesis lets her walk, jump and dance.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of osteosarcoma in Unger's left knee2. Unger receiving a rotationplasty3. Unger's ankle and foot being rotated 180 degrees then attached to her thigh4. Unger using her prosthetic leg to walk, jump and danceVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNN, 12-year-old Delaney Unger was diagnosed with osteosarcoma of the left knee in 2016, which required chemotherapy and amputation of her knee."  "Because of the location of her Unger's cancer, doctors were able to perform a rare procedure called a rotationplasty. During a 13 hour surgery in April of 2017, she had her left knee completely amputated.""According to Newsday, surgeons then took Unger's ankle and foot, rotated them 180 degrees and attached them to the stump of her thigh. This allowed her ankle to function as a knee." "In October of 2017, Unger, who is now cancer-free, received a prosthetic which fits over the backward-oriented foot and extends up the thigh. The prosthesis lets her walk, jump and dance."  SOURCES: CNN, Newsdayhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/10/health/cancer-survivor-backward-leg-dance/index.htmlhttps://www.newsday.com/news/health/ankle-knee-surgery-cancer-dancer-1.20932903***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/12/3693781/3693781_C55A23BEFA8544C7B71E44A0E66DBC1A_180912_3693781_Unique_surgery_allows_cancer_patient_to_dance_ag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/DB1/C13/DB1C13D2D18042DB92DFC5E1A6CBD4FA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, osteosarcoma, rotationplasty, prosthetic limbs, knee replacement]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3693636</guid>
      <title>Study finds probiotics might not be as helpful for the intestine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a study published in the journal Cell, probiotics were found to have "little or no effect inside the body."The researchers created their own "probiotic cocktail" by using 11 bacteria such as Lactobacillus and Bifidobacteria to test how well probiotics would colonize a healthy intestine.Half of the participants were given the 'probiotic cocktail while the other half were given a placebo.In about half the cases, the probiotic went in and came out the other end, without doing anything for the body.In the other half, the probiotic stayed for a while before being eventually crowded out by the microbes already in the body.Dr. Eran Elinav, a researcher involved with the study, told the BBC, in the future probiotics would "need to be tailored to the needs of individual patients."The study was conducted with a small group of participants, and needs further studies to confirm the results.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Probiotics are shown and medical body flashes red on the stomach.2. The "probiotic cocktail" is shown along with Lactobacillus and Bifidobacteria.3. A placebo is shown along with the "probiotic cocktail."4. The probiotics are shown inside the intestine.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the journal Cell, probiotics were found to have 'little or no effect inside the body.""The researchers created their own 'probiotic cocktail' by using 11 bacteria such as Lactobacillus and Bifidobacteria to test how well probiotics would colonize a healthy intestine.""Half of the participants were given the 'probiotic cocktail while the other half were given a placebo.""In about half the cases, the probiotic went in and came out the other end, without doing anything for the body. In the other half, the probiotic stayed for a while before being eventually crowded out by the microbes already in the body."SOURCES: Cell, The BBC, Straits Times, ABC News Australiahttps://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(18)31102-4?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0092867418311024%3Fshowall%3Dtruehttps://www.bbc.com/news/health-45434753https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/probiotics-benefits-to-gut-health-remain-questionable-studieshttp://www.abc.net.au/news/health/2018-09-07/probiotics-gut-health-bacteria-research/10208606***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/12/3693636/3693636_60AFD28AF8D14F02BD33A255C67EBA6D_180912_3693636_Study_finds_probiotics_might_not_be_as_helpful_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A9C/6E8/A9C6E85829174474A3D9DD620D1BA5E9_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, study, Israel, probiotics, yogurts, bacteria, good bacteria, intestine, off-the-shelf probiotic, probiotic foods, probiotics and healthy gut bacteria, probiotics bad for you]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3693604</guid>
      <title>Wildlife officials drop fish out of airplanes in Utah</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWildlife officials in Utah have been restocking remote lakes in the mountain by dropping fish from airplanes, reports Live Science.On Twitter, wildlife officials explained the lakes are being stocked "to provide fishing opportunities for the public."Officials say the fish used are usually only about 3 centimeters to 7 centimeters long and are used to restock more than 200 lakes in the state every year.Officials claim about 95% of the fish are expected to survive the drop because of their small size.Previous methods included using milk cans to store the fish and loading it onto animals such as horses to reach remote areas, CNN reports.However, officials say they have been using this method since 1956 and claims it is less stressful on the fish than the previous method used. The previous method of transporting the fish by ground also reportedly took a lot longer than the current method. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Airplane is shown dropping fishes into lake.2. One tiny fish and lake is shown.3. A group of tiny fish is shown. 4. A milk can and a horse is shown.VOICEOVER (in English): "Live Science reports wildlife officials in Utah have been restocking remote lakes in the mountain by dropping fish from airplanes.""Officials say the fish used are usually only about 3 centimeters to 7 centimeters long and are used to restock more than 200 lakes in the state every year.""Officials claim about 95% of the fish are expected to survive the drop because of their small size.""According to CNN, previous methods included using milk cans to store the fish and loading it onto animals such as horses to reach remote areas."SOURCES: Live Science, Utah Division of Wildlife Resources, Fox News, Miami Herald, CNN, https://www.livescience.com/63475-fish-fall-from-plane.htmlhttps://wildlife.utah.gov/http://www.foxnews.com/great-outdoors/2018/08/30/utah-department-wildlife-drops-fish-from-plane-for-extreme-restocking-lake.htmlhttps://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article217557765.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/videos/us/2018/08/31/utah-division-of-wildlife-resources-lakes-aerial-fish-stocking-orig-gs.cnn***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 07:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/12/3693604/3693604_F47D86FC67AA41E18F97F84159910E0B_180912_3693604_Wildlife_officials_drop_fish_out_of_airplanes_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C9F/9EC/C9F9EC6B53E64C06B33F6E5FD9061A5F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  Utah, lakes, wildlife, fishes, utah fish stocking, fish utah, fish utah lake, fish dropped out of planes, aerial fish stocking, remote lakes, fishing in Utah]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3694337</guid>
      <title>Amazon patented a human machine transport system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmazon patented a human machine transport system that pairs up humans and machines. According to the Seattle Times, illustrations that go with the patent, which was granted by the U.S. Patent and Trademark office in 2016, show a cage-like enclosure around a work space positioned on top of a robotic trolley. The company says it does not intend to use the technology, but said it was designed to allow humans to enter robot-only zones in Amazon's automated warehouses to make repairs or retrieve dropped objects. Amazon also said the system could be used to cut across an off-limits work space to reach a restroom. The reference to the cage transport system appears in a case study of the systems that make up Amazon's Echo ecosystem by Kate Crawford and Vladan Joler published on September 7.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Amazon human transport system2. Amazon worker operating the system3. Human transport system being used to pick up a dropped object4. System transporting worker to use restroomVOICEOVER (in English): "Amazon patented a human machine transport system that pairs up humans and machines." "According to the Seattle Times, illustrations that go with the patent, which was granted by the U.S. Patent and Trademark office in 2016, show a cage-like enclosure around a work space positioned on top of a robotic trolley." "The company says it does not intend to use the technology, but said it was designed to allow humans to enter robot-only zones in Amazon's automated warehouses to make repairs or retrieve dropped objects." "Amazon also said the system could be used to cut across an off-limits work space to reach a restroom." SOURCES: Seattle Timeshttps://www.seattletimes.com/business/amazon/amazon-has-patented-a-system-that-would-put-workers-in-a-cage-on-top-of-a-robot/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 08:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/13/3694337/3694337_BD0E4691526F415B9EEC9A8C4B2FBC34_180913_3694337_Amazon_patented_a_human_machine_transport_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/96A/179/96A179A9BBB3483CB2D0B54EB59562EB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Amazon, Amazon human transport system, Amazon patent, Amazon cage like transportation system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3695164</guid>
      <title>Facebook plans to fact-check photos and videos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook has announced plans to scan photos, videos and articles uploaded onto the social media site in order to expand its efforts to combat fake news, according to the Washington Post. The social media giant also listed a few examples of fake images found on the site such as a photoshopped image of a presidential candidate in Mexico and an out of context image of a girl in Syria.Facebook says it will be using an algorithm in 17 different countries including the U.S.Facebook will use reverse image searching as well as analyzing metadata to evaluate if videos or photos have been digitally altered.Once the algorithm identifies an altered image or video, Facebook will send the flagged posts to outside fact-checkers for further review.The new feature is equipped with "machine-learning" and was made to help reviewers quickly identify false content.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. An image being scanned on the Facebook site2. The globe is shown3. Reverse image searching and analyzing the metadata is shown4. Algorithm identifying an altered image and flagging itVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Washington Post, Facebook has announced plans to scan photos, videos and articles uploaded onto the social media site in order to expand its efforts to combat fake news.""Facebook says it will be using an algorithm in 17 different countries including the U.S.""Facebook will use reverse image searching as well as analyzing metadata to evaluate if videos or photos have been digitally altered.""Once the algorithm identifies an altered image or video, Facebook will send the flagged posts to outside fact-checkers for further review."SOURCES: Engadget, The Washington Post, Cnet, Techcrunchhttps://www.engadget.com/2018/09/13/facebook-fake-news-pictures-videos-fact-checking/https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2018/09/13/facebook-ramps-up-effort-combat-fake-images-video/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.0a23fe6abffdhttps://www.cnet.com/news/facebook-will-now-fact-check-photos-videos-as-it-fights-misinformation/https://techcrunch.com/2018/09/13/photo-video-fact-checking/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/14/3695164/3695164_830C103C171D4495B1CDB554F896244C_180914_3695164_Facebook_plans_to_fact_check_photos_and_videos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/5D3/1DB/5D31DB1412C143948A66D1A5F700817B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, facebook, social media, fake news, algorithm, technology, reverse image searching, analyzing metadata]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3695025</guid>
      <title>Translucent fish with no scales found in Pacific Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThree species of translucent fish without scales have been found by a group of scientists in the Pacific Ocean.According to researchers from Newcastle University, the three fish have temporarily been named pink, blue and purple Atacama snailfish.  According to USA Today, they were discovered in the Atacama Trench, an 8,000-meter deep trench located off the west coast of South America. The fish can handle extreme pressure and are translucent with no scales. According to Thomas Linley of Newcastle University, the hardest bones in the fish are located in their inner ear to help them maintain balance and their teeth. "Without the extreme pressure and cold to support their bodies they are extremely fragile and melt rapidly when brought to the surface," Linley said in a statement. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pink, blue and purple Atacama snailfish2. Snailfish swimming in the Atacama Trench3. Snailfish swimming4. Bone structure of the snailfishVOICEOVER (in English): "Three species of translucent fish without scales have been found by a group of scientists in the Pacific Ocean. According to researchers from Newcastle University, the three fish have temporarily been named pink, blue and purple Atacama snailfish."  "According to USA Today, they were discovered in the Atacama Trench, an 8,000 meter deep trench located off the west coast of South America." "The fish can handle extreme pressure and are translucent with no scales." "According to Thomas Linley of Newcastle University, the hardest bones in the fish are located in their inner ear to help them maintain balance and their teeth." SOURCES: USA Todayhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/09/11/three-new-fish-species-discovered-pacific-ocean/1264369002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 09:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/14/3695025/3695025_CD1680B816CC4B92BBD11DB74A113DAC_180914_3695025_Translucent_fish_with_no_scales_found_in_Pacific_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/372/E66/372E664E810A4E1C971D377DF0DAC6F8_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, translucent fish, translucent fish no scales, Atacama Trench, pink Atacama, blue Atacama, purple Atacama, Atacama snailfish]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3696590</guid>
      <title>Illnesses you could get from exposure to flood water from Hurricane Florence</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMembers of the public are at risk of catching illnesses from the flood water left behind by Hurricane Florence.Diarrheal diseases such as cryptosporidiosis, E.Coli or giardiasis could be caused by eating or drinking anything that have come into contact with the contaminated flood water, reports Journal-News.The different diarrheal diseases include symptoms such as diarrhea and nausea.Rashes and open wounds exposed to flood water also increase the risk of people being infected with tetanus, which is a bacterial infection that could break into the skin.Another illness people could contract by being in the flooded waters for too long is trench foot. This illness could cause pain, swelling and numbness.Stagnant flood waters is a gateway for bacteria to enter the body through any open wounds or injuries, ABC News reports.Officials are encouraging the public to try to avoid exposure to floodwaters, and to keep any open wounds as clean and as dry as possible.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Diarrheal diseases that one could get through exposure to contaminated flood water.2. Symptoms of diarrheal diseases.3. Tetanus disease is shown. 4. Trench foot disease is shown.VOICEOVER (in English): "Journal-News reports, diarrheal diseases such as cryptosporidiosis, E.Coli or giardiasis could be caused by eating or drinking anything that have come into contact with the contaminated flood water.""The different diarrheal diseases include symptoms such as diarrhea and nausea.""Rashes and open wounds exposed to flood water also increase the risk of people being infected with tetanus, which is a bacterial infection that could break into the skin.""Another illness people could get by being in the flooded waters for too long is trench foot. This illness could cause pain, swelling and numbness."SOURCES: Journal-News, ABC News, The Weather Channel https://www.journal-news.com/weather/hurricane-florence-aftermath-scary-infectious-illnesses-you-can-catch-from-floodwater/O0867RHawZ9LQit0MTUygN/https://abcnews.go.com/Health/florences-floodwaters-carry-hidden-dangers-electrocution-injury-disease/story?id=57821307https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2018-09-16-florence-health-hazards-electrocution-infection-injury***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 08:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/17/3696590/3696590_3AF1F95204004D2E877FFC0FC159F2C7_180917_3696590_Illnesses_you_could_get_from_exposure_to_flood_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/56A/CC6/56ACC67AA7204BDFA28C2E2765594392_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Hurricane Florence, illness, flood water, contamination, flood water contamination,bacteria, disease, cryptosporidiosis, E.Coli, giardiasis, wounds, tetanus, trench foot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3696576</guid>
      <title>Flashes of light show how plants signal distress</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have found that plants communicate distress by using their own signaling system. University of Wisconsin-Madison Professor of Botany Simon Gilroy and his lab revealed how glutamate activates a wave of calcium that spreads across leaves to warn of danger in a paper published on Sept. 13 in the journal Science. "We know there's this systematic signaling system, and if you wound in one place the rest of the plant triggers its defense responses," said Gilroy, speaking to the University of Wisconsin's news service. "But we didn't know what was behind this system." "We do know if you wound a leaf, you get an electrical charge, and you get a propagation that moves across the plant," he added. The scientists wanted to know what triggered the electric charge, and how it moved throughout the plant. Calcium was one possibility, but the researchers needed to be able to see calcium in real time, so special plants were developed the produce a protein that only fluoresces around calcium. The team then subjected the plants to caterpillar bites, scissor cuts and crushing wounds and used video to track the responses.In response to each type of distress, videos show the plants lighting up as calcium spreads from the site of damage to other leaves. The signal spread to the other leaves in a few minutes, which was then followed by a spike in defense-related hormones in distant leaves. The scientists were then able to pinpoint glutamate as the trigger the sent out the waves of calcium. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Researchers finding out glutamate activates calcium wave in plants2. Calcium wave spreading through leaves under distress3. Calcium wave spreading through plant4. Plants were subjected to different types of distress to cause calcium wavesVOICEOVER (in English): "University of Wisconsin-Madison Professor of Botany Simon Gilroy and his lab have revealed how glutamate activates a wave of calcium that spreads across leaves to warn of danger." "Scientists already knew that wounding a plant triggers a defense response, and that if you wound a leaf, you get an electrical charge, as well as a propagation that moves across plants. Gilroy and his team wanted to know what triggered the charge and how it moved through the plant."  "Calcium was one possibility, but the researchers needed to be able to see calcium in real time, so special plants were developed the produce a protein that only fluoresces around calcium." "The team then subjected the plants to caterpillar bites, scissor cuts and crushing wounds and used video to track the responses. In response to each type of distress, videos show the plants lighting up as calcium spreads from the site of damage to other leaves. The scientists were then able to pinpoint glutamate as the trigger the sent out the waves of calcium."SOURCES: University of Wisconsin-Madison, Science Magazine https://news.wisc.edu/blazes-of-light-reveal-how-plants-signal-danger-long-distances/http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/09/plants-communicate-distress-using-their-own-kind-nervous-system***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 08:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/17/3696576/3696576_E0076829AE414449838D02E28E58A9AE_180917_3696576_Flashes_of_light_show_how_plants_signal_distress_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/364/05E/36405E74E532453A9BE75E0D0C9D0708_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, plant distress, plant systematic signaling system, glutamate, calcium in plants]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3696481</guid>
      <title>Influx of spiders in UK homes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe reason why there is an increase of spiders appearing in people's' home is because it is mating season from September until October, the BBC reports.Professor Adam Hart, an entomologist who conducted research on the behavior pattern of spiders and how they are affected during different seasons, found that 82% of the spiders seen in houses are male.He explained female spiders are usually seen in webs formed in garages or window sills while the male spiders generally wander around looking for a dry place to mate.Professor Hart suggested keeping doors and windows closed and keeping the house clean to deter spiders.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Spiders and calendar icon.2. We see bigger spiders.3. Spiders are shown in the garage and window sills.4. Ways to deter spiders.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, the reason why there is an increase of spiders appearing in people's' home is because it is mating season from September until October.""Professor Adam Hart, an entomologist who conducted research on the behavior pattern of spiders and how they are affected during different seasons, found that 82% of the spiders seen in houses are male.""He explained female spiders are usually seen in webs formed in garages or window sills...""Professor Hart suggested keeping doors and windows closed and keeping the house clean to deter spiders."SOURCES: Wales Online, BioOne, BBC, Birmingham Live, Cambridgeshire Live, The Telegraphhttps://www.walesonline.co.uk/news/uk-news/more-spiders-starting-appear-your-15131334?utm_source=facebook.com&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=wales_main&_ga=2.201584209.112380977.1536719780-159262895.1536719780http://www.bioone.org/doi/abs/10.13156/arac.2017.17.7.331https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-45446568https://www.birminghammail.co.uk/news/midlands-news/more-creepy-spiders-invading-your-15138487https://www.cambridge-news.co.uk/news/uk-world-news/get-rid-house-spider-season-15138883https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/09/07/should-avoid-home-735pm-scared-spiders/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 05:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/17/3696481/3696481_09DD26B9631B465A93DE2250AF775C1F_180917_3696481_Influx_of_spiders_in_UK_homes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/92C/14F/92C14FE080D14264AA73F5203C9EA346_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, spider, home, UK, spider season, spiders UK, mating season, male spiders, female spiders, influx of spiders]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3697317</guid>
      <title>The difference between Hurricane Florence and Typhoon Mangkhut</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo powerful storms have been causing destruction on opposite sides of the earth, one in the southeastern coast of China and one in the east coast of the U.S., but both have been wreaking havoc in different ways.Typhoon Mangkhut had winds of 165 miles per hour, compared to Hurricane Florence which only had winds of 90 miles per hour when it hit North Carolina's coast, according to the weather channel.However, Hurricane Florence was deadly in terms of the amount of rain it produced,  causing water damage.Typhoon Mangkhut formed farther south in the western Pacific where water is warmer, which gave the typhoon the "perfect environment to intensify."In comparison, Hurricane Florence formed near Africa, and was out of the tropics by the time it made landfall, which caused the hurricane to be weakened by the dry air in the region.Experts say that both are "storms of the same type," but those that occur in the Pacific west of the International Date Line are called typhoons instead of hurricanes.They also expect Typhoon Mangkhut to be the deadlier storm, as it has already caused death and destruction in the Philippines, and is now heading for China's southeastern coast.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Typhoon Mangkhut is shown going towards the Philippines and China.2. Hurricane Florence is seen going to the US and dumping rain.3. Typhoon Mangkhut is seen forming and intensifying.4. Hurricane Florence is seen forming and weakening.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to the weather channel, Typhoon Mangkhut had winds of 165 miles per hour, compared to Hurricane Florence which only had winds of 90 miles per hour when it hit North Carolina's coast.""However, Hurricane Florence was deadly in terms of the amount of rain it produced,  causing water damage.""Typhoon Mangkhut formed farther south in the western Pacific where water is warmer, which gave the typhoon the 'perfect environment to intensify.' ""In comparison, Hurricane Florence formed near Africa, and was out of the tropics by the time it made landfall, which caused the hurricane to be weakened by the dry air in the region."SOURCES:The Weather Channel, ABC News,  https://weather.com/en-IN/india/news/news/2018-09-17-florence-mangkhut-water-windhttps://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/natures-fury-differently-florence-mangkhut-57849986***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/18/3697317/3697317_ED6580EA6AA74BC891158FEB3B464CA7_180918_3697317_The_difference_between_Hurricane_Florence_and_Ty_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/794/40B/79440BD576E2420F84A547BE9F52B2DB_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, hurricane florence 2018, hurricane florence, typhoon mangkhut,typhoon in philippines 2018, typhoon mangkhut hong kong,typhoon hong kong,  typhoon mangkhut philippines, typhoon vs hurricane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3697313</guid>
      <title>Flood of Mt. Gox payouts could trigger bitcoin crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANExperts are warning of a possible market crash as a now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange is set to finally payout its creditors.Fortune reports that in 2014, 850,000 bitcoins then valued at US$473 million were stolen from Japan-based exchange Mt. Gox, in one of the biggest digital heists in cryptocurrency history.Mt. Gox has since filed for bankruptcy, but is now set to finally payout 160,000 bitcoins at current valuations to its customers.A former Mt. Gox trader who "spearheaded the investigation into the exchange's bankruptcy" told the Telegraph that it's likely those who get their coins back will want to immediately sell them off, potentially causing supply to outstrip demand.And with the value of bitcoin already plunging in recent months, there are fears that the flood of payouts could lead to a price drop that would ultimately crash the market.Mt. Gox customers who lost money in the heist can file their payout claims until October 22, after which coin distribution is expected to begin.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of 2014 Mt. Gox digital heist2. Depiction of Mt. Gox bankruptcy and 2018 payout3. Depiction of bitcoin payout sold for cash4. Depiction of bitcoin crashVOICEOVER (in English): "In 2014, over 800,000 bitcoins then valued at nearly $500 million were stolen from Japan-based exchange Mt. Gox, in one of the biggest digital heists in cryptocurrency history.""Mt. Gox has since filed for bankruptcy, but is set to finally payout 160,000 bitcoins at current valuations to its customers.""Experts say it's likely those who get their coins back will want to immediately sell them off, potentially causing supply to outstrip demand.""And with the value of bitcoin already plunging in recent months, there are fears that the flood of payouts could lead to a price drop that would ultimately crash the market."SOURCES: The Telegraph, Fortune, Crypto News Reviewhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/09/16/flood-payouts-could-crash-bitcoin-market/http://fortune.com/longform/bitcoin-mt-gox-hack-karpeles/https://cryptonewsreview.com/fresh-concerns-over-possible-upcoming-bitcoin-market-crash/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/18/3697313/3697313_3C98C0C5FFF046B68F35BAA174270BA2_180918_3697313_Flood_of_Mt__Gox_payouts_could_trigger_bitcoin_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/58B/46E/58B46EA884DB4545A9ADABEC20AF43FC_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, bitcoin, bitcoin crash, mt gox, bitcoin exchange, cryptocurrency exchange, bitcoin heist, bitcoin hack, mt gox payout, bitcoin value, bitcoin price drop]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3697100</guid>
      <title>Chemicals in personal care products could be disrupting female hormones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has found that chemicals in skincare products can negatively affect women's hormones, and may even lead to infertility or breast cancer.According to the George Mason University study published in the journal Environment International, beauty products often contain environmental products such as parabens, which are antimicrobial preservatives, or benzophenones, which serve as UV filters.Researchers collected over 500 samples from 143 women aged 18 to 44 who had no chronic health conditions and didn't use birth control.Analysis of the samples indicate that those with the chemicals present in their system produced abnormal amounts of the reproductive hormones estrogen and progesterone, reports the Independent.Too much estrogen has been linked to fibroids and irregular periods, but too little prevents eggs from maturing. Excessive progesterone, meanwhile, is associated with breast cancer and unusual vaginal bleeding.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of chemicals in skincare products 2. Depiction of urine samples3. Chemicals present in urine linked to abnormal hormone levels4. Effects of abnormal estrogen and progesterone levelsVOICEOVER (in English): "Beauty products often contain chemicals such as parabens, which are antimicrobial preservatives, or benzophenones, which serve as UV filters.""Researchers from George Mason University collected over 500 samples from 143 women aged 18 to 44 who had no chronic health conditions and didn't use birth control.""Analysis of the samples indicate that those with the chemicals present in their system produced abnormal amounts of the reproductive hormones estrogen and progesterone.""Too much estrogen has been linked to fibroids and irregular periods, but too little prevents eggs from maturing. Excessive progesterone, meanwhile, is associated with breast cancer and unusual vaginal bleeding."SOURCES: George Mason University, The Independenthttps://chhs.gmu.edu/news/571246https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/beauty-products-breast-cancer-fertility-chemicals-women-birth-control-makeup-a8538931.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 06:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/18/3697100/3697100_8A16C81793D64737A6248D1A461CCD59_180918_3697100_Chemicals_in_personal_care_products_could_be_dis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/5EA/336/5EA3369B955C4878A7DB6A952E884D1A_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, beauty products, chemicals, hormones, female hormones, paraben, benzophenone, estrogen, cosmetics, personal care, UV filters]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3697085</guid>
      <title>BPA-Free plastics found to be as harmful as regular plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study published in Current Biology determined BPA-free plastic products aren't necessarily safer.Twenty years ago, when the researchers conducted the experiment for the first time, BPA was found to give rise to chromosomally abnormal embryos in mice, leading the researchers to believe the same could be happening to humans.BPA was found to interfere with the endocrine system in the body which regulates everything from fertility to brain development.In this new study, researchers used BPS, a bisphenol which is used to replace BPA, and found the mice in the study all began to develop reproductive problems even though they were kept in BPA-free cages  similar to their previous study.BPA was found to affect the developing brain, heart, lungs, as well as other organs in the body.The researchers are warning the public about the dangers of different types of plastics used in consumer products as they could ultimately affect the body.A researcher involved in the study said plastic containers should never be put into the microwave or dishwasher because this causes the chemicals in the container to leak.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. We see a mouse and an abnormal embryo inside it2. Endocrine system in the body.3. BPS is shown, along with the reproductive system of mice.4. The effects of BPA.VOICEOVER (in English): "Twenty years ago, when the researchers conducted the experiment for the first time, BPA was found to give rise to chromosomally abnormal embryos in mice, leading the researchers to believe the same could be happening to humans.""BPA was found to interfere with the endocrine system in the body which regulates everything from fertility to brain development.""In this new study, researchers used BPS, a bisphenol which is used to replace BPA, and found the mice in the study all began to develop reproductive problems even though they were kept in BPA-free cages  similar to their previous study.""BPA was found to affect the developing brain, heart, lungs, as well as other organs in the body."SOURCES: Cell, The Scientist, Science Mag, News Medical.net, Physics World, Medical Xpress, https://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(18)30861-3https://www.the-scientist.com/news-opinion/bpa-and-its-replacements-have-same-effects-on-mice-64795http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/09/bpa-substitutes-may-be-just-bad-popular-consumer-plastichttps://www.news-medical.net/news/20180916/BPA-free-plastic-not-safe-either-finds-study.aspxhttps://physicsworld.com/a/replacement-bisphenols-are-endocrine-disrupters-too/https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-09-bpa-substitutes-health-issues.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 05:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/18/3697085/3697085_6E8C220351AB43A2A75C23AB57D54F53_180918_3697085_BPA_Free_plastics_found_to_be_as_harmful_as_regu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/82E/5C2/82E5C22D89644D46956DAA2248FD40B9_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, plastic, BPA, BPS, BPA-free plastic,EPA plastic dangers, BPS, harmful to health, plastic is harmful to health, dangers of plastic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3697974</guid>
      <title>Global warming increasing hurricane intensity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGlobal warming is affecting hurricanes by making them wetter with more energy that intensify faster. According to the Associated Press, storm surges are more dangerous because of rising sea levels, with storms moving more slowly, thus increased levels of precipitation. The Associated Press talked with 17 meteorologists and researchers who study climate change, hurricanes or both.Dean of the environment school at the University of Michigan Jonathan Overpeck said, "Florence is yet another poster child for the human-supercharged storms that are becoming more common and destructive as the planet warms."Several months after Hurricane Harvey, studies found climate change significantly increased the chances for Harvey's record rain falls. Scientists say that for every degree the air warms, it can hold almost 4 percent more water and feeds more energy into the storm. University of Exeter climate scientist Peter Stott said the warmer air and water also make storms more intense or stronger. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration climate scientist Jim Kossin and Overpeck also mentioned that studies have shown storms intensifying more rapidly than before. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Large hurricane at sea2. Storm surge3. Increased temperature causes air to hold more water, and storms to have more energy4. Increased air and water temperature making hurricanes strongerVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Associated Press, who talked with 17 meteorologists and researchers who study climate change, hurricanes or both, global warming is affecting hurricanes by making them wetter with more energy that intensify faster.""Storm surges are also more dangerous because of rising sea levels, with storms moving more slowly, thus increased levels of precipitation and flooding." "Scientists say that for every degree the air warms, it can hold almost 4 percent more water and feeds more energy into the storm." "Climate scientists say the warmer air and water make storms stronger. Recent studies have also shown storms intensifying more rapidly than before." SOURCES: Associated Presshttps://apnews.com/47d8e0bf05354260931de08ad9976a37***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 10:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/19/3697974/3697974_179B55938BBC4FF2BA68E0758C18801D_180919_3697974_Global_warming_increasing_hurricane_intensity_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/BB5/851/BB5851AB9BE14D389FBB258BC2277C54_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, climate change, global warming, hurricanes, typhoons, hurricane intensity, storm surge, storm intensity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3697953</guid>
      <title>Household disinfectants could be linked to child obesity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCommonly used household disinfectants and multi-surface cleaners could be making children overweight by affecting their gut bacteria, according to a study published on Monday in the Canadian Medical Association Journal.  Infants living in households where antimicrobial disinfectants were used at least once a week were twice as likely to have elevated levels of the bacteria Lachnospiraceae at ages 3 to 4 months than children whose homes did not use disinfectants frequently, according to CNN. According to Anita Kozyrskyj, lead author of the study, higher levels of Lachnospiraceae in animal studies have been associated with higher body fat and insulin resistance. Researchers collected stool samples from 757 infants and analyzed their body mass index, BMI, at older ages in addition to parental use of disinfectant products.Scientists found that around 80 percent of Canadian households use disinfectant products at least once a week.  While the team found an increase in Lachnospiraceae with increased antimicrobial disinfectants, they did not find the same association in disinfectants without the bacteria-killing ingredients or eco-friendly cleaners. "These results suggest that gut microbiota were the culprit in the association between disinfectant use and the overweight," said Kozyrskyj, according to CNN. Though the results show connection between disinfectants and the gut microbiome, that does not imply causation. According to Kozyrskyj, further studies need to be carried out to establish a causal relationship. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Disinfectants affecting an infant's gut bacteria2. Study parameters3. Study found elevated levels of Lachnospiraceae in households using more disinfectants4. Disinfectants without antimicrobial agents were not associated with elevated levels of LachnospiraceaeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the Canadian Medical Association Journal, commonly used household disinfectants and multi-surface cleaners could be making children overweight by affecting their gut bacteria."  "According to CNN, researchers collected stool samples from 757 infants, analyzed their body mass index at older ages and parental use of disinfectant products. Higher levels of Lachnospiraceae bacteria in animal studies have been associated with higher body fat.""The study found infants living in households where antimicrobial disinfectants were used at least once a week were twice as likely to have elevated levels of Lachnospiraceae at ages 3 to 4 months old than children whose homes did not use disinfectants frequently." "While the team found an increase in Lachnospiraceae with increased antimicrobial disinfectants, they did not find the same association in disinfectants without the bacteria-killing ingredients or eco-friendly cleaners. This suggests an association between disinfectant use and the overweight."SOURCES: CNNhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/17/health/disinfectants-baby-gut-microbiota-bmi-study/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 10:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/19/3697953/3697953_419715344CB44E1A87FE03EAA51778F2_180919_3697953_Household_disinfectants_could_be_linked_to_child_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/0E5/ACE/0E5ACEF81362487DBF1C03F8FBB328C5_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, childhood obesity, child obesity disinfectants, household disinfectants, multi-purpose cleaners, disinfectants]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3697702</guid>
      <title>Study finds a few pieces of plastic enough to kill sea turtles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers found that ingesting just one piece of plastic could increase the chance of a sea turtle to die by 22 percent, according to a study published in the Scientific Reports.The researchers found younger turtles have a higher risk of dying from plastic than adult turtles as they tend to float with the ocean currents where most of the small lightweight plastic lies.Adult turtles in comparison tend to be choosier with what they eat, choosing instead to eat sea grass and crustaceans.The researchers explained a even a thin, flimsy piece of plastic could block the intestine, resulting in blockage in the long run. While harder pieces of plastic could cause internal injuries, which could ultimately lead to death.The study also found that about half of the sea turtles on Earth have already consumed plastic.Dr. Hardesty, one of the authors of the study, said we should "rethink our relationship with plastic" and work to reduce the turtles' exposure to plastic.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sea turtle and pieces of plastic.2.A young turtle surrounded by plastic in the ocean.3. The sea turtle's intestine is blocked by a piece of plastic. 4. Hard plastic causing internal injury to sea turtle.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the Scientific Reports, researchers found that ingesting just one piece of plastic could increase the chance of a sea turtle to die by 22 percent.""The researchers found younger turtles have a higher risk of dying from plastic than adult turtles as they tend to float with the ocean currents where most of the small lightweight plastic lies.""The researchers explained a even a thin, flimsy piece of plastic could block the intestine, resulting in blockage in the long run...""..while harder pieces of plastic could cause internal injuries."SOURCES: The BBC, The New York Times, Scientific Reports, ABC Australia, The Independent, https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-45509822https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/13/science/sea-turtles-plastic.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-30038-zhttp://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-14/eating-14-pieces-of-plastic-enough-to-kill-turtles/10243618https://www.independent.co.uk/environment/turtles-plastic-pollution-deaths-australia-microplastic-waste-a8536041.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 04:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/19/3697702/3697702_082B9A381BCC41A28908AA1DE3BAD844_180919_3697702_Study_finds_a_few_pieces_of_plastic_enough_to_ki_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9BD/265/9BD2651F1F724794B21EBC65BD181948_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Australia, study, plastic, plastic pollution,plastic pollution in the ocean, plastic sea pollution, turtles, oceans, marine life, sea turtles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3698501</guid>
      <title>Microplastics could be entering food chain through mosquitoes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMicroplastics could be entering the food chain through mosquitoes, threatening birds and other creatures that consume the flying insects, according to new research. Scientists from the University of Reading fed microplastics to mosquito larvae, and discovered the plastics remained inside the insects after they became adults. The study was published in the journal Biology Letters on Wednesday. Researchers used Culex pipiens mosquitoes because of their prevalence around many global habitats. The team found the larvae consumed fluorescent microplastic particles that were 0.0002 centimeters in size.  According to The Guardian, as the larvae matured into the pupa stage and then into adult mosquitoes, many of the particles were transferred as well. This means that creatures that eat the mosquitoes  such as birds, bats and spiders  are also ingesting the plastics. The lead author of the study, Amanda Callaghan, a biological scientist at Reading told the AFP, although the research was carried out in a lab, it was "highly possible" this process was also occurring in the wild.  "It's a very major problem and those plastics already in the environment are going to be with us for a very, very long time," Callaghan said.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mosquitoes with microplastics about to be eaten by a bird2. Larvae being fed microplastics3. Microplastics found in pupa and adult forms4. Birds, bats and spiders eating mosquitoes carrying microplasticsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to new research, microplastics could be entering the food chain through mosquitoes, threatening birds and other creatures that consume the flying insects.""Researchers from the University of Reading used Culex pipiens mosquitoes because of their prevalence around many global habitats. The team found the larvae consumed fluorescent microplastic particles that were 0.0002 cm in size."  "According to the Guardian, as the larvae matured into the pupa stage and then into adult mosquitoes, many of the particles were transferred as well." "This means that creatures that eat the mosquitoes  such as birds, bats and spiders  are also ingesting the plastics." SOURCES: The Guardian, Phys.org, Biology Lettershttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/sep/19/microplastics-can-spread-via-flying-insects-research-showshttps://phys.org/news/2018-09-microplastics-foodchain-mosquitoes.htmlhttp://rsbl.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/14/9/20180479***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 08:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/20/3698501/3698501_6A06633BC2A742518CAB494379FDCE67_180920_3698501_Microplastics_could_be_entering_food_chain_throu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/982/EAC/982EAC3F26174A22A22ECFEBEEC18FCF_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, microplastics, microplastics pollution, microbeads, microplastics mosquitoes, mosquito larvae microplastics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3698438</guid>
      <title>Researchers find abundant marine life at area once thought to be an "oceanic desert"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have conducted research as to why the great white sharks gather in the Pacific Ocean during winter and spring, according to the Monterey Bay Aquarium Research Institute.Researchers added tags to 20 sharks to track their movement in the ocean.The sharks were found leaving California waters in December to head for the middle of the ocean between Hawaii and California, an area the scientists considered to be an "oceanic desert."Scientists then used a research vessel called Falkor to explore the area, and found the "oceanic desert" was actually an oasis, as there was an abundance of jellyfish, phytoplankton, squid and fish, leading the researchers to refer to the area as the "White Shark Cafe."Marine life in the region were found swimming up and down the water column, in what is known as the midwater range.The scientists believe the sharks were feasting on the tiny marine life in the area, however they aren't completely sure as there is a possibility the sharks were also mating in the region.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tags are shown being added onto sharks.2. The sharks are shown swimming away and an X is marked on the coast of California and in the middle of the ocean.3. A research vessel is out in the sea, and an "oceanic oasis" is shown.4. Different marine life are shown swimming up and down.VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers added tags to 20 sharks to track their movement in the ocean..""The sharks were found leaving California waters in December to head for the middle of the ocean between Hawaii and California, an area the scientists considered to be an 'oceanic desert.'""Scientists then used a research vessel called Falkor to explore the area, and found the 'oceanic desert' was actually an oasis, as there was an abundance of jellyfish, phytoplankton, squid and fish...""Marine life in the region were found swimming up and down the water column, in what is known as the midwater range."SOURCES: Live Science, Monterey Bay Aquarium Research Institute, Schmidt Ocean Institutehttps://www.livescience.com/63614-great-white-sharks-lair.htmlhttps://www.mbari.org/shark-cafe-marine-life/https://schmidtocean.org/cruise/voyage-white-shark-cafe/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 07:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/20/3698438/3698438_2C85A010DA614E7E846C973F8E583B83_180920_3698438_Researchers_find_abundant_marine_life_at_area_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/087/65D/08765DE933874DB0B73F0C3447718240_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,Great White Shark,great white shark eating, shark gathering, mid-Pacific Ocean, shark videos, marine life, White Shark Cafe, White Shark Cafe video, White Shark Cafe research]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3698399</guid>
      <title>Daily aspirin has no benefit and may be harmful for healthy older adults, study says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaking a daily low-dose aspirin may have no benefit, or might actually be harmful to healthy, older adults, according to a new study. The study followed more than 19,000 people ages 65 and older in the United States and Australia for an average of 4.7 years, according to NPR. The results were published in the New England Journal of Medicine on Sunday. Participants were given 100 milligrams of aspirin daily or a placebo. According to NBC News, at the end of the trial period, 90.3 percent of the aspirin-treated patients were still alive, compared with 90.5 percent of those given placebos. The rates of physical disability and dementia were similar in both groups, while the rates of coronary heart disease, heart attacks and strokes were also similar. "We found there was no discernible benefit of aspirin on prolonging independent, healthy life for the elderly," said Anne Murray, a geriatrician and epidemiologist at Hennepin Healthcare in Minneapolis, who helped lead the study, according to NPR. The study found a significant risk of internal gastric bleeding in the aspirin-treated group, as well as a slight increase in cancer deaths within the same group.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Aspirin pills may have no benefit or might be harmful to older, healthy adults2. Study followed 19,000 participants for an average of 4.7 years3. Results for the aspirin-treated group and placebo-treated group were similar4. Aspirin group had internal gastric bleeding and increase in cancer deathsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the New England Journal of Medicine, taking a daily low-dose aspirin may have no benefit, or might actually be harmful to healthy, older adults." "According to NPR, the study followed more than 19,000 people ages 65 and older in the United States and Australia for an average of 4.7 years. Participants were given 100 milligrams of aspirin daily or a placebo."  "According to NBC News, at the end of the trial, 90.3 percent of the aspirin-treated patients were still alive, compared with 90.5 percent of those given placebos. The rates of physical disability and dementia were similar in both groups, while the rates of coronary heart disease, heart attacks and strokes were also similar." "The study found a significant risk of internal gastric bleeding in the aspirin-treated group, as well as a slight increase in cancer deaths with the aspirin group." SOURCES: NPR, NBC Newshttps://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2018/09/16/647415462/study-a-daily-baby-aspirin-has-no-benefit-for-healthy-older-peoplehttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/heart-health/daily-aspirin-may-be-harmful-healthy-older-adults-large-study-n909791?cid=par-twitter-feed_20180916***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 06:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/20/3698399/3698399_F44393BA230A43EA8D723001076810B4_180920_3698399_Daily_aspirin_has_no_benefit_and_may_be_harmful__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A74/D53/A74D530E2D494CD0AA1DCEB396203326_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, aspirin, low-dose aspirin, aspirin harmful healthy older people, aspirin no benefit elderly]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3699564</guid>
      <title>Scientists develop sodium battery as alternative to lithium-ion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found a way to successfully synthesize sodium as a viable replacement for lithium-ion in batteries.As the rare lithium used in most batteries is fast becoming scarce, scientists are looking into sodium, which is more abundant, and can service large power facilities at a lower cost, according to a Purdue University report.The problem with sodium is that it explodes when exposed to water. Sodium ions in a battery also tend to stick to the anode, building up into a solid electrolyte interface that can grow too large and hamper charging ability.To make sodium functional, Purdue University scientists used ultrasonic dispersion to melt it into a purple liquid. Once cooled into a powder, it is suspended in hexane for even particle distribution.A few drops of the suspension liquid on cathode or anode electrodes allows a sodium-ion battery to function with more stability, and at a higher capacity.According to Purdue assistant professor of chemical engineering Vilas Pol, adding in the sodium requires only minimal modifications to the battery production process, making it both promising and practical.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Advantage of sodium over lithium-ion batteries2. Issues with creating a sodium battery3. Depiction of sodium powder synthesis4. Depiction of functional sodium-ion batteryVOICEOVER (in English): "With rare lithium used in most batteries becoming scarce, scientists are looking into sodium, which is abundant, and can service large power facilities at a lower cost.""The problem with sodium is that it explodes when exposed to water. Sodium ions in a battery also tend to stick to the anode, building up into a solid electrolyte interface that can grow too large and hamper charging ability.""To make sodium functional, Purdue University scientists used ultrasonic dispersion to melt it into a purple liquid. Once cooled into a powder, it is suspended in hexane for even particle distribution.""A few drops of the suspension liquid on cathode or anode electrodes allows a sodium-ion battery to function with more stability, and at a higher capacity."SOURCES: Journal of Power Sources, Purdue Universityhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0378775318306712#undfig1https://www.purdue.edu/newsroom/releases/2018/Q3/super-cheap-earth-element-to-advance-new-battery-tech-to-the-industry.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 15:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/21/3699564/3699564_E342AA0B05AB4A9F8283A635081536A6_180921_3699564_Scientists_develop_sodium_battery_as_alternative_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/57D/027/57D02775F25F40ACB05CEE53D800C0AB_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, battery, batteries, sodium battery, sodium ion battery, lithium battery, lithium ion battery, sodium powder, cheap batteries, purdue university]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3699080</guid>
      <title>This year's autumn equinox to take place on Saturday</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThis year's fall equinox takes place on Saturday, September 22, 9:54 p.m. Eastern time, marking the end of summer, according to the weather channel.The autumn equinox, also known as the September equinox, occurs when the sun crosses the earth's equator from the Northern Hemisphere into the Southern Hemisphere.During the winter, Earth's Northern Hemisphere tilts away from the sun, and during the summer it tilts toward the sun. The shift in Earth's tilt is what causes the change in  seasons.During the equinox, day and night will be balanced to about 12 hours around the world.The Autumn equinox usually takes places on September 22, 23 or 24 in the Northern Hemisphere.After this, the days will start to get shorter while the nights get longer as it enters the winter season.The term "equinox" comes from two latin words meaning equal and night.This occasion is celebrated in different parts in the world, with some cultures the event by spending time with loved ones. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Autumn equinox is shown.2. Earth's tilt changes.3. A clock is shown rotating.4. Three calendar icons are shown to symbolize the dates the event usually takes place each year.VOICEOVER (in English): "The autumn equinox, also known as the September equinox, occurs when the sun crosses the earth's equator from the Northern Hemisphere into the Southern Hemisphere.""During the winter, Earth's Northern Hemisphere tilts away from the sun, and during the summer it tilts toward the sun. The shift in Earth's tilt is what causes the change in  seasons.""During the equinox, day and night will be balanced to about 12 hours around the world.""The Autumn equinox usually takes place on September 22, 23 or 24 in the Northern Hemisphere."SOURCES: USA Today, Tree Hugger, Express Co. UK, The Weather Channelhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/09/18/first-day-fall-autumnal-equinox-saturday/1347214002/https://www.treehugger.com/natural-sciences/12-facts-about-autumnal-equinox.htmlhttps://www.express.co.uk/life-style/life/1018265/autumn-equinox-2018-when-is-autumn-equinox-what-is-september-equinoxhttps://weather.com/science/nature/news/2018-09-19-fall-autumnal-equinox-september-2018***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 06:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/21/3699080/3699080_0C5B0CA6820942AB8C76D152E7FB3E86_180921_3699080_This_year_s_autumn_equinox_to_take_place_on_Satu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/C7F/8B3/C7F8B383670541DCA283567D66DC2E7C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,fall equinox 2018, fall equinox, equinox, autumn equinox, autumn equinox 2018, end of summer, summer, autumn, first day of autumn, first day of fall, Northern hemisphere, Southern hemisphere, september equinox]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3700862</guid>
      <title>Giant pandas can distinguish their mate through calls</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPandas are able to identify one another by their calls, according to a study published in  Scientific Reports.Pandas have a more than a dozen distinct vocal sounds they make but when it is time for mating season, there is a distinct sound that both male and female giant pandas use, a husky, rapid vibrato known as a bleat.The bleat helps to alert other pandas if there is a mate available in the area. It also contains information such as the size and identity of the panda.Pandas have a short mating season as the female pandas only ovulate once a year and are able to conceive for only a few days in an year, according to the New York Times.The researchers recorded the bleats of giant pandas and tested how well the sound would travel through dense bamboo thickets.However, the researchers found that the bleat works best if a potential mate is less than 10 meters away.The study could help conservationists trying to encourage pandas to breed as their population continues to dwindle.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two pandas are shown at a distance2. Male and female panda bleating3. Bleating sound traveling through the bamboo forest4. Potential mate for panda is shown at a distanceVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the Scientific Reports, pandas are able to identify one another by their calls, up to 20 meters in distance.""Pandas have a more than a dozen distinct vocal sounds, but when it is time for mating season, there is a distinct sound that both male and female giant pandas use, a husky, rapid vibrato known as the bleat.""The researchers recorded the bleats of giant pandas and tested how well the sound would travel through dense bamboo thickets.""Scientists found that the bleat works best if a potential mate is less than 10 meters away."SOURCES: BBC News, Scientific Reports, New York Times, https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-45575604https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-31155-5https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/20/science/panda-bleats.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 10:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/24/3700862/3700862_F380CDAA9FDD46F1B6B02F035B438FA2_180924_3700862_Giant_pandas_can_distinguish_their_mate_through__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/913/749/913749D272F54CB6A982EBE3FA680A7E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,panda, giant pandas, mating calls, bleat, pandas mating calls, panda mating season, bamboo, forest, bleating, pandas bleating, panda vocal sounds, panda video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3701313</guid>
      <title>Changes to SpaceX's BFR spacecraft headed for Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpaceX's Mars-colonizing Big Falcon Rocket spaceflight system will consist of two parts, a spaceship and a rocket booster, standing 118 meters tall at launch, 11 percent taller than their previous design, reports NBC News.Instead of placing six Raptor engines onto the spaceship, SpaceX now plans to add seven Raptor engines to power the BFR spaceship.The spaceship will also now include two movable fins near its nose and two larger fins near its tail. SpaceX's founder and CEO Elon Musk says this will help the vehicle maneuver its way to safe landings.The previous design didn't include any front fins.He also explained the vehicle will land like a skydive rather than an airplane, landing vertically after slowing its descent.Musk said he believes this design might be better than the previous one. He also added it "looks beautiful."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The BFR is shown flight system is shown.2. Six Raptor engines are shown being added onto the spacecraft.3. Fins are shown appearing on the spaceship's nose and tail.4. Spacecraft is shown landing vertically.VOICEOVER (in English): "NBC News reports SpaceX's Mars-colonizing Big Falcon Rocket spaceflight system will consist of two parts, a spaceship and a rocket booster, standing 118 meters tall at launch, 11 percent taller than their previous design.""Instead of placing six Raptor engines onto the spaceship, SpaceX now plans to add seven Raptor engines to power the BFR spaceship.""The spaceship will also now include two movable fins near its nose and two larger fins near its tail. SpaceX's founder and CEO Elon Musk says this will help the vehicle maneuver its way to safe landings.""The previous design didn't include any front fins.""He also explained the vehicle will land like a skydive rather than an airplane, landing vertically after slowing its descent."SOURCES: NBC News, Business Insider, Engadget, The Verge, Space.comhttps://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/how-spacex-s-huge-bfr-spaceship-mars-has-changed-ncna912121https://www.businessinsider.com/elon-musk-spacex-pictures-big-falcon-rocket-spaceship-2018-9https://www.engadget.com/2018/09/21/spacex-mars-base/https://www.theverge.com/2018/9/17/17871724/spacex-big-falcon-rocket-bfr-mars-design-elon-muskhttps://www.space.com/41825-spacex-giant-bfr-rocket-moon-flight-design-art.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 08:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/25/3701313/3701313_336AA3B1A0D34E2E9FF7F04F4792DDB1_180925_3701313_Changes_to_SpaceX_s_BFR_spacecraft_headed_for_Ma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/FCD/05A/FCD05A7C3FBD458797F736897D4F0AEF_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,SpaceX, SpaceX bfr, spacex mars, spaceship, spacecraft, Mars-colonizing Big Falcon Rocket, BFR spaceship, bfr mars mission, spacecraft to mars, vertical landing spacex, vertical landing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3701305</guid>
      <title>Scientists propose building artificial walls to save Antarctic glaciers from collapsing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have proposed a plan to build a wall around the Antarctic ice sheets in a bid to slow their collapse.As the planet heats up due to global warming, the world's ice sheets are rapidly melting and causing sea levels to rise at an alarming rate.To prevent this global catastrophe, scientists proposed constructing artificial undersea mounds to catch the ice as it flows forward, thereby allowing it to reground, according to new research published in The Cryosphere.A second idea aims to address the threat of warm water currents, which have been known to thin ice shelves.According to the research, building a long, continuous wall or sill across the front of the glacier will block warm water from seeping under the ice shelf.The study authors found that smaller structures would have a 30% success rate, and that larger walls may be even more effective.However, some scientists warn that such geoengineering is simply a band-aid for the real problem, and offers no real solution to reversing global warming.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of melting ice sheets contributing to sea level rise2. Depiction of mounds of dirt regrounding collapsing ice sheets3. Depiction of warm water thinning glaciers4. Depiction of long continuous wall blocking warm water currentsVOICEOVER (in English): "As the planet heats up due to global warming, the world's ice sheets are rapidly melting and causing sea levels to rise at an alarming rate.""To prevent this global catastrophe, scientists proposed constructing artificial undersea mounds to catch the ice as it flows forward, thereby allowing it to reground.""A second idea aims to address the threat of warm water currents, which have been known to thin ice shelves.""According to the research, building a long, continuous wall or sill across the front of the glacier will block warm water from seeping under the ice shelf."SOURCES: The Cryospherehttps://www.the-cryosphere.net/12/2955/2018/tc-12-2955-2018.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 08:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/25/3701305/3701305_C61FF52B7AD04470820EA2F286733CE2_180925_3701305_Scientists_propose_building_artificial_walls_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/6AB/EB6/6ABEB6A885984E8EAA7B8BA74EC9DD9D_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Antarctica, ice sheets, collapsing ice sheets, melting ice sheets, ice sheet collapse, Antarctic ice sheets, artificial wall, giant wall, massive wall, sea level rise, global warming, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3701171</guid>
      <title>Low-carb, keto diets may have negative long-term consequences</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew studies have found that low-carb diets may not be healthy in the long run.Business Insider reports that the ketogenic diet is a high-fat, low carb plan where healthy fats make up 80% of a person's daily calories, and protein 20%. Only 50 grams of carbohydrates are allowed a day, compared to the USDA recommendation of 225 to 325 grams.The idea is to go into a state of ketosis, in which the body burns fat instead of carbohydrates for energy.But while a ketogenic diet helps reduce sugar and processed food intake, according to a study of overweight men published in the American Journal of Clinical Nutrition, it doesn't necessarily burn more body fat.Dieters tend to eliminate healthier carbohydrates like bananas, legumes, or oats, and with them nutrients like magnesium, calcium, and potassium. Some of the findings suggest going low-carb could lead to glucose intolerance or even diabetes, though more research is needed to confirm this.Research that looked at eating patterns of U.S. adults found that those who ate a moderate amount of carbs were more likely to live longer than high or low carb eaters.A third study that surveyed Europeans' eating habits revealed that those who ate fewer fresh vegetables, fruits, and nuts are more likely to develop deadly cancers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Keto diet is high fat, low carb2. Carbs are limited to 50 grams with keto diet3. Body burns up glucose then turns fat into fatty acids when carbs are taken out of diet4. Keto diet doesn't burn more body fat than regular regime5. Low-carb diet eliminates healthy carbs, nutrients6. Moderate carb eaters live longer than high or low carb dieters7. People with diets of lower nutritional quality more likely to develop deadly cancersVOICEOVER (in English): "The ketogenic diet is a high-fat, low carb plan where healthy fats make up 80 percent of a person's daily calories, and protein 20 percent." "Only 50 grams of carbohydrates are allowed a day, compared to the USDA recommendation of 225 to 325 grams." "The idea is to go into a state of ketosis, in which the body burns fat instead of carbohydrates for energy." "But while a ketogenic diet helps reduce sugar and processed food intake, according to a laboratory testing of overweight men, it doesn't necessarily burn more body fat.""Dieters also tend to eliminate healthier carbohydrates like bananas, legumes, or oats, and with them nutrients like magnesium, calcium, and potassium.""Research that looked at eating patterns of U.S. adults found that those who ate a moderate amount of carbs were more likely to live longer than high or low carb eaters.""A third study that surveyed Europeans' eating habits revealed that those who ate fewer fresh vegetables, fruits, and nuts are more likely to develop deadly cancers."SOURCES: American Journal of Clinical Nutrition, PLOS Medicine, Business Insiderhttps://academic.oup.com/ajcn/article/104/2/324/4564649https://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1002651http://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-keto-diet-beginners-2017-12/#the-keto-diet-is-like-atkins-on-steroids-it-turns-the-body-into-a-fat-burning-machine-4https://www.businessinsider.com/low-carb-diets-linked-to-higher-risk-of-death-2018-8?utm_source=hearst&uthttps://www.businessinsider.com/amount-of-carbs-to-eat-for-a-long-life-2018-8?utm_source=hearst&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=allverticals***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 04:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/25/3701171/3701171_6D8B72780ACA4BA9BE44B5342D17F1D6_180925_3701171_Low_carb__keto_diets_may_have_negative_long_term_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/139/9F2/1399F2C7D7D2444BADEF97E03E9084D4_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, keto diet, ketogenic diet, low carb diet, low carb, consequences of keto diet, healthy diet, healthy eating, weight loss]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3702162</guid>
      <title>World's first floating dairy farm to open in Netherlands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe world's first fully-functional floating dairy farm is set to begin operations in the Netherlands. According to Business Insider, the multi-level, 89-by-89-foot complex will be floating in the water in Rotterdam. The floating dairy will have 40 cows and can produce around 211 gallons of milk daily. The bottom level of the facility will house the processing and packaging machinery, with the cows and milking robots on the second level, while the third floor will grow clover and grass for the cows to eat.  According to Minke van Wingerden, co-leader of the project, who spoke with Business Insider, the farm will try to recycle as much as possible. Cows will be fed leftover food waste from the city. The cows' manure will be processed and sold as fertilizer. She also said the floating farm can be made to be hurricane-resistant. Van Wingerden said Beladon is currently in talks with another Dutch city for a second farm. She said they are also interested in opening farms in Singapore and China. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The floating dairy farm2. The first, second and third level of the facility3. 40 cows can produce around 211 gallons daily4. Cows will be fed recycled food waste, while their manure will be processed into fertilizerVOICEOVER (in English): "The world's first fully-functional floating dairy farm is set to begin operations in the Netherlands. According to Business Insider, the three-level, 89-by-89 foot complex will be floating in the water in Rotterdam." "The bottom level of the facility will house the processing and packaging machinery, with the cows and milking robots on the second level, while the third floor will grow clover and grass for the cows to eat." "The floating dairy will have 40 cows and can produce around 211 gallons of milk daily.""According to Minke van Wingerden, co-leader of the project, who spoke with Business Insider, the farm will try to recycle as much as possible. Cows will be fed leftover food waste from the city. The cows' manure will be processed and sold as fertilizer." SOURCES: Business Insider, Interested Engineeringhttps://www.businessinsider.com/world-first-first-floating-dairy-farm-rotterdam-2018-9?utm_content=buffer2f108&utm_medium=social&utm_source=facebook.com&utm_campaign=buffer-tihttps://interestingengineering.com/worlds-first-floating-dairy-farm-is-set-to-open-in-the-netherlands***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 14:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/26/3702162/3702162_3AF81423B9EA426891DDB06E55C29FC7_180926_3702162_World_s_first_floating_dairy_farm_to_open_in_Net_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/B3A/930/B3A930CE341C4A5F8819A8D72E6CFB97_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, floating dairy farm, floating farm, Beladon, Beladon floating dairy farm, Beladon floating farm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3701908</guid>
      <title>NASA discovers three things that impact Earth's spin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThere are three reasons why our planet wobbles: glacial rebound, melting of ice and mantle convection, according to a study published in the journal Earth and Planetary Science Letters.Earth's shape and weight distribution isn't perfectly even, due to the mountains and glaciers on Earth's surface. Large glaciers, such as Antarctica or the Arctic, compress the earth which causes the sides of the planet to bulge outward.As the glaciers start to melt, the land would gradually start to regain its original shape. This process is referred to as glacial rebound and was found to only be responsible for about 3.5 centimeters of axis wobble each year.Scientists used to believe glacial rebound was the main reason why Earth would wobble.NASA found the melting of the ice, fueled by the release of greenhouse gases, accounted for one third of Earth's wobble.Mantle convection also affects the planet's spin as molten rock rises and falls and can redistribute Earth's mass.NASA says the planet's wobble will continue to increase as the combination of these three factors continue to affect Earth.However, they added the wobble isn't large enough to impact ecosystems...for now.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Earth's surface is shown bulging outward.2. The process of glacial rebound is shown.3. Glacial melting is shown.4. Mantle convection is also shown.VOICEOVER (in English): "Earth's shape and weight distribution isn't perfectly even, due to the mountains and glaciers on Earth's surface. Large glaciers, such as Antarctica or the Arctic, compress the earth, which causes the sides of the planet to bulge outward.""As the glaciers start to melt, the land would gradually start to regain its original shape. This process is referred to as glacial rebound and was found to only be responsible for about 3.5 centimeters of axis wobble each year.""NASA found the melting of the ice, fueled by the release of greenhouse gases, accounted for one third of Earth's wobble.""Mantle convection also affects the planet's spin as molten rock rises and falls and can redistribute Earth's mass."SOURCES: Forbes, NASA,Earth and Planetary Science Letters Journal , Live Science, New Atlas, https://www.forbes.com/sites/trevornace/2018/09/24/humans-are-causing-earth-to-wobble-more-as-it-spins-nasa-finds/#312a7ab2c820https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7240https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0012821X18305314?dgcid=rss_sd_all#!https://www.livescience.com/63655-why-earth-wobbles.htmlhttps://newatlas.com/nasa-earth-axis-shift/56443/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 08:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/26/3701908/3701908_F5CA65F14DE0481B84160A35B09CCC72_180926_3701908_NASA_discovers_three_things_that_impact_Earth_s__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/835/4B4/8354B404B1424BED920F52731502A57F_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, NASA, Earth, earth's wobble, earth's spin, glacial rebound, ice melting, mantle convection, factors affecting earth's wobble]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3701871</guid>
      <title>France cleaning up tire sea sanctuary</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFrance has begun removing 25,000 car tires it dumped into the Mediterranean in the 1980s off the French coast after they failed to restore marine life and instead began polluting the water. According to the AFP, beginning last week, divers and a specially rigged boat have begun hauling out hundreds of old rubber tires about 500 meters from the coastline between Cannes and Antibes. The original idea was to have the tires serve as a sanctuary for marine life and as a foundation for coral to grow. According to Denis Genovese, head of an association of local fisherman, talking to the AFP, sedentary creatures did not use them, while "grouper fish, conger eels and sea bream swim around them." A University of Nice study in 2005 discovered that the tires were leaching toxic chemicals, including heavy metals, into the water.Another concern now is that after 40 years, the tires will break down into smaller pieces putting nearby seagrass meadows at risk. In 2015, 2,500 tires were removed to show that the clean up could be done safely. Around 10,000 tires are scheduled to be removed over the next few weeks, with the remaining 12,500 set to be pulled in the second quarter of 2019. The tires will be sent to recycling centers where they will be broken down into smaller pieces to be used in construction.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boat and divers removing tires from water2. Old tires were meant as a sanctuary for marine life and coral to grow3. Old tires releasing toxic chemicals into water4. Boat removing tires from waterVOICEOVER (in English): "France has begun removing 25,000 car tires it dumped into the Mediterranean in the 1980s off the French coast after they failed to restore marine life and instead began polluting the water." "The original idea was to have the tires serve as a sanctuary for marine life and as a foundation for coral to grow." "Not only did that not happen, a University of Nice study in 2005 discovered the tires were leaching toxic chemicals, including heavy metals, into the water.""In 2015, 2,500 tires were removed to show that the clean up could be done safely. Around 10,000 tires are scheduled to be removed over the next few weeks, with the remaining 12,500 set to be pulled in the second quarter of 2019." SOURCES: France 24https://www.france24.com/en/20180923-france-reverses-car-tyre-sea-sanctuary-environmental-flop***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 07:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/26/3701871/3701871_F20F434CA9E1494AB886707DEBA6B5F9_180926_3701871_France_cleaning_up_tire_sea_sanctuary_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/96C/3D7/96C3D7C54B964E4596FB9859E2A9EC5D_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, France tire sea sanctuary, France tire sea, tire sea sanctuary cleanup, tire sanctuary]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3701807</guid>
      <title>Researchers use new method to help paralyzed patients walk again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have tested a new technique using electrical stimulation on the spinal cords of paralyzed patients to help them walk again.A device called the epidural stimulator was implanted over a portion of the lower spinal cord, according a study published in the New England Journal of Medicine.The device itself does not move the legs for the person, however it enables the neurons and nerves to be stimulated and receive signals the brain used to send before the patients became paralyzed.The device has the ability to be turned on and off by a touch of a button.The patients were also required to undergo intensive physical therapy along with electrical stimulation, and were taught how to train their bodies and minds on how to move again.A participant of the study says the stimulator helped restore functions of the body such as bladder control and regaining muscle mass. A researcher told The Washington Post, the study shows that the brain "has the capability of relearning to walk in the right conditions."The study was conducted with 14 paralyzed patients, with only three being able to regain the ability the walk.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The epidural stimulator is seen being added on to the spinal cord.2. The neurons and nerves are seen being stimulated.3. The patient is seen undergoing intensive physical therapy combined with electrical stimulation.4. The device helps restore some body functions such as bladder control and muscle mass.VOICEOVER (in English): "According a study published in the New England Journal of Medicine, a device called the epidural stimulator was implanted over a portion of the lower spinal cord.""The device itself does not move the legs for the person, however it enables the neurons and nerves to be stimulated and receive signals the brain used to send before the patients became paralyzed.""The patients were also required to undergo intensive physical therapy along with electrical stimulation, and were taught how to train their bodies and minds on how to move again.""A participant of the study says the stimulator helped restore functions of the body such as bladder control and regaining muscle mass."SOURCES: The Washington Post, CNN, Reuters, The Verge, CBS News, https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2018/09/24/paralyzed-people-are-beginning-walk-with-new-kind-therapy/?noredirect=on&utm_term=.f2bf100b55eehttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/24/health/paralyzed-woman-walks-again/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-paralysis/electrode-treatment-physical-therapy-combination-lets-two-paralyzed-people-walk-again-idUSKCN1M41UYhttps://www.theverge.com/2018/9/24/17896720/paralysis-spinal-cord-implant-walking-epidural-stimulation-devicehttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/experimental-device-helps-paralyzed-man-walk-the-length-of-four-football-fields/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 06:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/26/3701807/3701807_5CFA264CA3DC4066A734DA571648403C_180926_3701807_Researchers_use_new_method_to_help_paralyzed_pat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/338/6BA/3386BADB192D4E448B248195B7005931_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, spinal cord, therapy, spinal cord stimulation, epidural stimulator, paralyzed people walking again, physical therapy, relearning to walk, relearning to walk after injury]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3702844</guid>
      <title>Puppies spreading drug-resistant bacterial illnesses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says puppies are to blame for spreading a drug-resistant bacterial infection to more than 100 people across the country.  According to CNN, the CDC says campylobacter bacteria has caused illnesses in at least 17 states.  It's a common bacteria that causes diarrhea, stomach pains and fever. The main problem is that it is normally resistant to antibiotics. According to the CDC, puppies from six pet store chains between January 2017 and February 2018 were responsible for the outbreak. No deaths have been reported, but at least 26 people were hospitalized. Samples from all patients showed that the bacteria was resistant to all forms of antibiotics. Without treatment, patients normally recover from a campylobacter bacterial infection in around five days. According to the CDC, 95 percent of the patients say they had come into direct contact with a pet store puppy.    The CDC reminded the public to wash and sanitize hands before and after handling new animals. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Puppies responsible for bacterial infections in 17 states2. Campylobacter causes diarrhea, stomach pain and fever and is drug-resistant3. 6 pet store chains responsible for outbreak, at least 26 people hospitalized4. Patients recover from infection in around five daysVOICEOVER (in English): "The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says puppies are to blame for spreading a drug-resistant bacterial infection to more than 100 people across the country. The CDC says campylobacter bacteria has caused illnesses in at least 17 states."    "According to CNN, campylobacter is a common bacteria that causes diarrhea, stomach pains and fever, however, the main problem is that it is usually resistant to antibiotics." "According to the CDC, puppies from six pet store chains between January 2017 and February 2018 were responsible for the outbreak. No deaths have been reported, but at least 26 people were hospitalized.""Without treatment, patients normally recover from a campylobacter bacterial infection in around five days."SOURCES: CNN, CDChttps://www.wdtn.com/news/u-s-world/puppies-to-blame-for-nationwide-drug-resistant-illness-cdc-says/1476521925https://www.cdc.gov/campylobacter/outbreaks/puppies-9-17/map.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 12:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/27/3702844/3702844_EAB56D2455C04B85BD9C08AE70BA69FC_180927_3702844_Puppies_spreading_drug_resistant_bacterial_illne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/3C5/7D6/3C57D676CBE74046B74EDF5619A367D6_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, drug-resistant, antibiotic resistant, campylobacter bacteria, puppy campylobacter bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3702448</guid>
      <title>Archaeologists discover 400-year-old shipwreck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of archaeologists have discovered an ancient shipwreck off the coast of Cascais, Portugal earlier this month, reports The Guardian.The ship was believed to be returning from a trip to India and was carrying different relics from the late 16th or early 17th century when it sank.The wreckage was discovered 12 meters beneath the surface of the water, covering an area 100 meters long and 50 meters wide.The director of the project said the wreckage was discovered by divers using geophysical survey equipment.Peppercorns, cowrie shells and nine bronze cannons were found at the site as well as fragments of Chinese porcelain dating back to the 16th and 17th century.The mayor of Cascais said the discovery is extraordinary and helps us learn more about history. Officials plan to examine the artifacts and believe there is still more to be discovered at the site.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The location of where the shipwreck was discovered is shown on a map.2. The wreckage is shown.3. Divers are shown locating the wreckage.4. Relics found at the site are shown.VOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports a team of archaeologists have discovered an ancient shipwreck off the coast of Cascais, Portugal earlier this month.""The wreckage was discovered 12 meters beneath the surface of the water, covering an area 100 meters long and 50 meters wide.""The director of the project said the wreckage was discovered by divers using geophysical survey equipment.""Pepper corns, cowrie shells and nine bronze cannons were found at the site as well as fragments of Chinese porcelain dating back to the 16th and 17th century."SOURCES: Fox News, BBC News, Reuters, Newsweek, NPR, ABC News, http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/09/25/stunning-shipwreck-discovery-400-year-old-wreck-thrills-experts.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/av/uk-45636827/portugal-shipwreck-is-discovery-of-a-decadehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-archeology-ship/400-year-old-shipwreck-discovery-of-decade-for-portugal-idUSKCN1M42A4https://www.newsweek.com/incredible-images-reveal-renaissance-shipwreck-discovery-decade-1137100https://www.npr.org/2018/09/25/651362994/spices-ceramics-found-aboard-400-year-old-portuguese-shipwreckhttps://abcnews.go.com/International/remains-400-year-shipwreck-found-off-coast-portugal/story?id=58068501***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 05:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/27/3702448/3702448_CA738676CF10486BB76C22699D83280D_180927_3702448_Archaeologists_discover_400_year_old_shipwreck_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A6C/EC5/A6CEC50CBBC04FAFA6ABB200467014D7_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Portugal, shipwreck, shipwreck found off coast of Portugal, 400-year-old shipwreck, wreckage, artifacts, relics, cowrie shells, peppercorns, bronze cannons, chinese porcelain]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3702379</guid>
      <title>Dachshund fitted with 3D-printed titanium skull plate following tumor removal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDoctors in Canada used 3D-printing technology to replace a dog's skull with titanium following major cancer surgery.According to an article released by the University of Guelph, a 9-year-old dachshund named Patches had a large tumor growing into her skull, pushing dangerously close to her brain and eye socket.Using an innovative new approach, University of Guelph researchers used rapid prototyping to print out a 3D model of Patches' head and tumor.This enabled veterinary surgeons to do a test run of the tumor removal, and create a custom fitted titanium plate to replace the parts of the skull that would be lost.Because of the technique, what would have been a lengthy surgery took only four hours, with Patches waking up just 30 minutes after the procedure.The procedure is believed to be the first of its kind in North America, and marks an advancement in veterinary medicine that researchers say can also be useful in human medicine.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of brain tumor 2. Depiction of 3D printed model of skull and tumor3. Depiction of tumor removal, titanium plate fitted on skull4. Depiction of shorter surgery, recoveryVOICEOVER (in English): "A 9-year-old dachshund named Patches had a large tumor growing into her skull, pushing dangerously close to her brain and eye socket.""Using an innovative new approach, University of Guelph researchers used rapid prototyping to print out a 3D model of Patches' head and tumor.""This enabled veterinary surgeons to do a test run of the tumor removal, and create a custom fitted titanium plate to replace the parts of the skull that would be lost.""Because of the technique, what would have been a lengthy surgery took only four hours, with Patches waking up just 30 minutes after the procedure."SOURCES: University of Guelph, Globe and Mailhttps://ovc.uoguelph.ca/news/3-d-printing-research-opens-new-possibilities-cancer-surgerieshttps://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-ontario-researchers-use-3d-printing-technology-to-replace-majorty-of/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 03:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/27/3702379/3702379_2C515F1BDE644DE884F5392C03D4C285_180927_3702379_Dachshund_fitted_with_3D_printed_titanium_skull__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/7B3/ACD/7B3ACD211A914FCDA37045AFAAE1C7AB_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, 3D printing, cancer, brain tumor, cancer surgery, dog tumor, tumor, tumor surgery, rapid prototyping, dachshund, veterinary surgery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3703468</guid>
      <title>Antibiotics could be used to treat patients with appendicitis</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThere is an alternative to patients with appendicitis who don't want to get surgery, according to a study published in the Journal of the American Medical Association.In the past, appendicitis was considered a medical emergency, with surgeons removing the appendix immediately as they feared there was a possibility it would burst.However, the researchers found that nearly two-thirds of patients with appendicitis don't have to fear their appendix would burst and can choose to take antibiotics instead.Only 7 percent of patients who received antibiotics were found to have some kind of complications, with the authors saying the success rate for the antibiotic treatment was almost 64 percent.However, 36 percent of the patients eventually needed surgery to remove their appendix.The author of the study says antibiotics instead of surgery is a "feasible, viable and a safe option" for those who have an uncomplicated appendix, meaning they don't need to worry about their appendix bursting.In an editorial accompanying the study, the deputy editor of the journal said the treatment has a high chance of success, but that the public could also choose to get surgery if don't want to worry about appendicitis coming back again.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. We see an appendix in the body, it flashes red.2. Antibiotics appear along with the appendix in the body.3. Antibiotics are shown inside the appendix.4. Appendix is shown. VOICEOVER (in English): "In the past, appendicitis was considered a medical emergency, with surgeons removing the appendix immediately as they feared there was a possibility it would burst.""However, the researchers found that nearly two-thirds of patients with appendicitis don't have to fear their appendix would burst and can choose to take antibiotics instead.""Only 7 percent of patients who received antibiotics were found to have some kind of complications, with the authors saying the success rate for the antibiotic treatment was almost 64 percent.""However, 36 percent of the patients eventually needed surgery to remove their appendix."SOURCES: The Atlanta Journal-Constitution, Live Science, Journal of the American Medical Association,https://www.ajc.com/news/antibiotics-for-appendicitis-surgery-often-not-needed/svApubwPmfYtJE4AlCaoTK/https://www.livescience.com/63699-appendicitis-antibiotics.htmlhttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2703354***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/28/3703468/3703468_48378CC51CD44207B665D106AB904682_180928_3703468_Antibiotics_could_be_used_to_treat_patients_with_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/2A7/BC3/2A7BC317A81046A0AA97B1F0ECF89A5F_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, science, appendix, appendicitis, appendicitis surgery, antibiotics for appendicitis, appendicitis antibiotics used, complicated appendix, uncomplicated appendix]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3703141</guid>
      <title>Researchers find weed killer could be linked to increase of bee deaths</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMonsanto is being accused of killing off bees around the world, reports NPR.Bees are being exposed to glyphosate, an ingredient in weed killer, according to a new study published in Proceedings of the National Academy of SciencesScientists painted the bees' backs with colored dots to track them, and found that  glyphosate significantly decreased the amount of healthy gut bacteria in honey bees.This could increase the chance of bees receiving infections or even dying because of harmful bacteria.They believe glyphosate may be contributing to "colony collapse disorder," a phenomenon when bee colonies are wiped out.Scientists encouraged the public to avoid spraying using weed killers that contain glyphosate when they are spraying their flowers.The researchers involved say better guidelines are needed to regulate use of glyphosate in order to protect bees.In a statement, Monsanto denied the accusations and claims "no large-scale study has ever found a link between glyphosate and honey bee health issues."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Honey bees and weed killers with glyphosate are shown.2. Bees with painted backs and a vertical chart is shown.3. A bee is shown by a flower, and an inset of bacteria.4. A weed killer bottle is shown with a blocking sign.VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, bees are being exposed to glyphosate, an ingredient in weed killer.""Scientists painted the bees' backs with colored dots to track them, and found that  glyphosate significantly decreased the amount of healthy gut bacteria in honey bees. ""This could increase the chance of bees receiving infections or even dying because of harmful bacteria.""Scientists encouraged the public to avoid spraying using weed killers that contain glyphosate when they are spraying their flowers."SOURCES: NPR, CBS News, USA Today, Fox News, PNAS, The Guardianhttps://www.npr.org/2018/09/25/651618685/study-roundup-weed-killer-could-be-linked-to-widespread-bee-deathshttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/roundup-weed-killer-may-play-role-in-widespread-bee-deaths-study-finds/https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/09/25/weed-killer-ingredient-linked-honey-bee-deaths-glyphosate-study/1419248002/http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/09/25/popular-weed-killer-may-be-to-blame-for-honey-bee-deaths-study-suggests.htmlhttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/09/18/1803880115https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/sep/24/monsanto-weedkiller-harms-bees-research-finds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 05:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/28/3703141/3703141_46215536A21D403AA5A3CB091E5E7E32_180928_3703141_Researchers_find_weed_killer_could_be_linked_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/319/913/319913E31EF84A6FAA63281D99111D52_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Study, bees, honey bees, glyphosate, weed killer, colony collapse disorder,  colony collapse disorder bees]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3703116</guid>
      <title>Researchers develop new method aimed at curing Alzheimer's</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found a way to target toxic particles that destroys healthy brain cells and leads to illnesses such as Alzheimer's disease, according to a new study published in the journal PNAS.Alzheimer's disease causes the brain to shrink dramatically over time, which leads to memory loss, personality changes along with other symptoms.Researchers have identified the toxic particles, small clumps of protein known as oligomers, as the most likely cause of dementia.Proteins in the brain are usually responsible for vital cell processes, however when they form clumps and start to build up, they start killing healthy nerve cells instead.Researchers involved developed small molecules which would target oligomers and work to slow down the formation of these toxic particles.The study claims their method was the first to directly target the toxic oligomers.Alzheimer's disease affects millions of people worldwide and the team hopes the study would lead to the development of new drugs to treat the disease in a few years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The brain is shown shrinking.2. Oligomers are shown forming into clumps.3. The toxic clump are now shown going towards healthy nerve cells.4. Small molecules are shown targeting the toxic clump.VOICEOVER (in English): "Alzheimer's disease causes the brain to shrink dramatically over time, which leads to memory loss, personality changes along with other symptoms.""Researchers have identified the toxic particles, small clumps of protein known as oligomers, as the most likely cause of dementia.""Proteins in the brain are usually responsible for vital cell processes, however when they form clumps they start killing healthy nerve cells instead.""Researchers involved developed small molecules which would target oligomers and work to slow down the formation of these toxic particles."SOURCES: KXLY, University of Cambridge, Medical Xpress, Newsweek, Proceedings of the National Academy of Science of the United States of Americahttps://www.kxly.com/news/breakthrough-research-puts-scientists-closer-to-alzheimer-s-cure/799429005https://www.cam.ac.uk/research/news/scientists-reveal-plan-to-target-the-cause-of-alzheimers-diseasehttps://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-09-scientists-reveal-ground-breaking-alzheimer-disease.htmlhttps://www.newsweek.com/alzheimers-disease-drugs-targeting-toxic-dementia-causing-particles-could-be-1135812http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/09/25/1807884115***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 04:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/28/3703116/3703116_CA5D485AB8E44E8EB4D3758011D944C9_180928_3703116_Researchers_develop_new_method_aimed_at_curing_A_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/CB3/116/CB31160C0FB84C9393B7713FCCC3C5BA_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,Study, science, alzheimer's, alzheimer's disease, alzheimer's cure,oligomers, toxic oligomers, toxic particles, alzheimer's treatment, alzheimer's drugs, nerve cells, brain shrinkage, alzheimer's brain]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3703046</guid>
      <title>Methane fueled lake discovered in Alaska</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have discovered a lake in Alaska that is bubbling due to methane emissions. Due to increasing temperatures from global warming, ground that used to be permafrost in the Arctic is now thawing and releasing trapped greenhouse gases into the air, thereby accelerating climate change. According to the Washington Post, Katey Walter Anthony, an associate professor at the University of Alaska Fairbanks, Esieh Lake is bubbling because of methane gas.  The gases are geological in origin. The researchers say there are fossil fuels buried close to the bottom of the lake, and in combination with the melting of the permafrost, represent a source of greenhouse gases. The lake emits around two tons of methane gas daily  the equivalent of methane emissions from 6,000 dairy cows. Scientists will need to do further research to see if this phenomenon is occurring in other Arctic lakes.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Esieh Lake bubbling from methane gas release2. Global warming causing melting permafrost to release more greenhouse gases3. Methane gas coming from fossil fuels buried near bottom of the lake4. The lake emits two tons of methane dailyVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers have discovered a lake in Alaska that is bubbling due to methane emissions. In a feature for the Washington Post, according to Katey Walter Anthony, an associate professor at the University of Alaska Fairbanks, the bubbles in Esieh Lake are being caused by methane gas release." "Due to increasing temperatures from global warming, ground that used to be permafrost in the Arctic is now thawing and releasing trapped greenhouse gases into the air, thereby accelerating climate change." "The gases are geological in origin. The researchers say there are fossil fuels buried close to the bottom of the lake, and in combination with the melting of the permafrost, represent a source of greenhouse gases." "The lake emits around two tons of methane gas daily  the equivalent of methane emissions from 6,000 dairy cows." SOURCES: Washington Posthttps://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2018/national/arctic-lakes-are-bubbling-and-hissing-with-dangerous-greenhouse-gases/?utm_term=.e2909aec1e2a***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 02:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/09/28/3703046/3703046_EC57041FC4BA4613B8141D734949B755_180928_3703046_Methane_fueled_lake_discovered_in_Alaska_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/B80/729/B807290E3ACC4F7EBE421E7F941DB196_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Esieh Lake, Esieh Lake bubbling, Esieh Lake methane emissions, greenhouse gases, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3705019</guid>
      <title>Rare two-headed baby copperhead found in Virginia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have discovered an exceptionally rare two-head copperhead alive in the wild.According to the Wildlife Center of Virginia, a woman in Northern Virginia spotted a baby copperhead snake slithering in her yard, and upon closer inspection found it had two heads.Radiographs revealed that each head has its own brain, trachea, and esophagus, but shared a heart and a set of lungs. The left trachea is more developed than the right, while the right esophagus is more developed than the left.Scientists say it's better for the right head to eat based on the snake's anatomy, but are attempting to feed the left head due to it being more dominant and responsive.Two-headed serpents are an extremely rare find in the wild as they often have trouble coordinating their movements when escaping from predators, which contribute to their short life spans.The competing heads also tend to fight over food, though this particular copperhead's mutation is such that its heads don't quarrel, and seem almost oblivious to each other.Herpetologists estimate the animal is about 3 weeks old, but have yet to figure out its gender. They will continue to monitor the snake, and likely place it in a zoo or educational facility if it survives.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of two-headed copperhead found in yard2. Depiction of two-headed snake's anatomy3. Depiction of left head as dominant4. Depiction of two-headed snake's uncoordinated movementsVOICEOVER (in English): "A woman in Northern Virginia spotted a baby copperhead snake slithering in her yard, and upon closer inspection found it had two heads.""Radiographs revealed that each head has its own brain, trachea, and esophagus, but shared a heart and a set of lungs.""Scientists say it's better for the right head to eat based on the snake's anatomy, but are attempting to feed the left head due to it being more dominant and responsive.""Two-headed serpents are a rare find in the wild. They often have trouble coordinating their movements when responding to danger, which contributes to their short life spans."SOURCES: Wildlife Center of Virginia, NPRhttps://www.wildlifecenter.org/news_events/news/two-headed-copperheadhttps://www.npr.org/2018/09/29/652570287/extremely-rare-2-headed-snake-stuns-social-media-charms-scientists***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/10/01/3705019/3705019_626F0EA3EC0F4C7E8050DE1B18CC1470_181001_3705019_Rare_two_headed_baby_copperhead_found_in_Virgini_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/A41/FD4/A41FD4ABF93A464D8E30E3D40CBF9E06_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, two headed snake, two headed copperhead, copperhead, baby copperhead, baby snake, rare snake, venomous snake, viper, snake]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3705000</guid>
      <title>Killer whales threatened by PCBs in ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANToxic chemical polychlorinated biphenyls, or PCBs, were found lingering in marine life such as killer whales, according to a new study published in the journal Science.PCBs were banned in most countries decades ago, however they are still used in some parts of the world, which has allowed them to gradually seep into oceans, according to CNN.PCBs were used in paints, coolants, carbonless copy paper and other products. PCBs can be consumed by plankton, which are then eaten by larger fish. As the PCBs move up the food chain, they become more concentrated. This puts killer whales in danger of consuming highly concentrated PCBs as they are near the top of the food chain. The chemical was found to disrupt the whales' reproductive system, brain function and the endocrine system.Mother whales can also pass the deadly chemicals on to their offspring through lactation.  Researchers warn animals living off the coasts of the UK, Brazil, Hawaii, and Japan have a high risk of population collapse because of PCBs.ORCA, a charity group dedicated to protecting whales, described the report as "an absolute tragic state of affairs and… needs immediate action."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. PCBs being consumed by sea creatures.2. Concentrated amount of PCB is shown inside a killer whale.3. Cross section of a killer whale.4. Map of where marine life is being threatened.VOICEOVER (in English): "Polychlorinated biphenyls, or PCBs, can be consumed by plankton, which are then eaten by larger fish. As the PCBs move up the food chain, they become more concentrated.""This puts killer whales in danger of consuming highly concentrated PCBs as they are near the top of the food chain.""The chemical was found to disrupt the whales' reproductive system, brain function and the endocrine system.""Researchers warn animals living off the coasts of the UK, Brazil, Hawaii, and Japan have a high risk of population collapse because of PCBs."SOURCES: New York Times, Stockholm Convention, Science Journal, The Atlantic, BBC News, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/27/science/killer-whales-pcbs.htmlhttp://chm.pops.int/TheConvention/Overview/tabid/3351/Default.aspxhttp://science.sciencemag.org/content/361/6409/1373https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2018/09/pcbs-are-killing-killer-whales/571474/https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-45652149https://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/27/health/orca-killer-whale-pollution-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/10/01/3705000/3705000_1BB6356FDCFF4FF1BDDEA824982D31CC_181001_3705000_Killer_whales_threatened_by_PCBs_in_ocean_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/5D5/B72/5D5B72CBB91243B58A8ED510BD3C8FA9_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, Science, PCBs chemicals, toxic chemicals, marine life, killer whale, ocean, sea, toxic pollutants, killer whale threatened by toxic chemicals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3704937</guid>
      <title>Limited screen time for children associated with better cognition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn observational study has found that two hours of recreational screen time a day along with more sleep is linked to improved cognition in children.According to a study published in the Lancet Child and Adolescent Health, the Canadian 24-hour Movement Guidelines recommends 9 to 11 hours of sleep per night, less than two hours of screen time, and an hour of physical activity daily for kids aged 8 to 11.But a study of 4,520 U.S. children found that only 5 percent met all three recommendations. Forty-one percent met at least one guideline, 25 percent met two guidelines, while 29 percent met none at all. On average, American children slept 9.1 hours per night, had 3.6 hours of recreational screen time per day, and 3.7 hours of physical activity per week.According to the findings, screen time and sleep had the strongest links to improved cognition, and kids with more than two hours of screen time had poorer development.Researchers say parents should manage screen time, and suggest encouraging more physical activity and tech-free zones. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Canadian 24-hour movement guidelines2. Results of US children survey3. US children's average screen time, sleep, physical activity4. Screen time, sleep strongly linked to cognitive developmentVOICEOVER (in English): "For children aged 8 to 11, the Canadian 24-hour Movement Guidelines recommends 9 to 11 hours of sleep per night, less than two hours of screen time, and an hour of physical activity a day.""But a study of 4,520 U.S. children found that only 5 percent met all three recommendations, while 41 percent met at least one guideline, 25 percent met two, and 29 percent met none at all.""On average, American children slept 9.1 hours per night, had 3.6 hours of recreational screen time per day, and 3.7 hours of physical activity per week.""According to the findings, screen time and sleep had the strongest links to improved cognition, and kids with more than two hours of screen time had poorer development."SOURCES: The Lancet Child & Adolescent Health, Science Daily, CNNhttps://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2018-09/tl-lcr092518.phphttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/09/180926192102.htmhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/26/health/screen-time-cognition-study/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 09:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/10/01/3704937/3704937_8EE50869545B47D8AF6D3ED93B84803E_181001_3704937_Limited_screen_time_for_children_associated_with_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/2DA/BC8/2DABC8DF927D4A86AC8A824B5C7969B2_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, screen time, kids health, cognition, improving cognition, screen exposure, health guidelines, physical activity, better brains]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3704772</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered neuron circuit shows gut is directly connected to the brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new Duke University study has found a new neuron circuit that proves the gut has a more direct connection to the brain than previously thought.Science reports that enteroendocrine cells lining the gut have protrusions similar to neurons, leading researchers to suspect they may be sending signals to the brain via the vagus nerve.When a fluorescent green rabies virus was injected into the colons of mice, the virus labeled the vagus nerve before landing in the brain stem, proving there was a direct circuit.Enteroendocrine cells grown in the same petri dish as vagal neurons connected together and began firing signals. The cells released the neurotransmitter glutamate, involved in conveying senses like taste or smell, which the neurons picked up on within 100 milliseconds.The findings could have massive implications on our understanding of appetite and how to suppress it. Current suppressants target slow-acting hormones, but going after the synapses may in fact be the more effective approach.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of enteroendocrine cells with protrusions similar to neurons2. Depiction of vagal nerves as a direct circuit connecting the gut to the brain3. Depiction of synaptic connection between enteroendocrine cells and vagal neurons 4. Depiction of neurotransmitter glutamate VOICEOVER (in English): "Enteroendocrine cells that line the gut have protrusions similar to neurons, leading researchers to suspect they may be sending signals to the brain via the vagus nerve.""When a fluorescent green rabies virus was injected into the colons of mice, the virus labeled the vagus nerve before landing in the brain stem, proving there was a direct circuit.""Enteroendocrine cells grown in the same petri dish as vagal neurons connected together and began firing signals.""The cells released the neurotransmitter glutamate, involved in conveying senses like taste or smell, which the neurons picked up on within 100 milliseconds."SOURCES: Duke University, Sciencehttps://today.duke.edu/2018/09/%E2%80%9Cgut-sense%E2%80%9D-hardwired-not-hormonalhttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/09/your-gut-directly-connected-your-brain-newly-discovered-neuron-circuit***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 05:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/10/01/3704772/3704772_97B5E4FEBCDE4E9F8809A868B0A02156_181001_3704772_Newly_discovered_neuron_circuit_shows_gut_is_dir_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/9D2/434/9D24345FEF6642018810F5BAFDA96D1F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational,  gut brain connection, gut, brain, neuron circuit, gut sense, gut cells, enteroendocrine cells, vagal nerve, second brain, glutamate]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3704729</guid>
      <title>Skull-shaped asteroid to pass by Earth after Halloween</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANEarth will be having another spooky encounter with a 'death comet' that first swung by our planet three Halloweens ago.Spain's agencia SINC reports that asteroid 2015 TB145 is a skull-like space rock that came within 310,000 miles of Earth on October 31, 2015.Dubbed "The Great Pumpkin" by NASA due to its Halloween flyby, the asteroid is set to once again pass by our planet on November 11, 2018, but at a much farther distance of 24 million miles.Observations during the first flyby indicate that the asteroid most likely completes a rotation in 2.94 hours, and reflects only 5 to 6% of sunlight, making it just slightly more reflective than charcoal.Astronomers think the asteroid may be an extinct comet that lost its water and other volatile compounds after numerous orbits around the sun.Though the second approach may not be as favorable as the first in terms of distance, scientists say they will still be able to observe and obtain new data on the space rock.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of asteroid's October 2015 orbit2. Depiction of asteroid's November 2018 flyby3. Depiction of asteroid reflecting little sunlight4. Depiction of how asteroid may have become a death cometVOICEOVER (in English): "Asteroid 2015 TB145 is a skull-like space rock that came within 310,000 miles of Earth on October 31, 2015.""Dubbed 'The Great Pumpkin' by NASA, the asteroid is set to once again pass by our planet on November 11, but at a much farther distance of 24 million miles.""Observations during the first flyby indicate that the asteroid most likely completes a rotation in 2.94 hours, and reflects only 5 to 6% of sunlight, making it just slightly more reflective than charcoal.""Astronomers think the asteroid may be an extinct comet that lost its water and other volatile compounds after numerous orbits around the sun."SOURCES: Spain Information and Scientific News Service, Spacehttps://www.agenciasinc.es/en/News/The-Halloween-asteroid-prepares-to-return-in-2018https://www.space.com/39173-halloween-asteroid-2015-tb145-returns-2018.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 04:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/10/01/3704729/3704729_5B68376537D64C3C8FCA933716631BEE_181001_3704729_Skull_shaped_asteroid_to_pass_by_Earth_after_Hal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/22F/669/22F66916E9854942BF43D23F4C42D261_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, skull comet, skull asteroid, creepy asteroid, death comet, asteroid flyby, skull rock, the great pumpkin, space rocks, asteroid 2015 tb145, 2015 tb145, halloween, halloween asteroid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
