<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3517429</guid>
      <title>China to build 1-km-long solar expressway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina is testing a 1-km solar expressway in Jinan. Solar panels covering 5,875 square feet were laid on the expressway, reported Chinese state media outlet Xinhua News.According to Inhabitat, the expressway consists of three parts: insulation on the bottom, the solar panel in the middle and weight-bearing transparent concrete on the top.Xinhua reports that the road can generate enough power for 800 homes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Road being laid2. Layers of road3. Car driving on roadVOICEOVER (in English): The 1-km expressway was built in Jinan in Eastern China with 5,875 square feet of solar panels.The road comprises three parts: insulation on the bottom, the solar panel in the middle and weight-bearing transparent concrete on the top.According to Chinese state media outlet Xinhua, the road can generate enough power for 800 homes.SOURCES: Xinhua News, Inhabitathttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2017-12/28/c_136857894.htmhttps://inhabitat.com/new-1-km-solar-expressway-opens-in-jinan-china/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 05:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/02/3517429/3517429_73AA5AA86AD84E5E836764B874829D5D_180102_3517429_China_to_build_1_km_long_solar_expressway_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/483/556/4835565F87E544FF919B69D582BD6B0C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, solar road, solar highways, solar expressway, solar road in china, solar technology, solar news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3518441</guid>
      <title>Neuroscientist predicts better Alzheimer's treatment in 10 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEBritish neuroscientist is hopeful that breakthroughs in Alzheimer's research could lead to better treatment in just 10 years.In an interview with WBUR, neuroscientist Joseph Jebelli claims memory loss comes with age, but forgetting what certain everyday things are for could signal a more serious problem.Healthy brains shrink by about 10 percent between ages 50 and 80. Brain cells shrivel up slightly, reducing contact between each cell and causing them to function more slowly.In patients with Alzheimer's, toxic proteins cause a buildup of plaques and tangles in the brain, which causes cell death. Current medication only treats the symptoms, and can delay them for six months to a year.Researchers have been looking into ways of using sleep to treat the disease, since the brain uses cerebrospinal fluid to clean away the plaques and tangles during sleep.Scientists are also considering neural stem cells as a treatment for Alzheimer's, believing that the cells can be activated to generate new neurons  allowing the brain to heal itself.Jebelli believes the future of Alzheimer's treatment lies not in an outright cure but in being able to manage and control the disease enough to keep its symptoms at bay.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Healthy brains shrink with age, causes functions to become slower2. Toxic proteins cause buildup of brain plaques and tangles in patients with Alzheimer's3. Cerebrospinal fluid cleanses brain during sleep4. Neural stem cell treatments could generate new neurons to help brain heal itselfVOICEOVER (in English): "Healthy brains shrink by about 10 percent between ages 50 and 80. Brain cells shrivel up slightly, reducing contact between each cell and causing them to function more slowly.""In patients with Alzheimer's, toxic proteins cause a buildup of plaques and tangles in the brain, which causes cell death. Current medication only treats the symptoms, and can delay them for six months to a year.""Researchers have been looking into ways of using sleep to treat the disease, since the brain uses cerebrospinal fluid to clean away the plaques and tangles during sleep.""Scientists are also considering neural stem cells as a treatment for Alzheimer's, believing that the cells can be activated to generate new neurons  allowing the brain to heal itself."SOURCES: WBURhttp://www.wbur.org/npr/575055148/neuroscientist-predicts-much-better-treatment-for-alzheimers-is-10-years-away***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 11:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/03/3518441/3518441_1564061FCC6C4F0F846223167F1E69B9_180103_3518441_Neuroscientist_predicts_better_Alzheimer_s_treat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8C8/C10/8C8C109AF5F240B49DA474AFBFC1EEAD_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, alzheimer's, alzheimer's cure, alzheimer's treatment, memory loss, brain, sleep treatment, neural stem cells]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3518365</guid>
      <title>What is the keto diet?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new diet that has been gaining in popularity in Silicon Valley reportedly can help those practicing it burn 10 times as much fat as a standard diet. The ketogenic  keto  diet was first introduced in the 1920s to treat epilepsy and diabetes, Business Insider reported. It involves eating only 50 grams of carbohydrates a day, roughly one plain bagel or a cup of white rice. The USDA recommends people eat 225 to 325 grams of carbs a day. On a keto diet, the body switches into starvation mode and burns excess fat stores for fuel.On the diet, healthy fats make up 80 percent of daily caloric intake, while protein intake should be 20 percent. For comparison, the average American gets 50 percent of calories from carbs, 30 percent from fat and 15 percent from protein, according to the CDC.  The human body breaks down carbs into glucose, to be used for energy or stored in the liver and muscles as glycogen. When carbs are taken out of the diet, the body burns up glucose reserves and then breaks down stored fat into fatty acids. These fatty acids move to the liver and are converted into ketones.The brain and other organs use up ketones in a process called ketosis. Some studies have found a low-carb, high-fat diet could may promote weight loss, improve focus, and hold off age-related diseases.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Keto diet is high fat, low carb2. Carbs are limited to 50 grams with keto diet3. Body burns up glucose then turns fat into fatty acids when carbs are taken out of diet4. The fatty acids are turned into ketones in the liver, which feed brain and other organsVOICEOVER (in English): "The ketogenic diet is a high-fat, low carb plan where healthy fats make up 80% of a person's daily calories, and protein 20%."  "It involves eating only 50 grams of carbohydrates a day, roughly one plain bagel or a cup of white rice. By comparison, the USDA recommends people eat 225 to 325 grams of carbs a day." "When carbs are taken out of the diet, the body burns up glucose reserves and then breaks down stored fat into fatty acids." "These fatty acids move to the liver and are converted into ketones. The brain and other organs use up ketones in a process called ketosis." SOURCES: Business Insiderhttp://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-keto-diet-beginners-2017-12/#the-keto-diet-is-like-atkins-on-steroids-it-turns-the-body-into-a-fat-burning-machine-4***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 09:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/03/3518365/3518365_ABDC178C92254F4B800FA9C2BFDAF7B3_180103_3518365_What_is_the_keto_diet__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B92/E0A/B92E0A04F3A6468C9EFFB5F09A6EE2B9_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Ketogenic diet, keto diet, high fat low carb diet, high healthy fat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3518340</guid>
      <title>Cyclone bomb may hit U.S. east coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA meteorological phenomenon known as Bombogenesis, or a cyclone bomb, may occur off the eastern U.S. coast this week. According to CNN, this occurs when an area of low pressure drops by more than 24 millibars in 24 hours. The result is a bomb cyclone.Meteorologists predict that one could hit the U.S. on Wednesday or Thursday.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of cold air over Earth2. Depiction of storm forming3. Depiction of pressure dropping, time and bombogenesisVOICEOVER (in English): "Bombogenesis, or a cyclone bomb, happens after cold, dry air from the stratosphere makes its way into an area of low pressure.""This can generate a powerful storm.  Bombogenesis occurs when the pressure to drops by more than 24 millibars in 24 hours."SOURCES: CNN, Mashablehttp://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/02/us/cold-weather-continues/index.htmlhttp://mashable.com/2018/01/02/weather-bomb-to-strike-east-coast-arctic-blast-coldest-to-date/#Zl_tBM.LlaqN***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 09:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/03/3518340/3518340_E3E8BD823835444BB122ED26091271CD_180103_3518340_Cyclone_bomb_may_hit_U_S__east_coast_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8E2/F6C/8E2F6CC8495B45FD8E7E5B5EB908A294_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bomb cyclone, what is a bomb cyclone, what is a weather bomb, bombogenesis, us east coast, new york cyclone bomb, boston cyclone bomb, weather bomb]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3518334</guid>
      <title>Chocolate could go extinct by 2050</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists say chocolate is in danger of disappearing by 2050 due to effects from global warming. Researchers from the University of California are now working with the Mars company to save the cacao plant from disappearing, Business Insider reported. Warmer temperatures and drier weather conditions will soon threaten the world's cacao plants. Cacao can only grow within a narrow strip of rainforested land about 20 degrees north and south of the equator, where temperature, rain and humidity are relatively constant year round.   Over half of the world's chocolate currently comes from two west African countries: Cte d'Ivoire and Ghana.  Rising temperatures over the next few decades will make those regions unsuitable to grow cacao.Berkeley scientists are now using a technology known as CRISPR to modify of cacao plant DNA in order to see if it can be made to survive in different climates. Researchers hope to be able to develop cacao plants that don't wilt or rot at their current elevations under warmer conditions. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cacao plantation2. Cacao producing regions of the world3. Over half the world's chocolate comes from Cte d'Ivoire and Ghana4. Scientists are planning to use CRISPR technology to alter cacao DNAVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists say chocolate is in danger of disappearing by 2050 due to warmer and drier conditions from global warming." "Cacao can only grow within a narrow strip of rainforested land about 20 degrees north and south of the equator, where temperature, rain and humidity are relatively constant year round.   "Over half of the world's chocolate comes from two African countries  Cte d'Ivoire and Ghana, however, rising temperatures over the next decades will make those regions unsuitable for cacao."  "Berkeley scientists hope to modify cacao DNA using CRISPR technology to develop plants that don't wilt or rot at their current elevations under warmer conditions." SOURCES: Business Insider, International Business Times, Forbes http://www.ibtimes.com/chocolate-shortage-may-lead-disappearance-within-40-years-scientists-say-2635577https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/01/01/is-chocolate-going-extinct-whats-being-done-to-prevent-this-disaster/#7467fd73540f***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 09:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/03/3518334/3518334_B26D59804D72497291D2417456654DBE_180103_3518334_Chocolate_could_go_extinct_by_2050_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/67D/752/67D75207D35E46009BE172E04AEE5E8B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, chocolate, cacao, cacao shortage, cacao global warming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3518160</guid>
      <title>Google planning massive Sunnyvale campus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONESearch giant Google is set to acquire five acres of land to build new offices on the site of an old U.S. Air Force Base.  The company will construct a Google campus that'll include two large office buildings at the site. According to San Jose newspaper The Mercury news, one of these buildings will be five stories high.Concept designs illustrate how the office design incorporates floor to floor, inclining slopes. The Mercury News reports this will allow workers to get from floor to floor via walking, cycling or rollerblading.Google says the new premises could house 4,500 employees.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of new office 2. Land area where office is set to be built3. Depiction of concept office buildings 4. Number of employees5. Height of building6. Buildings' incline design7. How employees go from floor to floor 8. Front view of concept buildings9. Aerial view of concept buildingsVOICEOVER (in English): "Google, has proposed to build a new complex on land of the former Onizuka U.S. Air Force Base in Sunnyvale, California for $21 million dollars.""If approved, the company will construct a new offices that'll include two large buildings.""Google says the new premises could house 4,500 employees.""According to San Jose newspaper The Mercury news, one of these buildings will be five stories high.""Concept designs illustrate how the office design incorporates floor to floor, inclining slopes." "The Mercury News reports this will allow workers to get from floor to floor via walking, cycling or rollerblading.""The project is called Carribean after one of the avenues the offices are built along. "If their proposals get the go ahead, Google says workers would be in the buildings by 2021 at the earliest."SOURCES: The Mercury News, CBS San Franciscohttps://www.mercurynews.com/2017/12/20/google-proposes-big-sunnyvale-campus-where-4500-could-work/https://www.mercurynews.com/2017/12/22/google-expansion-quest-produces-sunnyvale-city-land-deal/http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2017/12/22/google-proposes-offices-sunnyvale-caribbean-drive/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 06:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/03/3518160/3518160_346894EDE2664D399CFDFB8E12996805_180103_3518160_Google_planning_massive_Sunnyvale_campus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/98A/FD4/98AFD42E90C2455C93495C84A7B6639C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, google sunnyvale campus, google campus, silicon valley campus, google hq, google office, sunnyvale, google]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3518030</guid>
      <title>China targets far side of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina reportedly is going to attempt landing on the far side of the moon later this year, a feat never attempted by any other spacefaring nation.  According to the Guardian, China will launch two missions known as Chang'e 4. The first will see a satellite stationed some 60,000km from the lunar body to act as a communications relay between Earth and the moon. The second mission will see China attempt to land a spacecraft on the far side of the moon. If successful, Chang'e 4 could see China become the first nation to ever to navigate to that area of the moon. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of first part of Chang'e 4 mission2. Depiction of satellite over far side of moon3. Depiction of mission control4. Depiction of lander touching down on far side of moonVOICEOVER (in English): The first part of China's Chang'e 4 lunar mission this year will see the PRC attempt to station a satellite some 60,000 km over the dark side of the moon.Landing on the far side of the moon is difficult because it is not within view of Earth, so radio communication isn't possible.The next part of the mission will see China use the satellite to navigate and land an unmanned spacecraft on the far side of the moon, something never attempted before.SOURCES: The Guardian, IEEE Spectrumhttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/dec/31/china-mission-to-far-side-of-the-moon-space-discoveryhttps://spectrum.ieee.org/aerospace/robotic-exploration/china-promises-the-moon***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 02:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/03/3518030/3518030_909FB713EF6545918AB1DE4867D2A79A_180103_3518030_China_targets_far_side_of_the_moon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/42F/FD2/42FFD28D6BC844879A590E619B4F08DE_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  far side of the moon, china, chang e 4 mission, china goes to space, china lunar mission, china on the moon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3519376</guid>
      <title>Smartphones listening to people's television habits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEHundreds of smartphone apps could be tracking their users' television viewing habits.According to The New York Times, various game apps use software named Alphonso, a program which collects television viewing data via smartphone microphone, reported the Times. The paper found the software on various apps designed for children.Alphonso says users can opt out of this and is made clear before users download an app. The company told The Times its disclosures comply with federal trade guidelines.Alphonso Chief Executive Ashish Chordia told the Times around 1,000 games, messaging and social apps use Alphonso software. He didn't tell the paper which apps or how many users Alphonso keeps track off. The Alphonso company website says the software uses automated content recognition to identify what ads and programing a user is watching within "a fraction of a second, in a completely anonymous fashion." The company collects this data for advertisers, reported the Times. Alphonso can also pinpoint what people are watching via audio signals in TV ads. The software can also track what films via people watch at the cinema based on audio snippets provided to the company from film studios, reported the Times, citing Alphonso Chief Executive Ashish Chordia. The company also gathers data from TiVO, televisions, and streaming devices from other manufacturers, reported the Times. This, the Times reports, can be combined with characteristics such as age, sex and income via large data companies.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of smartphone microphone listening to television2. Depiction of smartphone microphone listening to television and recognising the audio3. Depiction of smartphone microphone listening to movie and recognising the audio 4. Overview of where software is used and how it might be combined with other data.VOICEOVER (in English): "Via a device's microphone, many apps reportedly use advance automated content recognition software by company Alphonso to listen in on users' television-viewing habits.""According to the New York Times, Alphonso does this by pinpointing audio signals in television ads or shows. The company tracks this data for advertisers.""Alphonso Chief Executive Ashish Chordia says users are made aware of the technology and that it complies with federal trade guidelines""The software can also track what films via people watch at the cinema based on audio snippets provided to the company from film studios.""The company also gathers data from TiVO, televisions, and streaming devices from other manufacturers."This, the Times reports, can be combined with characteristics such as age, sex and income via large data companies."SOURCES: New York Times, Alphonsohttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/28/business/media/alphonso-app-tracking.htmlhttp://alphonso.tv/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 13:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/04/3519376/3519376_80AF9E9986BD4598AE31D742419A6B27_180104_3519376_Smartphones_listening_to_people_s_television_hab_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/20D/9F1/20D9F15A4736401283E4DCC04F124029_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,phone tracking ads, tv ads smartphone, alphonso software, smartphone microphone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3519242</guid>
      <title>Recycled plastic garbage piling up in U.K. following China plastic ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina's ban on importing recycled plastic garbage is causing trash to pile up recycling facilities around the UK. China imported 7.3 million tons of waste plastic in 2017 from the U.S., the EU, the UK and Japan, Conversation reported.But starting this year, it is now banning 24 categories of recyclables and solid waste.  Britain alone sends around two thirds  about 500,000 tons  of its recycled plastic garbage to China every year. Recycling companies are now scrambling to find other markets for their recyclables, the Telegraph reported.  Some UK recycling firms are now looking to Malaysia and Vietnam, however, both those countries have capacity issues. Unless other alternative markets can be found, the plastics will have to be sent for incineration or dumped in a landfill.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China imported 7.3 million tons of recycled plastic in 2017 2. Britain exports  of its plastics garbage to China3. UK recycling firms are now looking to export trash to Malaysia and Vietnam 4. The UK may start incinerating or dumping the plastic in landfillsVOICEOVER (in English): "China imported 7.3 million tons of waste plastic in 2017 from the US, the EU, the UK and Japan. But starting this year, it's banning 24 categories of recyclables and solid waste." "Britain alone sends around two thirds  about 500,000 tons  of its recycled plastic to China every year." "UK recycling firms are now looking to Malaysia and Vietnam, however, both those countries have capacity issues." "Unless other alternative markets can be found, the plastics will have to be sent for incineration or dumped in a landfill."   SOURCES: Conversation, The Telegraphhttps://theconversation.com/china-bans-foreign-waste-but-what-will-happen-to-the-worlds-recycling-85924?utm_medium=amptwitter&utm_source=twitterhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/02/plastic-waste-already-building-uk-following-chinas-ban/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 11:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/04/3519242/3519242_6FAEE34AAC494A7FBB095D5B3AEE7DBC_180104_3519242_Recycled_plastic_garbage_piling_up_in_U_K__follo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C9C/F73/C9CF73812E8F4CC9B55D855F7C516B30_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China plastic ban, China recycled plastic ban, UK plastic garbage, UK recycled plastic garbage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3519833</guid>
      <title>Woman trials first bionic hand with sense of touch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAn Italian woman has become the first woman to try out the first bionic hand with a sense of touch that can be worn outside a laboratory.BBC reports that scientists in Rome have unveiled a portable bionic hand which uses sensors and electrodes to restore a sense of touch, trialing the technology on Almerina Mascarello who lost her hand in an accident 25 years ago.Sensors on the prosthetic hand detect whether an object being held is hard or soft, and send electrical signals to a portable computer.The signals are converted into sensory impulses and sent to electrodes implanted in the upper arm, which then relay it to the brain.The process happens in real time, and Mascarello claimed she felt the sensation spontaneously, as though it were her real hand. Unfortunately, she had to give back the prototype once the six-month trial period ended.Scientists are now working on miniaturizing the electronics and making the technology clinically usable.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Portable bionic hand fitted with sensors tested on a woman2. Sensors detect objects in the hand, send electric signals to computer3. Signals converted, sent to implanted electrodes, relayed to brain4. Process happens in real time, provides woman with sense of touchVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists in Rome have unveiled a portable bionic hand which uses sensors and electrodes to restore a sense of touch, trialing the technology on a woman who lost her hand 25 years ago.""Sensors on the prosthetic hand detect whether an object being held is hard or soft, and send electrical signals to a portable computer.""The signals are converted into sensory impulses and sent to electrodes implanted in the upper arm, which then relay it to the brain.""The process happens in real time, and the woman claimed she felt the sensation spontaneously, as though it were her real hand."SOURCES: BBC, ANSAhttp://www.bbc.com/news/health-42430895http://www.ansa.it/canale_scienza_tecnica/notizie/biotech/2018/01/04/mano-bionica-impiantata-in-una-donna-italiana_04c9bef7-ab4c-4d92-b89d-e3366484079e.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 07:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/05/3519833/3519833_98656C0F911445C48FBE4775649575C0_180105_3519833_Woman_trials_first_bionic_hand_with_sense_of_tou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/094/CED/094CED83838043ACB19E5976DAF256DD_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bionic hand, bionic limb, prosthesis, prosthetic hand, prosthetic limb, amputee, sensation, sense of touch, bionics, bionic technology, sensors, electrodes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3519769</guid>
      <title>Earth to see first blue moon eclipse since 1866</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEEarth will witness its first blue moon total lunar eclipse in over a century at the end of January, 2018. According to Space.com, east and central Asian countries in central, along with Indonesia, New Zealand and much of Australia, will get a quality view of the celestial event. Hawaii, Alaska and northwest Canada will also be able to witness it.The last blue moon total lunar eclipse took place on March 31, 1866, reported Space.com, citing reference book Canon of Lunar Eclipses.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of lunar orbit and lunar eclipse2. Blue moon lunation3. Visibility on mapVOICEOVER (in English): "Regular lunation, the moon's orbit of the earth, follows a 29-day cycle.  This is why, in general, there is usually one full moon a month.""The lunar eclipse on Jan. 31, 2018 will be extra special as it will be twinned with another lunar event.""Blue moons occur when there are two full moons in a month, usually at the beginning and very end.""On Jan. 31, the lunar eclipse at the end of January will coincide with a blue moon for the first time in 152 years.""Much of Asia, Australasia and northwest America will get a quality view of the celestial event.""Most of South America, Africa and Western Europe will not be able to see it.""The rest of the world will have a limited view based on their location."SOURCES: Space, NASA, Engadgethttps://www.space.com/39241-first-blue-moon-total-eclipse-150-years.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/vision/universe/watchtheskies/07jul_bluemoon.htmlhttps://www.engadget.com/2018/01/02/rare-blue-moon-lunar-eclipse-january-31st/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 06:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/05/3519769/3519769_0926421C31F5410794F514A85A69871E_180105_3519769_Earth_to_see_first_blue_moon_eclipse_since_1866_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9EF/DC1/9EFDC16034C7463E81FD7A94DA910DC0_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, blue moon 2018, total lunar eclipse, eclipse 2018, where to see blue moon, blue moon in sky, blue moon, eclipse 2018, eclipse 2017]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3519764</guid>
      <title>Recycled plastic garbage piling up in U.K. following China plastic ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina's ban on importing recycled plastic garbage is causing trash to pile up recycling facilities around the UK. China imported 7.3 million tons of waste plastic in 2017 from the U.S., the EU, the UK and Japan, Conversation reported.But starting this year, it is now banning 24 categories of recyclables and solid waste.  Britain alone sends around two thirds  about 500,000 tons  of its recycled plastic garbage to China every year. Recycling companies are now scrambling to find other markets for their recyclables, the Telegraph reported.  Some UK recycling firms are now looking to Malaysia and Vietnam, however, both those countries have capacity issues. Unless other alternative markets can be found, the plastics will have to be sent for incineration or dumped in a landfill.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China imported 7.3 million tons of recycled plastic in 2017 2. Britain exports  of its plastics garbage to China3. UK recycling firms are now looking to export trash to Malaysia and Vietnam 4. The UK may start incinerating or dumping the plastic in landfillsVOICEOVER (in English): "China imported 7.3 million tons of waste plastic in 2017 from the US, the EU, the UK and Japan. But starting this year, it's banning 24 categories of recyclables and solid waste." "Britain alone sends around two thirds  about 500,000 tons  of its recycled plastic to China every year." "UK recycling firms are now looking to Malaysia and Vietnam, however, both those countries have capacity issues." "Unless other alternative markets can be found, the plastics will have to be sent for incineration or dumped in a landfill."   SOURCES: Conversation, The Telegraphhttps://theconversation.com/china-bans-foreign-waste-but-what-will-happen-to-the-worlds-recycling-85924?utm_medium=amptwitter&utm_source=twitterhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/02/plastic-waste-already-building-uk-following-chinas-ban/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 06:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/05/3519764/3519764_C4499565CC754B6D9E86D6A2D7C1EC67_180105_3519764_Recycled_plastic_garbage_piling_up_in_U_K__follo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A96/78C/A9678CDD5B9049A58E34ED8BF94A982A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China plastic ban, China recycled plastic ban, UK plastic garbage, UK recycled plastic garbage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3519757</guid>
      <title>F-35Bs may fly combat missions in 2018</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe F-35B jet may see action this year as models of the plane will reportedly be deployed to watercraft in potential conflict hotspots.According to Marine Corp Times, the jet will join U.S. Marine vessels in the Pacific and Middle East.Engadget reports that the F-35B is noted for its technological prowess, in particular  short takeoff and vertical landing (STVOL) process. This allows it to operate from vessels and bases with not built, or unable to accomodate for current aircraft.Engadget reports that the Marines plans to purchase 353 models of the b-variant and 67 of the aircraft carrier oriented c-variant.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. F-35B flying 2. F-35B taking off from ship3. Distance F-35B can fly with payload4. Number of F-35 models U.S. Marine Corp plans to purchaseVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Marine Corp Times, the F-35B will join U.S. Marine vessels in the Pacific and Middle East." "The F-35B is noted for its its short takeoff and vertical landing capability." "This allows it to fly from bases unable to accomodate planes as well as ships and vessels not built for conventional fighter jets.""Compared to the F-35A, the B's fuel tank is one third smaller to make room for vertical take off components.""The plane can fly at mach 1.6, holds a 7.0 maximum g-rating and can carry a 6,800-kilogram payload.""With payload, it can fly with that ordinance for up to 513 miles, or just 33 miles farther than the 480-mile distance between New York City and Detroit.""Engadget reports that the Marines plan to purchase 353 models of the B-variant and 67 of the aircraft carrier-oriented C-variant.SOURCES: Marine Corp Times, Engadgethttps://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2017/12/22/new-in-2018-f-35b-baptism-of-fire/https://www.engadget.com/2018/01/01/f-35-may-see-combat-in-2018/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/05/3519757/3519757_58068AE9DCFA4BC793B81CF472A58C39_180105_3519757_F_35Bs_may_fly_combat_missions_in_2018_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B9E/829/B9E8297FE4B9493CAB0B770FE79199F5_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  f-35b, f35 jet, f-35 lightning ii, us air force, SVTOL]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3519700</guid>
      <title>How the Ripple platform works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONERipple is currently the second most valuable digital currency on the market, second only to Bitcoin.Ripple is both a payment network and a cryptocurrency. It uses blockchain technology, but is differentiated from other platforms by its ties with legitimate financial institutions, reports CNN Money.Ripple's currency is known as XRP and is not mined by users; the company has control. The company initially created 100 billion coins, with 38 billion currently in circulation.The rest of the coins will reportedly be released into the market gradually  up to a billion XRP tokens a month.Other cryptocurrencies have a stored value and can be used to buy goods and services. But XRPs mainly cover transaction fees as an anti-spam measure, and are destroyed soon after.Ripple's main purpose is to facilitate global money transfers. Banks take 3 to 5 days to process cross-border payments, but transactions on the Ripple network are cleared in only 4 seconds.The platform also boasts low fees, and can handle up to 1,500 transactions per second, compared to only seven on Bitcoin.By and large, the core function of Ripple is markedly different from other cryptocurrencies available in the market. Whether or not it's a good investment is another thing entirely.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ripple payment network and cryptocurrency uses blockchain tech, has ties to financial institutions2. XRP controlled by one company, not mined like other cryptocurrencies 3. How XRP functions differently from other cryptocurrencies4. Ripple facilitates cross-border paymentsVOICEOVER (in English): "Ripple is both a payment network and a cryptocurrency. It uses blockchain technology, but is differentiated from other platforms by its ties with legitimate financial institutions.""Ripple's currency is known as XRP and is not mined by users. The company has control, initially creating 100 billion coins, with 38 billion currently in circulation.""Other cryptocurrencies have a stored value and can be used to buy goods and services. But XRPs mainly cover transaction fees as an anti-spam measure, and are destroyed soon after.""Ripple's main purpose is to facilitate global money transfers. Banks take 3 to 5 days to process cross-border payments, but transactions on the Ripple network are cleared in only 4 seconds."SOURCES: Ripple, CNN Moneyhttps://ripple.com/http://money.cnn.com/2018/01/02/technology/what-is-ripple-cryptocurrency/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 05:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/05/3519700/3519700_EF4F59A6FE464BEBB3193E890F253FBE_180105_3519700_How_the_Ripple_platform_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8DB/88B/8DB88B80330C47E2A45C6690F4326A91_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ripple, cryptocurrency, xrp, bitcoin, digital currency, ripple currency exchange, payment network, ripple network, ripplenet, cross border payment, global payment, global transactions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3521852</guid>
      <title>Sydney confirmed as the hottest place on Earth after reaching 47.3 C</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. northeast may be experiencing record-breaking low temperatures, but in the land down under, Aussies are melting from the sweltering heat.The Sydney Morning Herald reports that Sydney became the hottest place on Earth on January 7, with temperatures in the western suburb of Penrith reaching 47.3 degrees Celsius.It was a few degrees shy of breaking the record for hottest day in the area  a 47.8 degree temperature recorded in Richmond in 1939. The hot weather combined with strong winds increased bushfire occurrences, prompting certain areas to issue a total fire ban prohibiting open air fires, welding, barbecues, and throwing lit cigarettes, among others.The heat caused higher-than-normal ozone levels, prompting a forecast of poor air quality, which could affect those with respiratory problems.Extreme temperatures also affected train track infrastructure, and contributed to power outages, which affected roughly 3,000 properties throughout Sydney.The next few days are expected to be cooler compared to Sunday's scorcher, but still relatively hot.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Temperatures in Sydney up to 47.3 degrees Celsius2. Total fire ban in certain regions due to increased chances of bushfire3. Rise in ozone pollution caused by hot weather4. Public transport infrastructure and power also affected by high temperaturesVOICEOVER (in English): "Sydney became the hottest place on Earth on January 7, with temperatures in the western suburb of Penrith reaching 47.3 degrees Celsius.""The hot weather combined with strong winds increased bushfire occurrences, prompting certain areas to issue a total fire ban prohibiting open air fires, welding, barbecues, and throwing lit cigarettes, among others.""The heat caused higher-than-normal ozone levels, prompting a forecast of poor air quality, which could affect those with respiratory problems.""Extreme temperatures also affected train track infrastructure, and contributed to power outages, which affected roughly 3,000 properties throughout Sydney."SOURCES: Sydney Morning Herald, News.com.auhttp://www.smh.com.au/environment/weather/sydney-off-to-a-hot-start-as-it-braces-for-heatwave-temperatures-20180106-h0ej5h.htmlhttp://www.news.com.au/technology/environment/nsw-heatwave-sydney-the-hottest-place-on-earth/news-story/0486ad5df9b5025ac24a4507aa1b8a17***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 10:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/08/3521852/3521852_EC64F1E1591340DA95C91123183A94C9_180108_3521852_Sydney_confirmed_as_the_hottest_place_on_Earth_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/62E/3E7/62E3E7D7F02F4990B0860839D4847297_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hottest place, sydney hottest day, sydney heatwave, australia heatwave, nsw heatwave, australian summer, total fire ban, bushfire, ozone pollution, blackout, power outage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3521829</guid>
      <title>Ukraine getting anti-tank missiles from USA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEUkraine is set to receive anti-tank missiles from the U.S.In December, the U.S. government approved a 2014 request from Ukraine to receive FGM-148 Javelin manportable anti-tank guided missiles, reported Jane's 360. The missile has two attack modes and is controlled from a a reusable command launch unit, according to Military.com.It can be fired directly at a target in direct attack mode. The javelin also has a top attack mode, where it attacks targets from above.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of soldier and tank2. Depiction of soldier firing missile at tank3. Depiction of soldier blowing up tank4. Javelin missile attacking tank from aboveVOICEOVER (in English): "In December, the U.S. government approved a 2014 request from Ukraine to receive FGM-148 Javelin man-portable anti-tank guided missiles.""The missile has two attack modes and is controlled from a a reusable command launch unit.""It can be fired directly at a target in direct attack mode. The missile is reportedly lethal against most conventional tank armor.""The javelin also has a top attack mode, where it attacks targets from above."SOURCES: Jane's 360, Military.comhttp://www.janes.com/article/76837/javelin-atgms-approved-for-ukrainehttps://www.military.com/equipment/fgm-148-javelin***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 10:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/08/3521829/3521829_5D07632FCD6049A7A5FEBF51A3DF2343_180108_3521829_Ukraine_getting_anti_tank_missiles_from_USA_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FCB/0C8/FCB0C848EBF243908008740BE7282E5C_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, javelin missile, javelin, ukraine, fgm-148, anti-tank missile, javelin missile, javelin missiles, javelin v tank, military technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3521645</guid>
      <title>Researchers develop device to help those suffering from tinnitus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new device may hold the key to silencing the persistent ringing sufferers of tinnitus often hear.Tinnitus is characterized as a persistent ringing, or similar noise, that can heard in the ears. It affects around 25 million Americans, according to U.S. government information from the National Institute on Deafness and Other Communication Disorders. It isn't a disease, but a symptom of something wrong in the auditory system. This can be anything from ear wax in the canal, hearing loss to more serious conditions such as diseases of the heart and blood vessels.The device, designed by University of Michigan researchers, works by emitting timed sounds and low-strength electrical pulses that direct damaged nerve cells back toward normal functionality. According to a University of Michigan news release, researchers tested the device on animals and 20 human patients for four weeks. The human patients were divided into two groups, one with a real device and one that only produced sounds. After four weeks the group with the real device reported an improved life quality with the sound usually generated by tinnitus having decreased.Details of the device and research were published in the journal Science Translational Medicine.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of tinnitus patient2. Depiction of tinnitus3. Depiction of how the device works4. Depiction of neurons in brain returning to normal activityVOICEOVER (in English): "Tinnitus is characterized as a persistent ringing, or similar noise, that can heard in the ears.""Lead researcher Susan Shore says that the dorsal cochlear nucleus, a region of the brainstem, is the root of tinnitus.""Shore says that when neurons in these region become hyperactive and interact with each other, this generates the perceived noise.""The experimental University of Michigan device tackles tinnitus via two senses.""First it plays noise, and alternates that by firing a mild electrical pulse to the cheek or neck.""This dual approach triggers a process known as stimulus-timing dependent plasticity aimed at resetting the hyperactive neurons and how the brain processes the senses."SOURCES: University of Michigan, National Institute on Deafness and Other Communication Disorders, CBS Detroit  http://ns.umich.edu/new/multimedia/videos/25353-specially-timed-signals-ease-tinnitus-symptoms-in-test-aimed-at-condition-s-root-causehttps://www.nidcd.nih.gov/health/tinnitushttp://detroit.cbslocal.com/2018/01/03/u-m-researchers-say-new-device-provides-relief-from-tinnitus/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 06:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/08/3521645/3521645_7F5AFD6261944531ADFC00E1D52C44C6_180108_3521645_Researchers_develop_device_to_help_those_sufferi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D82/446/D82446FD041C47CF94E2C9DC26E809E2_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tinnitus research, tinnitus, ear health, auditory system health, tinnitus technology, university of michigan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3521623</guid>
      <title>The U.0.S doesn't actually have a nuclear button</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEIn the event the U.S. were to launch a nuclear attack, the president does not hit a "nuclear button."Instead, a mid-level military officer usually travels with the president at all times, who carries the "Presidential Emergency Satchel" also called the "The Football," Popular Mechanics reports.Inside the satchel is a black book with a list of strike options, a three-by-five-inch card with presidential authentication codes to confirm his or her identity; a list of secure presidential bunkers and instructions for using the Emergency Broadcast System.In the event the president chooses the nuclear option, he consults with his advisers on what contingency plans to activate from the black book. Next, the president's identity is confirmed to strategic nuclear forces by reading a code off the three-by-five-inch card, known as "The Biscuit."The president's orders are then passed down the chain of command to U.S. bomber, missile and submarine crews around the world. The system is made to be fast, but also has some measures in place to mitigate impulsiveness. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A military officer carrying the Football behind the President2. The satchel contains a black book, note card, bunker locations and Emergency Broadcast System instructions3. The operating procedure to initiate a nuclear attack4. President's orders are passed to bomber, missile and submarine crews worldwideVOICEOVER (in English): "The President travels at all times with a mid-level officer who carries the 'Presidential Emergency Satchel' also called the 'The Football.'" "Inside the satchel is a black book with a list of strike options, a three-by-five inch card with Presidential authentication codes to confirm his or her identity; a list of secure presidential bunkers and instructions for using the Emergency Broadcast System."If the President decides to go nuclear, he consults his advisers on what contingency plans to activate from the black book. Next, the President's identity is confirmed to strategic nuclear forces by reading a code off the three-by-five inch card, known as "The Biscuit.""The President's orders are then passed down the chain of command to U.S. bomber, missile and submarine crews around the world." SOURCES: Popular Mechanics, CNNhttp://www.popularmechanics.com/military/weapons/a14559914/there-isnt-actually-a-nuclear-button/http://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/03/politics/trump-nuclear-football-explainer/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 06:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/08/3521623/3521623_CB73F8FBF1304EB5961F781E2E751F27_180108_3521623_The_U_0_S_doesn_t_actually_have_a_nuclear_button_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ACB/CC0/ACBCC04FB18B477198A9959073206542_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Presidential Emergency Satchel, The Football, The Biscuit, nuclear launch procedures]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3521603</guid>
      <title>Tabby's Star flicker is caused by space dust</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists say they now have an explanation for why Tabby's Star flickers  space dust. Thanks to a Kickstarter-crowdfunded astronomy project, a team of 200 scientists now believe a cloud of dust particles is causing the star to appear to flicker, the Washington Post reported. KIC 8462852  the official star name  is best known for its sudden drops in brightness, according to Science News. Researchers reported that Tabby Star grew dimmer in blue wavelengths than in red ones, Science News reported. The dimming is most likely being caused by dust particles less than a micrometer in size.The researchers will next try to determine where the dust originates from. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tabby's Star and space dust2. Las Cumbres reflecting telescopes3. Tabby Star growing dimmer in blue wavelengths than in red ones4. The dust particles are less than a micrometer in sizeVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists say they now have an explanation for why Tabby's Star flickers  space dust. The star is best known for its sudden drops in brightness." "A team of 200 scientists now believe a cloud of dust particles is causing the star to appear to flicker.""Researchers reported that Tabby's Star grew dimmer in blue wavelengths than in red ones between March 2016 and May 2017.""They believe this is likely being caused by dust particles less than a micrometer in size."SOURCES: Science News, Washington Posthttps://www.sciencenews.org/article/aliens-ruled-out-why-tabbys-star-flickershttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/speaking-of-science/wp/2018/01/03/the-strangest-star-in-the-sky-finally-has-an-explanation-for-its-flicker/?utm_term=.26b92a8f6258***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 05:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/08/3521603/3521603_1F549234E4E74A2CAD37A9055A6744DD_180108_3521603_Tabby_s_Star_flicker_is_caused_by_space_dust_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ACF/1CC/ACF1CC7986734416B779BE4DED053F8A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Tabby's Star, KIC 8462852, Tabby Star's flickering, Tabby Star's dimming, space dust]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3521525</guid>
      <title>Dutch company plans to build world's largest offshore wind farm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA sand bank in the North Sea could be home to a vast offshore wind farm by 2027  possibly the world's largest.The Guardian reports that a Dutch energy company is planning to build a massive offshore wind farm on Dogger Bank in the North Sea, which will include an artificial island equipped with a runway, harbor, and other facilities.The turbines harness wind energy to generate alternating current, which will be sent via cables to the island. Since alternating currents incur power losses when transported over long distances, converters on the island will change it into direct current before transmitting it to the UK, Belgium, the Netherlands, Germany, Denmark, and Norway.The current largest offshore wind farm, the London Array, can produce 630 megawatts of power. The Dogger Bank project, if it comes to fruition, is set to produce over 30,000 megawatts.Energy company TenneT will likely shoulder the 1.5 billion-euro cost of building the island hub, and source wind farm developers to install the turbines.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Offshore wind farm and artificial island hub on Dogger Bank2. How wind farm works3. Electricity transmitted to six countries around the North Sea4. Power capacity of Dogger Bank wind farm compared to London ArrayVOICEOVER (in English): "A Dutch company is planning to build a massive offshore wind farm on Dogger Bank in the North Sea, which will include an artificial island equipped with a runway, harbor, and other facilities.""The turbines harness wind energy to generate alternating current, which will be sent via cables to the island. There, it will be converted into direct current, to avoid incurring power losses when it's transmitted to the UK, Belgium, the Netherlands, Germany, Denmark, and Norway""The current largest offshore wind farm, the London Array, can produce 630 megawatts of power. The Dogger Bank project, if it comes to fruition, is set to produce over 30,000 megawatts."SOURCES: The Guardian, BBChttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/dec/29/is-this-the-future-dutch-plan-vast-windfarm-island-in-north-seahttp://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-humber-42552319***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 03:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/08/3521525/3521525_F5045C5225F9441199FB849C513DA8A3_180108_3521525_Dutch_company_plans_to_build_world_s_largest_off_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/26C/6AD/26C6ADAE2DA24019AC5B0CA4B4B3102F_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, wind farm, wind energy, offshore wind farm, world's biggest wind farm, wind power, north sea, dogger bank, dogger sand bank, TenneT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3522536</guid>
      <title>China aims for total surveillance using facial recognition technology</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFacial recognition is popping up everywhere in China, as the government looks to technology to keep constant track of its people and what they're up to.According to the Washington Post, Chinese apartments equipped with keyless entry use cameras to scan and verify residents' faces. But although convenient, the technology is also being used by authorities to monitor individuals and identify alleged 'bad guys' and persons of interest.The project, called 'Sharp Eyes', intends to connect public security cameras with those in private compounds and buildings, to form a nationwide surveillance and data-sharing network.Sharp Eyes' aim is to compile information on citizens, including criminal and medical records, travel and purchase history, and social media use, and link it to a face and identity card.Its name derives from a Communist slogan, and is linked to Chairman Mao's attempts to get citizens to spy on each other.Supposedly, the system can track suspicious behavior to help eliminate crime, which in China can be anything from homicide to speaking out against the government.Ultimately, the goal is for total surveillance, and in a country where being an ethnic minority or an activist can get you flagged, that prospect is frightening.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Facial recognition employed in apartment buildings, homes2. Police using technology to track people and analyze their behaviors3. Sharp eyes project to integrate public and private surveillance4. Citizens' data compiled and linked to an identity card5. Chinese citizens assigned a social credit scoreVOICEOVER (in English): "Chinese apartments equipped with keyless entry use cameras to scan and verify residents' faces.""But although convenient, the technology is also being used by authorities to monitor individuals and identify alleged 'bad guys' and persons of interest.""The project, called 'Sharp Eyes', intends to connect public security cameras with those in private compounds and buildings, to form a nationwide surveillance and data-sharing network.""Sharp Eyes' aim is to compile information on citizens, including criminal and medical records, travel and purchase history, and social media use, and link it to a face and identity card."SOURCES: Washington Posthttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/world/wp/2018/01/07/feature/in-china-facial-recognition-is-sharp-end-of-a-drive-for-total-surveillance/?utm_term=.2b02765ffcc7***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/09/3522536/3522536_A6A676B099164FE9A61559DF5E27E722_180109_3522536_China_aims_for_total_surveillance_using_facial_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/49E/2F3/49E2F3C76302496BADD3D80EECA496D7_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, facial recognition, surveillance, surveillance state, china surveillance, police state, sharp eyes project, china surveillance system, total surveillance, social credit, sesame credit, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3523431</guid>
      <title>Kodak announces its own cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEOnce dismal Kodak shares are now soaring after the company announced plans to get into the cryptocurrency business during the 2018 CES tech event in Las Vegas.BBC reports that Kodak is launching an image rights platform with its own blockchain. Photographers register their images and instantly get paid per use with the company's own virtual currency, called  Kodak coins.To guard against copyright infringement, Kodak software will continuously search the web for violations and take care of licensing.The company is set to host an initial coin offering on January 31.Kodak's other initiative is the Kash Miner, a bitcoin mining rig box equipped with processors and a fan, that uses the same amount of electricity as a continuously-running hair dryer.The machines will be rented out to customers for two years, with an upfront payment of $3,400, plus 50% of all proceeds generated by the machine from mining Bitcoin.According to the company, customers should be able to earn more than $300 a month, or $9,000 overall.Still, many are skeptical. Some critics believe Kodak is merely getting into cryptocurrency to raise stock prices. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Kodak to have own blockchain and cryptocurrency for photographers2. Kodak software will be used to search the web for copyright violations 3. Kodak Kash Miner components and electricity usage4. Kodak Kash Miner rented out for bitcoin miningVOICEOVER (in English): "Kodak is launching an image rights platform with its own blockchain. Photographers register their images and instantly get paid per use with Kodak coins, the company's own virtual currency.""To guard against copyright infringement, Kodak software will continuously search the web for violations and take care of licensing.""Kodak's other initiative is the Kash Miner, a bitcoin mining rig box equipped with processors and a fan, that uses the same amount of electricity as a continuously-running hair dryer.""The machines will be rented out to customers for two years, with an upfront payment of $3,400, plus 50% of all proceeds generated by the machine from mining Bitcoin."SOURCES: BBC, Business Wire, Business Insiderhttp://www.bbc.com/news/technology-42630136https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180109006183/en/KODAK-WENN-Digital-Partner-Launch-Major-Blockchainhttp://www.businessinsider.com/kashminer-kodak-bitcoin-mining-2018-1***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 11:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/10/3523431/3523431_D4C1AA78AD614BDA85A3BDEFE24C5CA4_180110_3523431_Kodak_announces_its_own_cryptocurrency_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2F5/19B/2F519BD7B9D44E0EB6E40D597D6C0EFE_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kodak, kodak coin, cryptocurrency, blockchain, blockchain technology, bitcoin, bitcoin mining, photography, copyright, Kodak Kash Miner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3523955</guid>
      <title>Japanese astronaut tweets about getting taller in space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA Japanese astronaut has grown nearly an inch taller after launching into space 21 days ago.Japanese astronaut Norishige Kanai mistakenly tweeted this week that he had grown 3.5 inches after spending 3 weeks on board the International Space Station. He later corrected that claim to 0.8 inches.Astronauts spines often expand in space due to the lack of gravity, reports the BBC. This results in a height increase. The height returns to normal after the astronaut returns to Earth. Astronauts can also experience a loss of bone minerals and muscle mass.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Astronaut in ISS2. Expansion of spine3. Loss of muscle mass and bone mineralVOICEOVER (in English): Japanese astronaut Norishige Kanai mistakenly tweeted this week that he had grown 3.5 inches after spending 3 weeks on board the International Space Station. He later corrected that claim to 0.8 inches.In space, astronauts spines often expand due to the lack of gravity. This results in a height increase.Height returns to normal after the astronaut returns to Earth.Astronauts can also experience a loss of bone minerals and muscle mass.SOURCES: BBC, Newsweekhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-42618786http://www.newsweek.com/astronaut-grows-35-inches-space-may-not-fit-spacecraft-seat-ride-home-775289***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 06:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/11/3523955/3523955_450155F8106D4689BCA215D34342ED8E_180111_3523955_Japanese_astronaut_tweets_about_getting_taller_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D0D/0AB/D0D0AB604D4C40ED997FEA4C8002E5F4_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, pace effects on the human body, space human body, taller from space, international space station, Norishige Kanai, ISS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3523819</guid>
      <title>Study connects painkillers to weakened fertility</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe National Academy of Sciences has found that some painkillers can negatively impact male reproductive organs.According to CNN, aspirin, paracetamol and ibuprofen can brought about a condition known as compensated hypogonadism in young men. This condition is linked to weakened fertility, depression and increased risk of stroke or heart failure. Previous research demonstrated that the painkillers impacted the testicles of male babies when ingested by mothers during pregnancy, CNN reported.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of pill and penis2. Overview of study3. Depiction of blood stream4. Depiction of brian, penis and heartVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study by the U.S. National Academy of Sciences, common pain medication negatively impacts male reproductive organs." "CNN reports that the research looked at ibuprofen, aspirin and acetaminophen (better known as paracetamol). These drugs disrupt male hormones.""The study looked at 31 healthy Caucasian men between 18 and 35 and gave one group two 600 milligram ibuprofen doses per day, and the others dummy placebo pills." "After a fortnight, men taking the painkiller had their luteinizing hormones  hormones linked to testosterone and sperm production  match the ibuprofen in their blood.""They also simultaneously saw their rate of testosterone to luteinizing hormones diminish.""This created a condition linked to weakened fertility, stroke and heart attacks known as compensated hypogonadism in the men affected.""A researcher told CNN the impact on the men in the study is reversible but the impact of long-term use is unknown."SOURCES: National Academy of Sciences, CNNhttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/01/03/1715035115.fullhttp://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/08/health/ibuprofen-male-fertility-study/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/11/3523819/3523819_48CC4EA94F7D48DCAB03644AF9B88DD8_180111_3523819_Study_connects_painkillers_to_weakened_fertility_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EF9/3A0/EF93A07DCE434DAFBC16E936D6AE41AB_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, infertility, infertile men, compensated hypogonadism, ibuprofen side effects, pain medication side effects, paracetamol side effects, aspirin side effects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3523804</guid>
      <title>New method of coral sowing could help large-scale restoration</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers have found a new way to cheaply and efficiently restore dying corals, using a method similar to how farmers scatter seedlings onto a field.With the world's corals deteriorating at an alarming rate, and restoration often slow and laborious, a team of scientists from nonprofit group Secore International has come up with a better approach to sowing corals.According to Secore, the new method involves harvesting coral larvae and planting them on tetrapod-shaped cement substrates. In a few weeks, the larvae will turn into coral polyps which can be sown on the reef. The seeding units don't require manual attachment and only need to be wedged into reef's crevices. One day, they can be sown from boats or by underwater drone.Twelve months after the sowing, the scientists found at least one coral growing on half the units.They believe the technique can sow 10,000 corals in just 50 working hours, compared to the hundreds or even thousands of hours needed for common restoration methods.The team is currently working to refine each step of their novel sowing approach.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of degraded coral reefs and manual coral transplanting2. Coral larvae harvested, settled on tetrapod-shaped substrates, and left to grow3. Substrates with coral polyps sown on the reefs4. Corals growing from the substratesVOICEOVER (in English): "With the world's corals deteriorating at an alarming rate, and restoration often slow and laborious, a team of scientists has come up with a better approach to sowing corals.""The new method involves harvesting coral larvae and planting them on tetrapod-shaped cement substrates. In a few weeks, the larvae will turn into coral polyps...""...which can be sown on the reef. The seeding units don't require manual attachment and only need to be wedged into reef's crevices. One day, they can be sown from boats or by underwater drone.""Twelve months after the sowing, the scientists found at least one coral growing on half the units."SOURCES: Secore Internationalhttp://www.secore.org/site/newsroom/article/sowing-corals-a-new-approach-paves-the-way-for-large-scale-coral-reef-restoration.159.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 03:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/11/3523804/3523804_259ECF4A425F4D36B12E7C8A3329BFDA_180111_3523804_New_method_of_coral_sowing_could_help_large_scal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/018/43F/01843FAB08F445DD9AE6439D748F2FBD_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, corals, coral sowing, sowing corals, coral planting, coral reefs, coral bleaching, coral restoration, substrates]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3525162</guid>
      <title>How alligators survive a freezing winter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA video released Monday shed light on the unique way alligators adapt to icy winter conditions. The Charlotte Observer reports that in the video, alligators in Shallotte River Swamp Park in North Carolina were seemingly frozen inside a pond, with only their snouts visible above the ice.Alligators are ectothermic, which means they don't generate their own body heat, and rely on the environment to regulate their internal temperature. Most gators live in temperate climates. But occasionally, a bomb cyclone brings in an icy winter and the scaly creatures have to deal.When temperatures reach freezing, gators are known to stick their snouts out of the water before the surface ices over.This allows them to continue breathing as they lower their body temperatures and metabolism, falling into a hibernating state in a process known as brumation.Once it becomes warm and the water thaws, the cold-blooded animals will slowly begin thermoregulating their body temperatures.Days after the frozen gator video made its rounds online, an update was posted showing the gators now out and about, though apparently still grumpy from their winter nap.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of alligators as ectothermic2. Alligators poke their snout out of the water during freezing conditions3. Depiction of brumation4. Alligators thermoregulate their bodies once temperatures become warmerVOICEOVER (in English): "Alligators are ectothermic, which means they don't generate their own body heat, and rely on the environment to regulate their internal temperature.""When temperatures reach freezing, gators are known to stick their snouts out of the water before the surface ices over.""This allows them to continue breathing as they lower their body temperatures and metabolism, falling into a hibernating state in a process known as brumation.""Once it becomes warm and the water thaws, the cold-blooded animals will slowly begin thermoregulating their body temperatures."SOURCES: Charlottle Observer, Business Insider, WECThttp://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article193968599.htmlhttp://www.businessinsider.com/alligators-survive-in-north-carolina-frozen-in-ice-for-days-nature-science-2018-1http://www.wect.com/story/37213619/alligators-get-a-nose-up-on-icy-conditions***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 16:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/13/3525162/3525162_564E448B1E7740A48C409D4A3A62C9E7_180113_3525162_How_alligators_survive_a_freezing_winter_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8F1/DE9/8F1DE9BF5DFD4D5181DBE462210B08CE_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, frozen alligators, frozen gators, alligator, gator, gator hibernation, gator brumation, hibernation, brumation, reptile hibernation, reptile brumation, cold blooded, ectothermic, north carolina]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3524605</guid>
      <title>Warming temperatures causing sea turtles to be born female</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONERising temperatures have caused a major downturn in male turtle populations in the northern Great Barrier Reef.A new study, published in the journal Current Biology, has found that 99 percent of sea turtles in the Pacific Ocean biggest green sea turtle rookery are female. Researchers say this is due to warming global temperatures.According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, a sea turtle's sex is temperature dependent. Males are born at around 27.7 degrees centigrade, while females are born at around 31 degrees centigrade.According to National Geographic, an area further south holds a ratio of 2 female to 1 males sea turtles.  Worldwide is around 3 to 1, reports National Geographic, citing research looking at 75 rookeries worldwide.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of turtle and eggs2. How sea turtles are born male or female3. Overview of turtle populationsVOICEOVER (in English): "New research has found that 99 percent of sea turtles in the Pacific Ocean's biggest green sea turtle rookery are female.""Researchers suspect this is due to warming temperatures.""A sea turtle's sex is temperature dependent.""Males are born at around 27.7 degrees centigrade, while females are born at around 31 degrees centigrade.""An area further south holds a ratio of two females to one male sea turtle.""According to National Geographic, recent research looking at 75 rookeries from around the globe put the ratio at 3 to 1""If rising temperatures continue, male turtles may be wiped out."SOURCES: NOAA, National Geographichttps://swfsc.noaa.gov/news.aspx?ParentMenuId=147&id=22881https://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/temperature-dependent.htmlhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/01/australia-green-sea-turtles-turning-female-climate-change-raine-island-sex-temperature/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 04:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/12/3524605/3524605_6360B16C613F4D309BB41B789417508A_180112_3524605_Warming_temperatures_causing_sea_turtles_to_be_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FB8/84C/FB884CDC37DC45E797DAB43EDB737638_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sea turtle sex, turtle gender, global warming, global warming, baby sea turtle, sea turtles hatching]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3526753</guid>
      <title>What are debris flows?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMore than a dozen people are dead and many more injured after a torrent of mud and debris swept through California's Santa Barbara County last week.The Ventura County Star reports that this deadly and shockingly common occurrence is called a 'debris flow,' though it's also commonly called a mudslide.Often at risk for debris flows are mountainous areas that have been ravaged by wildfire. Fire kills vegetation and nutrients in the soil, causing it to become hydrophobic or water-repellant.During intense rainfall, water that would normally be absorbed into the ground instead saturates it and causes the earth to liquefy into a flowing river of mud.Debris flows grow in size as they pick up boulders, trees, and other debris, and are powerful enough to uproot or destroy entire neighborhoods.Many of the deaths in Montecito reportedly occurred while most residents were asleep, after heavy rain fell in a short period of time around 3:30 a.m.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of wildfires burning through a mountain slope2. Soil becomes hydrophobic3. Heavy rainfall mixes with soil and loose rocks, forming debris flow  4. Debris flow capable of picking up large boulders, destroying housesVOICEOVER (in English): "Often at risk for debris flows are mountainous areas that have been ravaged by wildfire.""Fire kills vegetation and nutrients in the soil, causing it to become hydrophobic or water-repellant.""During intense rainfall, water that would normally be absorbed into the ground instead saturates it and causes the earth to liquefy into a flowing river of mud.""Debris flows grow in size as they pick up boulders, trees, and other debris, and are powerful enough to uproot or destroy entire neighborhoods."SOURCES: Wired, Ventura County Starhttps://www.wired.com/story/post-wildfire-mudslide/http://www.vcstar.com/story/news/2018/01/09/what-debris-flows-and-why-do-they-occur/1019382001/?from=new-cookie***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/15/3526753/3526753_7D566B09C02849689D5D3AE8F0790BF5_180115_3526753_What_are_debris_flows__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/632/B67/632B67AE4B754650BB88FC6ABFA66B4B_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, debris flow, mudslide, mudflow, wildfire, california debris flow, hydrophobic soil, disaster, natural disaster, fire flood cycle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3526653</guid>
      <title>Plane skids during landing and nearly winds up in sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA plane carrying 168 passengers and crew nearly wound up in the Black Sea after skidding during its landing at the weekend.Pegasus Airlines flight PC 8622 ran into problems while landing at Trabzon airport on Turkey's northern Black Sea coast on Saturday evening. Several media indicate the runway was freezing or icy. The Boeing 737-800 skidded and went down a cliffside beside the runway. Photos of the aftermath show the aircraft close to the Black Sea.The airline said in a statement all of the 168 passengers were without injury and disembarked the aircraft safely.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 2. Depiction of aircraft landing from plane's point of view3. Depiction of aircraft moving off runway4. Depiction of aircraft near Black Sea VOICEOVER (in English): "Pegasus Airlines flight PC 8622 ran into problems while landing at Trabzon airport on Turkey's northern Black Sea coast on Saturday evening.""Several media indicate the runway was freezing or icy.""The airline said the plane had a runway excursion incident during landing.""According to Reuters, the Boeing 737-800 skidded and went down a slope beside the runway.""The craft settled meters from the water.""Pegasus Airlines said all of the 168 passengers were uninjured following the incident."SOURCES: Pegasus Airlines, Hurriyet Daily News, Twitter @AmichaiStein1,  Reuters, Guardian, Evening Standardhttps://www.flypgs.com/en/press-room/announcement/about-pc-8622-ankara-trabzon-flighthttp://www.hurriyetdailynews.com/plane-skids-off-runway-in-northern-turkey-125679https://twitter.com/AmichaiStein1/status/952461393588117504https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jan/14/plane-skids-off-runway-trabzon-black-sea-coast-turkeyhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-airplane/plane-skids-off-turkish-runway-and-plunges-towards-sea-idUSKBN1F30C1?il=0https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/passenger-jet-skids-off-runway-and-comes-perilously-close-to-plummeting-into-sea-in-turkey-a3739551.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 09:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/15/3526653/3526653_61B25FD1ABD7415EBAC6DC074794825C_180115_3526653_Plane_skids_during_landing_and_nearly_winds_up_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/218/8A5/2188A547DE6B471E8FF094AC3F19767D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, landing goes wrong, plane skids off runway, plane landing turkey, landing goes wrong turkey, plane landing, pegasus airlines, trabzon landing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3526466</guid>
      <title>Taiwan unveils stage 1 of new circular metro line</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEConstruction is underway for a circular metro line that passes through the densely populated areas of Taipei and New Taipei City. The line will connect with the existing lines of the Taipei Metro system.The Circular line  or Yellow line  is an elevated, medium-capacity rapid transit system. All stations are designed with natural lighting, transparency, and spaciousness in mind.Stage I of the line is about 15.4 km (9.6 mi) long and consists of 14 stations. Dapinglin station, an existing underground station on the green line of the Taipei metro will serve as a transfer station for the circular line.The circular line will connect Dapinglin station in southern New Taipei City to New Taipei Industrial Park, in the western part of the city. Jing'an, Banciao, Touqianzhuang, will also serve as transfer hubs to train station and other MRT lines, while New Taipei Industrial Park connects passengers to the Taoyuan Airport MRT line. The Circular line's 17 driverless trains each consists of four carriages with a total of 68 carriages manufactured by Hitachi Rail ItalyInternational architect Emmanuelle Moureaux, who specializes in large-scale color projects, has been commissioned to design the color scheme for the stations and carriages. Constructed by Taiwan's RSEA Engineering Corporation, stage I broke ground seven years ago at a reported estimated cost of US$1.8 billion(NT$54.7 billion). Stage I of the circular line is scheduled to open to the public in June 2018.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show one of the stations2. Stage I's length and 14 stations3. Dapinglin station and passengers using it4. Train move from Southern New Taipei City to Western New Taipei City5. Train passing through the densely populated city. 6. Show one AbsaldoBreda's train car consists of four carriages  7. Stage I constructed 7 years ago, and costs about 1.8 billion USD. VOICEOVER (in English): "The Circular line or Yellow line is an elevated, medium-capacity rapid transit system, all stations are designed with natural lighting, transparency, and spaciousness.""The Stage I construction of the line is about 15.4 km (9.6 mi) long and consists of 14 stations.""Dapinglin station, an existing underground station on the green line of the Taipei metro will serve as a transfer station for the circular line.""The circular line will be going from Dapinglin station on the southern part of New Taipei City to New Taipei Industrial Park, on the western part of the city.""The circular line's train will pass through a wide range of urban environment within the densely populated New Taipei City.""The Circular line's 17 driverless train cars each consists of four carriages with a total of 68 carriages manufactured by Hitachi Rail Italy owned AbsaldoBreda."Constructed by Taiwan's RSEA Engineering Corporation, stage I broke ground 7 years ago, and reportedly estimated around 1.8 billion US dollars(NT$54.7 billion)."SOURCES: http://www.dorts.gov.taipei/public/Data/58251030171.pdfhttp://www.emmanuellemoureaux.com/circular-line/http://www.jjpan.com/portfolio/%E5%8F%B0%E5%8C%97%E6%8D%B7%E9%81%8B%E7%92%B0%E7%8B%80%E7%B7%9Adf112/http://italy.hitachirail.com/en/taipei_437.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 06:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/15/3526466/3526466_6B73BD2CBDD04788983F3D9D4E7B9ECE_180115_3526466_Taiwan_unveils_stage_1_of_new_circular_metro_lin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/240/9D5/2409D56F234A49C3888B29A528D415C4_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, taiwan circular line, taiwan circular line first stage, taiwan circular line construction, taiwan mrt , taiwan mrt line, taiwan public transportation technology, department of rapid transit systems, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3526434</guid>
      <title>Chelsea's new stadium plans on hold over 'right to light' dispute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA family cottage has halted development on Chelsea Football Club's new stadium in an upmarket area of London.Plans for redevelopment of their Stamford Bridge stadium has been suspended as it may block a local home's "right to light," reports the BBC. As the name suggests, that's a right for English landowners to receive light on their property. The concerned household believe say the new stadium could affect sunlight and daylight. Plans for the 1 billion pound project got the go ahead last year from London authorities last year.  Officials will meet on Monday to discuss how to proceed, the BBC reports. The new stadium would be capable of hosting 60,000 fans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of new Chelsea stadium2. Depiction of new Chelsea stadium blocking light3. Depiction of fans at planned Chelsea stadium4. Depiction of planned Chelsea stadiumVOICEOVER (in English): Chelsea Football Club's plans for redevelopment of their Stamford Bridge stadium has been suspended as it may block a local home's "right to light."As the name suggests, that's a right for English landowners to receive light on their property.The concerned household say the new stadium could affect sunlight and daylight. Plans for the 1 billion project got the go ahead last year from London authorities.  Officials will reportedly meet on Monday to discuss how to proceed.SOURCES: BBC, Stadium Database,  http://www.bbc.com/sport/football/42648061http://stadiumdb.com/designs/eng/stamford_bridge***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 05:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/15/3526434/3526434_0353D06CC5224B8D9B1D647FB9FCE9E5_180115_3526434_Chelsea_s_new_stadium_plans_on_hold_over__right__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E56/5A3/E565A373E9FB4D83A713F76CD281D289_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, chelsea new stadium plans, new chelsea stadium, chelsea stadium plans 3d, chelsea football club, stamford bridge, chelsea right to light]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3526421</guid>
      <title>Ice sheets found beneath Martian surface</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers have discovered ice sheets on Mars, according to a new study in the journal Science.The research looked at data from spacecraft on eight locations on Mars and found large swathes of ice.The sheets are said to be located near the surface, as well as close to depths of 100 m. Researchers also found cliffs made up of water ice.According to Science, the ice sheets could be useful for future missions to Mars.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Mars from space2. Depiction of Martian surface near ground3. Depiction of Martian surface from bird's eye view4. Depiction of astronauts exploring MarsVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Science, NASA, Gizmodohttp://science.sciencemag.org/content/359/6372/199https://www.nasa.gov/feature/jpl/steep-slopes-on-mars-reveal-structure-of-buried-icehttps://gizmodo.com/water-might-be-easier-to-find-on-mars-than-we-thought-1821990091***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 04:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/15/3526421/3526421_58BAB8E236AB41F6967F63F2ED426F68_180115_3526421_Ice_sheets_found_beneath_Martian_surface_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/18B/654/18B6541FEC1843478360F15BB1D64A90_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, water on mars, ice on mars, mars ice sheets, mission to mars, nasa, mars research, exploring mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3527530</guid>
      <title>Philippines volcano threat level moved to "critical"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEEruptions of steam and ash from an active volcano has made more than 3,000 people flee their homes in the Philippines.According to CNN,  the Mayon Volcano on Luzon island in the Philippines began erupting on Sunday.  Officials moved the alert level to 3 at the weekend, saying there was an "increased tendency towards hazardous eruption" in weeks or days. There are 5 alert levels in total. Authorities suspect the crater glow at the peak points to "the growth of a new lava dome and beginnings of lava flow towards the southern slopes". Level 3 is considered "critical", Cedric Daep, head of the Albay Provincial Disaster Risk Reduction and Management Office told Reuters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of volcano2. Depiction of volcano summit3. Depiction of volcano cross sectionVOICEOVER (in English): "The Mayon Volcano on Luzon island in the Philippines started spewing streams of lava and ash, making 3,000 flee the surrounding area,.""Authorities suspect the crater glow at the top suggests "the growth of a new lava dome and beginnings of lava flow towards the southern slopes".""Officials moved the alert level to 3 at the weekend, saying there was an "increased tendency towards hazardous eruption" in weeks or days. "There's 5 levels in total."SOURCES: PHIVOLCS-DOST, CNN, Reutershttps://twitter.com/phivolcs_dost/status/952523778956836866http://cnnphilippines.com/news/2018/01/14/PHIVOLCS-Mayon-Volcano-updates.htmlhttp://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/15/asia/mayon-volcano-alert-level-increased/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 11:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/16/3527530/3527530_7BB9BCD9C3D243EEAA5E5B5B206D49B3_180116_3527530_Philippines_volcano_threat_level_moved_to__criti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/836/911/8369117EED0145FB847BEE60214EBA87_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mayon volcano, volcanic eruption, luzon volcano, philippines volcano, lava eruption, volcanoes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3527367</guid>
      <title>UAE says Qatari jets intercepted two commercial flights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe United Arab Emirates said on Monday Qatari air force planes had intercepted two civilian aircraft en route to Bahrain, however Qatar denies the allegations. The UAE, along with Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and Egypt, imposed travel, diplomatic and trade restrictions on Qatar in June 2017, accusing it of funding terrorism, Reuters reported. The UAE General Civil Aviation Authority said two Emirati airliners carrying 277 passengers were met by Qatari fighter jets while flying between UAE and Bahrain.One of the flights was intercepted at 10:30 a.m., and the second at 11:05 a.m. at between 9,000 and 10,000 feet. The report did not say when the incidents occurred.   The UAE described the event as "a serious and renewed breach of international conventions and the safety of civil aircraft traffic."Qatar's foreign ministry claims that UAE fighter jets violated its airspace on Dec. 21 and Jan. 3. UAE has denied the claim. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Qatar fighter jets intercepting Emirates plane2. Two Emirati airliners were met by Qatari fighter jets3. Two separate flights were intercepted by Qatari planes4. Four Gulf states have imposed restrictions on QatarVOICEOVER (in English): "The United Arab Emirates said on Monday Qatari air force planes had intercepted two civilian aircraft en route to Bahrain, however Qatar denies the allegations." "The UAE General Civil Aviation Authority said two Emirati airliners carrying 277 passengers were met by Qatari fighter jets while flying between UAE and Bahrain.""One of the flights was intercepted at 10:30 a.m., and the second at 11:05 a.m. at between 9,000 and 10,000 feet. The report did not say when the incidents occurred."   "The UAE, along with Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and Egypt, imposed travel, diplomatic and trade restrictions on Qatar in June 2017, accusing it of funding terrorism, a claim Qatar denies."SOURCES: Reuters, CNNhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-emirates/uae-says-qatari-jet-fighters-intercepted-civilian-flights-idUSKBN1F40ZV?feedType=RSS&http://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/15/middleeast/uae-qatar-jets-intl/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/16/3527367/3527367_5C754A9213CC46B2A237BEE1518942D7_180116_3527367_UAE_says_Qatari_jets_intercepted_two_commercial__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/091/613/09161381A34843329598BEDF4CEBF548_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, United Arab Emirates, Qatar, Qatari fighter jets, UAE military aircraft, Emirates plane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3527295</guid>
      <title>Israel launches strike on Hamas attack tunnel under Gaza crossing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEIsrael announced on Sunday that it destroyed 'terror infrastructure' that infiltrated Israeli territory.According to the Israel Defense Forces, authorities detected a tunnel running from the Gaza strip into Israel and Egypt, reportedly built by militant group Hamas.Israel has claimed to have an advanced system for detecting tunnels underground, but did not provide details.The concrete tunnel passed under the Kerem Shalom crossing, the main passageway for goods entering Gaza, and was positioned near oil and gas pipelines.Authorities determined it was an attack tunnel, and could be used by militants to go to Egypt from Gaza, in order to attack Israel from the Sinai Peninsula.On Saturday, Israeli fighter jets launched an airstrike from the Gaza side that destroyed the tunnel.Three others have been destroyed in the last two months, with the military vowing to eliminate all Hamas attack tunnels by the end of 2018.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tunnel built by Hamas ran from Gaza to Egypt while crossing through Israel2. Tunnel passed under Kerem Shalom border crossing, and Israeli gas and oil pipelines3. Militants could use tunnel to go to Egypt from Gaza, for attack on Israel4. Tunnel destroyed by Israeli fighter jets from Gaza sideVOICEOVER (in English): "Israel's Defense Forces detected a tunnel running from the Gaza strip into Israel and Egypt, reportedly built by militant group Hamas.""The concrete tunnel passed under the Kerem Shalom crossing, the main passageway for goods entering Gaza, and was positioned near oil and gas pipelines.""Authorities determined it was an attack tunnel, and could be used by militants to go to Egypt from Gaza, in order to attack Israel from the Sinai Peninsula.""On Saturday, Israeli fighter jets launched an airstrike from the Gaza side that destroyed the tunnel."SOURCES: Israel Defense Forces, CNN, Reutershttps://www.idf.il/en/minisites/hamas/thwarting-hamas-terror-one-tunnel-at-a-time/http://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/14/middleeast/israel-hamas-tunnel/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-palestinians-tunnel/israel-says-it-destroyed-gaza-attack-tunnel-under-egyptian-border-idUSKBN1F3079?feedType=RSS&feedName=newsOne***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 07:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/16/3527295/3527295_F2160D95514941F198B46DC629D72CF9_180116_3527295_Israel_launches_strike_on_Hamas_attack_tunnel_un_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A46/5AE/A465AED35BD641E9A656A84A933222B0_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hamas tunnel, tunnel, gaza tunnel, hamas, gaza, attack tunnel, israel palestine conflict, Kerem Shalom border, border crossing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3527220</guid>
      <title>GM wants to test self-driving cars with no steering wheel by 2019</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEGM is asking the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration for permission to test self-driving vehicles without steering wheels by 2019. The carmaker has already been testing the autonomous Chevy Bolt in San Francisco and Phoenix, according to the Daily Dot. The fourth-generation Cruise AV has no steering wheel, no pedals, no manual controls and no driver. The self-driving vehicle will be using for ride-hailing, not personal use, the Daily Dot reported. If granted approval, GM could deploy more test vehicles in cities across the U.S. Currently, only seven states allow testing for vehicles with no steering wheels or pedals: Michigan, North Carolina, Tennessee, Georgia, Texas, Colorado and Nevada. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People getting into a fourth-generation Cruise AV2. Interior of Cruise AV3. Cruise AV being used for ride-hailing 4. Cruise AV being tested on the highwayVOICEOVER (in English): "GM is asking the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration for permission to test self-driving vehicles without steering wheels by 2019." "The fourth-generation Cruise AV has no steering wheel, no pedals, no manual controls and no driver." "The self-driving vehicle will be using for ride-hailing, not personal use." "If granted approval, GM could deploy more test vehicles in cities across the U.S. Currently, only seven states allow testing of vehicles with no steering wheel or pedals."SOURCES: Daily Dothttps://www.dailydot.com/debug/gm-driverless-car-2019/?tw=dd***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 06:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/16/3527220/3527220_8F78E90718224DE2915AF5A8DEDCE096_180116_3527220_GM_wants_to_test_self_driving_cars_with_no_steer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B25/D24/B25D245F3ED14155A8FB7C974C530D71_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, GM Cruise AG, GM self-driving vehicle, GM autonomous vehicle, GM no steering wheel, GM no pedals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3527201</guid>
      <title>Drones attack two Russian military bases in Syria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONERussia claims to have identified the source of a drone attack that targeted two military bases in Syria.CNBC reports that the drones were launched from a village in southern Idlib province, by forces aiming to destroy Russian relations with Iran and Turkey, according to RT.On January 6, Russian defense forces detected 10 drones approaching Khmeimim Air base, and another three targeting a naval base in Tartus, Syria.The drones were assembled using a simple engine and cheap materials. Each carried eight to 10 bombs stuffed with PETN explosives and strings of ball bearings.At least one drone was equipped with a camera and had the ability to adjust the track of the others, which were all guided by GPS and a pre-programmed flight path.Seven drones were shot down by Russian anti-aircraft missiles, while electronic warfare units took control of the rest. Three exploded upon landing, while three others survived.The Russian bases did not suffer damages or casualties.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Armed drones attack Russian air and naval bases in Syria2. Drones made with cheap materials, carried bombs filled with PETN and ball bearings3. One drone equipped with camera, all others guided by GPS with pre-programmed flight path 4. Drones either shot down by Russian anti-aircraft missiles or controlled by Russian Electronic Warfare units  VOICEOVER (in English): "On January 6, Russian defense forces detected 10 drones approaching Khmeimim Air base, and another three targeting a naval base in Tartus, Syria.""The drones were assembled using a simple engine and cheap materials. Each carried eight to ten bombs stuffed with PETN explosives and strings of ball bearings.""At least one drone was equipped with a camera and had the ability to adjust the track of the others, which were all guided by GPS and a pre-programmed flight path.""Seven drones were shot down by Russian anti-aircraft missiles, while electronic warfare units took control of the rest, three of which exploded upon landing."SOURCES: https://www.facebook.com/mod.mil.rus/posts/2031218563787556http://www.atimes.com/article/russians-asking-help-swarming-drone-attacks/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 05:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/16/3527201/3527201_CA30EEDBD8D1402489542163D4D7877E_180116_3527201_Drones_attack_two_Russian_military_bases_in_Syri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/25A/AC7/25AAC75D2F274B209F8D7E05E91F8B87_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, drones, armed drones, drone swarm, drone attack, Russian drone attack, Russian military base, bomb, bomblets, anti aircraft missiles, EW units, electronic warfare]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3528415</guid>
      <title>Campaigns look to fight plastic straw pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEPlastic straws are increasingly drawing attention from conservation movements around the world. In the U.S. alone, Americans discard around 500 million plastic straws a day, enough to circle the globe twice, or fill 125 school buses, according to CNN. Straws normally are not recycled because they are often made from several different types of plastics, and they're small in size. Straw pollution contributes to the eight million tons of plastic dumped into the oceans each year, CNN reported. At the current rate, there will be more plastic than fish in the water by 2050. Campaigns in the U.S. and the U.K. have looked to reduce plastic straw use. Reusable glass straws, stainless steel, copper and bamboo all more sustainable alternatives than single-use plastic. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Americans discard around 500 million plastic straws a day, enough to circle the globe twice, or fill 125 school buses2. Plastic straws are normally not recycled 3. Ocean plastic pollution4. Alternatives to plastic strawsVOICEOVER (in English): "Plastic straws are increasingly drawing attention from conservation movements. In the U.S. alone, Americans discard around 500 million plastic straws a day, enough to circle the globe twice, or fill 125 school buses.""Straws normally are not recycled because they are often made from several different types of plastics and their small size." "Straw pollution contributes to the eight million tons of plastic dumped into the oceans each year. At the current rate, there will be more plastic than fish in the water by 2050." "Reusable glass straws, stainless steel, copper and bamboo all more sustainable alternatives than single-use plastic straws." SOURCES: CNNhttp://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/14/world/plastic-straws-ban-campaigns/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 13:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/17/3528415/3528415_5B1C27576561406F8CC16F8CEF56509A_180117_3528415_Campaigns_look_to_fight_plastic_straw_pollution_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8DA/150/8DA150AB793C4F4CA318182F922B9193_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, plastic straw, plastic straw dumping, plastic straw campaigns, plastic straw alternatives]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3528303</guid>
      <title>Measles alert issued at Chicago airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA health warning was issued for anyone who was at Chicago O'Hare International Airport last Wednesday after someone tested positive for measles.Measles is contagious and usually transmitted via the air or contact with an infected infected individual. According to the World Health Organization, it attacks the respiratory tract and then spreads across the body.U.S. government information says symptoms can include fever, cough, runny nose, aches and white spots inside the mouth. No treatment exists for the virus, but immunization and vaccinations can help combat  it.The World Health organization says those most at risk include unvaccinated pregnant women and unvaccinated young children. Complications from the disease can lead to more serious health problems.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of measles transmission2. Depiction of measles in the body3. Depiction of measles symptoms 4. Depiction of pregnant woman and young childVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Fox News, WHO, Medicine Plus, www.foxnews.com/travel/2018/01/15/chicago-ohare-travelers-possibly-exposed-to-measles.htmlhttps://medlineplus.gov/measles.htmlhttp://www.who.int/mediacentre/factsheets/fs286/en/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 11:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/17/3528303/3528303_E6C68FC538B74039B1093DB7B960A8B8_180117_3528303_Measles_alert_issued_at_Chicago_airport_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5B2/6FC/5B26FCBC23D4414EA9190ABF46DC7ED4_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, measles alert chicago, chicago airport measles, what is measles, measles explainer, measles, chicago o hare measles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3528278</guid>
      <title>The dangers of blowfish toxin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEJapanese authorities sent out an emergency warning in a coastal city on Monday after several packages of fugu or blowfish were mistakenly sold to unsuspecting customers.The Japan Times reports that a grocery store in Gamagori accidentally sold five packages of assorted blowfish meat with its poisonous parts still intact.Three of the packages have been recovered, but two have yet to be found.The liver and internal organs of blowfish are known to contain tetrodotoxin, a lethal neurotoxin 1,200 times more potent than cyanide. One fish has enough poison to kill 30 adult humans, according to National Geographic.Tetrodotoxin targets motor neurons, causing numbness in the lips, loss of muscle control, and organ paralysis. A fatal dose could lead to respiratory arrest and death. There is no known antidote.Despite the danger, blowfish meat is a delicacy in Japan. But because of the high risk, only rigorously trained and licensed chefs are allowed to prepare the deadly dish.There are still those who die from blowfish poisoning, though these are mostly amateur cooks or sport fishermen who try to cut the fish up themselves.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Packages of poisonous blowfish meat mistakenly sold by Japanese grocery2. Blowfish liver and internal organs contain tetrodotoxin3. Effects of tetrodotoxin poisoning4. Only licensed and trained chefs allowed to prepare blowfish meat for consumptionVOICEOVER (in English): "A grocery store in Gamagori accidentally sold five packages of assorted blowfish meat with its poisonous parts still intact.""The liver and internal organs of blowfish are known to contain tetrodotoxin, a lethal neurotoxin 1,200 times more potent than cyanide. One fish has enough poison to kill 30 adult humans.""Tetrodotoxin targets motor neurons, causing numbness in the lips, loss of muscle control, and organ paralysis. A fatal dose could lead to respiratory arrest and death. There is no known antidote.""Despite the danger, blowfish meat is a delicacy in Japan. But because of the high risk, only rigorously trained and licensed chefs are allowed to prepare the deadly dish."SOURCES: Japan Times, Washington Post, National Geographichttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2018/01/16/national/deadly-fugu-fish-flub-prompts-emergency-warning-aichi-city/#.Wl6wIoiGOUlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/food/wp/2018/01/16/a-japanese-grocer-accidentally-sold-five-packages-of-deadly-blowfish-two-are-still-missing/?utm_term=.529c87ad7ccbhttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/fish/group/pufferfish/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 11:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/17/3528278/3528278_C246F0D0FF1A48AB91C0788D9FA40ECE_180117_3528278_The_dangers_of_blowfish_toxin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/04C/099/04C099A86A65463DA5DF9C68717EE15A_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, fugu, blowfish, puffer fish, fugu poisoning, blowfish poisoning, tetrodotoxin, deadly food, neurotoxin, poison, poisonous fish, poisonous food]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3528167</guid>
      <title>Cocoliztli outbreak tied to Salmonella</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists have come one step closer to unlocking the secrets of an centuries-old contagion.New research published in Nature Ecology and Evolution details a study looking at teeth from the remains of 29 skeletons at a centuries old burial site in Teposcolula-Yucundaa.Those at the burial site are said to have died during the cocoliztli outbreak, a 1545 epidemic that killed millions.The study linked the DNA found at Teposcolula-Yucundaa with a subspecies of Salmonella enterica connected to the deadly enteric typhoid fever. The cocoliztli outbreak lasted from 1545 to 1550. According to National Geographic, another study from 2017 found the same bacteria on the remains of a Norwegian woman who passed in 1200.But whether or not the Mexican outbreak was from colonial Europeans remains unknown.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Teposcolula-Yucundaa burial site2. Depiction of remains and DNA3. Depiction of tooth and bacteria4. Depiction of bacteria in Mexico in 1545 and Norway in 1200VOICEOVER (in English): New research published in Nature Ecology and Evolution details a study looking at teeth from the remains of 29 skeletons at a centuries old burial site in Teposcolula-Yucundaa.Those at the burial site are said to have died during the cocoliztli outbreak, a 1545 epidemic that killed millions.The study linked the DNA found at Teposcolula-Yucundaa with a subspecies of Salmonella enterica connected to the deadly enteric typhoid fever.The cocoliztli outbreak lasted from 1545 to 1550.  According to National Geographic, another study from 2017 found the same bacteria on the remains of a Norwegian woman who passed in 1200.But whether or not the Mexican outbreak was from colonial Europeans remains unknown.SOURCES: Nature, Max Planck Institute, National Geographic, NPRhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41559-017-0446-6http://www.shh.mpg.de/788316/possible-cause-of-early-colonial-era-mexican-epidemic-identifiedhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/01/cocoliztli-salmonella-outbreak-mexico-dna-spd/https://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2018/01/15/577681552/salmonella-may-have-caused-massive-aztec-epidemic-study-finds***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 09:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/17/3528167/3528167_711A309303C14E4E897F1474A0F42CF4_180117_3528167_Cocoliztli_outbreak_tied_to_Salmonella_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D8F/3EF/D8F3EF5131724A9D982998CA6F8C66F9_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Cocoliztli, salmonella, Cocoliztli epidemic, ancient pathogen, mexico epidemic, ancient mysteries]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3529167</guid>
      <title>U.S. deploys B-52s to Guam</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. Air Force is sending half-a-dozen B-52 heavy bombers to Guam.Six B-52H Stratofortress bombers, along with 300 airmen, are being deployed from  Barksdale Air Force Base in Louisiana to Guam. Those aircraft have an operational range of 8,800 miles.The B-52 is capable of flying at speeds at 1,037 km per hour, or Mach. 0.86, at a height of 50,000 feet while carrying a nuclear payload. According to Technical Specifications on Boeing, the aircraft's wingspan measures 56.4 meters, while it's length and height are 48.5 m and 12.4 m respectively. Its powered by 8 Pratt and Whitney engines that can provide up to 17,000 lbs of thrust.Those engines can support a maximum take off weight of 480,000 lbs including a crew of five, 312,197 lbs of fuel and 70,000 lbs of armaments.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of B-52 in hangar2. Depiction of B-52 flying at altitude of 50,000 feet and aircraft dimensions3. Depiction of B-52 engines and mid-air refuelling4. Crew and armaments of a B-52VOICEOVER (in English):   "Six B-52H Stratofortress bombers, along with 300 airmen, are being deployed from Barksdale Air Force Base in Louisiana to Guam.""They have an operational range of 8,800 miles.""The B-52 is capable of flying at speeds at 1,037 km per hour, or Mach. 0.86, at a height of 50,000 feet.""It's wingspan measures 56.4 meters, while it's length and height are 48.5 m and 12.4 m respectively.""It's powered by eight Pratt and Whitney engines that can provide up to 17,000 lbs of thrust.""The B-52 can also be refueled in mid-air, allowing for non-stop flight.""It can fly with a maximum take off weight of 480,000 lbs including a crew of five, over 312,000 lbs of fuel and 70,000 lbs of armaments and nuclear weapons."SOURCES: U.S. Air Force, Boeing, Business Insiderhttp://www.af.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/1415819/b-52s-return-to-pacific-for-routine-continuous-bomber-presence-mission/http://www.boeing.com/defense/b-52-bomber/#/technical-specificationshttp://www.businessinsider.com/heres-how-many-bombs-a-b-52-can-haul-2015-6***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 12:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/18/3529167/3529167_0657763003F34983931A52ACCD4D4732_180118_3529167_U_S__deploys_B_52s_to_Guam_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CF1/54C/CF154C41E76A452BAA33A6DC438FD41B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,guam, b-52 stratofortress, air force, b-52 in action, b-52 explainer, boeing b-52]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3529156</guid>
      <title>China plans to use lasers to clean space junk from Earth's orbit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina has come up with a new plan to rid the earth of its space garbage, using giant lasers.Wired reports that Earth's orbit is currently cluttered with fragments from old satellites and rocket stages, called space debris, which number at least 20,000.Satellites and spacecrafts are frequently at risk of colliding with the fragments and being damaged by even small, pebble-sized pieces.To address this problem, Chinese researchers from the Air Force Engineering University in Xi'an have proposed a plan to launch a satellite-mounted laser that will emit short bursts of infrared light to target small debris. The laser will break down the space debris into tiny, harmless particles, and hopefully rid the Earth of its space junk.The plan sounds reasonable enough, but of course, with China, there's no telling if the space laser will actually be for cleaning, or be used as a tool for world domination.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Space debris cluttering Earth's orbit2. Satellites and spacecrafts can be damaged by collisions with space debris3. Depiction of laser mounted on a satellite, blasting space debris with infrared light4. Space debris broken down into tiny pieces, reducing debris around EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Earth's orbit is currently cluttered with fragments from old satellites and rocket stages, called space debris, which number at least 20,000.""Satellites and spacecrafts are frequently at risk of colliding with the fragments and being damaged by even small, pebble-sized pieces.""To address this problem, Chinese researchers have proposed launching a satellite-mounted laser that will emit short bursts of infrared light to target small debris.""The laser will break down the space debris into tiny, harmless particles, and hopefully rid the Earth of its space junk."SOURCES: Optik, Wiredhttp://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0030402617312068http://www.wired.co.uk/article/space-junk-incidents-china-lasers-zap-pow***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 12:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/18/3529156/3529156_162255B82BC5439686B86272AED98FF4_180118_3529156_China_plans_to_use_lasers_to_clean_space_junk_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/50F/A18/50FA1829B71542E28C5E83A9083365BC_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, space debris, space junk, space garbage, space laser, china laser, china space laser, giant laser]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3529106</guid>
      <title>How your car is spying on you</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONECars are now computers on wheels that have access to drivers' personal data.The Washington Post reports that connected cars can track and monitor location, driving habits, fuel usage, and even music preferences, and relay this information back to automakers.The data is supposedly meant to update car features and improve safety, and in some cases help law enforcement evaluate accidents or crashes.But it can also put consumers at risk. Location data can be used to infer sensitive information about a person's health, religion, or political affiliation, and a unique profile can be developed with enough data points.With no car privacy rule to regulate them, automakers can partner with data firms, and generate revenue when the information is sold to third party companies.Car companies technically inform customers about the data collection, but they're often buried in lengthy contracts.Despite claims that driver data is not shared without consent, a lack of transparency means customers don't know what happens to their data and how exactly it is used.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Connected cars track location and other data and send it back to the car maker2. Data meant to improve car features, provide information during accidents3. Location data can be used to infer individual's habits, affiliations 4. Car makers working with data firms that sell customer data to third parties for a profitVOICEOVER (in English): "Connected cars can track and monitor location, driving habits, fuel usage, and even music preferences, and relay this information back to automakers.""The data is supposedly meant to update car features and improve safety, and in some cases help law enforcement evaluate accidents or crashes.""But it can also put consumers at risk. Location data can be used to infer sensitive information about a person's health, religion, or political affiliation, and a unique profile can be developed with enough data points.""With no car privacy rule to regulate them, automakers can partner with data firms, and generate revenue when the information is sold to third party companies."SOURCES: Washington Post, WSB-TVhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/innovations/wp/2018/01/15/big-brother-on-wheels-why-your-car-company-may-know-more-about-you-than-your-spouse/?utm_term=.3c360e5844bfhttp://www.wsbtv.com/news/clark-howard/your-car-is-spying-on-you-and-heres-what-it-knows/685118765***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 11:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/18/3529106/3529106_0C55C6EDDE7E42C6BB2A1DE2ECC2491F_180118_3529106_How_your_car_is_spying_on_you_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DC1/9D8/DC19D8D77DF04D7A88EB219B08A8011C_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, data, privacy, car, car data, car privacy, car spying, data collection, data firm, car data, personal data, private information]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3529010</guid>
      <title>Google planning to build three new underwater internet cables</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEGoogle is planning on laying three new underwater cables in 2019 to help expand its cloud business. The company announced its new routes in a blog post on Tuesday, CNBC reported. The first will run from Los Angeles to Chile, the second will link the U.S. to Denmark and Ireland, and the third will connect Hong Kong and Guam. The cables are set to be ready by 2019. The cable from L.A. to Chile will allow Google to provide better cloud services to users across Latin America. The cable running from the U.S. to Denmark and Ireland will boost capacity for North Atlantic users.The Hong Kong-Guam cable will help Google reach customers in the Pacific region and Australia. Google now has investments in 11 cables that are planned or under construction, CNBC reported. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ship laying down underwater internet cables 2. The three new proposed internet cable paths3. Cable laying ship putting down new internet cables4. Cable laying ship pulling up cable ploughVOICEOVER (in English): "Google is planning on laying three new underwater cables in 2019 to help expand its cloud business." "The first will run from Los Angeles to Chile, the second will link the U.S. to Denmark and Ireland, and the third will connect Hong Kong and Guam." "Laying these new cable systems will help Google develop its cloud services in Latin America, the North Atlantic and the Pacific region and Australia.""Google now has direct investments in 11 cables that are planned or under construction."SOURCES: CNBC, Popular Mechanicshttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/01/16/google-plans-to-build-3-new-underwater-cables-to-expand-cloud-business.htmlhttp://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/infrastructure/a15173083/google-is-about-to-build-its-own-undersea-internet-cables/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 09:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/18/3529010/3529010_9BBD1439058E4DA8A37FB82C219D56E6_180118_3529010_Google_planning_to_build_three_new_underwater_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F05/120/F051206AA3B7479894E6C22F16FCEED1_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Google, Google undersea internet cables, Google cloud services, Google internet cables]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3529912</guid>
      <title>Cape Town to run out of water in 90 days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEOne of the biggest cities in South Africa may soon become the first major city in the world to run out of water.Cape Town is facing a water crisis, and has less than a hundred days before "Day Zero" on April 21, when the water supply is expected to run out, according to the South African.Years of extreme drought have caused storage levels in dams to drop below 30%. Once it falls to 13.5%, taps in the city will be shut off.Local authorities restricted water usage to 87 liters per person per day, but after only 39% of residents complied, the limit has now been lowered to 50 liters.Its four million residents are being told to take 2-minute showers, and have been banned from filling pools, watering gardens, or washing cars.Households that go over their water allowance will also be asked to pay higher tariffs.After "Day Zero", citizens will need to line up at one of 200 water collection points throughout the city, where each can collect a maximum of 25 liters a day.Authorities have also been looking into alternative ways to source water, like wastewater recycling, drilling into aquifers, or seawater desalination.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cape Town expected to run out of water by April 212. Long drought lowered water level in dams3. Residents' water usage limited to 50 liters per person per day 4. Residents to be rationed water from collection points after April 21VOICEOVER (in English): "Cape Town is facing a water crisis, and has less than a hundred days before 'Day Zero' on April 21, when the water supply is expected to run out.""Years of extreme drought have caused storage levels in dams to drop below 30%. Once it falls to 13.5%, taps in the city will be shut off.""Local authorities restricted water usage to 87 liters per person per day, but after only 39% of residents complied, the limit has now been lowered to 50 liters.""After 'Day Zero', citizens will need to line up at one of 200 water collection points throughout the city, where each can collect a maximum of 25 liters a day."SOURCES: The South African, The Sunday Times, Al Jazeerahttps://www.thesouthafrican.com/cape-town-water-restrictions-50l-a-day/https://www.timeslive.co.za/politics/2018-01-18-de-lilles-drought-levy-about-turn-a-victory-for-the-people-says-anc/http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/01/cape-town-confronts-looming-day-water-crisis-180114121145902.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 10:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/19/3529912/3529912_FEE998E9B13D4FB5B6EB9818E1D5458B_180119_3529912_Cape_Town_to_run_out_of_water_in_90_days_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/477/015/4770153DF521486CA8AB1B0244823CFA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, water crisis, cape town water crisis, drought, no water, cape town, cape town drought, water shortage, water supply, south africa, water rationing, rations]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3529795</guid>
      <title>Chinese iPhone factory workers risk toxic exposure: report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEWorkers at an Apple iPhone suppliers' factory in Suqian, China are exposed to toxic substances, according to an investigation.The report by New York-based China Labour Watch has criticised Chinese factory employees working at Apple supplier Catcher Technology work 10 hour days, six days per week.The report also claims that the workers face exposure to toxic substances. It claims some workers hands aren't adequately protected by the provided gloves and that protective ear plugs and eye wear are not always available.China Labour Watch says that some employees' eyes have experienced vision issues from cutting fluid and that noise in the factory can cause irreversible hearing damage.The report also claims the factory's wastewater was directly dispensed into the public sewage system. Analysis of this found that it exceeded local standards for water quality.In May last year, the report says 90 were sent to hospital following a chemical leak at the plant, and that five were in intensive care as a result. Investigation of the incident by the Administrative Committee of the Suzhou-Suqian Industrial Park said the cause was a mechanical failure, notes the report.Apple told the Guardian it investigated these claims, interviewed 150 factory workers and found no violations of it's code of conduct. The tech giant told the paper that workers were provided with protective equipment and that wastewater was treated appropriately.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of working conditions in factory in report2. Overview of health issues in report3. Overview of wastewater in report4. Overview of May incident in reportVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: China Labor Watch, Guardian, Bloomberg, Taipei Timeshttp://www.chinalaborwatch.org/report/131http://www.chinalaborwatch.org/upfile/2018_01_12/20180116-1.pdfhttps://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/jan/16/workers-making-iphones-in-china-exposed-to-toxic-hazards-report-says-apple-catcher-technology?CMP=twt_a-global-development_b-gdndevhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-01-16/workers-at-apple-supplier-catcher-describe-harsh-conditionshttp://www.taipeitimes.com/News/biz/archives/2018/01/18/2003685954***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/19/3529795/3529795_0F5F012B0D584F108D3B307DF05D6C63_180119_3529795_Chinese_iPhone_factory_workers_risk_toxic_exposu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B5D/5E9/B5D5E965A1A54301A2C91A4C3C7CF718_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, factory worker in china, chinese iphone workers, catcher technology, china labour watch, chinese iphone factory, iphone, apple, apple code of conduct]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3529754</guid>
      <title>A massive "potentially hazardous" asteroid will fly close to Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA massive space rock will fly past Earth in February  the largest that's expected to come close to the planet this year. Newshub reports that asteroid 2002 AJ129 is 1.1 kilometers wide, making it slightly longer than the Burj Khalifa, the world's tallest building.The asteroid is hurtling through space at a speed of more than 107,000 kilometers per hour, 15 times faster than the hypersonic X-15 aircraft.It is set to pass within 4.2 million kilometers from Earth on February 4, 2018, a distance NASA considers 'potentially dangerous' despite a low chance of a direct hit.If an asteroid this size were to collide with Earth, studies suggest debris could cloud up the atmosphere, blocking the sun and causing temperature drops that could trigger a mini ice age.NASA is currently incapable of intercepting an asteroid beelining straight for Earth. That technology won't be ready until after 2024.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of asteroid size2. Depiction of asteroid speed3. Asteroid to fly within 4.2 million kilometers of Earth4. Possible effects of a large asteroid hitting EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Asteroid 2002 AJ129 is 1.1 kilometers wide, making it slightly longer than the Burj Khalifa, the world's tallest building.""The asteroid is hurtling through space at a speed of more than 107,000 kilometers per hour, 15 times faster than the hypersonic X-15 aircraft.""It is set to pass within 4.2 million kilometers from Earth on February 4, 2018, a distance NASA considers 'potentially dangerous' despite a low chance of a direct hit.""If an asteroid this size were to collide with Earth, studies suggest debris could cloud up the atmosphere, blocking the sun and causing temperature drops that could trigger a mini ice age."SOURCES: Atlanta Journal-Constitution, Tech Times, Newshubhttp://www.ajc.com/news/potentially-hazardous-monster-asteroid-will-fly-close-earth/eFACuRT7nCZ1hmUzGY1uDM/http://www.techtimes.com/articles/219070/20180117/potentially-hazardous-asteroid-to-fly-by-close-to-earth-next-month.htmhttp://www.newshub.co.nz/home/world/2018/01/asteroid-longer-than-world-s-tallest-building-to-pass-earth.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 08:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/19/3529754/3529754_3CA4CF693F66459B96921891E2E75A4D_180119_3529754_A_massive__potentially_hazardous__asteroid_will__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4BA/759/4BA7593A75544384B028B2382BEEBDC9_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, asteroid, asteroid apocalypse, asteroid approaching Earth, 2002 AJ129, big asteroid, asteroid hit, asteroid collision, space rock, mini ice age, burj khalifa X-15, hypersonic, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3530341</guid>
      <title>North Korea testing subsea missile barge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENorth Korea is working on a barge capable of launching ballistic missiles from underwater.The North has begun work on a second submarine-launched ballistic missile test stand barge. According to 38 North, it resembles old Russian PSD-4 test barges.The barge reportedly measures 9 meters by 22 meters, making it around one third of the length of the Sinpo Class Submarine.According to submarine expert HI Sutton, the old Soviet raft could be sunk to a set depth, and then the missile would be launched from a central a tube.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of barge on water2. Depiction of barge against Sinpo Class Submarine3. Depiction of barge being sunk to a depth4. Depiction of missile being launched from bargeVOICEOVER (in English): "The North has begun work on a second submarine-launched ballistic missile test stand barge."According to 38 North, it resembles old Russian PSD-4 test barges.""The barge reportedly measures 9 meters by 22 meters, making it around one third of the length of the Sinpo Class Submarine.""According to submarine expert HI Sutton, the old Soviet raft could be sunk to a set depth.""And then the missile would be launched from a central tube."SOURCES: Yonhap News, 38 North, Defence Blog, H I Sutton, Arms Control Wonkhttp://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/news/2018/01/17/0200000000AEN20180117011200315.htmlhttp://www.38north.org/2018/01/nampo011618/http://www.38north.org/2017/12/nampo120117/http://defence-blog.com/news/analysis-sinpo-class-ballistic-missile-sub.htmlhttp://www.hisutton.com/Analysis%20-%20Sinpo%20Class%20Ballistic%20Missile%20Sub.htmlhttps://www.armscontrolwonk.com/archive/207631/dprk-slbm-test/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 01:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/20/3530341/3530341_4026DE7962CA4026BB80F2D495610C8E_180120_3530341_North_Korea_testing_subsea_missile_barge_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DC1/86A/DC186A79F22841CC8B14DE3A8C02D7E1_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, north korea missile, north korea missile barge, slbm, sinpo class submarine, russian psd4]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3531776</guid>
      <title>First Amazon Go store opens to the public</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAmazon's first cashier-free store in Seattle is now open to the public, nearly 14 months after it began a trial run for company employees.The New York Times reports that customers enter the Amazon Go store via an app on their phones, which generates a QR code that is scanned on an electronic turnstile.Cameras mounted on the ceiling do not have facial recognition technology, instead detecting motion and sensing depth to track shoppers through the store.This, combined with weight sensors on the shelves, helps the system identify what items are being picked up by which shopper.Once an item is taken off a shelf, it is added to a customer's virtual cart. If an item is picked up but later returned, the system removes it from the cart.Once the customer finishes shopping and leaves the store, the cost of items in the cart is calculated, and the total amount charged directly to the linked Amazon account.Despite having no checkout and no cashiers, the store has staff to check the IDs of shoppers purchasing alcohol. Employees are also on hand to restock shelves and prepare the store's ready-to-eat meals.Amazon has said it might open more Amazon Go stores in the future, but the plans are not immediate, and the company wants to focus on its flagship store for now.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Customers entering Amazon Go store using QR code on Amazon app2. App scans code, links shopper to Amazon account3. Ceiling-mounted cameras track each shopper through store4. Shelves equipped with weight sensors5. Items added to virtual shopping cart once taken from shelf6. Items removed from virtual shopping cart if customer puts it back on shelf7. Cost calculated and charged to Amazon account once customer leaves store8. Amazon Go store has human staff to check IDs of people buying alcohol9. Other employees restock shelves, prepare packed meals in kitchenVOICEOVER (in English): "Customers enter the Amazon Go store via an app on their phones, which generates a QR code that is scanned on an electronic turnstile.""Cameras mounted on the ceiling do not have facial recognition technology, instead detecting motion and sensing depth to track shoppers through the store.""This, combined with weight sensors on the shelves, helps the system identify what items are being picked up by which shopper.""Once an item is taken off a shelf, it is added to a customer's virtual cart.""If an item is picked up but later returned, the system removes it from the cart.""Once the customer finishes shopping and leaves the store, the cost of items in the cart is calculated, and the total amount charged directly to the linked Amazon account.""Despite having no checkout and no cashiers, the store has staff to check the IDs of shoppers purchasing alcohol.""Employees are also on hand to restock shelves and prepare the store's ready-to-eat meals."SOURCES: New York Times, CNN, TechCrunchhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/01/21/technology/inside-amazon-go-a-store-of-the-future.htmlhttp://money.cnn.com/2018/01/21/technology/business/amazon-go-seattle-store/index.htmlhttps://techcrunch.com/2018/01/21/inside-amazons-surveillance-powered-no-checkout-convenience-store/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 10:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/22/3531776/3531776_108441E0EEA84D258F5A7E04E66A05B1_180122_3531776_First_Amazon_Go_store_opens_to_the_public_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4CE/404/4CE404C08C3F4D4C9A1219EAFEE64725_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, amazon go, amazon, amazon go store, cashierless store, automated store, weight sensors, camera, motion detection, motion tracker, amazon app, amazon account, seattle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3531619</guid>
      <title>The U.S. government shutdown explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. government shutdown over the weekend after legislators failed to reach a funding agreement.Shutdowns happen when the U.S. President and Congress fail to sign a bill authorising spending to let the government function.There's been 19 in total. Past shutdowns have gone on for a few days to several weeks.Essential services such as the post office, TSA and air traffic control will continue as normal. As will the military, border guard, prisons and social security.Meanwhile non-essential staff will be furloughed and won't go to work on Monday. Services such as the ATF, Department of Education and National Parks could be affected during this time.The 2013 government shutdown saw up to 850,000 not report to work, reports CNN.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the U.S. government shuts down 2. What services are still running3. What services may not be runningVOICEOVER (in English): "Shutdowns happen when the U.S. President and Congress fail to sign a bill authorising spending to let the government function.""There's been 19 in total. Past shutdowns have gone on for a few days to several weeks.""Essential services such as the post office, TSA and air traffic control will continue as normal.""As will the military, border guard, prisons and social security.""Meanwhile non-essential staff will be furloughed and won't go to work on Monday.""Services such as the ATF, Department of Education and National Parks could be affected during this time.""The 2013 government shutdown saw up to 850,000 not report to work."SOURCES: Fox News, CNN, Reuters, NBC News, New York Timeshttp://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/01/21/what-happens-during-government-shutdown-7-things-should-know.htmlhttp://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/20/politics/what-next-government-shutdown/index.htmlhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-shutdown-impact-factbox/factbox-impact-of-the-u-s-government-shutdown-idUSKBN1FA18Chttps://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/government-shutdown-2018-what-s-open-what-s-closed-n839456https://www.nytimes.com/2018/01/20/us/politics/government-agencies-shutdown.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 07:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/22/3531619/3531619_1600F48FB05D457B9E51C742F163FA8F_180122_3531619_The_U_S__government_shutdown_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/54A/2A2/54A2A289E5E341C0A6906A7F9BD0EC93_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, government shutdown, government shutdown explained, us government shut down, shut down explained, congress shutdown, shutdown explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3531610</guid>
      <title>NASA tests nuclear reactors that can power life on Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA is testing a nuclear fission reactor prototype that could enable long-term stays on the surface of the red planet.The Las Vegas Review-Journal reports that the first humans on Mars will need to be able to generate power to transform the planet's water and carbon dioxide into liquid oxygen and fuel.To enable such a feat, NASA and the Department of Energy have come up with the Kilopower project, a nuclear power system that comes with a Uranium reactor core, which uses fission to generate electricity.Kilopower can generate 1 kilowatt of electricity, which can power a toaster, to 10 kilowatts, which can light up 100 bulbs.Four to five 10-kilowatt units will be needed to power the habit- charging vehicles, generating safe drinking water, and oxygen.The months-long testing for the kilopower prototype began in November at a Department of Energy National Security Site in Nevada.Though a flight test is at least six to eight years away, if all goes well, the technology could be ready by the mid-2020s to early 2030s.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mars settlement will need electricity to generate liquid oxygen and fuel2. How the Kilopower nuclear reactor works3. Electricity generated by Kilopower4. Kilopower to be used to power Mars habitatVOICEOVER (in English): "The first humans on Mars will need to be able to generate power to transform the planet's water and carbon dioxide into liquid oxygen and fuel.""Addressing this concern is the Kilopower project, a nuclear power system that comes with a Uranium reactor core, which uses fission to generate electricity.""The system can generate 1 kilowatt of electricity, which can power a toaster, to 10 kilowatts, which can light up 100 bulbs.""Four to five 10-kilowatt units will be needed to power the habit- charging vehicles, generating safe drinking water, and oxygen."SOURCES: Las Vegas Review-Journal, Reutershttps://www.reviewjournal.com/news/science-and-technology/nuclear-reactor-being-tested-in-nevada-could-power-mars-mission/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-nuclear/u-s-tests-nuclear-power-system-to-sustain-astronauts-on-mars-idUSKBN1F72T8***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/22/3531610/3531610_A250A8E3762C416BB41957985251DB6F_180122_3531610_NASA_tests_nuclear_reactors_that_can_power_life__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/348/9CD/3489CD6F1E1B4659A4F2435B37B4816B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mars habitat, life on mars, kilopower, nuclear reactor, uranium, mars power, mars electricity, martian, mars settlement, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3531534</guid>
      <title>Bat research finds brain socially maps others' locations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew research on bats published in the journal Science provides insights into how the brain maps the social geography of areas.Researchers trained pairs of bats, with one alpha male labelled as a teacher and the other a student, to retrieve fruit from a stand inside a room. They noted how student typically tracked the teacher's path toward the fruit.The bats were fitted with technology to record brain cell activity. Activity was normal in students bats acting on their own, but fired when tracking the position of the teacher. Researchers believe this was social place-cells in the hippocampus.Students bats also tracked objects like balls and dice but their brain activity responded differently. Researchers suspect this could provide insights into how that the brain cognitively maps out the environment socially, and physically.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of experiment2. Depiction of bat hippocampus during experiment3. Depiction of bats and inanimate objects4. Depiction of bats at nightVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers trained pairs of bats, with one alpha male labelled as a teacher and the other a student, to retrieve fruit from a stand inside a room.""They noted how student typically tracked the teacher's path toward the fruit." "The bats were fitted with technology to record brain cell activity.""Activity was normal in students bats acting on their own, but fired when tracking the position of the teacher. "Researchers believe this was social place-cells in the hippocampus.""Student bats also tracked objects like balls and dice, but their brain activity responded differently.""Researchers suspect this could provide insights into how that the brain cognitively maps out one's environment socially, and physically."SOURCES: Weizmann Institute of Science, Science, Naturehttps://wis-wander.weizmann.ac.il/life-sciences/mapping-social-landscapehttp://science.sciencemag.org/content/359/6372/218https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-00484-w***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 05:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/22/3531534/3531534_59C9D3443CA14ABA8F10C35D98A3E716_180122_3531534_Bat_research_finds_brain_socially_maps_others__l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/30F/3DD/30F3DDD712F74AE8B47BED021EE881C2_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, brain social map, bat study, bat flying, bat research, social place cells, regular place cells]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3532660</guid>
      <title>Scientists fear chronic wasting disease in deer could spread to humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEA mysterious neurological disease is killing North American deer species, and scientists are worried it might spread to humans next.The Atlanta Journal-Constitution reports that since its discovery in 1967, chronic wasting disease has infected deer populations in 24 US states and Canada, and has also been found in South Korea and Norway.Chronic wasting disease is caused by prions, deformed proteins which accumulate in certain organs. Infected deer can live two years before symptoms like weight loss, thick saliva, and behavioral changes manifest, according to the CWD Alliance.The disease is contagious, and typically spreads via the saliva and feces of diseased deer, which can contaminate the environment and infect other animals.Prion diseases are typically limited to certain species, but may evolve to overcome the interspecies barrier and infect new hosts.Mad Cow Disease is one example, with humans contracting the disease from eating cows that had been infected by prions from sheep.While no humans have been infected by CWD, monkeys in a recent study reportedly contracted the disease after ingesting infected deer meat.Public health officials continue to monitor for any sign of brain-wasting diseases in humans. They have also warned hunters not to consume deer meat without getting it tested, regardless of how healthy the animal looks. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cause and symptoms of chronic wasting disease in deer2. Bodily fluids of diseased deer can contaminate environment, spread infection3. Prions may evolve and break past interspecies barrier to infect humans4. Macaque monkeys contracted disease after eating infected deer meatVOICEOVER (in English): "Chronic wasting disease is caused by prions, deformed proteins which accumulate in certain organs. Infected deer can live two years before symptoms like weight loss, thick saliva, and behavioral changes manifest.""The disease is contagious, and typically spreads via the saliva and feces of diseased deer, which can contaminate the environment and infect other animals.""Prion diseases are typically limited to certain species, but may evolve to overcome the interspecies barrier and infect new hosts.""While no humans have been infected by CWD, monkeys in a recent study reportedly contracted the disease after ingesting infected deer meat.SOURCES: Chronic Wasting Disease Alliance, Atlanta Journal-Constitution, NPR, New York Timeshttp://cwd-info.org/http://www.ajc.com/news/national/scientists-worry-brain-wasting-zombie-deer-disease-could-spread-humans/rjpiryXSOn92IxD9qVx1ZL/https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/01/17/578582087/concerns-grow-that-infected-zombie-deer-meat-can-jump-to-humanshttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/26/science/chronic-wasting-disease-deer-elk-prions.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/23/3532660/3532660_92F178E8A0B1418DA19B40D900BB84D7_180123_3532660_Scientists_fear_chronic_wasting_disease_in_deer__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/104/73A/10473ADD2C3F47FDA3E68420999F5525_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, chronic wasting disease, CWD, deer, zombie deer disease, zombie deer, neurological disorder, brain disease, prions, infectious disease, interspecies barrier, interspecies infection, mad cow]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3532302</guid>
      <title>China says U.S. breached its sovereignty in disputed island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[China has complained that U.S. breached its sovereignty in the South China Sea.U.S. Navy officials says USS Hopper, a destroyer vessel, sailed near the Scarborough Shoal last week, reports Reuters. The rocky outlet is claimed by Taiwan, China and the Philippines.China says the vessel came with 12 nautical miles of the island and breached the country's sovereignty by doing so. The Chinese Navy reportedly ordered the USS Hopper to withdraw immediately after discerning its identity, reported Reuters.The U.S. says it was an "innocent passage" and followed international law.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of U.S. ship sailing2. Depiction of U.S. ship sailing near disputed island3. Depiction of Chinese navy warning U.S. shipVOICEOVER (in English): "U.S. Navy officials says USS Hopper, a destroyer vessel, sailed near the Scarborough Shoal last week. "The rocky outlet is claimed by Taiwan, China and the Philippines.""China says the vessel came within 12 nautical miles of the island and breached the country's sovereignty by doing so."The U.S. says it was an "innocent passage" and followed international law.""The Chinese Navy reportedly ordered the USS Hopper to withdraw immediately after discerning its identity."SOURCES: Reuters, Japan Times, Guardianhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-us-sovereignty/china-says-u-s-warship-violated-its-south-china-sea-sovereignty-idUSKBN1F9088https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2018/01/21/asia-pacific/china-accuses-u-s-sailing-warship-near-disputed-scarborough-shoal-south-china-sea/#.WmVZcWiWaUkhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jan/21/china-vows-action-after-us-warship-sails-near-south-china-sea-island***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 06:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/23/3532302/3532302_1BB86BDFB01A4111A405DDCC6341FF42_180123_3532302_China_says_U_S__breached_its_sovereignty_in_disp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D7B/EE4/D7BEE4F540F743AFAAE40DDEE0E5DC46_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, south china sea dispute, south china sea us navy, us navy, china claims, uss hopper south china sea,  scarborough shoal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3533519</guid>
      <title>Russia developing underwater nuclear torpedo, suggests Pentagon document</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEA leaked draft of a Pentagon document suggests that Russia is working on an underwater thermonuclear torpedo.First reported by the Washington Free Beacon, the project  codenamed "Kanyon" by the Pentagon  was conceived to target coastal areas, naval bases and sea ports. The weapon is believed to operate autonomously, the New York Times reported, citing officials. Russia reportedly refers to the device as "Ocean Multipurpose System Status-6".According to Popular Mechanics, the weapon operates like a drone. It has a range of 6,200 miles, can dive to over 3000 feet and travel at 100 knots (around 115 mph). The warhead measures 5.5 feet wide and is 79 feet long, reported Popular Mechanics, citing submarine expert H. I. Sutton.The device can also wield a 100 megaton nuclear payload and reportedly has the radioactive isotope Cobalt-60, meaning area struck by it would be dangerous to humans for around a century. It is being tested by the Russian Navy on a Sarov-class submarine which carries it on its pressure hull, reported Popular Mechanics.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of warhead moving toward city2. Depiction of warhead's measurements3. Depiction of warhead's radioactivity4. Depiction of fallout from attackVOICEOVER (in English): "The autonomous underwater vehicle  dubbed "Kanyon" by the U.S.  was conceived to target coastal areas.""Russia reportedly refers to it as "Ocean Multipurpose System Status-6".""The warhead measures 5.5 feet wide and is 79 feet long.""According to Popular Mechanics, it has a range of 6,200 miles, can dive to over 3000 feet and travel at 100 knots.""The device can also wield a 100 megaton nuclear payload and reportedly contains the radioactive isotope Cobalt-60.""That means an area struck by it would be dangerously radioactive to humans for around a century."SOURCES: Huffington Post, H I Sutton, Popular Mechanics, New York Times, Diplomat, Washington Free Beaconhttp://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/trump-nuclear-posture-review-2018_us_5a4d4773e4b06d1621bce4c5http://www.hisutton.com/Newsflash-KANYON.htmlhttp://www.popularmechanics.com/military/weapons/a15227656/pentagon-document-confirms-existence-of-russian-doomsday-torpedo/https://www.nytimes.com/2018/01/16/us/politics/pentagon-nuclear-review-cyberattack-trump.htmlhttps://thediplomat.com/2016/12/russia-tests-nuclear-capable-underwater-drone/http://freebeacon.com/national-security/russia-tests-nuclear-capable-drone-sub/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/24/3533519/3533519_F1554CA209E143CC9CF8E7E4D08D3694_180124_3533519_Russia_developing_underwater_nuclear_torpedo__su_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FA6/672/FA66721F0B704BA9924A243BED9ED2CA_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, russian nuke torpedo, moscow, torpedo nuke, underwater nuke, underwater atomic bomb, Ocean Multipurpose System Status-6, kanyon bomb]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3533195</guid>
      <title>Deadly school shooting in Kentucky kills 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONETwo are dead and 17 others injured after a teenage boy opened fire inside a Kentucky school.The Lexington Herald Leader reports that the incident at Marshall County High School in Benton, Kentucky began just before 8 a.m., when a shooter started firing at students in the common area.The shooting continued as the students ran for cover. A 15-year-old girl was shot and killed on the scene, while more than a dozen others were wounded.Five gunshot victims were airlifted to a Nashville hospital, where one boy later died from head wounds. The four others are expected to survive after being shot in the head, arm, chest, and abdomen.Police have apprehended the 15-year-old male suspect, who will be charged with murder and attempted murder.The gunman's identity has not been disclosed since he's still a juvenile, but will likely be made public if the case is moved to adult court.At least nine US school shootings have been reported so far in 2018, but the incident in Kentucky is the year's first fatal school shooting.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 15-year-old shooter opens fire inside Kentucky high school2. Students running from shooter; one dead on scene, others injured3. Five shooting victims airlifted to Nashville4. Shooter apprehended by policeVOICEOVER (in English): "The incident at Marshall County High School in Benton, Kentucky began just before 8 a.m., when a shooter started firing at students in the common area.""The rampage continued as the students ran for cover. A 15-year-old girl was shot and killed on the scene, while more than a dozen others were wounded.""Five shooting victims were airlifted to a Nashville hospital, where one boy later died from head wounds. The four others are expected to survive after being shot in the head, arm, chest, and abdomen.""Police have apprehended the 15-year-old male suspect, who will be charged with murder and attempted murder."SOURCES: Lexington Herald Leader, Courier Journal, WSMVhttp://www.kentucky.com/news/state/article196104979.htmlhttps://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2018/01/23/police-respond-shooting-marshall-county-high-school/1057137001/http://www.wsmv.com/story/37328417/gunman-in-custody-after-2-killed-17-injured-in-ky-high-school-shooting***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 07:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/24/3533195/3533195_195DF6706DE743BE99DC896AE2A2003F_180124_3533195_Deadly_school_shooting_in_Kentucky_kills_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/957/5B7/9575B791350C4970A7A60A8B2E85A0AE_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kentucky school shooting, school shooting, kentucky shooting, kentucky high school shooting, teen shooter, marshall county school, benton, kentucky]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3533171</guid>
      <title>Study shows geoengineering may do more harm than good</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEAs global warming gets progressively worse, scientists consider engineering the climate to cool it down, but a new study shows it may do more harm than good.Stratospheric aerosol injection is a form of geoengineering that involves spraying sulfur dioxide into the upper atmosphere to form clouds that reflect solar radiation, according to AFP.Using computer models, a study published in Nature Ecology and Evolution found that spraying 5 million tonnes of sulfur dioxide above the equator every year for 50 years could drop surface temperatures by one degree Celsius.But if sulfur seeding is suddenly stopped, the planet would warm rapidly, with temperatures rising several times faster than the predicted rate.Plant populations would die out, and wildlife, especially amphibians and land animals, would not be able to migrate quickly enough. The loss of just one species could impact an entire ecosystem.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Sulfur dioxide sprayed into stratosphere form clouds that reflect sunlight2. 5M tonnes of sulfur dioxide sprayed yearly for 50 years could reduce surface temperature by 1 degree3. If spraying suddenly stopped, planet rapidly heats up 4. Plant and animal species may be depleted as a resultVOICEOVER (in English): "Stratospheric aerosol injection is a form of geoengineering that involves spraying sulfur dioxide into the upper atmosphere to form clouds that reflect solar radiation.""Using computer models, a study found that spraying 5 million tonnes of sulfur dioxide above the equator every year for 50 years could drop surface temperatures by one degree Celsius.""But if sulfur seeding is suddenly stopped, the planet would warm rapidly, with temperatures rising several times faster than the predicted rate.""Plant populations would die out, and wildlife, especially amphibians and land animals, would not be able to migrate quickly enough. The loss of just one species could impact an entire ecosystem."SOURCES: AFP, Discover Magazine http://www.straitstimes.com/world/dimming-the-sun-to-cool-earth-could-ravage-wildlife-studyhttp://blogs.discovermagazine.com/d-brief/2018/01/22/geoengineering-stop-suddenly/#.WmbRBlT1W8o***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 07:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/24/3533171/3533171_56A1FC580B6045F1A2DDE526D59FE0E1_180124_3533171_Study_shows_geoengineering_may_do_more_harm_than_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EA6/DFD/EA6DFDE808A14B70874FF6329E8B2F49_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, geoengineering, solar geoengineering, climate change, global warming, sulfur dioxide spray, carbon emissions, carbon dioxide, greenhouse gas, stratospheric injection, stratospheric aerosol injection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3533050</guid>
      <title>Earth to get 'Super Blue Blood Moon' on Jan. 31</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONENASA says Earth is in for a lunar trifecta of a "super blue blood moon" on January 31, 2018.The lunar orbit of Earth follows a 29-day cycle. The blue moon, like the one on January 31, occurs when there are two full moons in a calendar month.The moon will also be close to Earth during this time, meaning it will be brighter than normal. This is called a supermoon. When the moon passes through the Earth's shadow during the Jan. 31 lunar eclipse it will appear red. This creates the blood moon.Most of Asia, Australasia and the northwestern America will be able to see this super blue blood moon, while much of South America, Africa and West Europe will not.The rest of the world will be able to see it partially depending on their location.The last time a total lunar eclipse coincided with a blue moon was in 1982, reports Time, citing NASA programmer Ernest Wright and ex-NASA astrophysicist Fred Espenak.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Explanation of blue moon and supermoon2. Depiction of blood moon3. Depiction where super blue blood moon is visible4. Depiction of total lunar eclipseVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA says Earth is in for a lunar trifecta of a "super blue blood moon" on January 31, 2018.""Lunar orbit of Earth follows a 29-day cycle. The blue moon, like the one on January 31, occurs when there are two full moons in a calendar month.""The moon will also be close to Earth during this time, meaning it will be brighter than normal. This is called a supermoon. ""When the moon passes through the Earth's shadow during the Jan. 31 lunar eclipse it will appear red. "This is known as a blood moon.""Much of South America, Africa and West Europe will not be able to see the cosmic event, while most of Asia, Australasia and the northwestern America will.""The rest of the world maybe able to see it partially depending on their location.""According to Time, the last total lunar eclipse to coincided with a blue moon was in 1982."SOURCES: NASA, Time, Spacehttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/super-blue-blood-moon-coming-jan-31http://time.com/5095721/blue-moon-total-lunar-eclipse-2018/https://www.space.com/39432-get-ready-for-super-blue-blood-moon-eclipse.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 04:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/24/3533050/3533050_E99F0123325F446B97C4582EF84702ED_180124_3533050_Earth_to_get__Super_Blue_Blood_Moon__on_Jan__31_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7CE/D72/7CED722AD4FC495191A5BB488DAE9213_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, super blue blood moon, blue moon, blood moon, super moon, nasa, total lunar eclipse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3534322</guid>
      <title>Chinese scientists successfully clone monkeys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEChina successfully cloned monkeys using transferred DNA, marking the first time such a feat has been achieved and possibly paving the way for human cloning.Nature reports that biologists in Shanghai have cloned two genetically identical macaques using the same technique that produced Dolly the Sheep.Somatic cell nuclear transfer involves taking the nucleus of a cell, which contains its genetic material, and injecting it into an egg that has had its own nucleus removed.The egg cell is then treated with enzymes to stimulate embryo development, just like a naturally fertilized egg.In all, the researchers created 109 embryos and implanted them into 21 surrogate monkeys, resulting in six pregnancies but only two live births.The macaques, named Zhong Zhong and Hua Hua, aren't the first primates to be cloned though  that distinction belongs to Tetra, a rhesus monkey created using a simpler embryo-splitting method.The Chinese team believes the monkey clones could be useful in medical research, specifically in the study of genetic diseases like Parkinson's or autism.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese scientists clone genetically identical macaques2. Depiction of somatic cell nuclear transfer3. Depiction of egg cell being stimulated to develop into an embryo4. Depiction of embryo being transplanted into a surrogate VOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists in Shanghai have cloned two genetically identical macaques using the same technique that produced Dolly the Sheep.""Somatic cell nuclear transfer involves taking the nucleus of a cell, which contains its genetic material, and injecting it into an egg that has had its own nucleus removed.""The egg cell is then treated with enzymes to stimulate embryo development, just like a naturally fertilized egg.""In all, the researchers created 109 embryos and implanted them into 21 surrogate monkeys, resulting in six pregnancies but only two live births."SOURCES: Nature, National Geographichttps://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-01027-zhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/01/monkey-clones-dolly-sheep-china-medicine-science/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 11:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/25/3534322/3534322_806BF044CE0346F7A3BB4377C89DAE89_180125_3534322_Chinese_scientists_successfully_clone_monkeys_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A8F/F2C/A8FF2CDBD302448AA819E8F5A1625DE5_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cloned monkey, monkey clone, macaque clone, clone, cloning, animal cloning, cloning technique, somatic cell nuclear transfer, SCNT, dolly the sheep, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3534292</guid>
      <title>Pacific Ocean's Ring of Fire is active, UN agency says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONERecent volcanic and seismic activity in various Pacific Ocean nations prompted the UN to warn that the "Ring of Fire" is active.The warning, posted to the official UN Office of Disaster Risk Reduction Twitter feed, comes after eruptions and earthquakes hit areas in the Philippines, Indonesia, Japan and Alaska this week.As the naming implies, it is a ring of hundred of volcanoes spanning 25,000 miles across the Pacific Ocean. Much of it was created through the subduction of tectonic plates.This is where oceanic crust of the Earth clashes with heavier continental plates, and is forced underneath them due to the weight, reports DW. The resulting pressure is explosive and results in magma eruptions and earthquakes.Because of these subduction zones, the Ring of Fire is home to 452 volcanoes and around 90 percent of the world's earthquakes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of eruptions and earthquakes2. Depiction of Ring of Fire on map3. Depiction of subduction zone4. Overview of Ring of Fire volcanoes and earthquakesVOICEOVER (in English): "After recent eruptions and earthquakes in the Philippines, Indonesia, Japan and Alaska the United Nations has warned the Ring of Fire is active.""As the naming implies, it is a ring of hundreds of volcanoes spanning 25,000 miles across the Pacific Ocean""Much of it was created through the subduction of tectonic plates.""This is where oceanic crust of the earth clashes with heavier continental plates, and is forced underneath them due to the weight.""The resulting pressure is explosive and results in magma eruptions and earthquakes.""Because of these subduction zones, the Ring of Fire is home to 452 volcanoes and around 90 percent of the world's earthquakes."SOURCES: United Nations, Channel News Asia, CNN, DWhttps://twitter.com/unisdr/status/955799496801255426https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asiapacific/un-warns-pacific-ring-of-fire-is-active-as-volcanoes-erupt-9891808https://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/23/us/alaska-earthquake/index.htmlhttp://www.dw.com/en/ring-of-fire-five-facts-about-the-most-earthquake-prone-region-in-the-world/a-36676363***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/25/3534292/3534292_D6A4A5DE02034FE48067AD17E6C7781A_180125_3534292_Pacific_Ocean_s_Ring_of_Fire_is_active__UN_agenc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/647/6D3/6476D3DAC3F041F1A257E87B5363A538_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News ,pacific ocean, tectonic subduction, ring of fire pacific ocean, ring of fire volcano, ring of fire earthquake, ring of fire pacific ocean video, ring of fire pacific active, japan, indonesia, philippines, us]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3534170</guid>
      <title>How the flu turns deadly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEThe flu season in the U.S. this year has been particularly harsh, already having claimed the lives of at least 30 children, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.   Although most people do not die from the flu, young children and people with other illnesses, such as heart disease, lung disease and diabetes are at elevated risks. Adults can succumb to the flu in three ways: pneumonia, sepsis and heart attack. Pneumonia can develop in a person who is infected with influenza.Pneumonia causes the small air sacs of the lungs to fill with fluid or pus, sometimes leading to death. With sepsis, the influenza virus can trigger the body to release chemicals into the blood to fight infection that triggers inflammation throughout the body. That inflammation can then trigger multiple organ system failure. The third way the flu kills adults is by triggering heart attacks. A new study in the New England Journal of Medicine found that a person is six times more likely to have a heart attack during the week after being diagnosed with the flu, compared to the year before or after the infection. Experts are urging people to get flu shots, even though it may not always prevent an infection from the flu virus.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Young children and people with underlying illnesses have higher risks of dying from flu2. Flu can lead to pneumonia3. Flu can lead to sepsis4. Flu can increase chance of heart attackVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: CNN, NPRhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/24/health/how-flu-kills/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2018/01/24/579997381/aw-seriously-the-flu-can-trigger-a-heart-attack-too***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 09:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/25/3534170/3534170_61A2EF7540EC4437A3B172A7B29ED373_180125_3534170_How_the_flu_turns_deadly_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A8F/0F9/A8F0F90C8817484786588A004B55C52A_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, flu, flu season, flu vaccine, flu shots, flu pneumonia, flu sepsis, flu heart attack, influenza]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3534115</guid>
      <title>Luxury floating lapland hotel planned in Sweden</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEA team of Swedish architects have unveiled plans to construct a floating luxury hotel.Dubbed The Arctic Bath and Spa, the hotel will be placed on the Lule River in Harads village, northern Sweden, reports Fortune. It will be frozen into the river during the winter and float the rest of the year.Inhabitat reports the hotel could potentially open this year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of hotel2. Depiction of hotel on water in summer and winter3. Depiction of hotel log cabin on water in summer and winter4. Depiction of hotel area during aurora borealisVOICEOVER (in English): "The Arctic Bath and Spa hotel will be placed on the Lule River in Harads village, northern Sweden.""It will be frozen into the river during the winter and float the rest of the year.""The hotel's log cabins will also be placed on the river and will freeze or float depending on the time of year.""Inhabitat reports the hotel could potentially open this year for business."SOURCES: Arctic Bath Hotel, Inhabitat, Fortunehttp://www.arcticbath.sehttps://issuu.com/arctictrend/docs/arctic_bath_koncept_2017_presentatihttps://inhabitat.com/this-floating-hotel-and-spa-in-sweden-will-fill-you-with-wanderlust/https://www.forbes.com/sites/carriecoolidge/2018/01/12/floating-hotel-and-spa-to-open-near-arctic-circle-in-northern-sweden/#770fd6f13ad1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 08:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/25/3534115/3534115_8668A2D8C5794B90856CABA22FC9DB62_180125_3534115_Luxury_floating_lapland_hotel_planned_in_Sweden_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/157/18B/15718B982D854EBCAAAFE0C9AFADEA08_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, floating hotels, buildings that float on water, lule river, swedish river, floating hotel, arctic bath and spa, luxury hotel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3533965</guid>
      <title>Tesla autopilot crash prompts federal investigation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. government is looking into an accident involving a Tesla Model S on autopilot and a fire truck.Culver City firefighters were at the scene of an accident on Monday when a Tesla Model S, reportedly driving on autopilot, rear ended a parked fire truck.Fire officials said the car was traveling at 65 miles per hour before it crashed into the truck on Interstate 405. No one was hurt in the accident, but it has prompted an investigation by the U.S. National Transportation Board."Tesla told KTLA that autopilot function is intended for use by fully attentive drivers. The function isn't fully autonomous. According to the San Jose Mercury News, firefighters advised the drive to see medical staff after the crash but he refused treatment and showed no major injuries.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of driver using autopilot and accident2. Depiction of accident from behind car3. Depiction of crash sceneVOICEOVER (in English): "Culver City firefighters were at the scene of an accident on Monday when a Tesla Model S, reportedly driving on autopilot, rear ended a parked fire truck.""Fire officials said the car was traveling at 65 miles per hour before it crashed into the truck on Interstate 405.""No one was hurt in the accident, but it has prompted an investigation by the U.S. National Transportation Board.""Tesla said autopilot is intended for use by fully attentive drivers. The function isn't fully autonomous."SOURCES: San Jose Mercury News, KTLA, CNN https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/01/22/tesla-on-autopilot-slams-into-parked-fire-truck-on-freeway/http://ktla.com/2018/01/23/federal-officials-investigating-crash-involving-tesla-on-autopilot-in-culver-city/http://money.cnn.com/2018/01/23/technology/tesla-fire-truck-crash/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 05:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/25/3533965/3533965_BDFE6C5B04F0462D9E6FB12BDDA83FEF_180125_3533965_Tesla_autopilot_crash_prompts_federal_investigat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7D3/8BA/7D38BA45402A43A69BC8C5ED7A97AE72_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tesla model s fire truck, telsa, tesla autopilot crash, tesla autopilot accident, tesla autopilot fail, tesla model s crash, elon musk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3535344</guid>
      <title>Hackers using malicious cryptocurrency apps to steal money, personal data</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEHackers are using malicious cryptocurrency apps to steal money and personal data from Apple and Google apps stores, according to a new study. Researchers from internet security firm RiskIQ looked at more than 18,000 apps to find ones blacklisted by cybersecurity vendors, CNBC reported. They discovered 661 blacklisted cryptocurrency apps across 20 app stores including Google Play and Apple's App Store. Google Play offered the highest number of malicious apps with 272 available for download. Hackers used phrases like "bitcoin exchange," "bitcoin wallet" and "cryptocurrency" to trick potential victims, the report said.  RiskIQ recommended investors thoroughly research possible exchanges and wallet apps before use. People should check the developer's name, user reviews and number of app downloads.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 18,000 apps were scanned, 661 blacklisted crypto apps were found2. Google Play offered 272 blacklisted apps3. Hackers used certain phrases to lure victims4. People should properly research exchanges and wallet apps before useVOICEOVER (in English): "Internet security firm RiskIQ looked at more than 18,000 apps to find ones blacklisted by cybersecurity vendors, and detected 661 blacklisted crypto apps across 20 app stores being used by hackers to steal money and personal data." "Google Play offered the highest number of malicious apps with 272 available for download." "Hackers used phrases like 'Bitcoin exchange', 'Bitcoin wallet' and 'cryptocurrency' to trick potential victims.""The report suggests investors thoroughly research possible exchanges and wallet apps before use. People should check the developer's name, user reviews and number of app downloads."SOURCES: CNBChttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/01/24/hackers-targeting-apple-google-app-stores-with-malicious-crypto-apps.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 16:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/27/3535344/3535344_A0FD66B467074CCFB6B03632BE73D4E8_180127_3535344_Hackers_using_malicious_cryptocurrency_apps_to_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/97D/3AB/97D3AB94314F4D199E0BD0F6D201F38B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, hacker, cryptocurrency apps, malicious cryptocurrency apps, Apple App Store, Google Play Store, cryptocurrency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3535336</guid>
      <title>South Korea owns submersible that also doubles as surface vessel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEThe South Korean Navy has a submersible that also doubles as a surface vessel.According to Korean Naval manufacturer VOGO, the vessel can be deployed via airdrop from a C-17 or C-130 aircraft. It can carry a crew of 10. On the surface the SDV 1000W can travel at 35 knots, or 40 mph via diesel engines and waterjet propulsors. While submerged it can travel at 6 knots or 7 mph using lithium polymer batteries and silent electric motors.Submarine expert H I Sutton reports that the vessel functions like a wet-sub, in that the crew still wear diving gear and receive oxygen from a sizeable on-board air system. This lets passengers exit underwater, but the vessel can also be run up a beach.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of SDV 1000W 2. Depiction of SDV 1000W's surface and submerged speeds3. Depiction of SDV 1000W underwater4. Depiction of SDV 1000W on a beachVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Korean Naval manufacturer VOGO, the the SDV 1000W can be deployed via airdrop from a C-17 or C-130 aircraft. It can carry a crew of 10." "On the surface it can travel at 35 knots, or 40 mph via its diesel engines and waterjet propulsors." "While submerged it can travel at 6 knots or 7 mph using lithium polymer batteries and silent electric motors.""Submarine expert H I Sutton reports that the vessel functions like a wet-sub, in that the crew still wear diving gear and receive oxygen from a sizeable on-board air system.""This lets passengers exit underwater.""The vessel can also be landed on a beach."SOURCES: VOGO, H I Sutton, Jane's 360http://www.vogoeng.com/bbs/board.php?bo_table=product01_e&wr_id=2http://www.hisutton.com/Vogo_SDV-1000W.htmlhttp://www.janes.com/article/65241/special-delivery-service-indodef16-d3***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 15:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/26/3535336/3535336_71F64DB9527D42A2964A91185650003C_180126_3535336_South_Korea_owns_submersible_that_also_doubles_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EDC/979/EDC97930BD0640218A082DFD0AF51D53_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, underwater boat, sdv 1000w, south korea navy, VOGO, UDV, submersible]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3535173</guid>
      <title>Jawbone found in Israeli cave may be earliest human remains</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists have found what they suspect are the earliest human remains outside of Africa in a cave on Mount Carmel, Israel.The partial upper jawbone, found in a 2002 excavation then intensively analyzed for 15 years, is said to be between 170,000 and 200,000 years old. According to the Smithsonian Magazine, many archaeologists believed humans migrated from Africa 60,000 years ago.Details of the finding were published this month in the journal, Science. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of jawbone 2. Depiction of earliest human finding in Morocco, human migration, and jawbone finding in Israel3. Depiction of similarities between jaw and human skull4. Depiction of jaw inside human skullVOICEOVER (in English): "The partial upper jawbone, found during an 2002 excavation inside the Misliya cave in Israel, took scientists 15 years to date.""Their research, which included virtual reconstruction, places the jawbone as between 170,000 and 200,000 years old.""The oldest human remains on record were found at Jebel Irhoud in Morocco. These are 300,000 years old.""Many archaeologists believed humans migrated out of Africa around 60,000 to 150,000 years ago.""The jawbone finding suggests humans left Africa 200,000 years ago." "The jawbone contains 5 similarities to human jawbones.""These are the small parabolic dental arch, area of the incisive foramen.""The finding corresponds with where the upper jaw and jaw ridge connect with the maxilla area of a human skull, as well as the position of the nasal cavity floor.""If accepted as human, the jawbone could push back the history of human evolution by at least 100,000 years."SOURCES: Science, Times of Israel, Smithsonian, Reuters, The Guardianhttp://science.sciencemag.org/content/359/6374/456https://www.timesofisrael.com/jawbone-fossil-found-in-israeli-cave-resets-clock-for-modern-human-evolution/https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/earliest-humans-remains-outside-africa-just-discovered-israel-180967952/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-humans/oldest-human-remains-outside-africa-found-in-israeli-cave-idUSKBN1FE2SY?feedType=RSS&feedName=scienceNewshttps://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/jun/07/oldest-homo-sapiens-bones-ever-found-shake-foundations-of-the-human-story***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 11:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/26/3535173/3535173_7C9401171BB74F619B787190D38532B4_180126_3535173_Jawbone_found_in_Israeli_cave_may_be_earliest_hu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/855/AA2/855AA2AC1BF8404C8E14C2B4A8EDA34E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, earliest human remains found, ancient humans remains, most ancient civilization, oldest human remains, ancient humans, ancient findings unearthed, oldest ever human remains, m]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3534897</guid>
      <title>Recurring snowfalls in Sahara desert stems from global warming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEIncreasingly frequent snowfalls on one of the hottest places on Earth stems from global warming, says the head of Russia's environmental monitoring agency.The Russian News Agency reports that on January 7, a blanket of snow fell on the Sahara desert, near the northern Algerian town of Ain Sefra.The Sahara has been known to get as hot as 122 degrees Fahrenheit during the day. But while temperatures drop at night, it's unusual to see snow due to the dry air.In 1979, snow fell in the area for 30 minutes. It was 37 years before the next snowfall, but only a year passed between then and the most recent one, which saw 15 inches of snow cover.According to Roman Vilfand, Head of Russia's Federal Service for Hydrometeorology and Environmental Monitoring, the frequency of such an unusual weather phenomenon is evidence that global warming is on the rise. He adds that the same is true the current cold spell in the eastern US, an unusually warm Russian winter, and rainfall and flooding in Western EuropeWith the state of the climate as dismal as it is and with no signs of improvement, guess there'll be more extreme weather in our future. Yikes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Snowfall on the Sahara desert2. High temperatures and dry air in the Sahara 3. Depiction of recurring snowfall on the Sahara desert4. Extreme weather conditions possibly caused by global warmingVOICEOVER (in English): "On January 7, a blanket of snow fell on the Sahara desert, near the northern Algerian town of Ain Sefra.""The Sahara has been known to get as hot as 122 degrees Fahrenheit during the day. But while temperatures drop at night, it's unusual to see snow due to the dry air.""In 1979, snow fell in the area for 30 minutes. It was 37 years before the next snowfall, but only a year passed between then and the most recent one, which saw 15 inches of snow cover.""This, along with the cold spell in the US, an unusually warm Russian winter, and rainfall and flooding in Western Europe, is evidence that global warming is on the rise."SOURCES: Russian News Agency, Space, CNNhttp://tass.com/society/984271https://www.space.com/39411-satellite-images-capture-rare-snowfall-sahara.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/09/africa/sahara-snow-trnd/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 08:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/26/3534897/3534897_1E842D5AB048422ABA4B80CD6D9C1710_180126_3534897_Recurring_snowfalls_in_Sahara_desert_stems_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A9B/E7C/A9BE7C8E5E4D485484FD1B96512DE152_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, snow on the sahara, sahara snow, sahara snowfall, desert snow, desert snowfall, extreme weather, global warming, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3537046</guid>
      <title>Hackers using YouTube ads for cryptomining</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEHackers are using YouTube as a way to turn passive viewers into cryptocurrency miners, according to cybersecurity firm Trend Micro.The issue was brought to light at the beginning of the week over social media with complaints that YouTube ads were raising red flags in anti-virus software, Mashable reported. A service called Coinhive was apparently taking over a viewer's CPU and using it to mine digital coins. According to Trend Micro, attackers used Google's DoubleClick ad software for traffic distribution.Japan, France, Taiwan, Italy and Spain were affected by the malvertising campaign. Google confirmed the cryptojacking threat, and eventually blocked the ads and removed the "malicious actors" from their platform. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Passive viewers being turned into cryptocurrency miners2. YouTube ads triggering virus alerts3. Coinhive using CPUs to mine for digital coins4. Japan, France, Taiwan, Italy and Spain were affectedVOICEOVER (in English): "Hackers are using YouTube as a way to turn passive viewers into cryptocurrency miners.""The issue was brought to light over social media with complaints that YouTube ads were raising red flags in anti-virus software. "A service called Coinhive was apparently taking over a viewer's CPU and using it to mine digital coins." "Attackers used Google's DoubleClick ad software for traffic distribution. Japan, France, Taiwan, Italy and Spain were affected by the malvertising campaign." SOURCES: MASHABLEhttps://mashable.com/2018/01/27/coinhive-youtube-google-doubleclick/#aYdLQfEQhaqS***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 12:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/29/3537046/3537046_66C91A53CB8F4615A66E6D927E510F85_180129_3537046_Hackers_using_YouTube_ads_for_cryptomining_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ED8/03D/ED803DA229534B81A69CE20083548E1F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, YouTube cryptomining, YouTube ads, cryptomining, cryptojacking, Coinhive, cryptocurrency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3536802</guid>
      <title>Fitness trackers reportedly revealing U.S. soldiers' information</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEInformation about location and staffing of U.S. military bases around the world has been revealed by a fitness-tracking company.The data was released by Strava in a data map that indicates all the activity tracked by users of the fitness app, the Guardian reported. The Global Heat Map published by Strava uses satellite information to plot the location and movements of its users over a two-year period by lighting up areas of activity. The app can be used on smartphones or fitness trackers to see running popular routes in cities, or track people in remote areas. Military analysts discovered over the weekend the data also reveals sensitive information about U.S. soldiers on active service. Nathan Ruser, a researcher at the Institute for United Conflict Analysts, first discovered the oversight. "If soldiers use the app like normal people do, by turning it on tracking when they go to do exercise, it could be especially dangerous," Ruser said. In locations like Afghanistan, Djibouti and Syria, Strava users are almost all foreign military personnel, meaning their bases stand out brightly. Strava apps and devices can have their location services turned off. The company issued a statement urging users to visit their website to make sure they fully understand the privacy settings. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. US soldiers using fitness apps when running2. Fort Benning map and Strava heat map3. Strava heat map of US Helmand Afghanistan base4. US soldier turning off tracking function on fitness deviceVOICEOVER (in English): "Military analysts discovered data released by fitness tracking company Strava reveals sensitive information about U.S. bases and military personnel around the world."  "The Global Heat Map published by Strava uses satellite information to plot the location and movements of its users by lighting up areas of activity." "In locations like Afghanistan, Djibouti and Syria, Strava users are almost all foreign military personnel, meaning their bases stand out brightly, which could be dangerous for operational security." "Strava apps and devices can have their location services turned off. The company issued a statement urging users make sure they understand the privacy settings." SOURCES: Guardian, Washington Posthttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jan/28/fitness-tracking-app-gives-away-location-of-secret-us-army-baseshttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/a-map-showing-the-users-of-fitness-devices-lets-the-world-see-where-us-soldiers-are-and-what-they-are-doing/2018/01/28/86915662-0441-11e8-aa61-f3391373867e_story.html?utm_term=.6dbed8e5f31f***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 07:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/29/3536802/3536802_D7F796BF1C7440A78227ACD78C488EA6_180129_3536802_Fitness_trackers_reportedly_revealing_U_S__soldi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/051/3CE/0513CEA55CA749398CC88D3876DDAADC_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Strava Global Heat Map, Strava fitness tracking company, fitbit, US military personnel fitness apps, US soldier fitness apps]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3536771</guid>
      <title>Secret Service issues 'ATM jackpotting' alert</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. Secret Service this week issued an alert, warning banks about an ATM exploit known called "jackpotting."According to online security blogger and journalist Brian Krebs, the Secret Service has been warning banks that attacks are taking place in the USA. Krebs, citing the Secret Service alert, reports that thieves use an endoscope attached to a phone to find an internal part of the ATM that'll connect with their laptop.After that, the cash machine appears as Out of Service and will be in control of the thieves, according to the Secret Service alert reported by Krebs. They can order the ATM to dispense currency to a collector, or "money mule", at a rate of 40 bills per 23 seconds.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of endoscope and ATM thieve2. Depiction of thieve gaining control of ATM3. Depiction of ATM as 'Out of Service'4. Depiction of ATM dispensing cash to 'money mule'VOICEOVER (in English): "Online security blogger and journalist Brian Krebs, citing a Secret Service alert to banks, reports that thieves use an endoscope attached to a phone to begin the exploit.""They use this to find an internal part of the ATM that'll connect with their laptop.""After that, the cash machine appears as Out of Service to and will be in control of the thieves.""They can order the ATM to dispense currency to a collector, or 'money mule', at a rate of 40 bills per 23 seconds."SOURCES: Reuters, Krebs on Security, New York Daily Newshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-cyber-atms-usa/atm-makers-warn-of-jackpotting-hacks-on-u-s-machines-idUSKBN1FG0WUhttps://krebsonsecurity.com/2018/01/first-jackpotting-attacks-hit-u-s-atms/http://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/u-s-secret-service-warns-jackpotting-attacks-atms-article-1.3782934***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 07:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/29/3536771/3536771_447EB778C51847FFA65B2B79B1D5CB18_180129_3536771_Secret_Service_issues__ATM_jackpotting__alert_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B01/47A/B0147A38E5224032A9C86860641FA9C0_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, atm jackpotting hack, us secret service, atm jackpot hack, atm jackpotting, atm robbery hack, atm machine robbery, cash machine jackpot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3536702</guid>
      <title>Study finds eardrums point where eyes look</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONENew research has found that eyeballs and eardrums work together to decode vision and noise.Researchers discovered found that eardrum movement corresponds with where the eyes are looking, even when no sound is present.The research was published in January in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of man sitting down and looking at lights2. Depiction of eardrums and eyeballs tracking the light3. Depiction of brain sending signals to eyes and earsVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists placed 16 people in a room with no sound and placed small microphones in their ears to record eardrum movement.""They tracked how the individuals responded to shifting LED lights without moving their head.""Researchers discovered found that eardrum movement corresponds with where the eyes are looking, even when no sound is present.""They also detected vibrations in the eardrum just before the eyeballs shifted to wherever the light was."SOURCES: Duke University, New Atlashttps://today.duke.edu/2018/01/when-eyes-move-eardrums-move-toohttps://newatlas.com/eardrums-move-with-eyes/53113/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 05:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/01/29/3536702/3536702_4D835810A02C498EA137F170E1A75FED_180129_3536702_Study_finds_eardrums_point_where_eyes_look_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/234/B43/234B433B1104438385D4E2CBF2F42CDE_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, duke university, sight and sound, how do we see and hear, how do eardrums work, vision and hearing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
