<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3822268</guid>
      <title>UK scientists aim to target air pollution by using a "biosolar leaf"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists in the UK have created a 'biosolar leaf' that could potentially suck up carbon dioxide from the atmosphere, The Guardian reports. London's Imperial College and technology startup Arborea are collaborating to build a 'biosolar leaf' that would be capable of removing greenhouse gases while generating oxygen to disperse into the air.Arborea founder, Julian Melchiorri, told the Guardian that this new technology is able to process carbon dioxide at an extremely low pressure.According to an Imperial College London news release, the "biosolar leaf" was made by a cultivation system that is able to grow tiny plant life such as microalgae and phytoplankton onto a solar panel-like structure.The developers claim that this technology could do the work of 100 trees while only using the surface area of one.They eventually plan to place the structures onto the roofs of large buildings in cities to improve air quality.The Biosolar Leaf cultivation system will be used on the college's White City Campus South Site as a test pilot, According to the Imperial College London news release.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the biosolar leaf will work2. How the leaf was made3. A leaf one the podium with trees on the other podium4. How the Biosolar Leaf cultivation system will be usedVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports London's Imperial College and technology startup Arborea are collaborating to build a 'biosolar leaf' that would be capable of removing greenhouse gases while generating oxygen to disperse into the air.""According to an Imperial College London news release, the 'biosolar leaf' was made by a cultivation system which is able to grow tiny plant life such as microalgae and phytoplankton onto a solar panel-like structure.""The developers claim that this technology could do the work of 100 trees while only using the surface area of one.""They eventually plan to place the structures onto the roofs of large buildings in cities to improve air quality."SOURCES: The Guardian, Imperial College London, CNBC, Arboreahttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/apr/28/biosolar-leaf-project-targets-air-pollution-on-london-campushttps://www.imperial.ac.uk/news/191026/worlds-first-biosolar-leaf-tackle-pollution/https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/29/uk-scientists-aiming-to-use-bionic-leaves-to-tackle-air-pollution.htmlhttp://arborea.io/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 06:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/02/3822268/3822268_A6E4FAF80BEE481BBFA73475158015AC_190502_3822268_UK_scientists_aim_to_target_air_pollution_by_usi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, pollution, air pollution, biosolar leaf, biosolar leaf project, BioSolar Leaf project london, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3822233</guid>
      <title>SpaceX lowers orbiting height for internet satellites</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Federal Communications Commission has allowed SpaceX to run 1,584 of its satellites at a lower altitude than previously approved going from 1,150 kilometers to 550 kilometers, despite fear of interference and collisions with other satellites operating at the same altitude.According to a statement released by the FCC, they have also allowed the company to reduce the number of satellites in its home broadband constellation from 4,425 to 4,409.SpaceX's satellite internet network project, Starlink, plans on deploying thousands of satellites that will connect with one million ground stations on Earth, providing internet access worldwide.According to the FCC, permitting these changes make it easier for SpaceX to deliver internet services in remote areas more quickly and efficiently. Half of the satellites are expected to be launched by 2024 and the official rollout of all satellites is expected in three to five years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SpaceX Starlink satellites connected around Earth2. SpaceX authorized to lower the number of its satellites3. SpaceX lowers orbiting height for internet satellites4. SpaceX Satellites connecting to remote areas; roll out date VOICEOVER (in English): "SpaceX's satellite internet network project, Starlink, plans on deploying thousands of satellites that will connect with one million ground stations on Earth, providing internet access worldwide.""According to a statement released by the Federal Communications Commission, SpaceX has received authorization to reduce the number of satellites in its home broadband constellation from 4,425 to 4,409.""The FCC also allowed the company to run 1,584 of its satellites at a lower altitude than previously approved going from 1,150 kilometers to 550 kilometers, despite fear of interference and collisions with other satellites operating at the same altitude. ""According to the FCC, permitting these changes make it easier for SpaceX to deliver internet services in remote areas more quickly and efficiently. Half of the satellites are expected to be launched by 2024 and the official rollout of all satellites is expected in three to five years."SOURCES: Federal Communications Commissionhttps://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DA-19-342A1.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 06:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/02/3822233/3822233_5BBEC8C0FC814C90B9300889B853BDE0_190502_3822233_SpaceX_lowers_orbiting_height_for_internet_satel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  spacex, starlink, internet, starlink internet, starling spacex, elon musk starlink, satellite internet network, FCC]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3823234</guid>
      <title>Jawbone discovery sheds light on mysterious Denisovan race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe discovery of a jawbone in the Tibetan plateau reveals new details about a race of ancient humans.According to a study published in Nature, a jaw fossil with two unusually large teeth was found in Baishya Karst Cave in Xiahe, China by a local monk in 1980.Recent analysis of proteins extracted from one of the molars indicates that the fossil is 160,000 years old, and belongs to a hominin population known as the Denisovans.This race of humans were first discovered in 2010 by researchers from the Max Planck Institute for Evolutionary Anthropology via a finger bone from Russia's Denisova Cave.The New York Times reports that based on their DNA, the Denisovans shared a common ancestor with the Neanderthals some 400,000 years ago, later interbreeding with them and with modern humans. Traces of their DNA are found in present-day Asians, Australians, and Melanesians.The fossil discovery suggests Denisovans had adapted to living in the low oxygen, high-altitude environment of the Tibetan plateau, which sits at an elevation of 10,760 feet.According to the Institute of Tibetan research, this genetic adaptation was likely passed on to modern Himlayan populations, who were found to have a Denisovan gene that allows them to cope with thin air.According to the New York Times, the jawbone is the first Denisovan fossil found outside Denisova Cave, and supports the theory that the species once lived across central and east Asia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Jawbone fossil in Tibetan cave is 160,000 years old, belongs to Denisovans2. Denisovans share common ancestor with Neanderthals; Denisovan DNA in present-day Asians, Australians, Melanesians3. Denisovans adapted to low oxygen, high altitude environment; gene passed to modern Himalayan populations4. Denisovans may have lived across central and east AsiaVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in Nature, a jaw fossil with two unusually large teeth was found in Baishya Karst Cave in Xiahe, China by a local monk in 1980.""Recent analysis of proteins extracted from one of the molars indicates that the fossil is 160,000 years old, and belongs to a hominin population known as the Denisovans.""The New York Times reports that based on their DNA, the Denisovans shared a common ancestor with the Neanderthals some 400,000 years ago, later interbreeding with them and with modern humans.""Traces of their DNA are found in present-day Asians, Australians, and Melanesians.""The fossil discovery suggests Denisovans had adapted to living in the low oxygen, high-altitude environment of the Tibetan plateau, which sits at an elevation of 10,760 feet.""According to the Institute of Tibetan research, this genetic adaptation was likely passed on to modern Himlayan populations, who were found to have a Denisovan gene that allows them to cope with thin air.""According to the New York Times, the jawbone is the first Denisovan fossil found outside Denisova Cave, and supports the theory that the species once lived across central and east Asia."SOURCES: Max Planck Institute for Evolutionary Anthropology, Nature, New York Times, National Geographic, The Guardianhttps://www.mpg.de/13386452/first-hominins-on-the-tibetan-plateau-were-denisovanshttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1139-xhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/01/science/denisovans-tibet-jawbone-dna.htmlhttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/05/mysterious-ancient-human-denisovan-found-roof-world/https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/may/01/denisovan-jawbone-discovered-in-tibetan-cave***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/04/3823234/3823234_57A4276424A54BB7AA958A053BA4115F_190504_3823234_Jawbone_discovery_sheds_light_on_mysterious_Deni_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, denisovan, denisovans, denisovan fossil, denisovan jawbone, ancient humans, hominin, ancient human species, tibetan cave, tibetan plateau]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3823110</guid>
      <title>'Biodegradable' plastic bags are not breaking down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from the University of Plymouth found that some biodegradable bags do not break down even after three years of natural exposure.According to the study published in the journal Environmental Science and Technology, scientists compared five different types of bags: two kinds of oxo-biodegradable bags, a biodegradable bag, a compostable bag, and a normal plastic bag.The team exposed the bags to air, water, and soil for extended periods of time to test  their rate of degradation.Results showed that after three years of exposure to soil, the biodegradable, oxo-biodegradable and normal plastic bags could still be used to carry things without breaking apart.The compostable bag broke down completely in water within three months but was still present in soil after 27 months of exposure.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Types of bags tested in the study2. All bags are exposed to air, wind, and soil3. Exposure does not affect Biodegradable, oxo-biodegradable and normal plastic bags4. Compostable bag breaks down in water but is still present in soil VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the University of Plymouth found that some biodegradable bags do not break down even after three years of natural exposure.""According to the study published in the journal Environmental Science and Technology, they compared five different types of bags: two kinds of oxo-biodegradable bags, a biodegradable bag, a compostable bag, and a normal plastic bag.""The team exposed the bags to air, wind, and soil for extended periods of time to test  their rate of degradation.""Results showed that after three years of exposure to soil, the biodegradable, oxo-biodegradable and normal plastic bags could still be used to carry things without breaking apart.""The compostable bag broke down completely in water within three months but was still present in soil after 27 months of exposure."SOURCES: EurekAlert, Environmental Science and Technologyhttps://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-04/uop-bbc042519.phphttps://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.est.8b06984***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 13:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/03/3823110/3823110_EED2A413FE5E4BEA82FBA2E9D710C386_190503_3823110__Biodegradable__plastic_bags_are_not_breaking_do_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, biodegradable bags, biodegradable, compostable bags, compostable materials, environment, pollution, marine pollution, biodegradable plastics, biodegradable plastic, biodegration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3822963</guid>
      <title>British navy to get a new laser weapon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANe Dragonfire Laser Directed Energy Weapon is currently being developed for use on Royal Navy ships, according to a news release from the British government.Dragonfire would have a power rating of 50 kW, according to UK Defence Journal. A spokesperson from the British military explained the technology was inspired by the Williams F1 team.The laser uses the Flywheel Energy Storage System or FESS to store rotational energy created from the ship. The system would then use stored energy to fire the laser. It can also generate high-power electrical pulses.According to the UK Defence Journal, the laser would be able to aim targets on land or in maritime environments. Dragonfire would also be able to provide very-short range air defence capability, and counter unmanned aerial vehicles.The laser was tested in the United States and in the United Kingdom while using a virtual ship power system.The laser will be installed on British ships by the mid-2020's, UK defence journal reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Dragonfire laser weapon2. Power rating of the laser3. The laser's Flywheel Energy Storage System 4. Where the laser would be able to aimVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a press release from British Defence, the Dragonfire Laser Directed Energy Weapon is currently being developed for use on Royal Navy ships.""Dragonfire would have a power rating of 50 kW, according to UK Defence Journal.""The laser uses the Flywheel Energy Storage System or FESS to store rotational energy created from the ship. The system would then use stored energy to fire the laser.""It can also generate high-power electrical pulses.""According to the UK Defence Journal, the laser would be able to aim targets on land or in maritime environments.""Dragonfire would also be able to provide very-short range air defence capability, and counter unmanned aerial vehicles."SOURCES: Gov.uk, Institution of Mechanical Engineers, UK Defense Journal, https://www.gov.uk/government/news/uk-usa-test-naval-power-systemshttps://www.imeche.org/news/news-article/navy-s-new-dragonfire-laser-weapon-get-energy-boost-from-formula-one-flywheelhttps://ukdefencejournal.org.uk/dragonfire-new-british-laser-weapon/https://ukdefencejournal.org.uk/dragonfire-guide-new-british-laser-weapon/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 09:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/03/3822963/3822963_14096EEA7CB44D558E8DC3039344CE0C_190503_3822963_British_navy_to_get_a_new_laser_weapon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, united kingdom, military, navy, dragon fire laser weapon, Dragonfire Laser Directed Energy Weapon, flywheel energy storage system, FESS, UK Dragonfire, UK Armed Forces]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3822924</guid>
      <title>Spinning black hole blasts wobbly plasma jets as it warps space and time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers have discovered unusually rapid jets of plasma spewing from an extraordinary black hole in space.According to research published in the journal Nature, the V404 Cygni binary system located 7,800 light years from Earth contains a black hole that feeds on a nearby star, with the material siphoned circling the hole in the form of an accretion disc.Some of the particles that fall into the black hole escape via jets of plasma called relativistic jets that shoot from its poles.But while most jets shoot straight out, the jets of the V404 Cygni black hole shoot out rapidly in different directions and at different times.According to Einstein's theory of general relativity, a spinning black hole's gravitational field pulls space and time around with it  an effect called frame-dragging.In V404 Cygni, the black hole and disc are misaligned, causing the frame-dragging effect to warp the doughnut-shaped inner ring. This in turn causes it to wobble like a spinning top and fire jets out in different directions.Researchers from the International Centre for Radio Astronomy Research say that since the black hole was moving so fast, the usual radio telescopes that rely on long exposure for imaging became useless. Instead, the team produced 103 individual images each roughly 70 seconds long, that they then joined together into a movie.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. V404 Cygni black hole siphoning material off its companion star2. Black hole's relativistic jets shooting out rapidly in different directions3. Spinning black hole's gravitational force pulls space and time around with it4. Misalignment with black hole causing inner disc to wobble and fire jets in different directionsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to research published in the journal Nature, the V404 Cygni binary system located 7,800 light years from Earth contains a black hole that feeds on a nearby star, with the material siphoned circling the hole in the form of an accretion disc.""Some of the particles that fall into the black hole escape via jets of plasma called relativistic jets that shoot from its poles.""But while most jets shoot straight out, the jets of the V404 Cygni black hole shoot out rapidly in different directions and at different times." "According to Einstein's theory of general relativity, a spinning black hole's gravitational field pulls space and time around with it  an effect called frame-dragging.""In V404 Cygni, the black hole and disc are misaligned, causing the frame-dragging effect to warp the doughnut-shaped inner ring. This in turn causes it to wobble like a spinning top and fire jets out in different directions."SOURCES: International Centre for Radio Astronomy Research, Naturehttps://www.icrar.org/Cygnihttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1152-0***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 08:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/03/3822924/3822924_39E1B9BEDC964E17AD40CC93258052C3_190503_3822924_Spinning_black_hole_blasts_wobbly_plasma_jets_as_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, black hole, V404 Cygni, spinning black hole, black hole wobbly jets, wobbly jets, relativistic jets, frame dragging, einstein, albert einstein, theory of relativity, warping space, warping space and time]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3822765</guid>
      <title>Drone used to deliver transplant kidney for the first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have successfully used an unmanned drone system to deliver a donor kidney, according to a University of Maryland news release.The drone was able to fly a kidney about 4.5 kilometers from a location in southwest Baltimore to surgical team at the medical center of the University of Maryland.The kidney was kept in a cargo compartment which was sealed while in the air. It is called HOMAL or Human Organ Monitoring and Quality Assurance Apparatus for Long-Distance Travel.The cargo box was able to maintain its own temperature while being able to track the altitude and GPS coordinates. This data was transmitted in real-time to the surgical team's smartphones.This was so that the doctors could make sure the kidney was still viable, as organs tend to become less and less healthier as soon as they are removed from a donor, according to the New York Times. The newspaper reports the kidney was then successfully transplanted onto a 44-year-old woman named Trina Glipsy in Baltimore.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Drone and kidney2. Drone flying in the sky3. The cargo compartment where the kidney was kept4. Description of what the carbox was able to do and how the data was being transmittedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a University of Maryland news release, researchers have successfully used an unmanned drone system to deliver a donor kidney.""The drone was able to fly a kidney about 4.5 kilometers from a location in southwest Baltimore to surgical team at the medical center of the University of Maryland.""The kidney was kept in a cargo compartment which was sealed while in the air." "It is called HOMAL or Human Organ Monitoring and Quality Assurance Apparatus for Long-Distance Travel.""The cargo box was able to maintain its own temperature while being able to track the altitude and GPS coordinates.""This data was transmitted in real-time to the surgical team's smartphones."SOURCES: University of Maryland, The New York Times, New Atlas, https://eng.umd.edu/news/story/pioneering-breakthrough-unmanned-aircraft-delivers-organ-for-successful-kidney-transplant-in-marylandhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/30/health/drone-delivers-kidney.htmlhttps://newatlas.com/drone-kidney-transplant/59508/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 04:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/03/3822765/3822765_5143DF5262684BFAB46983B7E9C201EC_190503_3822765_Drone_used_to_deliver_transplant_kidney_for_the__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, drone delivery, technology, medical advances, kidney, drone-delivered kidney, transporting organs, organ transplant, multicopter drone, organ deliveries]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3824542</guid>
      <title>Violence intensifies amid tensions between Israel and Gaza</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPalestinian and Israeli forces clashed on Sunday over a sniper who wounded two Israeli soldiers, The New York Times reports.Violence quickly escalated, with both sides launching rockets and missiles at each other. The Israeli army says Gaza launched 600 projectiles over a period of two days.Israel used its Iron Dome anti-missile batteries to shoot down incoming projectiles from Gaza, according to the New York Times.Israel's military also used jets, drones, tanks and attack helicopters to evade incoming attacks from Gaza.According to CNN, four people in Israel were killed by rockets from Gaza. As many as 23 Gazans have been reported to be killed by Israeli strikes, Haaretz reports. Health officials in Gaza as saying tDhat two pregnant women, two infants and a 12-year-old boy had also been killed in the attack, CNN reports.Officials in Gaza claim both of the infants died as a result of an Israeli air strike. Israel claims one of the infants died due to a misfired rocket.A Palestinian official told Reuters an Egyptian-mediated ceasefire agreement had been reached between both sides to end the violence on Monday, May 6.This is one of the worst conflicts between the two sides since 2014, according to The New York Times.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Palestinian flag and Israeli flag, and a sniper targeting two Israeli soldiers 2. Gaza on a map and projectiles being launched3. The Iron Dome anti-missile batteries and an Israeli military jet, drone tank and attack helicopter4. Number of deaths in Israel and PalestineVOICEOVER (in English): "The New York Times reports Palestinian and Israeli forces clashed on Sunday over a sniper who wounded two Israeli soldiers." "This quickly escalated, with both sides launching rockets and missiles at each other.""The Israeli army says Gaza launched 600 projectiles over a period of two days.""According to the New York Times, Israel used its Iron Dome anti-missile batteries to shoot down incoming projectiles from Gaza.""Israel's military also used jets, drones, tanks and attack helicopters to evade incoming attacks from Gaza.""According to CNN, four people in Israel were killed by rockets from Gaza.""Haaretz reports as many as 23 Gazans have been reported to be killed by Israeli strikes.""CNN reports health officials in Gaza as saying that two pregnant women, two infants and a 12-year-old boy had also been killed in the attack."SOURCES: The Jerusalem Post, The Guardian, The New York Times, CNN, Reutershttps://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Cabinet-directs-IDF-to-continue-attacks-and-prepare-for-Gaza-escalation-588868https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/05/gaza-militants-and-israeli-forces-lurch-into-new-round-of-violencehttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/05/world/middleeast/gaza-rockets-israel-palestinians.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/05/middleeast/israel-airstrikes-gaza-rockets-intl/index.html?no-st=1557110487https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-palestinians-truce/palestinians-say-gaza-ceasefire-reached-with-israel-idUSKCN1SC02H***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 13:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/06/3824542/3824542_DAC586E30A2B450084370C550AB88BC5_190506_3824542_Violence_intensifies_amid_tensions_between_Israe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, israel, jerusalem, palestine, gaza, airstrikes, rockets, Iron Dome anti-missile batteries, israel news, israel rockets, israel gaza, Iron Dome, Israel Iron Dome, israel palestine conflict, israel gaza news, israel gaza conflict]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3824330</guid>
      <title>Indian spacecraft will attempt to land on the moon in September</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Indian space agency plans to launch the Chandrayaan-2 spacecraft between July 6 to 19 as it will attempt to land on the moon on September 6.According to a press release by the Indian Space Research Organization, the spacecraft will comprise a lander, a rover and an orbiter.The rover will be housed within the lander.Once Chandrayaan-2 gets within 100 km of the moon's orbit, the lander will separate from the orbiter and will attempt to land on the moon's surface.The lander will have a soft landing at a site close to the moon's south pole, the Times of India reports.The rover will then be able to move around semi-autonomously. It will analyze the moon's surface and send back data to earth.However, the orbiter will continue revolving around the moon and scanning it to collect scientific information.According to the Times of India, the country had previously launched its lunar mission Chandrayaan-1 in 2008.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The spacecraft being launched and the moon2. What the spacecraft will be comprised of3. The lander separating from the orbiter and landing on the moon's surface4. The rover analyzing the lunar surface and the orbiter revolving around the moonVOICEOVER (in English): "The Indian space agency plans to launch the Chandrayaan-2 spacecraft between July 6 to 19 as it will attempt to land on the moon on September 6.""According to a press release by the Indian Space Research Organization, the spacecraft will comprise a lander, a rover and an orbiter.""The rover will be housed within the lander.""Once Chandrayaan-2 gets within 100 km of the moon's orbit, the lander will separate from the orbiter and will attempt to land on the moon's surface.""The Times of India reports the lander will have a soft landing at a site close to the moon's south pole.""The rover will then be able to move around semi-autonomously. It will analyze the moon's surface and send back data to earth.""However, the orbiter will continue revolving around the moon and scanning it to collect scientific information."SOURCES: The Times of India, NDTV,  Indian Space Research Organization, https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/india-likely-to-land-on-moon-on-september-6/articleshow/69136567.cmshttps://www.ndtv.com/science/indias-second-visit-to-moon-likely-to-begin-in-july-says-space-agency-2031557https://www.isro.gov.in/gslv-mk-iii-chandrayaan-2-mission***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 08:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/06/3824330/3824330_5481C6687CFD432BB30FF0C9AA3228DD_190506_3824330_Indian_spacecraft_will_attempt_to_land_on_the_mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space, space exploration, india, moon, Chandrayaan-2 , Chandrayaan-2  spacecraft, Chandrayaan-2 mission, Chandrayaan-2 lunar mission, moon mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3824288</guid>
      <title>FDA approves the first vaccine for dengue virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. authorities have approved a controversial vaccine that prevents dengue, but it comes with important restrictions. Dengue is a viral disease carried by female mosquitoes of the species Aedes aegypti, which can also carry diseases such as chikungunya, yellow fever, and Zika. According to the World Health Organization, roughly half of the world is at risk of contracting dengue, for which there is no specific treatment.According to Stat News, last Wednesday, the Food and Drug Administration authorized the distribution of Dengvaxia, a vaccine manufactured by French pharmaceutical company, Sanofi Pasteur.The decision has sparked controversy since the vaccine was pulled from the Philippines in 2017 due to safety issues. However, the FDA has announced clear restrictions for its use in the US.Stat News reports that it can only be used in patients ages 9 through 16 that have already had one previous dengue infection, and are living in areas of the US where the virus is endemic. The virus is only present in Puerto Rico and other offshore regions in the US.The European Commission approved the use of Dengvaxia in dengue-endemic regions late last year. In Europe, the vaccine can only be applied to patients ages 9 to 45 who have had the disease at least once before. Dengvaxia is also available in 10 countries in Asia and Latin America.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Visualization of aedes aegypti and the diseases it carries2. FDA approves Dengvaxia3. Restrictions applied to the use of the vaccine in the US4. Restrictions applied to the use of the vaccine in EuropeVOICEOVER (in English): "Dengue is a viral disease carried by female mosquitoes of the species Aedes aegypti, which can also carry diseases such as chikungunya, yellow fever, and Zika."  "According to the World Health Organization, roughly half of the world is at risk of contracting dengue, for which there is no specific treatment.""According to Stat News, last Wednesday, the Food and Drug Administration authorized the distribution of Dengvaxia, a vaccine manufactured by French pharmaceutical company, Sanofi Pasteur.""The decision has sparked controversy since the vaccine was pulled from the Philippines in 2017 due to safety issues. However, the FDA has announced clear restrictions for its use in the US.""Stat News reports that it can only be used in patients ages 9 through 16 that have already had one previous dengue infection, and are living in areas of the US where the virus is endemic. The virus is only present in Puerto Rico and other offshore regions in the US.""The European Commission approved the use of Dengvaxia in dengue-endemic regions late last year. In Europe, the vaccine can only be applied to patients ages 9 to 45 who have had the disease at least once before. Dengvaxia is also available in 10 countries in Asia and Latin America."SOURCES: World Health Organization, Stat News, BioSpacehttps://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dengue-and-severe-denguehttps://www.statnews.com/2019/05/01/fda-dengue-vaccine-restrictions/https://www.statnews.com/2017/11/30/dengue-vaccine-worsen-disease-sanofi/https://www.biospace.com/article/fda-approves-sanofi-s-dengue-fever-vaccine-with-restrictions/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 07:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/06/3824288/3824288_05492C7C80FC477280B5C56145989C73_190506_3824288_FDA_approves_the_first_vaccine_for_dengue_virus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dengue, dengvaxia, dengue vaccine, dengue fever, dengue virus, dengue virus life cycle, dengue virus infection, dengue fever treatment, dengue fever symptoms, FDA, Food and Drug Administration, Sanofi Pasteur, Sanofi]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3824190</guid>
      <title>China uses mobile app to track Muslims in Xinjiang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has been watching residents of the Muslim-majority Xinjiang province on an unprecedented scale, according to a Human Rights Watch report.The report claims Chinese authorities are using a mobile app to track and store personal data on individuals from China's Xinjiang province.It claims the software can store data such as a person's height, weight and even the color of their car by linking it to the their national identification number.The New York-based group said they discovered this after they reverse engineered the Chinese software.The Integrated Joint Operations Platform or IJOP is said to gather data about a person's movements via their smartphones and other GPS devices. It can collect this information from various checkpoints in Xinjiang, but also places such as gas stations and schools.The app also labels a person as "suspicious" if they use Virtual Private Networks and apps such as Whatsapp and Viber  both of which are currently blocked in China.According to the report, the app would target and monitor "36 person types." These would include individuals who rarely use their front door, use an unusual amount of electricity and those go on Hajj without state authorization.The app can also observe and alert authorities on what it considers to be "unusual" activities.It would also target those who have suddenly returned from abroad as well as those who have "enthusiastically" collected money and materials for a mosque.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mobile app to track Chinese Uighurs2. How the app collects information 3. Types of individual the app would target4. More types of people the app would targetVOICEOVER (in English): "The Human Rights Watch report claims Chinese authorities are using a mobile app to track and store personal data on individuals from China's Xinjiang province.""The report claims the software can store data such as a person's height, weight and even the color of their car by linking it to the their national identification number.""The Integrated Joint Operations Platform or IJOP is said to gather data about a person's movements via their smartphones and other GPS devices." "It can collect this information from various checkpoints in Xinjiang, but also places such as gas stations and schools.""According to the report, the app would target and monitor '36 person types.'""These would include individuals who rarely use their front door, use an unusual amount of electricity and those go on Hajj without state authorization.""The app can also observe and alert authorities on what it considers to be 'unusual' activities.""It would also target those who have suddenly returned from abroad as well as those who have 'enthusiastically' collected money and materials for a mosque."SOURCES:  Bloomberg, Al Jazeera, Human Rights Watch, BBC News, The Washington Post,  https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-01/alibaba-backed-face-scans-show-big-tech-ties-to-china-s-xinjianghttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/05/hrw-china-mobile-app-surveillance-uighurs-190502031404525.htmlhttps://www.hrw.org/report/2019/05/01/chinas-algorithms-repression/reverse-engineering-xinjiang-police-mass-surveillancehttps://www.hrw.org/news/2019/05/01/interview-chinas-big-brother-apphttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-48130048https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/chinese-database-is-tracking-cellphone-usage-car-location-and-even-electricity-usage-of-xinjiang-residents/2019/05/01/12eb3996-6c8a-11e9-be3a-33217240a539_story.html?noredirect=on&utm_term=.6a3efffb1155***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 03:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/06/3824190/3824190_C9796359282341C39E2ADFBC2CD13612_190506_3824190_China_uses_mobile_app_to_track_Muslims_in_Xinjia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, uyghur, uighur, xinjiang, uyghur crackdown, china surveillance, minorities, Muslim minorities, ethnic minorities, China, China human rights, chinese surveillance, xinjiang surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3825139</guid>
      <title>US deploys carrier and bombers in response to threats from Iran</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUS National Security Advisor John Bolton says the US has sent an aircraft carrier to the Middle East as a warning to Iran, according to the BBC.The US is deploying the USS Abraham Lincoln Carrier Strike Group and a bomber task force to the region, Reuters reports.The carrier strike group consists of the Abraham Lincoln, an aircraft carrier, the USS leyte Gulf, a Ticonderoga-class guided missile cruiser, US Navy Carrier Air Wing Seven, and destroyer vessels from Destroyer Squadron Two, NBC News reports.According to NPR, the task force would also consist of land-based bombers.Citing an unidentified US official, CNN reports that threats were made against US maritime and ground based forces in the Middle East.Reuters cites Bolton as saying that any attack on US interests or US allies will be met with quote "unrelenting force."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. US flag, Map of Middle East in the background and the aircraft carrier in the foreground2. What the US plans to deploy to the Middle East3. What the Carrier strike group consists of 4. US flag, Iran flag, Middle east on a globeVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, US National Security Advisor John Bolton says the US has sent an aircraft carrier to the Middle East as a warning to Iran.""Reuters reports the US is deploying the USS Abraham Lincoln Carrier Strike Group and a bomber task force to the region.""NBC News reports the carrier strike group consists of the Abraham Lincoln, an aircraft carrier, the USS leyte Gulf, a Ticonderoga-class guided missile cruiser, US Navy Carrier Air Wing Seven, and destroyer vessels from Destroyer Squadron Two.""According to NPR, the task force would also consist of land-based bombers.""Citing an unidentified US official, CNN reports that threats were made against US maritime and ground based forces in the Middle East.""Reuters cites Bolton as saying that any attack on US interests or US allies will be met with quote 'unrelenting force.'"SOURCES:BBC News, Al Jazeera, The Guardian,Reuters, CNN, NBC News, NPRhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-48173357https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/05/carrier-middle-east-credible-iran-threat-pentagon-190506194124855.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/06/us-deploys-aircraft-carrier-and-bombers-after-troubling-indications-from-iranhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran/u-s-deploying-carrier-bombers-to-middle-east-in-warning-to-iran-bolton-idUSKCN1SC01Bhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/05/politics/iran-carrier-bomber-task-force/index.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/02/politics/us-iran-oil-waivers/index.htmlhttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/u-s-sending-carrier-strike-group-send-message-iran-n1002196https://www.npr.org/2019/05/06/720800641/u-s-to-deploy-carrier-and-bomber-task-force-after-concerns-about-iran-threat***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/07/3825139/3825139_6A1C34B59E55481EBA8288681048EC22_190507_3825139_US_deploys_carrier_and_bombers_in_response_to_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, iran, tehran, USA, aircraft carrier, bomber task force, Strait of Hormuz, USS Abraham Lincoln Carrier Strike Group, Middle East, US warns Iran, Iranian Regime]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3825045</guid>
      <title>China planning to expand military presence in Arctic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn annual report on China's military status from the Pentagon shows Beijing has growing interests to expand its military influence in the Arctic.According to a report released by the U.S. Department of Defense, China's presence in the Arctic has continued to increase since it gained observer status on the Arctic Council in 2013. The report states that China has sent a Ukranian-built research icebreaker vessel called the Xuelong to map out the Arctic and has also proposed satellite research stations in Greenland, Iceland and Norway.The Pentagon warned that Beijing might deploy nuclear-armed submarines as it's simultaneously growing its submarine fleet.The report details that China currently has four nuclear-powered ballistic missile submarines, six nuclear-powered attack submarines, and 50 diesel powered attack submarines.The Pentagon predicts that by 2020 the fleet could increase to up to 65 to 70 submarines. According to the report, Beijing is also planning on building a new advanced guided-missile nuclear attack submarine Type 093B that the Pentagon claims could help China carry out more covert land-attacks.China's growing interest in the Arctic could also be due to its interest in creating a trade route in the Arctic called the 'Northern Sea Route', connecting Shanghai to Northern Europe as part of its One Belt, One Road Initiative.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China research icebreaker mapping the Arctic 2. Type of submarines China currently has3. Type of submarine China is building4. Visualization of possible Northern Sea RouteVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report released by the U.S. Department of Defense, China's presence in the Arctic has continued to increase since it gained observer status on the Arctic Council in 2013." "The report states that China has sent a Ukranian-built research icebreaker vessel called the Xuelong to map out the Arctic and has also proposed satellite research stations in Greenland, Iceland and Norway.""The Pentagon warned that Beijing might deploy nuclear-armed submarines as it's simultaneously growing its submarine fleet.""The report details that China currently has four nuclear-powered ballistic missile submarines, six nuclear-powered attack submarines, and 50 diesel powered attack submarines.""The Pentagon predicts that by 2020 the fleet could increase to up to 65 to 70 submarines. According to the report, Beijing is also planning on building a new advanced guided-missile nuclear attack submarine Type 093B that the Pentagon claims could help China carry out more covert land-attacks.""China's growing interest in the Arctic could also be due to its interest in creating a trade route in the Arctic called the 'Northern Sea Route', connecting Shanghai to Northern Europe as part of its One Belt, One Road Initiative."SOURCES: Reuters, Department of Defensehttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-military-arctic/pentagon-warns-on-risk-of-chinese-submarines-in-arctic-idUSKCN1S829H\https://media.defense.gov/2019/May/02/2002127082/-1/-1/1/2019%20CHINA%20MILITARY%20POWER%20REPORT%20(1).PDF***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 11:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/07/3825045/3825045_D8288C5F49974D6FA8A670022AE38DBC_190507_3825045_China_planning_to_expand_military_presence_in_Ar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, china military, china us, us military, arctic, one belt one road, china submarines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3824821</guid>
      <title>Heavy metals found scattered throughout our solar system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPrecious elements such as gold, uranium, and platinum are found in our solar system due to a clash that took place between two neutron stars 4.6 billion years ago, according to a new study published in the journal Nature.When two neutron stars clash together, powerful gravitational waves are formed, creating enough energy for these heavy metals to be forged.Scientists tested out this theory by analyzing the isotopic decay of ancient meteorites that had fallen to Earth. This was then compared to a numerical simulation of our solar system.The researchers believe that the collision occurred around 100 million years before Earth was formed.This celestial phenomenon is said to have enriched our planet with up to 0.3 percent of its heaviest elements present today, according to a University of Florida news release.Imre Bartos, a researcher involved with the study, said he believes that the study could provide an insight into the origin and composition of our solar system.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Heavy metals found in the solar system2. Two neutron stars clashing3. Ancient meteorite being analyzed and the numerical simulation of the solar system4. Earth and a pie chartVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the journal Nature, precious elements such as gold, uranium, and platinum are found in our solar system due to a clash that took place between two neutron stars 4.6 billion years ago.""When two neutron stars clash together, powerful gravitational waves are formed, creating enough energy for these heavy metals to be forged.""Scientists tested out this theory by analyzing the isotopic decay of ancient meteorites that had fallen to Earth.""This was then compared to a numerical simulation of our solar system.""According to a University of Florida news release, this celestial phenomenon is said to have enriched our planet with up to 0.3 percent of its heaviest elements present today."SOURCES: New Atlas, Nature, University of Florida https://newatlas.com/neutron-star-collision-heavy-elements/59542/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1113-7https://news.ufl.edu/2019/04/neutron-star-merger-explains-actinide-abundance-/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 06:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/07/3824821/3824821_413CDA5D5B2F4372A62A0CD0BB46A0C7_190507_3824821_Heavy_metals_found_scattered_throughout_our_sola_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, solar system, neutron stars, neutron stars colliding, neutron stars collision, stars, heavy elements, gold, uranium, solar system, galaxy universe, science, milky way, planets]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3825494</guid>
      <title>Luke Perry buried in eco-friendly mushroom burial suit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLuke Perry's daughter Sophie recently revealed that her late father chose an alternative form of internment, in the form of a biodegradable mushroom suit.According to the BBC, human bodies contain toxic pollutants such as lead and mercury that are released into the environment during decomposition and cremation.The mushroom suit, or infinity burial suit, developed by Jae Rhim Lee of green burial company Coeio claims to neutralize these pollutants.The suit, made of organic cotton, contains biomix made from mushrooms and other microorganisms that aids decomposition, cleans toxins in the body and soil, and delivers nutrients to plants.According to the Coeio website, mushrooms break down material by emitting enzymes, and are able to eliminate both organic toxins and heavy metals in the environment through a process called mycoremediation.Coeio's suit requires no special preparations. The body is simply dressed in it, and then buried at an optimal depth of 4 feet, with or without a casket.The mushroom suit costs $1,500, which the company says is far less than traditional burial options that can run up to $6,000. Coeio also has a version of the suit for pets.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Human bodies releasing toxic pollutants during decomposition and cremation2. Benefits of mushroom suit with built-in biomix3. Mushrooms emit enzymes to break down material, remove toxins4. How body is buried in the suitVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the BBC, human bodies contain toxic pollutants such as lead and mercury that are released into the environment during decomposition and cremation.""The mushroom suit, or infinity burial suit, developed by Jae Rhim Lee of green burial company Coeio claims to neutralize these pollutants.""The suit, made of organic cotton, contains biomix made from mushrooms and other microorganisms that aids decomposition, cleans toxins in the body and soil, and delivers nutrients to plants.""According to the Coeio website, mushrooms break down material by emitting enzymes, and are able to eliminate both organic toxins and heavy metals in the environment through a process called mycoremediation.""Coeio's suit requires no special preparations. The body is simply dressed in it, and then buried at an optimal depth of 4 feet, with or without a casket."SOURCES: Coeio, BBChttp://coeio.com/https://www.bbc.com/news/48140812***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 08:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/08/3825494/3825494_76C67CB6675742C5BB51D19895FB442C_190508_3825494_Luke_Perry_buried_in_eco_friendly_mushroom_buria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Luke Perry, mushroom suit, mushroom burial suit, luke perry, infinity burial suit, eco friendly burial, eco friendly death, biodegradable mushroom suit, coeio, alternative burial, mycoremediation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3825486</guid>
      <title>Shooting at Colorado school leaves 1 dead and 7 injured</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTwo male students opened fire at a science and technology school in suburban Denver last Tuesday, killing one person and injuring seven others, Reuters reports.Two individuals, one adult, and an underage student, entered a STEM School in Highlands Ranch, Denver armed with at least one handgun and attacked their classmates last Tuesday afternoon.According to authorities, the two individuals opened fire at two different locations in the school before 2 p.m.During a press briefing, Douglas County Sheriff, Tony Spurlock, stated that authorities arrived at the school within two minutes of the first report and struggled with the suspects before apprehending them.According to authorities, the shooting left one 18-year-old student dead and 7 others injured. The youngest victim was15 years old.The Highlands Ranch incident occurred not far from Columbine Highschool and just weeks after the 20th anniversary of the deadly high school shooting.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. School location; armed suspects enter school2. Students open fire in different classrooms3. Authorities arrive at school and arrest suspects4. Victims of the shootingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, two individuals, one adult, and an underage student, entered a STEM School in Highlands Ranch, Denver armed with at least one handgun and attacked their classmates last Tuesday afternoon.""According to authorities, the two individuals opened fire at two different locations in the school before 2 p.m.""During a press briefing, Douglas County Sheriff, Tony Spurlock, stated that authorities arrived at the school within two minutes of the first report and struggled with the suspects before apprehending them.""According to authorities, the shooting left one 18-year-old student dead and 7 others injured. The youngest victim is 15 years old. "SOURCES: Reuters, CNNhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-colorado-shooting-idUSKCN1SD2H2https://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/07/us/colorado-denver-area-school-shooting/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 08:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/08/3825486/3825486_C051C00A446F4851BD0DB85345269ABC_190508_3825486_Shooting_at_Colorado_school_leaves_1_dead_and_7__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, colorado school, colorado school shooting, colorado highlands ranch, stem school, law enforcement, school shooting, colorado]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3825413</guid>
      <title>Scientists find brain region activated by Pokemon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThere is a region of the brain that tends to retain animated characters such as Pokemon rather than other visual information, according to a study published in the journal Nature.The researchers conducted their study on a group of adults who had extensive experience playing with Pokemon on Gameboy devices as kids.The eleven adults were considered "experienced" as they had began playing Pokemon between the ages of five and eight and were able to name all 150 characters.According to a Stanford University press release, the participants went through an MRI scanner and were shown images of Pokemon characters while the researchers observed how their brains responded.Researchers found that the participants' visual cortex, located at the bottom of the temporal lobe, was stimulated by looking at the different animated characters, according to a Penn Today news release.The images stimulated the same areas of the brain in all study participants.Michael Barnett, a researcher involved with the study, explained that the brain is capable of developing a specialized area for recognizing stimuli such as Pokemon due to continued exposure to the animated characters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Male medical body, brain and an inset of Pikachu2. Male medical body and a gameboy3. A participant going through an MRI scan and a brain4. The part of the brain that was stimulated, Pikachu and a fire PokemonVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the journal Nature, there is a region of the brain that tends to retain animated characters such as Pokemon rather than other visual information.""The researchers conducted their study on a group of adults who had extensive experience playing with Pokemon on Gameboy devices as kids.""According to a Stanford University press release, the participants went through an MRI scanner and were shown images of Pokemon characters while the researchers observed how their brains responded.""According to a Penn Today news release, researchers found that the participants' visual cortex, located at the bottom of the temporal lobe, was stimulated by looking at the different animated characters.""The images stimulated the same areas of the brain in all study participants."SOURCES: Engadget, Stanford news release, Penn Today, Medical Xpress, https://www.engadget.com/2019/05/06/stanford-university-pokemon-brain-development/https://news.stanford.edu/2019/05/06/regular-pokemon-players-pikachu-brain/https://penntoday.upenn.edu/news/pokemon-activates-unique-part-brain-offering-insights-its-structurehttps://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-05-brain-region-pokemon-characters.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 06:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/08/3825413/3825413_C755831AD61F411D94534634E545E5AF_190508_3825413_Scientists_find_brain_region_activated_by_Pokemo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  science, brain scan, pokemon, brain region, Pokemon region in the brain, pokemon science, rewiring brain, occipitotemporal sulcus, developing brain regions, Pikachu, Wobbuffet, Bulbasaur]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3826293</guid>
      <title>'Algae bioreactor' sent to the ISS to generate food and oxygen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA bioreactor that runs on algae has been sent to the International Space Station to convert carbon dioxide into oxygen and to generate food, according to a press release by the German Aerospace Center.The Photobioreactor contains an algae species called Chlorella vulgaris[c][d], which uses photosynthesis to produce oxygen.The press release says the freshwater algae could create an edible biomass that would be high in protein content. It could one day replace around 30 percent of an astronaut's current meals.The reactor will also create fresh air for the space station for around six months and will be supported by the Advanced Closed-Loop System, which is currently used to recycle carbon dioxide into oxygen for astronauts in the space station.Thebioreactor could one day help support astronauts on long missions in base stations on the Moon or on planets such as Mars, according to the German Aerospace Center. It would make it possible for less food and equipment to be carried onto future space missions.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the Photobioreactor functions2. The algae species used within the Photobioreactor 3. Edible biomass, astronaut meal and a pie chart4. The Photobioreactor inside the ISS"According to a press release by the German Aerospace Center, a Photobioreactor has been sent to the International Space Station to convert carbon dioxide into oxygen and to generate food.""The Photobioreactor contains an algae species called Chlorella vulgaris[e][f], which uses photosynthesis to produce oxygen.""The press release says the freshwater algae could create an edible biomass that would be high in protein content.""It could one day replace around 30 percent of an astronaut's current meals.""The reactor will also create fresh air for the space station for around six months and will be supported by the Advanced Closed-Loop System, which is currently used to recycle carbon dioxide into oxygen for astronauts in the space station."SOURCES: Space.com, German Aerospace Center, European Space Agency https://www.space.com/space-station-algae-experiment-fresh-air.htmlhttps://www.dlr.de/dlr/presse/en/desktopdefault.aspx/tabid-10172/213_read-33413/year-all/#/gallery/34129https://www.esa.int/Our_Activities/Human_and_Robotic_Exploration/Research/Advanced_Closed_Loop_System***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 13:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/09/3826293/3826293_481F57D25A1948D7A6F947106442B521_190509_3826293__Algae_bioreactor__sent_to_the_ISS_to_generate_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space, international space station, bioreactor, algae-powered bioreactor, Photobioreactor, Advanced Closed-Loop System]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3826259</guid>
      <title>How does the NBA draft lottery work?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe 2019 NBA Draft Lottery will be held on May 14, but how does the process actually work? According the NBC Sports Chicago, the 14 NBA teams that did not qualify for the postseason make up the eligible Lottery pool. A thousand possible Lottery combinations are divided among those 14 teams based on regular season records.  This is how the drawing works. There are 14 ping pong balls numbered 1 to 14. Those balls are dropped into a glass drum and mixed for 20 seconds. At that point, four balls are drawn for the first pick in 10-second intervals. This process will then be repeated to select picks two, three and four. According to NBC Sports Chicago, the remaining 10 draft picks are then slotted to the remaining 10 teams in reverse standing order. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the 14 teams are selected and Lottery combinations divided up2. Ping pong balls and NBA Draft Lottery machine 3. How the first four picks are drawn4. NBA Draft Lottery machineVOICEOVER (in English): "How does the NBA Draft Lottery process work? According the NBC Sports Chicago, the 14 NBA teams that did not qualify for the postseason make up the eligible Lottery pool." "A thousand possible Lottery combinations are divided among those 14 teams based on regular season records."  "This is how the drawing works. There are 14 ping pong balls numbered 1 to 14. Those balls are dropped into a glass drum and mixed for 20 seconds." "At that point, four balls are drawn for the first pick in 10-second intervals." "This process will then be repeated to select picks two, three and four.""According to NBC Sports Chicago, the remaining 10 draft picks are then slotted to the remaining 10 teams in reverse standing order." SOURCES: NBC Sports Chicago, Bleacher Reporthttps://sports.yahoo.com/does-nba-draft-lottery-process-151225864.htmlhttps://bleacherreport.com/articles/2774679-nba-draft-lottery-rules-how-the-process-works***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 12:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/09/3826259/3826259_A3C5BA31A31C489C9B9CEF36FCBB76BB_190509_3826259_How_does_the_NBA_draft_lottery_work__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NBA, NBA Draft, NBA Draft Lottery, NBA Draft Lottery explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3826010</guid>
      <title>EPA claims toxic chemical in Roundup doesn't cause cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe EPA continues to back the use of glyphosate in Roundup, even after it has been identified as a carcinogenic.The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has approved the use of glyphosate in the herbicide Roundup.Their endorsement comes despite findings by the World Health Organization's International Agency for Research on Cancer that claim glyphosate is "probably carcinogenic to humans."According to the National Pesticide Information Center, glyphosate is a non-selective herbicide first introduced in 1974 by Monsanto. Glyphosate blocks protein production of an enzyme in certain plants, preventing them from growing.According to National Geographic, Roundup is the second most widely used herbicide in the US. It can be used in farms, gardens, and weeds in urban areas.Humans can be exposed to glyphosate if herbicides comes in contact with their skin and eyes or by breathing it in during spraying.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. EPA approves the use of glyphosate; glyphosate found to be carcinogenic2. How glyphosate works3. Where Roundup can be used4. How humans can be exposed to glyphosateVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has approved the use of glyphosate in the herbicide Roundup.""Their endorsement comes despite findings by the World Health Organization's International Agency for Research on Cancer that claim glyphosate is 'probably carcinogenic to humans.'""According to the National Pesticide Information Center, glyphosate is a non-selective herbicide first introduced in 1974 by Monsanto. Glyphosate blocks protein production of an enzyme in certain plants, preventing them from growing."" According to National Geographic, Roundup is the second most widely used herbicide in the US. It can be used in farms, gardens, and weeds in urban areas.""Humans can be exposed to glyphosate if herbicides comes in contact with their skin and eyes or by breathing it in during spraying."SOURCES: Inhabitat, National Pesticide Information Center, National Geographichttps://inhabitat.com/epa-backs-the-use-of-toxic-herbicide-chemical-glyphosate/http://npic.orst.edu/factsheets/glyphogen.htmlhttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2015/04/150422-glyphosate-roundup-herbicide-weeds/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 06:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/09/3826010/3826010_4FBE40ECD09A459E850FA8B5DEDC9EEC_190509_3826010_EPA_claims_toxic_chemical_in_Roundup_doesn_t_cau_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, glyphosate, roundup,  Environmental Protection Agency, epa, carcinogen, pesticide, herbicide, weed killer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3826859</guid>
      <title>Blue Origin unveils its new moon lander</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAmazon founder Jeff Bezos' private aerospace company Blue Origin unveiled its new moon lander called the Blue Moon on Thursday May 9, The Guardian reports.The unmanned vehicle would be capable of carrying upto 6.5 metric tons of payload onto the surface of the moon.According to Blue Origin's website, the lander has been in development for years. It would carry supplies needed to lay out the infrastructure for future space missions. According to Blue origin, Blue Moon would use descent sensors in order to land.The lander would use fuel cells for longer missions and also to last through the night on the moon. The spacecraft's fuel cells are capable of using only hydrogen and oxygen to generate electricity.According to CNet, Bezos said a larger version of the lander would be able to take Americans to the moon by 2024.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Blue Origin Logo and the Blue Moon2. How much the vehicle can carry3. The lander in space and the spacecraft landing on the moon4. How the lander will generate electricityVOICEOVER (in English): "Amazon founder Jeff Bezos' private aerospace company Blue Origin unveiled its new moon lander called the Blue Moon on Thursday May 9.""The Guardian reports the unmanned vehicle would be capable of carrying upto 6.5 metric tons of payload onto the surface of the moon.""According to Blue Origin's website, the lander has been in development for years. It would carry supplies needed to lay out the infrastructure for future space missions.""According to Blue Origin's website, Blue Moon would use descent sensors in order to land.""The lander would use fuel cells for longer missions and also to last through the night on the moon.""The spacecraft's fuel cells are capable of using only hydrogen and oxygen to generate electricity."SOURCES: Blue Origin, The Verge, The Guardian, CNet, https://www.blueorigin.com/blue-moonhttps://www.theverge.com/2019/5/9/18550258/blue-origin-moon-lunar-lander-jeff-bezos-spacehttps://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/may/09/blue-origin-jeff-bezos-moon-announcementhttps://www.cnet.com/news/jeff-bezos-unveils-blue-moon-lunar-lander-plans-for-huge-space-colonies/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 12:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/10/3826859/3826859_0DF9A003331B42058854F43CAE51AA1F_190510_3826859_Blue_Origin_unveils_its_new_moon_lander_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space, space travel, Blue Origin, Jeff Bezos, moon lander, blue origin moon lander, Blue Moon, Blue Origin Blue Moon, lunar lander]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3826848</guid>
      <title>Google's Sidewalk Labs faces legal challenges in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoogle's Sidewalk Labs is facing controversy over its plans to build a high-tech neighborhood in Canada.Sidewalk Labs won a bid in 2017 to turn a 12-acre patch of industrial landscape in Quayside, Toronto into a smart neighborhood, BBC News reports.The company is collaborating with Waterfront Toronto to transform the neighborhood's waterfront area into a mini metropolis.According to Sidewalk Labs' website, the neighborhood would consist of a next-generation transit system that would include buses and rails to improve street safety. The area will include housing and real estate that would have flexible designs that enable multi-purpose usage.It would also include sustainable design and infrastructure to reduce landfill waste and carbon emissions.The futuristic neighborhood would use open digital infrastructure that would collect data on traffic, noise and air quality, according to the BBC. This has raised questions about what exactly the data is being gathered for.The company told the BBC that the sensors wouldn't be used for monitoring purposes and would instead allow governments to be flexible on how they want the sensors to be used in the neighborhood.According to the BBC, privacy advocates are concerned the project will increase surveillance and outsource government responsibilities to a private corporation.Privacy advocates and digital rights activists in Toronto urged the government to stop the redevelopment of the area due to privacy concerns and a lack of transparency from the U.S. based company, reported The Star.The Canadian Civil Liberties Association has now filed a lawsuit against Waterfront Toronto, the municipal, provincial and federal governments, BBC News reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Transformation of the neighborhood2. Transportation system the smart neighborhood would have3. Housing in the neighborhood4. Sustainable infrastructure in the neighborhoodVOICEOVER (in English): "BBC News reports Sidewalk Labs won a bid in 2017 to turn a 12-acre patch of industrial landscape in Quayside, Toronto into a smart neighborhood.""The company is collaborating with Waterfront Toronto to transform the neighborhood's waterfront area into a mini metropolis.""According to Sidewalk Labs' website, the neighborhood would consist of a next-generation transit system that would include buses and rails to improve street safety.""The area will include housing and real estate that would have flexible designs that enable multi-purpose usage.""It would also include sustainable design and infrastructure to reduce landfill waste and carbon emissions."SOURCES: BBC News, The Star, Sidewalk Labs, Engadget,  https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-47956760https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-41414872https://www.thestar.com/news/gta/2019/04/02/toronto-group-wants-google-sister-company-removed-from-quayside-project.htmlhttps://www.sidewalklabs.com/https://sidewalktoronto.ca/https://www.engadget.com/2019/04/05/sidewalk-labs-toronto-midp/https://www.engadget.com/2019/02/15/alphabet-sidewalk-labs-toronto-tax-revenue/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 11:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/10/3826848/3826848_5138CFFB3D6D44499F1BE64128237215_190510_3826848_Google_s_Sidewalk_Labs_faces_legal_challenges_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, google, alphabet inc, Sidewalk Labs, sidewalk labs toronto, sidewalk labs smart city, google sidewalk labs, smart city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3828016</guid>
      <title>U.S. military devloeps knife bombs to minimize civilian casualties</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA report by the Wall Street Journal gives details of a missile developed by U.S. intelligence designed to attack targets while reducing civilian casualties.According to a report by the Wall Street Journal, the Central Intelligence Agency and U.S. Department of Defense have developed a missile called Hellfire R9X, designed to carry out precision strikes while minimizing collateral damage.The Hellfire R9X missile carries a payload of over 100 pounds of metal and six blades that spread before impact instead of an explosive warhead.Other Hellfire models carry explosives and can injure or kill any individual within its blast radius.The Journal reports that the Hellfire R9X has been used roughly six times in different attacks in Libya, Syria, Iraq, Yemen, and Somalia.The R9X was also used on Feb 26, 2017, where it targeted and killed al-Qaeda deputy leader Abu Al-Khayr al-Masri during an attack in Syria. Photographs show the roof of al-Masri's car with a hole in its roof and a broken windshield, but no severe collateral damage in the surrounding area.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Visualization of Hellfire R9X2. Comparison of Hellfire R9X and conventional Hellfire missiles3. Countries where Hellfire R9X has been used4. Hellfire R9X missile hits al-Qaeda deputy leader Abu Al-Khayr al-Masri VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report by the Wall Street Journal, the Central Intelligence Agency and U.S. Department of Defense have developed a missile called Hellfire R9X, designed to carry out precision strikes while minimizing collateral damage.""The Hellfire R9X missile carries a payload of over 100 pounds of metal and six blades that spread before impact instead of an explosive warhead.""Other Hellfire models carry explosives and can injure or kill any individual within its blast radius.""The Journal reports that the Hellfire R9X has been used roughly six times in different attacks in Libya, Syria, Iraq, Yemen, and Somalia.""The R9X was also used on Feb 26, 2017, where it targeted and killed al-Qaeda deputy leader Abu Al-Khayr al-Masri during an attack in Syria. Photographs show the roof of al-Masri's car with a hole in its roof and a broken windshield but no severe collateral damage in the surrounding area."SOURCES: The Wall Street Journal, Ars Technicahttps://www.wsj.com/articles/secret-u-s-missile-aims-to-kill-only-terrorists-not-nearby-civilians-11557403411https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2019/05/dod-cia-developed-flying-ginsu-missile-to-take-out-single-targets/?amp=1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/13/3828016/3828016_B3D73D671F1544EBA19815DA642D6E20_190513_3828016_U_S__military_devloeps_knife_bombs_to_minimize_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Hellfire R9X, hellfire missile, Central Intelligence Agency, terrorist attack, missile, missile attack, us military, us missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3827945</guid>
      <title>An explainer on the bubonic plague</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA couple in Mongolia contracted the deadly plague after consuming some raw rodent meat, The Guardian reports.The couple had apparently eaten raw marmot meat and were thought to have developed the pneumonic plague from that.The bubonic plague is usually spread from animals to humans by fleas, BBC News reports.  According to NPR, the plague is caused by the bacterium Yersinia pestis which lives in infected animals, such as rodents.Mongolian authorities have warned residents against consuming raw marmot meat because it carries this bacterium, The Guardian reports.The plague causes bleeding and infected sores on a person. If left untreated, it can kill a person in a number of days. The disease can turn septicemic or pneumonic once the bacteria has spread to the lungs. The pneumonic plague can spread from person to person via droplets in the air.Symptoms of bubonic plague include fever, headache, swollen lymph nodes, vomiting and joint pain, while symptoms of pneumonic plague include fever, headaches, cough, chest pain and muscle weakness. If diagnosed early, the disease can be treated with antibiotics such as streptomycin and tetracycline, according to the World Health Organization.The Mongolian government declared a quarantine for six days in the region starting on May 1 to prevent the spread of the deadly plague, BBC News reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. How the bubonic plague is spread2. Bacterium that causes the plague3. The plague causing bleeding and open, infected sores4. What happens when the disease spread to the lungs and how it could be spread5. Symptoms of bubonic plague and symptoms of pneumonic plague6. How the plague could be treatedVOICEOVER (in English): "BBC News reports the bubonic plague is usually spread from animals to humans by fleas.""According to NPR, the plague is caused by the bacterium Yersinia pestis which lives in infected animals, such as rodents.""The plague causes bleeding and infected sores on a person. If left untreated, it can kill a person in a number of days.""The disease can turn septicemic or pneumonic once the bacteria has spread to the lungs." "The pneumonic plague can spread from person to person via droplets in the air.""Symptoms of bubonic plague include fever, headache, swollen lymph nodes, vomiting and joint pain, while symptoms of pneumonic plague include fever, headaches, cough, chest pain and muscle weakness." "If diagnosed early, the disease can be treated with antibiotics such as streptomycin and tetracycline, according to the World Health Organization."SOURCES: The BBC,  NPR, Euronews, The Guardian, World Health Organizationhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-48182646https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2019/05/07/721167330/bubonic-plague-strikes-in-mongolia-why-is-it-still-a-threathttps://www.euronews.com/2019/05/07/european-tourists-quarantined-in-mongolia-after-two-die-of-bubonic-plaguehttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/06/mongolian-couple-die-of-bubonic-plague-after-eating-marmothttps://www.who.int/csr/disease/plague/en/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 06:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/13/3827945/3827945_0763C1E33AE94EDF9AACD8935859810A_190513_3827945_An_explainer_on_the_bubonic_plague_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, bubonic plague, black death, disease, mongolia, mongolia bubonic plague, bubonic plague symptoms, plague bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3828845</guid>
      <title>Study finds shrinking moon may be causing powerful quakes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNewly-published research has found evidence that the moon is shrinking and may still be tectonically active.In a new study published in Nature Geoscience, researchers analyzed data from seismometers placed on the moon during the Apollo missions. They found 28 recorded moonquakes between 1969 to 1977 that ranged from magnitude two to five on the Richter scale.According to NASA, the moon contracts and shrinks as its interior cools, forming geological formations called thrust faults when sections of the brittle crust are forced up over neighboring parts.Eight of the 28 epicenters were found to be within 30 kilometers of these faults.Analysis also found that six of the quakes happened when the moon was at apogee. This is the farthest point from the Earth in its orbit, and the period when our planet's gravity inflicts additional stress.Scientists believe it's likely that the stress build up as the lunar crust is compressed by global contraction and tidal forces, causes the faults to slip and produce the quakes. Other evidence of recent tectonic activity on the moon include tracks on the lunar surface from landslides or dislodged boulders that have not yet been erased by micrometeoroid activity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Apollo-era instruments recording seismic activity on the lunar surface2. Moon shrinks as interior cools, forming thrust faults; eight quakes happened in close proximity to faults3. Six quakes occurred when moon was at apogee and subject to additional stress from Earth's gravity4. Global contraction and tidal forces causes fault to slip and produce quakesVOICEOVER (in English): "In a new study published in Nature Geoscience, researchers analyzed data from seismometers placed on the moon during the Apollo missions. They found 28 recorded moonquakes between 1969 to 1977 that ranged from magnitude two to five on the Richter scale.""According to NASA, the moon shrinks as its interior cools, forming geological formations called thrust faults when sections of the brittle crust are forced up over neighboring parts.""Eight of the 28 epicenters were found to be within 30 kilometers of these faults.""Analysis also found that six of the quakes happened when the moon was at apogee. This is the farthest point from the Earth in its orbit, and the period when our planet's gravity inflicts additional stress." "Scientists believe it's likely that the stress build up as the lunar crust is compressed by global contraction and tidal forces, causes the faults to slip and produce the quakes." SOURCES: NASA, Nature Geosciencehttps://www.nasa.gov/press-release/goddard/2019/moonquakeshttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41561-019-0362-2***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 18:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/15/3828845/3828845_5E86F20D6D5E467E9360E1FE5BDB1D0C_190515_3828845_Study_finds_shrinking_moon_may_be_causing_powerf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, moonquakes, shrinking moon, moon, Apollo missions, seismometer, lunar seismometer, seismic activity, thrust faults, scarps, moon scarp]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3828577</guid>
      <title>China to fund Sri Lankan mega project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBeijing is providing a US$1.4 billion loan to Sri Lanka for their Port City Colombo project, The South China Morning Post reports.This project aims to develop a metropolis from land reclaimed from the sea. According to The South China Morning Post, the Chinese loan would be the largest foreign investment in Sri Lankan history. The project is said to be part of China's Belt and Road Initiative, whereby China invests large amounts of money into a country in order to develop its infrastructure.According to the China Daily, a total of 269 hectares of land reclamation was completed in January. The basic infrastructure for the project is expected to be completed in 15 months.Plans for the city include skyscrapers, hospitals, hotels and theme parks. The port city would be turned into a major financial hub that may one day rival Singapore and Dubai, according to Chinese state media. Chinese authorities claim the project would create 83,000 jobs and attract upto US$13 billion worth of investments to develop the city.Beijing has already lent Colombo over US$8 billion dollars to fund other ambitious projects such as airports, ports, railways and more, The South China Morning Post reports. In December 2017, Sri Lanka had to hand over the Hambantota Port and 15,000 acres of land surrounding the area to China for 99 years as the country was unable to pay back a loan.Smruti Pattanaik, from the Institute for Defence Studies and Analyses in New Delhi, was quoted by the South Morning China Post as saying that, "The lure of belt and road money is hard to resist for developing nations as it provides something they are [badly] in need of  funding for infrastructure."  Adding that the Chinese funding comes at a cost.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China and Sri Lanka icon, money icon going into Sri Lanka, the new Port City Colombo2. China's Belt and Road initiative3. Land being reclaimed4. What would be included into the new Port City5. Tall buildings in the Port city and the flag of Singapore and the UAEVOICEOVER (in English): "Beijing is providing a US$1.4 billion loan to Sri Lanka for their Port City Colombo project. This aims to develop a metropolis from land reclaimed from the sea.""According to The South China Morning Post, the Chinese loan would be the largest foreign investment in Sri Lankan history.""The project is said to be part of China's Belt and Road Initiative, whereby China invests large amounts of money into a country in order to develop its infrastructure.""According to the China Daily, a total of 269 hectares of land reclamation was completed in January. The basic infrastructure for the project is expected to be completed in 15 months.""Plans for the city include skyscrapers, hospitals, hotels and theme parks.""According to Chinese state media, the port city would be turned into a major financial hub that may one day rival Singapore and Dubai."SOURCES:  The South China Morning Post,CNN, Port City Colombo, China Daily, https://www.scmp.com/week-asia/geopolitics/article/3009731/next-hambantota-welcome-chinese-funded-us14-billion-port-cityhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3007175/sri-lanka-rejects-fears-chinas-debt-trap-diplomacy-belt-andhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/04/26/asia/belt-and-road-summit-beijing-intl/index.htmlhttp://www.portcitycolombo.lk/http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/201904/28/WS5cc502fea3104842260b8d43.html ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/14/3828577/3828577_2F9651398C9844429C5D2618DBC611B8_190514_3828577_China_to_fund_Sri_Lankan_mega_project_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, port city, china sri lanka port, china sri lanka port city project, china sri lanka relations, china sri lanka hambantota,hambantota port china,  hambantota port sri lanka, hambantota port china sri lanka]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3828557</guid>
      <title>Japan will start testing the world's fastest bullet train</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan will begin testing the world's fastest Shinkansen bullet-train which is capable of reaching speeds of up to 400 kilometers per hour.According to Bloomberg, Japanese rail company JR East will begin testing its fastest bullet train called Alfa-X this Friday between the cities of Aomori and Sendai over the next three years.Alfa-X stands for "Advanced Labs for Frontline Activity in rail eXperimentation." It has ten passenger cars and an elongated nose at the front measuring 22 meters.The train will operate three types of brakes: standard brakes, airbrakes on its roof and magnetic plates at the rails.Dampers and air suspension systems will help the train stabilize on curves. JR East plans on letting the Alpha-X run at 360 kilometers per hour, that is 10 kilometers per hour faster than China's Fuxing Hao train which is capable of reaching the same top speeds.The Alfa-X is scheduled to go into service in 2030.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.  Alfa-X test routes2.  Alfa-X passenger car and nose length3.  Alfa-X brake types4.  Alfa-X curve stabilization; Comparison to China's Fuxing Hao train VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Bloomberg, Japanese rail company JR East will begin testing its fastest bullet train called Alfa-X this Friday between the cities of Aomori and Sendai over the next three years.""Alfa-X stands for 'Advanced Labs for Frontline Activity in rail eXperimentation.' It has ten passenger cars and an elongated nose at the front measuring 22 meters.""The train will operate three types of brakes: standard brakes, airbrakes on its roof and magnetic plates at the rails.""Dampers and air suspension systems will help the train stabilize on curves. JR East plans on letting the Alpha-X run at 360 kilometers per hour, that is 10 kilometers per hour SOURCES: Bloomberg, CNNhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-10/world-s-fastest-bullet-train-starts-high-speed-tests-in-japanhttps://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/japan-fastest-bullet-train-alfax-scli-intl/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/14/3828557/3828557_83FDFD0790654110A0F2240DF57C36C7_190514_3828557_Japan_will_start_testing_the_world_s_fastest_bul_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, alfa x, japan bullet train, tokyo bullet train, Shinkansen, Advanced Labs for Frontline Activity in rail eXperimentation, japan trains, japan train, bullet train]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3828300</guid>
      <title>Chinese surgeons use brain implants to treat drug addiction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese surgeons are using deep brain stimulation or DBS to treat methamphetamine addiction in its first ever clinical trial, according to the Associated Press.The technique involves a device being surgically implanted onto the brain. This wouldstimulate targeted areas of the brain in an attempt to stop drug addiction.The surgeon drilled two holes through the patient's skull and placed two electrodes at the nucleus accumbens. This part of the brain is believed to be connected with addiction.Next, the man had a battery pack implanted on his chest to power the brain device. After two days, the doctor switched on the DBS devices to activate the electrodes.According to the Associated Press, there are risks to the surgery. These include  seizures, infection or potential death via a brain hemorrhage.Critics believe that human experiments like this are at a premature stage and don't address biological, social and psychological factors that cause a person to become addicted in the first place.There is also concern around issues regarding participants' informed consent in places such as China, The Associated Press reports.Speaking to the Associated Press, investigators from similar U.S. based studies explained their attempts at trials for treating alcoholism were stopped. This was because study design and preliminary results didn't justify the risk.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of China, deep brain stimulation device and methamphetamine 2. The device being put into the brain3. The process of implanting the device inside the brain during surgery4. The risks of the brain implant surgeryVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Associated Press, Chinese surgeons are using deep brain stimulation or DBS to treat methamphetamine addiction in its first ever clinical trial.""The technique involves a device being surgically implanted onto the brain. This wouldstimulate targeted areas of the brain in an attempt to stop drug addiction.""The surgeon drilled two holes through the patient's skull and placed two electrodes at the nucleus accumbens.  This part of the brain is believed to be connected with addiction.""Next, the man had a battery pack implanted on his chest to power the brain device. After two days, the doctor switched on the DBS devices to activate the electrodes.""According to the Associated Press, there are risks to the surgery. These include  seizures, infection or potential death via a brain hemorrhage."SOURCES: The Associated Press, The Washington Post, Live Science, The South China Morning Post,   https://www.apnews.com/fd2226d9e7bf46ca8d2542bdf88c26behttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/chinese-researchers-try-brain-implants-to-treat-drug-addicts/2019/05/07/7fd1496a-713f-11e9-9331-30bc5836f48e_story.html?utm_term=.692f9af5285ehttps://www.livescience.com/65453-brain-implant-drug-addiction-treatment.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/video/china/3009773/chinese-researchers-test-brain-implants-help-drug-addicts***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/14/3828300/3828300_EC62A4FA2C2A4847A7454593296D7B23_190514_3828300_Chinese_surgeons_use_brain_implants_to_treat_dru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, deep brain stimulation, brain, brain implants, DBS device, methamphetamine, methamphetamine addiction, brain surgery, DBS brain surgery, dbs deep brain stimulation surgery, clinical trials DBS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3829194</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia oil pipeline attacked by armed drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn oil pipeline in Saudi Arabia was targeted by drones amid heightened tensions in the gulf.According to Gulf News, Saudi Arabia's energy minister said that explosive-laden drones attacked two oil pumping stations for the East-West oil pipeline.The Associated Press reports that the two stations are located in al-Duadmi and Afif, several hundred kilometers west of Riyadh.Government-controlled oil company Saudi Aramco temporarily shut down the pipeline as a precaution, and contained a fire that caused minor damage to one pumping station. Oil and gas supplies were not affected.According to AP, Saudi Arabia is currently at war with the Houthi rebels in Yemen, who claimed to have launched seven drones targeting vital Saudi installations. The Houthis later claimed responsibility for the pipeline attack.Saudi Arabia's 1200-kilometer East-West pipeline was built in the 1980s and has a total capacity of 4.8 million barrels of oil a day, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration.It serves as an alternative channel for crude exports should the vital Strait of Hormuz be closed - something Iran has repeatedly threatened to do.The Tuesday attack occurred mere days after four oil tankers were damaged off the coast of the UAE port of Fujairah in what the Saudis describe as sabotage.Details of the alleged sabotage to the tankers - two of which are Saudi, one Norwegian, and one Emirati - remain unclear.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Armed drone attack on Saudi Arabia oil pumping stations2. Location of pumping stations; immediate aftermath of attack3. Houthi militia in Yemen claim responsibility for drone attack4. East-West oil pipeline as alternative to Strait of HormuzVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Gulf News, Saudi Arabia's energy minister said that explosive-laden drones attacked two oil pumping stations for the East-West oil pipeline.""The Associated Press reports that the two stations are located in al-Duadmi and Afif, several hundred kilometers west of Riyadh.""Government-controlled oil company Saudi Aramco temporarily shut down the pipeline as a precaution, and contained a fire that caused minor damage to one pumping station. Oil and gas supplies were not affected.""According to AP, Saudi Arabia is currently at war with the Houthi rebels in Yemen, who claimed to have launched seven drones targeting vital Saudi installations.""The Houthis later claimed responsibility for the pipeline attack.""Saudi Arabia's 1200-kilometer East-West pipeline was built in the 1980s and has a total capacity of 4.8 million barrels of oil a day, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration.""It serves as an alternative channel for crude exports should the vital Strait of Hormuz be closed - something Iran has repeatedly threatened to do."SOURCES: Associated Press, Gulf Newshttps://www.apnews.com/63d729241e0645539dad32f57de7bc95https://gulfnews.com/world/gulf/saudi/saudi-arabia-oil-stations-attacked-by-drones-1.63934993***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 09:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/15/3829194/3829194_BC913CBC3542408A833BBB61894FDB5C_190515_3829194_Saudi_Arabia_oil_pipeline_attacked_by_armed_dron_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, saudi oil, oil pipeline attack, drone attack, saudi oil pipeline, saudi vs iran, saudi vs houthis, strait of hormuz, east west pipeline, saudi aramco, houthis, houthi]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3830024</guid>
      <title>Trump targets Huawei in new ban on foreign telecom gear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Trump administration made a move to enable a ban on Huawei gear, amid an escalating trade war between the U.S. and China. According to the New York Times, President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Wednesday to ban U.S. telecom firms from using foreign-made equipment from sources that may pose a risk to national security.While no nation or company was singled out in the ban, the Commerce Department later added Huawei and its affiliates on a list of firms considered to be undermining American interests.The listing prevents Huawei from purchasing U.S. parts or technologies without the government's approval.According to CNN, U.S. officials have openly warned against using gear from Huawei and other Chinese companies, arguing that these tech products could allow China to spy on U.S. communications.Major mobile phone companies in America are largely unaffected as they don't use Huawei equipment, but the order may be costly for rural wireless carriers who do use Huawei as a cheaper alternative to European brands like Nokia or Ericsson.CNN reports that the executive order would apply to past purchases of telecom gear, though officials didn't say whether the government would help smaller carriers pay to remove or switch out their foreign gear. It is also unclear what the punishment would be for those who don't comply.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Trump signs order to ban telecom equipment from foreign sources deemed security threat2. Huawei added to list of firms that pose a risk to national security3. Officials warn of China using Huawei tech to spy on U.S. communications4. Ban costly for rural carriers who use Huawei as cheap alternative to European techVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the New York Times, President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Wednesday to ban U.S. telecom firms from using foreign-made equipment from sources that may pose a risk to national security.""While no nation or company was singled out in the ban, the Commerce Department later added Huawei and its affiliates on a list of firms considered to be undermining American interests.""The listing prevents Huawei from purchasing U.S. parts or technologies without the government's approval.""According to CNN, U.S. officials have openly warned against using gear from Huawei and other Chinese companies, arguing that these tech products could allow China to spy on U.S. communications.""Major mobile phone companies in America are largely unaffected as they don't use Huawei equipment, but the order may be costly for rural wireless carriers who do use Huawei as a cheaper alternative to European brands like Nokia or Ericsson."SOURCES: New York Times, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/15/business/huawei-ban-trump.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/15/tech/trump-executive-order-telecom-security/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/17/3830024/3830024_0EEC437ACCC9409BBEEC4C945FA8A488_190517_3830024_Trump_targets_Huawei_in_new_ban_on_foreign_telec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump ban, Huawei ban, foreign telecom gear, Huawei, Huawei equipment, China spying, Huawei 5g, Huawei spying, China, Trump, Donald Trump]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3829524</guid>
      <title>AI SpaceFactory wins NASA's Mars Habitat competition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAI SpaceFactory has won first place in NASA's 3D printed Habitat Challenge for its Mars habitat prototype, according to a  press release by the company.The 3D-printed structures were tested and evaluated on the mix of material used, leakage, durability and strength, according to a NASA news release.The pod-shaped habitat is called Marsha and was 3D-printed over the course of 30 hours. According to the company, the habitat would be made from materials such as biopolymer basalt composite, which can be extracted from Mars. This process would be enabled by In-situ resource utilization or ISRU, which would harvest the Red Planet's surface to collect the resources needed. The robotic 3D printers would then use the materials to print the Martian habitats.AI SpaceFactory explained on its website that Marsha utilizes a dual-shell system that would isolate the habitat from extreme weather temperature shifts on Mars.It would also include strategically placed windows that would allow natural light to enter the habitat while keeping out harmful solar and cosmic radiation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Mars Habitat2. The habitat being printed3. The process of building the habitat on Mars4. How the habitat would survive extreme weather conditions of MarsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a press release by AI SpaceFactory, the New York-based company has won first place in NASA's 3D printed Habitat Challenge for its Mars habitat prototype.""The pod-shaped habitat is called Marsha and was 3D-printed over the course of 30 hours.""According to the company, the habitat would be made from materials such as biopolymer basalt composite, which can be extracted from Mars.""This process would be enabled by In-situ resource utilization or ISRU, which would harvest the Red Planet's surface to collect the resources needed.""The robotic 3D printers would then use the materials to print the Martian habitats.""AI SpaceFactory explained on its website that Marsha utilizes a dual-shell system that would isolate the habitat from extreme weather temperature shifts on Mars.""It would also include strategically placed windows that would allow natural light to enter the habitat while keeping out harmful solar and cosmic radiation."SOURCES: AI Space Factory, NASA, Space.com, Popular Mechanics, https://www.aispacefactory.com/post/ai-spacefactory-wins-1st-place-prize-for-nasa-3d-printing-habitat-challengehttps://www.aispacefactory.com/marshahttps://www.nasa.gov/directorates/spacetech/centennial_challenges/3DPHab/19-017.htmlhttps://www.space.com/nasa-3d-printed-habitat-competition-winners.htmlhttps://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/infrastructure/a27432340/nasa-crowns-mars-habitat-competition-winner/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 02:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/16/3829524/3829524_1BB7A8A64FFF4E92A48251AA4329AC2D_190516_3829524_AI_SpaceFactory_wins_NASA_s_Mars_Habitat_competi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, mars, NASA, nasa mars habitat, nasa 3d printed mars habitat, space, space exploration, 3D printing, 3D printing NASA, 3D printing technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3830537</guid>
      <title>Bering Sea ice receding alarmingly: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Bering Sea's ice is vanishing, endangering surrounding indigenous communities, sealife and fisheries. However, scientists cannot pinpoint what is causing the ice to recede.According to a report by ScienceMag, the late winter sea ice of the Bering Sea is falling to some of the lowest levels in the past 40 years. The report states that around March every year, sea ice usually stretches out from the south of the Bering Sea and reaches the areas surrounding the Aleutian Islands. But in 2018 it only stretched as far as Alaska. The rapid ice loss could be due to changes in wind direction and water temperature. One of the explanations offered by ScienceMag is that climate change is altering the polar jet stream, bringing warmer winds to the Bering Sea and causing the ice to recede.   Oceanographer Seth Danielson told ScienceMag the ice loss could also be a result of rising temperatures in the Bering Sea. Data gathered in early 2018 shows the sea was 2 degrees warmer than usual. This increase in temperature delays ice formation by three weeks. The ice formation and high temperatures could have also been affected by low ice coverage in 2017, which might have allowed the sea ice to absorb more heat.The lack of sea ice in 2018 also affected local ecosystems and animal life. Populations of zooplankton, algae, fish, and seabirds have already been affected. These shifts in temperature could also affect American fisheries located in the southeastern Bering Sea. If the sea ice continues to recede, fish factories in the north could be too far from fishing grounds, making it more expensive to haul fish.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Geographic location of Bering Sea; Bering Sea ice receding2. Changes in wind direction and water temperature in the Bering Sea3. Temperature rise in the Bering Sea4. Ecosystem affected by rise in temperatureVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a report by ScienceMag, the late winter sea ice of the Bering Sea is falling to some of the lowest levels in the past 40 years." "The report states that around March every year, sea ice usually stretches out from the south of the Bering Sea and reaches the areas surrounding the Aleutian Islands. But in 2018 it only stretched as far as Alaska.""The rapid ice loss could be due to changes in wind direction and water temperature. One of the explanations offered by ScienceMag is that climate change is altering the polar jet stream, bringing warmer winds to the Bering Sea and causing the ice to recede."   "Oceanographer Seth Danielson told ScienceMag the ice loss could also be a result of rising temperatures in the Bering Sea. Data gathered in early 2018 shows the sea was 2 degrees Celsius warmer than usual. This increase in temperature delays ice formation by three weeks." "The ice formation and high temperatures could have also been affected by low ice coverage in 2017, which might have allowed the sea ice to absorb more heat.""The lack of sea ice in 2018 also affected local ecosystems and animal life. Populations of zooplankton, algae, fish, and seabirds have already been affected." SOURCES: ScienceMaghttps://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/05/vanishing-bering-sea-ice-threatens-one-richest-us-seafood-sources***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 12:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/17/3830537/3830537_56703AF122104A8A99C9BBCD4F42E494_190517_3830537_Bering_Sea_ice_receding_alarmingly__Report_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Bering Sea ice, Bering Sea, climate change, environment, sea ice,  Aleutian Islands, Alaska]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3830533</guid>
      <title>Jeff Bezos unveils space colony vision</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a press conference, Jeff Bezos envisions human colonies in outer space capable of holding up to 1 trillion people in rotating cylinders called O'Neill Cylinders.Bezos stated that the colonies would have high-speed transportation, farming land, urban areas, and recreational areas with zero gravity. He added that some areas of the colonies could be replicas of famous cities on Earth. He claims that these cylindrical colonies are better for sustaining human life outside of Earth as opposed to Martian or Lunar colonies due to how far and how small they are to Earth in comparison.  In order to cut costs, Bezos proposes transporting humans to and from the colonies in reusable spacecraft such as Blue Origin's New Shephard, a suborbital space vehicle powered using liquid nitrogen designed for space tourism.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. View of O'Neill cylinders from Earth 2. Dimensions of O'Neill cylinders3. Land areas inside O'Neill cylinders4. Areas inside the O'Neill cylinders5. Replicas of Earth cities inside the O'Neill cylinders6. Optimal weather inside the O'Neill cylinders7. Comparison in dimensions between Earth, Mars and the Moon8. Blue Origin's New Shephard taking  offVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a press conference, Jeff Bezos envisions human colonies in outer space capable of holding up to 1 trillion people in rotating cylinders called O'Neill Cylinders.""The O'Neill Cylinder was developed by Princeton physicist Gerard K. O'Neill in 1974. According to data from the National Space Society, the design is made up of two 20-mile-long cylinders, both measuring 4 miles in diameter.""The cylinders contain 3 land areas that cover a total of 500 square miles. They rotate in opposite directions, keeping the colonies aimed towards the sun.""Bezos stated that the colonies would have high-speed transportation, farming land, urban areas, and recreational areas with zero gravity."He added that some areas of the colonies could be replicas of famous cities on Earth." "The weather in these cylinders would be adjusted for optimal human comfort. According to Bezos, there would be no earthquakes, and no rain.""He claims that these cylindrical colonies are a better bet for sustaining human life outside of Earth as opposed to Martian or Lunar colonies due to how far and how small they are to Earth in comparison."  "In order to cut costs, Bezos proposes transporting humans to and from the colonies in reusable spacecrafts such as Blue Origin's New Shephard, a suborbital space vehicle powered using liquid nitrogen designed for space tourism."SOURCES: National Space Society, Blue Origin https://space.nss.org/o-neill-cylinder-space-settlement/https://www.blueorigin.com/news/going-to-space-to-benefit-earth-full-event-replay***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 12:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/17/3830533/3830533_57AE76BBA78D41D5B25C3281B4D0E56C_190517_3830533_Jeff_Bezos_unveils_space_colony_vision_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, blue origin, jeff bezos, amazon, oneill cylinder, blue moon, space colony]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3830304</guid>
      <title>New study detects Alzheimer's up to 30 years before symptoms appear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have identified a range of biomarkers that could determine if an individual develops Alzheimer's disease years in advance, according to a study published in the journal Frontiers in Aging Neuroscience.In a John Hopkins university press release, Laurent Younes, a researcher involved with the study, said that brain imaging and spinal fluid analysis could be used to examine the risk of Alzheimer's at least 10 years before symptoms appear.Scientists tested their studies on 290 participants over the age of 40. Those who were part of the study had at least one first degree relative with a form of Alzheimer's.Participants of the study were asked to conduct memory, learning, reading and attention tests annually from 1995 to 2013.The researchers found an increase of the tau protein present in the cerebrospinal fluid around 30 years before any symptoms of Alzheimer's appeared. Proteins such as amyloid beta and phosphorylated tau also started to appear around 10 to 15 years before the indications of Alzheimers began to manifest.Scientists also found a slight decrease in the size of the medial temporal lobe in the brain, three to nine years before any cognitive impairment was noticeable. This part of the brain is responsible for memory. By the end of the study, 81 participants had been diagnosed with mild cognitive impairment or Alzheimer's disease. The researchers plan to conduct further studies in five different research sites around the world to compare data, according to the study.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Blue medical body with its brain flashing red2. Insets of brain imaging and spinal fluid and a calendar3. A participant, first-degree relative and tests the participants had to conduct4. Illustrations of proteins found in the brain and the medial temporal lobe shrinkingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the journal Frontiers in Aging Neuroscience, researchers have identified a range of biomarkers that could determine if an individual develops Alzheimer's disease years in advance.""In a John Hopkins university press release, Laurent Younes, a researcher involved with the study, said that brain imaging and spinal fluid analysis could be used to examine the risk of Alzheimer's at least 10 years before symptoms appear.""Scientists tested their studies on 290 participants over the age of 40. Those who were part of the study had at least one first degree relative with a form of Alzheimer's.""Participants of the study were asked to conduct memory, learning, reading and attention tests annually from 1995 to 2013.""The researchers found an increase of the tau protein present in the cerebrospinal fluid around 30 years before any symptoms of Alzheimer's appeared.""Proteins such as amyloid beta and phosphorylated tau also started to appear around 10 to 15 years before the indications of Alzheimers began to manifest.""Scientists also found a slight decrease in the size of the medial temporal lobe in the brain, three to nine years before any cognitive impairment was noticeable. This part of the brain is responsible for memory."SOURCES: New Atlas, Frontiers in Aging Neuroscience, John Hopkins University Press release, Interesting Engineeringhttps://newatlas.com/alzheimers-dementia-biomarkers-early-diagnose/59704/https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fnagi.2019.00074/full#h1https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/newsroom/news-releases/brain-changes-linked-with-alzheimers-years-before-symptoms-appearhttps://interestingengineering.com/brain-changes-seen-decades-before-alzheimers-onset***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 08:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/17/3830304/3830304_D7D6DAA5DED94220A3B0F71712F73730_190517_3830304_New_study_detects_Alzheimer_s_up_to_30_years_bef_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Alzheimer's disease, alzheimer's disease biomarkers, dementia, mild cognitive impairment, cerebrospinal fluid, tau protein, amyloid beta, phosphorylated tau, biomarkers alzheimer's, alzheimer's biomarkers tau]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3830289</guid>
      <title>Dark matter may have punched holes in the Milky Way</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew evidence suggests something strange is punching holes in the Milky Way, but scientists aren't sure what it is.Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics researcher Ana Bonaca presented findings at the American Physical Society conference of a series of holes in GD-1, our galaxy's longest stellar stream.According to Physics, stellar streams like GD-1 are remnants of star clusters or dwarf galaxies that have been ensnared by our galaxy, and stretched out while being drawn into its orbit.Under normal conditions, the stream is a single line. But a high-resolution map of GD-1 created from Gaia observatory data revealed gaps in the stream, along with a spur  a thorn-like structure that had not been seen before.Bonaca and her colleagues believe something large plunged through the stream, but couldn't map it to any of the luminous objects they observed.They suspect the culprit to be a clump of dark matter, but need more evidence to support the theory, or to rule out other possibilities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Holes in GD-1 stellar stream2. Depiction of a stellar stream3. High-resolution map shows gaps and spur in GD-1 stream4. Large clump of dark matter may have caused the gaps in the streamVOICEOVER (in English): "Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics researcher Ana Bonaca presented findings at the American Physical Society conference of a series of holes in GD-1, our galaxy's longest stellar stream.""According to Physics, stellar streams like GD-1 are remnants of star clusters or dwarf galaxies that have been ensnared by our galaxy, and stretched out while being drawn into its orbit.""Under normal conditions, the stream is a single line. But a high-resolution map of GD-1 created from Gaia observatory data revealed gaps in the stream, along with a spur  a thorn-like structure that had not been seen before.""Bonaca and her colleagues believe something large plunged through the stream, but couldn't map it to any of the luminous objects they observed.""They suspect the culprit to be a clump of dark matter, but need more evidence to support the theory, or to rule out other possibilities."SOURCES: Ana Bonaca / Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysicshttps://absuploads.aps.org/presentation/upload/APR19/Q04/APR19-001602/presentation15143_rzrcxcjdlgef.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 07:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/17/3830289/3830289_70D2061013D440D89634A22397A7F143_190517_3830289_Dark_matter_may_have_punched_holes_in_the_Milky__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, dark matter, milky way, holes in milky way, space mysteries, stellar stream, dark impactor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3830097</guid>
      <title>Climate change causes trees to grow faster in China, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLarch trees in northeastern China were found to have grown faster in the past 40 years as a result of climate change, according to a study published in the Journal of Geophysical Research.Researchers looked at the trees' growth rings and found that trees older than 400 years have grown faster from 2005 to 2014 than in the previous 300 years. Trees between 250 and 300 years old grew around 35 percent more during the same period. The authors of the study explained that they believe that warmer soil temperatures may be causing the trees to grow rapidly. This is because roots start to expand and absorb more nutrients as the depth of the permafrost layer is lowered.A press release from Advancing Earth and Space Science, cites Xianliang Zhang, lead author of the study as saying that growth in old trees is unusual. Adding that it could be as a result of well-developed root systems present in the older trees that are able to absorb nutrients from the soil more efficiently.The researchers added that this may be good in the short term basis, but would be disastrous for forests in the long run. This is because permafrost underneath trees could degrade or no longer support trees as the climate becomes warmer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. OR Map and larch trees2. 400-year-old trees and a measurement bar 3. 250-300 year-old trees and a pie chart 4. What causes the trees to grow rapidly VOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the Journal of Geophysical Research, larch trees in northeastern China were found to have grown faster in the past 40 years as a result of climate change. ""Researchers looked at the trees' growth rings and found that trees older than 400 years have grown faster from 2005 to 2014 than in the previous 300 years.""Trees between 250 and 300 years old grew around 35 percent more during the same period.""The authors of the study explained that they believe that warmer soil temperatures may be causing the trees to grow rapidly.""This is because roots start to expand and absorb more nutrients as the depth of the permafrost layer is lowered."SOURCES: Interesting Engineering, Advancing Earth and Space Science, AGU Studyhttps://interestingengineering.com/climate-change-is-making-trees-grow-fasterhttps://news.agu.org/press-release/climate-change-is-giving-old-trees-a-growth-spurt/https://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1029/2018JG004882***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 02:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/17/3830097/3830097_1FA4E067800149E7BF36E81625621072_190517_3830097_Climate_change_causes_trees_to_grow_faster_in_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, climate change, China, trees, climate change, trees, climate change old trees, ecosystem, northeast china, Dahurian larch, forest ecosystems, trees and climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3831869</guid>
      <title>Manchester arena marks attack anniversary with memorial service</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe second anniversary of the Manchester terror incident will be marked by a private memorial service on May 22.The New York Times reports that Ariana Grande concert goers were leaving Manchester Arena on the night of May 22, 2017 when a blast rocked the venue.According to the publication, Islamic extremist Salman Abedi had stood in the foyer carrying a homemade TATP bomb inside a backpack. Evidence found at the scene shows the device was powered by a 12-volt, 2.1 amp lead acid battery, and packed with metal bolts and screws.The BBC reports that Abedi detonated the incendiary device at 10:31 p.m., killing himself and 22 people, and injuring over a hundred others.According to the Guardian, mobile phone footage recorded panic inside the auditorium immediately after the explosion, as people ran to the exits to try and get out.According to the BBC, 22-year-old Abedi is believed to have been taught bomb making while in Libya. He then returned to the U.K. days before the attack to construct his device.Abedi had been flagged for review as a subject of interest but wasn't under active investigation. The lack of monitoring or travel restrictions reportedly allowed him to return to Britain undetected.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bomb in foyer of Manchester Arena2. Salman Abedi carrying TATP bomb inside backpack3. Salman Abedi detonating bomb4. People trying to exit Manchester Arena5. Salman Abedi's family6. Salman Abedi taught bomb making in Libya7. Salman Abedi constructing explosive8. Salman Abedi flagged as subject of interest by MI5VOICEOVER (in English): "The New York Times reports that Ariana Grande concert goers were leaving Manchester Arena on the night of May 22, 2017 when a blast rocked the venue.""According to the publication, Islamic extremist Salman Abedi had stood in the foyer carrying a homemade TATP bomb inside a backpack.""Evidence found at the scene shows the device was powered by a 12-volt, 2.1 amp lead acid battery, and packed with metal bolts and screws.""The BBC reports that Abedi detonated the incendiary device at 10:31 p.m., killing himself and 22 people, and injuring over a hundred others.""According to the Guardian, mobile phone footage recorded panic inside the auditorium immediately after the explosion, as people ran to the exits to try and get out.""Salman Abedi had been born and raised in Manchester to Libyan refugee parents. He has three siblings, all born in England.""According to the BBC, 22-year-old Abedi is believed to have been taught bomb making while in Libya.""He then returned to the U.K. days before the attack to construct his device.""A report by parliamentary watchdog ISC criticized MI5 and counter terrorism police for missing chances to prevent the bombing.""Abedi had been flagged for review as a subject of interest but wasn't under active investigation. The lack of monitoring or travel restrictions reportedly allowed him to return to Britain undetected."SOURCES: New York Times, BBC, The Guardian, ISChttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/05/23/world/europe/what-happened-at-the-manchester-arena-explosion.htmlhttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/05/24/world/europe/manchester-arena-bomb-materials-photos.html?_r=1https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-43554555https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-manchester-48072588?intlink_from_url=https://www.bbc.com/news/topics/c80k5y7my9wt/manchester-arena-attack&link_location=live-reporting-storyhttps://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/may/22/manchester-the-night-of-the-bomb-reviewhttps://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/664682/Attacks_in_London_and_Manchester_Open_Report.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 14:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/20/3831869/3831869_22BB6C1C6FDD4E85AFDB04F5EA85E849_190520_3831869_Manchester_arena_marks_attack_anniversary_with_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, manchester bombing, manchester terror attack, manchester arena attack, manchester anniversary, manchester incident, ariana grande concert, salman abedi, manchester victims]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3831644</guid>
      <title>China claims social credit  system will 'restore trust'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA report from China's National Development and Reform Commission published in the Global Times states that authorities are developing security regulations over privacy leak concerns. The Commission is behind China's social credit system, a reputation system that categorizes citizens based on their behavior. The Chinese government claims the system will "help the country restore social trust".In a press release, Chinese authorities announced new regulations for behavior in public transportation that could affect people's social credit. They state that eating on trains, playing loud music, illegally purchasing tickets and even occupying more than one seat can cost citizen's points. China's strict policies have even reached public toilets. According to a report by the South China Morning Post, in April 2018, China rolled out high-tech toilets with facial recognition to hand out limited amounts of toilet paper in the cities of Chongqing and Changsha. The toilets hand-out 40 centimeters of toilet paper after scanning an individual's face. The bathrooms are equipped with WiFi, mobile charging ports and sensors inside each cubicle that alert authorities if a person has been inside the toilet for more than 10 minutes. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of data leak concerns in China2. New regulations in public transportation3. Facial recognition machines outside public toilets4. Public toilets include Wifi and charging portsVOICEOVER (in English): "A report from China's National Development and Reform Commission published in the Global Times states that authorities are developing security regulations over privacy leak concerns.""The Commission is behind China's social credit system, a reputation system that categorizes citizens based on their behavior. The Chinese government claims the system will "help the country restore social trust".""In a press release, Chinese authorities announced new regulations for behavior in public transportation that could affect people's social credit. They state that eating on trains, playing loud music, illegally purchasing tickets and even occupying more than one seat can cost citizen's points.""China's strict policies have even reached public toilets. According to a report by the South China Morning Post, in April 2018, China rolled out high-tech toilets with facial recognition to hand out limited amounts of toilet paper in the cities of Chongqing and Changsha.""The toilets hand-out 40 centimeters of toilet paper after scanning an individual's face. The bathrooms are equipped with WiFi, mobile charging ports and sensors inside each cubicle that alerts authorities if a person has been inside the toilet for more than 10 minutes."SOURCES: Global Times, South China Morning Post, Beijing Governmenthttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1149741.shtmlhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2141609/chinese-public-toilets-go-hi-tech-wifi-facial-recognitionhttp://www.beijing.gov.cn/zhengce/wenjian/192/33/50/438650/1574644/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 07:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/20/3831644/3831644_83A081AD5D444845B4C94C6DEFFB50A6_190520_3831644_China_claims_social_credit__system_will__restore_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china surveillance, china ai system, china ai, facial recognition, surveillance, surveillance state, china surveillance, police state, sharp eyes project, china surveillance system, total surveillance, social credit, sesame credit, china, beijing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3831636</guid>
      <title>Pollution impairing Asian summer monsoon , study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Asian summer monsoon typically brings about a lot of rainfall, but scientists have found that the rate of precipitation has actually been declining over the past eight decades, according to a study published in Geophysical Research Letters.According to National Geographic, the summer monsoon usually takes place between the months of April to September.New research from the journal Geophysical Research Letters says that rainfall during the Asian summer monsoon has been found to be decreasing in strength over the past 80 years.Human-made atmospheric pollutants such as sulfate aerosol emissions could be contributing to the reduction, according to a University of Arizona news release.Using climate models, scientists found that as the amount of pollutants in the atmosphere increases, the rate of monsoon rain tends to decline.The researchers also looked at tree-ring data from north China over the past 450 years to determine precipitation rates over the decades. This is because trees tend to grow thicker rings during wetter years.Factors such as solar variability and volcanic eruptions are also believed to impact the strength of the Asian summer monsoon.As rainfall from the summer monsoon has been declining, this has had an impact on water availability, ecosystems and agriculture across the globe.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Heavy rainfall during the monsoon season and a measurement bar2. Pollutants in the atmosphere3. Tree ring data4.  Factors that could be causing the Asian summer monsoon to decrease in strengthVOICEOVER (in English): "New research from the journal Geophysical Research Letters says that rainfall during the Asian summer monsoon has been found to be decreasing in strength over the past 80 years.""According to a University of Arizona news release, human-made atmospheric pollutants such as sulfate aerosol emissions could be contributing to the reduction.""Using climate models, scientists found that as the amount of pollutants in the atmosphere increases, the rate of monsoon rain tends to decline.""The researchers also looked at tree-ring data from north China over the past 450 years to determine precipitation rates over the decades.""This is because trees tend to grow thicker rings during wetter years.""Factors such as solar variability and volcanic eruptions are also believed to impact the strength of the Asian summer monsoon."SOURCES: Phys.org, Geophysical Research  Letters, The University of Arizona news release, The Hindu, Science Daily https://phys.org/news/2019-05-unprecedented-weakening-asian-summer-monsoon.htmlhttps://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1029/2019GL082497https://uanews.arizona.edu/story/weakening-asian-summer-monsoon-blamed-pollutionhttps://www.thehindu.com/sci-tech/energy-and-environment/asian-summer-monsoon-weakening-unprecedented-study/article27146879.ecehttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/05/190515102137.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 07:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/20/3831636/3831636_506FAE99119A45CDAAA6AAB398D6E139_190520_3831636_Pollution_impairing_Asian_summer_monsoon___study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, monsoon, asian summer monsoon, ecosystem, agriculture, tree rings, climate change,monsoon weakens, asian summer monsoon dynamics, asian summer monsoon weakens, monsoon climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3831485</guid>
      <title>UN chief raises concerns over nuclear coffin leaking into the Pacific</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUN Secretary General Antonio Guterres has raised concerns over a concrete dome in the Marshall Islands leaking radioactive waste into the Pacific Ocean.The nuclear dome was built in the late 1970s during the Cold War era. The dome was originally built to contain radioactive waste from nuclear tests conducted by the U.S., CBS News reports.According to CBS News, the U.S. conducted 64 nuclear weapons tests at Bikini and Enewetak atolls in the Marshall Islands from 1946 to 1958.The tests included the "Bravo" hydrogen bomb, which was said to be a 1,000 times more powerful than the atomic bomb the U.S. dropped on Hiroshima, reports Al Jazeera. Radioactive ash and soil from nuclear explosions were put into the crater, which was closed with an 18-inch-thick concrete dome. This was originally meant to be a temporary solution with the bottom of the crater never being lined.Decades of exposure has caused cracks to develop on the surface of the concrete, raising concerns that the radioactive waste present in the dome could slowly be making its way into the Pacific Ocean, CBS News reports. Guterres, who was speaking to students in Fiji during a press event as part of his South Pacific tour, was quoted by CBS News as saying, "The consequences of these [issues] have been quite dramatic, in relation to health, in relation to the poisoning of waters in some areas."Guterres is currently touring the South Pacific to raise awareness on issues related to climate change.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Marshall Islands flag and the nuclear dome2. Radioactive waste barrels and a waving U.S. flag3. Radioactive materials stored in the dome 4. Cracks appearing on the nuclear domeVOICEOVER (in English): "UN Secretary General Antonio Guterres has raised concerns over a concrete dome in the Marshall Islands leaking radioactive waste into the Pacific Ocean." "The nuclear dome was built in the late 1970s during the Cold War era.""CBS News reports the dome was originally built to contain radioactive waste from nuclear tests conducted by the U.S.""Radioactive ash and soil from nuclear explosions were put into the crater, which was closed with a concrete dome that is 18 inches thick.""This was originally meant to be temporary solution with the bottom of the crater never being lined.""CBS News reports decades of exposure has caused cracks to develop on the surface of the concrete, raising concerns that the radioactive waste present in the dome could slowly be making its way into the Pacific Ocean."SOURCES: Al Jazeera, RT News, Sputnik News, CBS News, The Guardian,  https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/05/chief-guterres-concerned-nuclear-coffin-leaking-pacific-190516073758642.htmlhttps://www.rt.com/news/459499-un-confirms-nuclear-waste-pacific/https://sputniknews.com/asia/201905161075066780-un-worries-nuclear-leak-pacific/https://www.cbsnews.com/news/enewetak-atoll-dome-un-antonio-guterres-concerns-marshall-islands-structure-leaking-radioactive-material-pacific/https://www.theguardian.com/world/2015/jul/03/runit-dome-pacific-radioactive-waste***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 03:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/20/3831485/3831485_147EF09C119D45D48D70AB8A444AAAAE_190520_3831485_UN_chief_raises_concerns_over_nuclear_coffin_lea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  UN, united nations, nuclear coffin, pacific, marshall islands, nuclear coffin in pacific, nuclear coffin marshall islands, nuclear coffin leaking,concrete dome,radioactive material, radioactive material leaking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3831467</guid>
      <title>Trump targets Huawei in new ban on foreign telecom gear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Trump administration made a move to enable a ban on Huawei gear, amid an escalating trade war between the U.S. and China. According to the New York Times, President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Wednesday to ban U.S. telecom firms from using foreign-made equipment from sources that may pose a risk to national security.While no nation or company was singled out in the ban, the Commerce Department later added Huawei and its affiliates on a list of firms considered to be undermining American interests.The listing prevents Huawei from purchasing U.S. parts or technologies without the government's approval.According to CNN, U.S. officials have openly warned against using gear from Huawei and other Chinese companies, arguing that these tech products could allow China to spy on U.S. communications.Major mobile phone companies in America are largely unaffected as they don't use Huawei equipment, but the order may be costly for rural wireless carriers who do use Huawei as a cheaper alternative to European brands like Nokia or Ericsson.CNN reports that the executive order would apply to past purchases of telecom gear, though officials didn't say whether the government would help smaller carriers pay to remove or switch out their foreign gear. It is also unclear what the punishment would be for those who don't comply.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Trump signs order to ban telecom equipment from foreign sources deemed security threat2. Huawei added to list of firms that pose a risk to national security3. Officials warn of China using Huawei tech to spy on U.S. communications4. Ban costly for rural carriers who use Huawei as cheap alternative to European techVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the New York Times, President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Wednesday to ban U.S. telecom firms from using foreign-made equipment from sources that may pose a risk to national security.""While no nation or company was singled out in the ban, the Commerce Department later added Huawei and its affiliates on a list of firms considered to be undermining American interests.""The listing prevents Huawei from purchasing U.S. parts or technologies without the government's approval.""According to CNN, U.S. officials have openly warned against using gear from Huawei and other Chinese companies, arguing that these tech products could allow China to spy on U.S. communications.""Major mobile phone companies in America are largely unaffected as they don't use Huawei equipment, but the order may be costly for rural wireless carriers who do use Huawei as a cheaper alternative to European brands like Nokia or Ericsson."SOURCES: New York Times, CNNhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/15/business/huawei-ban-trump.htmlhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/15/tech/trump-executive-order-telecom-security/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 02:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/20/3831467/3831467_A00163DD9DF54BC6AEE4BBC77CA053EE_190520_3831467_Trump_targets_Huawei_in_new_ban_on_foreign_telec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump ban, Huawei ban, foreign telecom gear, Huawei, Huawei equipment, China spying, Huawei 5g, Huawei spying, China, Trump, Donald Trump]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3832282</guid>
      <title>Scientists find 'super coral' in Hawaii</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew studies show coral reefs located in Kane'ohe Bay, Hawaii are capable of growing in acidic and warm waters. Human activity has contributed to the destruction of coral reefs via overfishing, pollution and coral bleaching.  From 1930 to 1970, reefs located in Kane'ohe Bay, Hawaii were subject to dredging, coastal development and sewage dumping. All of this destroyed 95 percent of reefs.  In 1978, sewage outposts were removed from the area.Two decades later, the reef surface had recovered to between 50 and 95 percent. According to a recent study published in the journal Proceedings of the Royal Society B: Biological Sciences, the reefs were able to thrive despite the acidification of the water. The team gathered branches of three main coral species from about 10 to 12 colonies in Waimanalo and Kane'ohe Bay. They exposed them to warm or acidic water in a controlled environment for five weeks.     The results showed that corals extracted from Kane'ohe Bay had a higher tolerance to warm and acidic water which allowed them to blossom more than twice as fast as the corals from Waimanalo Bay.   Christopher Jury, the lead scientist from the study, believes that because the reefs in Kane'ohe Bay have the properties to flourish in polluted environments they make the area, quote, "incredibly valuable as a possible window into the future."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Human activity polluting coral; Percentage of coral lost2. Sewage outposts removed; Coral reefs recover3. Scientists study three branches from different reef colonies4. Kane'ohe reefs withstand acidic and warm waters better than other reefsVOICEOVER (in English): "Human activity has contributed to the destruction of coral reefs via overfishing, pollution and coral bleaching." "From 1930 to 1970, reefs located in Kane'ohe Bay, Hawaii were subject to dredging, coastal development and sewage dumping. All of this destroyed 95 percent of reefs."  "In 1978, sewage outposts were removed from the area. 20 years later the reef surface had recovered to between 50 and 95 percent." "According to a recent study published in the journal Proceedings of the Royal Society B: Biological Sciences, the reefs were able to thrive despite the acidification of the water." "The team gathered branches of three main coral species from about 10 to 12 colonies in Waimanalo and Kane'ohe Bay. They exposed them to warm or acidic water in a controlled environment for five weeks."     "The results showed that corals extracted from Kane'ohe Bay had a higher tolerance to warm and acidic water which allowed them to blossom more than twice as fast as the corals from Waimanalo Bay." SOURCES:Proceedings of the Royal Society B, Discoverhttps://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rspb.2019.0614http://blogs.discovermagazine.com/d-brief/2019/05/15/some-corals-in-hawaii-thrive-in-warm-acidic-water/#.XOIFUZgzaUl***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 09:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/21/3832282/3832282_AEB54E95E3E34ACE830CB80D8F567AC3_190521_3832282_Scientists_find__super_coral__in_Hawaii_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, coral bleaching, coral reef death, super coral, coral reef dying, coral reef pollution, reef dying, coral reef, hawaii reef, hawaii coral reef, human pollution, ocean pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3832188</guid>
      <title>Atmospheric carbon dioxide hits all time record high</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists at the Mauna Loa Observatory in Hawaii have recorded the highest levels of atmospheric carbon dioxide ever in human history.Increases in carbon dioxide concentration have caused rises in temperature during ice age cycles over the past million years or more, according to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.According to data from the observatory, CO2 concentration levels were recorded to be over 415 parts per million, or ppm.The last time carbon dioxide concentration levels were this high was more than 3 million years ago, according to the NOAA.Atmospheric carbon dioxide is currently increasing at a rate of 3 parts per million every year.According to a report from the UN's Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, global temperatures have already risen by approximately 1 degree Celsius above pre-industrial levels due to human activity.Eric Holthaus, a meteorologist who writes for climate change and social justice site Grist, tweeted his response to the report, saying: "This is the first time in human history our planet's atmosphere has had more than 415 ppm CO2.""Not just in recorded history, not just since the invention of agriculture 10,000 years ago. Since before modern humans existed millions of years ago."He added: "We don't know a planet like this."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mauna Loa Observatory, carbon dioxide molecule, measurement bar, 2. Graph showing CO2 concentration levels3. Earth's atmosphere with carbon dioxide molecules4. Planet Earth, thermometer increasing by 1 degree CelsiusVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists at the Mauna Loa Observatory in Hawaii have recorded the highest levels of atmospheric carbon dioxide ever in human history.""According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, increases in carbon dioxide concentration have caused rises in temperature during ice age cycles over the past million years or more.""According to data from the observatory, CO2 concentration levels were recorded to be over 415 parts per million, or ppm.""According to the NOAA, the last time carbon dioxide concentration levels were this high was more than 3 million years ago.""Atmospheric carbon dioxide is currently increasing at a rate of 3 parts per million every year.""According to a report from the UN's Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, global temperatures have already risen by approximately 1 degree Celsius above pre-industrial levels due to human activity."SOURCES: Live Science, Science Alert, CNN, Scientific American, Scripps Institution of Oceanography, Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Changehttps://www.livescience.com/65469-highest-carbon-dioxide-levels.htmlhttps://www.sciencealert.com/it-s-official-atmospheric-co2-just-exceeded-415-ppm-for-first-time-in-human-historyhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/13/health/carbon-dioxide-world-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.scientificamerican.com/article/co2-levels-just-hit-another-record-heres-why-it-matters/?redirect=1https://scripps.ucsd.edu/programs/keelingcurve/https://www.ipcc.ch/sr15/chapter/summary-for-policy-makers/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 07:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/21/3832188/3832188_3BCF873289544FECA031E7834242C56F_190521_3832188_Atmospheric_carbon_dioxide_hits_all_time_record__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,pollution and climate change, carbon dioxide, atmospheric carbon dioxide, climate change and carbon dioxide,  global warming,  carbon emissions, earth, record levels of atmospheric carbon dioxide]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3832145</guid>
      <title>Scientists find new way for volcanoes to form</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe now-dormant volcano that created the island of Bermuda formed in a way that has not been observed before, according to a study published in the journal Nature.Scientists examined the chemical composition of a core sample drilled from the volcano in 1972 and found that it contained large amounts of water enclosed in crystals.This indicates that the core consists of material from the earth's mantle transition zone, which is 250 to 400 miles beneath the planet's crust.The scientists developed numerical models and found that a disturbance in the transition zone most likely caused the materials to melt and permeate to earth's surface. The water found in the crystals most likely aided the rocks in melting while in the transition zone, according to the researchers.Previously, volcanoes were known to form when tectonic plates converge or drift apart, or when mantle plumes rise from the core-mantle boundary.The researchers had been expecting to find that Bermuda was formed a mantle plume, as was Hawaii.Senior author of the study Esteban Gazel was quoted in a Cornell University news release as saying: "With this work we can demonstrate that the Earth's transition zone is an extreme chemical reservoir.""Our next step is to examine more locations to determine the difference between geological processes that can result in intraplate volcanoes and determine the role of the mantle's transition zone in the evolution of our planet."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Globe and island of Bermuda2. What the scientists found in the rock core sample3. Cross section of earth showing the mantle transition zone 4. Cross section of earth showing materials from the transition zone moving up to earth's surfaceVOICEOVER (in English): "The now-dormant volcano that created the island of Bermuda formed in a way that has not been observed before, according to a study published in the journal Nature.""Scientists examined the chemical composition of a core sample drilled from the volcano in 1972 and found that it contained large amounts of water enclosed in crystals.""This indicates that the core consists of material from the earth's mantle transition zone, which is 250 to 400 miles beneath the planet's crust.""The scientists developed numerical models and found that a disturbance in the transition zone most likely caused the materials to melt and permeate to earth's surface.""The water found in the crystals most likely aided the rocks in melting while in the transition zone, according to the researchers."SOURCES: Nature, Brinkwire, National Science Foundation, Science Daily, Phys.org,  Cornell University  https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1183-6http://brinkwire.com/science/scientists-discover-new-way-for-volcanoes-to-form/https://www.nsf.gov/discoveries/disc_summ.jsp?cntn_id=298562https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/05/190515144028.htmhttps://phys.org/news/2019-05-earth-deep-mantle-scientists-volcanoes.htmlhttps://news.cornell.edu/stories/2019/05/earths-deep-mantle-scientists-discover-new-way-volcanoes-form***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 06:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/21/3832145/3832145_BCDDDA6C711A4A1A9B30B7849A1EE144_190521_3832145_Scientists_find_new_way_for_volcanoes_to_form_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, bermuda island, volcanoes, bermuda island volcanoes, ancient dormant volcano, volcanic origins, how volcanoes form, bermuda mysteries, volcano lava, bermuda lava core, bermuda volcano island eruption]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3832999</guid>
      <title>Pluto's underground ocean kept from freezing by gas layer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research provides evidence of an ocean buried in Pluto that's kept from freezing by an insulating layer.According to CNN, observations made by NASA's New Horizons spacecraft in 2015 on  Pluto's ellipsoidal basin Sputnik Planitia have led scientists to believe an ocean exists beneath the planet's icy surface.Pluto is roughly 4.6 billion years old and isn't in the vicinity of a gas giant that could heat it using tidal forces. Its ocean should have frozen millions of years ago, but evidence suggests it has not.A new study published in Nature Geoscience suggests an insulating layer of gas hydrates, which are ice-like solids that form when gas bubbles  in this case methane  are trapped between frozen water molecules.Computer simulations conducted by the researchers show the ocean hardly freezes with a gas hydrate layer present. Without the hydrate layer, however, the subsurface ocean would have frozen completely hundreds of millions of years ago.The theory might also explain the unique composition of Pluto's atmosphere, which is rich in nitrogen but poor in methane.Researchers say that if gas hydrate insulating layers could indeed keep subsurface oceans from freezing, there may be more oceans in the universe than previously thought. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Underground ocean on Pluto2. Pluto's ocean not frozen despite its age and location3. Depiction of gas hydrate layer4. Gas hydrate layer insulates ocean to keep it from freezingVOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNN, observations made by NASA's New Horizons spacecraft in 2015 on  Pluto's ellipsoidal basin Sputnik Planitia have led scientists to believe an ocean exists beneath the planet's icy surface.""Pluto is roughly 4.6 billion years old and isn't in the vicinity of a gas giant that could heat it using tidal forces. Its ocean should have frozen millions of years ago, but evidence suggests it has not.""A new study published in Nature Geoscience suggests an insulating layer of gas hydrates, which are ice-like solids that form when gas bubbles  in this case methane  are trapped between frozen water molecules.""Computer simulations conducted by the researchers show the ocean hardly freezes with a gas hydrate layer present. Without the hydrate layer, however, the subsurface ocean would have frozen completely hundreds of millions of years ago.""The theory might also explain the unique composition of Pluto's atmosphere, which is rich in nitrogen but poor in methane."SOURCES: Nature Geoscience, Science Dailyhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41561-019-0369-8https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/05/190520115657.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/22/3832999/3832999_CE9CD213EBF24E04B6EB098696EC20F9_190522_3832999_Pluto_s_underground_ocean_kept_from_freezing_by__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Pluto, underground ocean, subsurface ocean, Pluto ocean, gas hydrate layer, gas hydrates, hidden ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3832869</guid>
      <title>Study finds air pollution may be damaging 'every organ in the body'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA comprehensive new global review has found that air pollution may be harming nearly every cell in the human body.According to a review published in Chest Journal, the harmful effects of toxic air begin when it is inhaled.Once in the lungs, it can cause breathing problems, including asthma and emphysema. It can also cause serious harm to the heart, with narrowing arteries and weakening muscles resulting in an increased risk of heart attacks.Small pollution particles penetrate the lungs and are mistaken as bacteria by immune cells, which then release enzymes and acids to try and kill them.These proteins spread around the body, causing systemic inflammation. The damage is far-reaching, affecting the brain, kidneys, and pancreas.Brain conditions associated with pollution include stroke, dementia, and reduced intelligence. There's evidence to suggest poor sleep may also be a consequence of breathing in bad air.The Guardian reports that research highlighted in the review links air pollution to various cancers, including in the bladder and gut.Toxic air likewise affects bones and skin, and has been associated with brittle bones, skin aging, and hives.According to the review, exposure to polluted air can lead to reduced fertility and increased miscarriages.It poses a risk for unborn babies, with a recent study finding pollutants in fetal placentas.Air pollution is also linked to low birth weights for babies, and can lead to stunted development in children.Prof. Dean Schraufnagel, who led the reviews, is worried that doctors may be unaware of how much damage is associated with air pollution, and suggests they should pay attention, and then speak up and educate their patients.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Air pollution causing lung and heart problems2. Inflammation spreading in body due to immune response to pollution particles3. Air pollution linked to cancer, skin and bone damage4. Effects of air pollution on fertility, babies, childrenVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a review published in Chest Journal, the harmful effects of toxic air begin when it is inhaled.""Once in the lungs, it can cause breathing problems, including asthma and emphysema. It can also cause serious harm to the heart, with narrowing arteries and weakening muscles resulting in an increased risk of heart attacks.""Small pollution particles penetrate the lungs and are mistaken as bacteria by immune cells, which then release enzymes and acids to try and kill them.""These proteins spread around the body, causing systemic inflammation. The damage is far-reaching, affecting the brain, kidneys, and pancreas.""The Guardian reports that research highlighted in the review links air pollution to various cancers, including in the bladder and gut.""Toxic air likewise affects bones and skin, and has been associated with brittle bones, skin ageing, and hives.""According to the review, exposure to polluted air can lead to reduced fertility and increased miscarriages.""It poses a risk for unborn babies, with a recent study finding pollutants in fetal placentas.""Air pollution is also linked to low birth weights for babies, and can lead to stunted development in children."SOURCES: The Guardian, Chest Journalhttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/ng-interactive/2019/may/17/air-pollution-may-be-damaging-every-organ-and-cell-in-the-body-finds-global-reviewhttps://journal.chestnet.org/article/S0012-3692(18)32723-5/fulltext***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 10:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/22/3832869/3832869_BEE31B3049244A5F98B6F26E4BEFD2CD_190522_3832869_Study_finds_air_pollution_may_be_damaging__every_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, air pollution, pollution particles, pollution, organ damage, cancer, air pollution effects, air pollution diseases]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3832842</guid>
      <title>Huawei CFO Meng's house arrest conditions explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANHuawei's Chief Financial Officer is currently under house arrest in her six bedroom mansion worth millions of dollars, according to Reuters.Meng Wanzhou has been detained in Canada since December 2018 for her role in allegedly misleading banks to evade US sanctions against Iran, CNN reports.  Since then Meng has requested a judge on the Canadian Supreme Court to move into another one of her properties, on Matthews Street residence.The mansion is around 8,170 square feet and contains seven bedrooms and eight bathrooms, according to Reuters.This new mansion would be fully fenced and allows "controlled access" for pedestrians and vehicles entering the house.According to Reuters, Meng is allowed to move around Vancouver relatively freely. But, as reported by CNN, she is required to wear a GPS ankle bracelet.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Meng Wanzhao and the first mansion2. Fencing outside of the second mansion3. House dimensions and house interior4. Vancouver on a map and Meng Wanzhao wearing a GPS ankle braceletVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, Huawei's Chief Financial Officer is currently under house arrest in her six bedroom mansion worth millions of dollars.""Since then Meng has requested a judge on the Canadian Supreme Court to move into another one of her properties, on Matthews Street residence.""According to Reuters, the mansion is around 8,170 square feet and contains seven bedrooms and eight bathrooms.""This new mansion would be fully fenced and allows 'controlled access' for pedestrians and vehicles entering the house.""According to Reuters, Meng is allowed to move around Vancouver relatively freely.""But, as reported by CNN, she is required to wear a GPS ankle bracelet."SOURCES: Reuters, CNN, https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-huawei-tech-meng/huawei-cfo-house-arrest-contrasts-with-canadians-detained-in-china-idUSKCN1SQ0C3https://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/13/tech/meng-wanzhou-huawei-letter/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 09:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/22/3832842/3832842_908C466F407B44B9820DEC5826596905_190522_3832842_Huawei_CFO_Meng_s_house_arrest_conditions_explai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Huawei, Meng Wanzhou, Meng Wanzhou, China, United States, Huawei CFO, huawei meng wanzhou, huawei controversies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3832725</guid>
      <title>Iran suspected to have carried out an attack against Saudi Arabia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA report by a Norwegian insurance company states it is highly likely that Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards orchestrated a drone attack on Saudi tankers in the Persian Gulf. Reuters reports that four tankers, including two Saudi ships, one UAE vessel, and one Norwegian tanker, were attacked in the United Arab Emirates on May 13.According to an insurance report by the Norwegian Shipowners' Mutual War Risks Insurance Association, the attacks against the tankers may have been carried out by a nearby vessel.The ship is thought to have released underwater drones carrying around 30 to 50 kilograms of high-grade explosives to detonate on impact. In the report, the insurance company detailed the factors that lead them to believe the attacks were organized by Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards, or IRGC. They claim there is a similarity in the shrapnel found on the Norwegian tanker to shrapnel in Houthi drone boats. The IRGC has also previously supplied the Houthi militia with drone boats equipped with explosives, and GPS systems for improved accuracy during strikes.  The report states that the attacks occurred around six to 10 nautical miles off Fujairah, close to the Strait of Hormuz. Iran has previously threatened to stop all exports passing through the strait. Roughly a fifth of the world's oil travels through Hormuz.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Norwegian, Saudi and UAE tankers in the ocean2. Houthi boat carrying underwater drones3. Hole in tanker; Houthi drone boats 4. Location of attack and Strait of HormuzVOICEOVER (in English): "Reuters reports that four tankers, including two Saudi ships, one UAE vessel, and one Norwegian tanker, were attacked in the United Arab Emirates on May 13.""According to an insurance report by the Norwegian Shipowners' Mutual War Risks Insurance Association, the attacks against the tankers may have been carried out by a nearby vessel.""The ship is thought to have released underwater drones carrying around 30 to 50 kilograms of high-grade explosives to detonate on impact.""In the report, the insurance company detailed the factors that lead them to believe the attacks were organized by Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards, or IRGC.""They claim there is a similarity in the shrapnel found on the Norwegian tanker to shrapnel in Houthi drone boats." "The IRGC has also previously supplied the Houthi militia with drone boats equipped with explosives, and GPS systems for improved accuracy during strikes."  "The report states that the attacks occurred around six to 10 nautical miles off Fujairah, close to the Strait of Hormuz."SOURCES: Reutershttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran-oil-tankers-exclusive-idUSKCN1SN1P7***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/22/3832725/3832725_672BC17E1EF748BB80C8B5105C013BC5_190522_3832725_Iran_suspected_to_have_carried_out_an_attack_aga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, saudi oil, tanker attack, drone attack, saudi tankers, saudi vs iran, saudi vs houthis, strait of hormuz, Norway, saudi aramco, houthis, houthi, DNK]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3833584</guid>
      <title>Massive asteroid with its own moon to pass close to Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA massive asteroid with its own mini moon will be passing close to Earth this weekend.According to NASA, Asteroid 1999 KW4 is a binary system composed of a nearly mile-wide main body shaped like a walnut or spinning top, orbited by a smaller rock that is a third of a mile across.Each orbit takes 17 and a half hours, according to the Las Cumbres Observatory.NASA reports that the asteroid has been doing flybys several times each century since the 1600s, and will be making another close approach to Earth on May 25.Although classified as 'potentially hazardous' by the Minor Planet Center, the asteroid will be passing near Earth at a safe distance of more than three million miles, or over 13.5 lunar distances.CNET reports that Asteroid 1999 KW4 will be moving fast at 48,123 miles per hour when it flies by, which may make it easier for amateur observers to see.According to NASA, double asteroid's next approach will be closer, but won't be until 2036.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid 1999 KW4 consists of mile-wide main body with a smaller moon orbiting it2. Asteroid 1999 KW4 to pass close to Earth on May 253. Asteroid will pass at a safe distance despite classified as potentially hazardous4. Asteroid will be moving at 48,123 miles per hourVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA, Asteroid 1999 KW4 is a binary system composed of a nearly mile-wide main body shaped like a walnut or spinning top, orbited by a smaller rock that is a third of a mile across.""Each orbit takes 17 and a half hours, according to the Las Cumbres Observatory.""NASA reports that the asteroid has been doing flybys several times each century since the 1600s, and will be making another close approach to Earth on May 25.""Although classified as 'potentially hazardous' by the Minor Planet Center, the asteroid will be passing near Earth at a safe distance of more than three million miles, or over 13.5 lunar distances.""CNET reports that Asteroid 1999 KW4 will be moving fast at 48,123 miles per hour when it flies by, which may make it easier for amateur observers to see."SOURCES: NASA, Las Cumbres Observatory, CNEThttps://echo.jpl.nasa.gov/asteroids/1999KW4/1999KW4_planning.2019.htmlhttps://asteroidtracker.lco.global/asteroid/14/https://www.cnet.com/news/walnut-asteroid-nearly-a-mile-wide-seen-approaching-with-its-own-moon/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 15:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/23/3833584/3833584_2531066BAB574D028BFEFCCC9D8579BC_190523_3833584_Massive_asteroid_with_its_own_moon_to_pass_close_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, asteroid flyby, asteroid close approach, asteroid with moon, asteroid 1999 KW4, walnut asteroid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3833508</guid>
      <title>How U.S. ban will affect Huawei technology</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLast Monday, news broke that Trump had banned Chinese tech giant, Huawei, from the U.S. market after trade negotiations went stale. This is how the move could affect the technology company.  Chinese tech company, Huawei, was blacklisted by the U.S. government last Monday. The tech company  as do most tech corporations  depends heavily on foreign components. Huawei's P30 Pro motherboard is an example of this. According to BBC, only two components from the motherboard are Chinese, its RF transceivers and audio chip. Both are made by HiSilicon, which is owned by Huawei.Two of the chip's front end modules which connect the phone to network signals and allows it to manage different radio frequencies are made in two separate American semiconductor firms. One is located in Massachusetts and the other in Greensboro, North Carolina. Both will be affected by the ban. The device's flash storage located at the back of the motherboard is made by a semiconductor company from Idaho called Micron Technologies. Benchmark analysts estimate that 13 percent of the company's revenue comes from Huawei.  The P30 Pro's dynamic random access memory or DRAM is also foreign. This piece of equipment is from South Korean component company, SK Hynix.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Huawei blacklisted by U.S. government2. Huawei P30 Pro motherboard's RF transceivers and audio chip3. Huawei P30 Pro motherboard's front end modules 4. Huawei P30 Pro motherboard's flash storage and dynamic random access memory VOICEOVER (in English): "Chinese tech company, Huawei, was blacklisted by the U.S. government last Monday. The tech company  as do most tech corporations  depends heavily on foreign components." "Huawei's P30 Pro motherboard is an example of this. According to BBC, only two components from the motherboard are Chinese, its RF transceivers and audio chip. Both are made by HiSilicon, which is owned by Huawei.""Two of the chip's front end modules which connect the phone to network signals and allows it to manage different radio frequencies are made in two separate American semiconductor firms. One is located in Massachusetts and the other in Greensboro, North Carolina. Both will be affected by the ban." "The device's flash storage located at the back of the motherboard is made by a semiconductor company from Idaho called Micron Technologies. Benchmark analysts estimate that 13 percent of the company's revenue comes from Huawei."  "The P30 Pro's dynamic random access memory or DRAM is also foreign. This piece of equipment is from South Korean component company, SK Hynix."  SOURCES: BBC, Fortune, The Verge, Investopedia, Tech Radarhttps://bbc.in/2Enx2oXhttps://bit.ly/2HKpAVAhttps://bit.ly/2WTEfEshttps://bit.ly/2VICybkhttps://www.techradar.com/news/huawei-android-ban-temporarily-lifted-but-its-still-not-good-news-for-the-brand***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 12:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/23/3833508/3833508_8C219DA3F66145FDA70D74B85AD19B43_190523_3833508_How_U_S__ban_will_affect_Huawei_technology_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, huawei, huawei components, china, us, trade war, china us trade war, huawei us ban, us ban huawei]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3833345</guid>
      <title>SpaceX all set to launch 60 'Starlink' satellites into space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSpaceX is set to launch 60 "Starlink" satellites that would provide broadband internet services and orbit around Earth, according to Space.com.The satellites will be launched on Thursday via the Falcon 9 rocket at Cape Canaveral in Florida.The launch was initially planned for May 15. It was, however, delayed due to high winds, according to CNet.This is the early stages of SpaceX's plans to launch an affordable high-speed broadband network into space. Starlink would be able to provide internet access to those who are yet to be connected online, according to SpaceX's website.SpaceX CEO Elon Musk was cited by Space.com as saying that the Starlink network would require around 400 satellites to provide "minor" internet coverage around the world, while 800 would be needed for "moderate" internet coverage.According to CNet, this will be the beginning of SpaceX's plans to launch a megaconstellation with as many as 12,000 satellites orbiting Earth's atmosphere.Previously, the FCC had given SpaceX permission for its satellites to orbit at a lower altitude from 1,150 kilometers to 550 kilometers.By operating satellites at a lower orbit, according to The Verge, Starlink would be able to cut down transmission time and is expected to transfer data in just 15 milliseconds.According to Tech Times, the company will need to launch six to 12 more Starlink missions in order to provide internet coverage to a larger global audience.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. An internet satellite and a network of internet satellites appearing around earth2. The Falcon 9 rocket launching3. The Starlink satellites, a computer, and a wifi signal illustrating strength4. External map of satellites surrounding earth5. The satellites lowering in orbitVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Space.com, SpaceX is set to launch 60 'Starlink' satellites that would provide broadband internet services and orbit around Earth.""The satellites will be launched on Thursday via the Falcon 9 rocket at Cape Canaveral in Florida.""This is the early stages of SpaceX's plans to launch an affordable high-speed broadband network into space." "Starlink would be able to provide internet access to those who are yet to be connected online, according to SpaceX's website.""SpaceX CEO Elon Musk was cited by Space.com as saying that the Starlink network would require around 400 satellites to provide 'minor' internet coverage around the world, while 800 would be needed for 'moderate' internet coverage.""According to CNet, this will be the beginning of SpaceX's plans to launch a megaconstellation with as many as 12,000 satellites orbiting Earth's atmosphere.""Previously, the FCC had given SpaceX permission for its satellites to orbit at a lower altitude from 1,150 kilometers to 550 kilometers.""By operating satellites at a lower orbit, according to The Verge, Starlink would be able to cut down transmission time and is expected to transfer data in just 15 milliseconds."SOURCES: SpaceX, CNet, Tech Times, Space.com, FCC, The Verge, https://www.spacex.com/webcasthttps://www.cnet.com/news/spacex-starlink-now-launching-may-23/https://www.techtimes.com/articles/243517/20190521/spacex-to-launch-60-starlink-internet-service-satellites.htmhttps://www.space.com/spacex-starlink-satellites-launch-back-on-may-2019.htmlhttps://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DA-19-342A1.pdfhttps://www.theverge.com/2019/4/27/18519778/spacex-starlink-fcc-approval-satellite-internet-constellation-lower-orbit***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/23/3833345/3833345_19E5C68BB5BB474AA2C6597506432FE2_190523_3833345_SpaceX_all_set_to_launch_60__Starlink__satellite_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, spacex, starlink, internet, starlink internet, starling spacex, elon musk starlink, satellite internet network, SpaceX internet plan, spacex launch, spacex starlink]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3833980</guid>
      <title>U.S. Postal Service to test mail delivery using autonomous trucks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Postal Service has started testing self-driving trucks to transport mail across three states.According to Reuters, the USPS began a two-week pilot program using autonomous trucks from startup company TuSimple to carry the mail on five roundtrips between the distribution centers in Phoenix and Dallas.Each one-way trip through Arizona, New Mexico, and Texas is over 1,600 kilometers, which will take 22 hours and include overnight driving.The Verge reports that TuSimple trucks are equipped with nine cameras and two LIDAR sensors to help its vision-based system detect vehicles, pedestrians, and other obstacles up to 1,000 meters away.According to a TuSimple press release, the autonomous trucks have a driver and safety engineer on board for the duration of the testing period.USA Today reports that the pilot can have huge benefits for the Postal Service. It will also help validate TuSimple's system and speed up tech development and commercialization. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Autonomous truck mail route between USPS distribution centers in Phoenix and Dallas2. Distance and length of driving time per trip3. How the autonomous truck works4. Driver and safety engineer onboard the truck VOICEOVER (in English): "According to Reuters, the USPS began a two-week pilot program using autonomous trucks from startup company TuSimple to carry the mail on five roundtrips between the distribution centers in Phoenix and Dallas.""Each one-way trip through Arizona, New Mexico, and Texas is over 1,600 kilometers, which will take 22 hours and include overnight driving.""The Verge reports that TuSimple trucks are equipped with nine cameras and two LIDAR sensors to help its vision-based system detect vehicles, pedestrians, and other obstacles up to 1,000 meters away.""According to a TuSimple press release, the autonomous trucks have a driver and safety engineer on board for the duration of the testing period."SOURCES: TuSimple, Reuters, The Verge, USA Todayhttps://www.tusimple.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/USPS-TuSimple-Press-Release-FINAL.pdfhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-tusimple-autonomous-usps/self-driving-trucks-begin-mail-delivery-test-for-u-s-postal-service-idUSKCN1SR0YBhttps://www.theverge.com/2019/5/21/18633904/usps-postal-service-autonomous-big-rigs-ship-mail-testhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/05/21/us-postal-service-test-autonomous-trucks-transporting-mail/3752641002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 10:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/24/3833980/3833980_E5E5DEB17BC740A0B2D2B4F51921AB5F_190524_3833980_U_S__Postal_Service_to_test_mail_delivery_using__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  autonomous trucks, driverless trucks, self driving trucks, autonomous semi, driverless semi, US mail, snail mail, USPS, US Postal Service, mail delivery, TuSimple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3833950</guid>
      <title>Increase of CFC emissions linked to China, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCFC-11, a potent greenhouse gas and one of the main culprits in depleting the ozone layer, was set to be phased out by 2010.But starting in 2012 scientists noticed a considerable slowdown in the decline of global concentrations of CFCs. The bulk of an increase of trichlorofluoromethane, better known as CFC-11, in the atmosphere has been found to originate from areas in eastern China, according to a new study published in the journal Nature.The gas is believed to be stronger than carbon dioxide or methane in terms of its contribution to damaging effects from greenhouse emissions, the Guardian reports.For the study, researchers from South Korea and Japan used air monitoring stations and created model simulations with the data they collected. They found the CFC-11 molecules originated from the northeastern Chinese provinces of Shandong and Hebei.According to the study, CFC-11 emissions from these Chinese regions have increased by around 7,000 metric tons since 2013. This was a 110 percent increase compared emissions from 2008 to 2012, or 40 percent to 60 percent of the extra global CFC-11 emissions.CFCs were once commonly used in refrigerators, aerosol cans and dry cleaning chemicals before they were banned in 1987 due to their contribution to the hole in the ozone layer over Antarctica under the Montreal Protocol.In response to concerns regarding CFC emissions, a Chinese official was quoted by state-run news agency Xinhua as saying: "The Chinese government has no tolerance for any illegal production of ozone-depleting substances."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. CFC-11 molecule, map of China with a cooling tower on top of it, carbon dioxide molecule and a methane molecule2. South Korean flag, Japanese flag, air monitoring station, and model simulation 3. A 110 percent increase of CFC-11 emissions from the region4. Materials CFCs are typically found inVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the journal Nature, the better part of an increase of trichlorofluoromethane, better known as CFC-11, in the atmosphere has been found to originate from areas in eastern China.""The Guardian reports that the gas is believed to be stronger than carbon dioxide or methane in terms of its contribution to damaging effects from greenhouse emissions.""For the study, researchers from South Korea and Japan used air monitoring stations and created model simulations with the data they collected.""They found that the CFC-11 molecules originated from the northeastern Chinese provinces of Shandong and Hebei.""According to the study, CFC-11 emissions from the Chinese regions have increased by around 7,000 metric tons since 2013.""This was a 110 percent increase compared emissions from 2008 to 2012, or 40 percent to 60 percent of the extra global CFC-11 emissions.""CFCs used to commonly be used in refrigerators, aerosol cans and dry cleaning chemicals before they were banned in 1987 due to their contribution to the hole in the ozone layer over Antarctica under the Montreal Protocol."SOURCES: The New York Times, Nature, The Guardian, CNN, Xinhua  https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/22/climate/china-cfcs-banned-chemicals-ozone.htmlhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1193-4https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/23/china-factories-releasing-thousands-of-tonnes-of-illegal-cfc-gases-study-findshttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/22/health/china-cfc-pollution-environment-intl-scn/http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-03/19/c_137908026.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 09:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/24/3833950/3833950_FA263CF679994778B3EC414E28740983_190524_3833950_Increase_of_CFC_emissions_linked_to_China__study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, ozone layer, ozone layer depletion, ozone layer hole, shandong, eastern china, CFC molecules, CFC emissions, CFC-11, trichlorofluoromethane, Ozone-depleting substances]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3833728</guid>
      <title>Major mobile carriers suspend Huawei smartphone orders</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMobile networks around the globe have suspended orders of Huawei smartphones after US president Donald Trump added the Chinese company to an export blacklist, CNN reports.The Chinese company is no longer allowed to use Google's Android system in its new devices. As a result, Huawei users won't be able to access apps that depend on Google, such as Gmail, Youtube and Google Maps.According to CNN, the US Commerce Department has issued a temporary reprieve to allow Google's Android system to service existing Huawei smartphones for the next 90 days.According to The Verge, major carriers in the UK such as Vodafone and EE have also suspended orders of Huawei devices.The Verge cites Marc Allera, CEO of the BT Group which owns EE, as saying that the company wouldn't launch new Huawei smartphones until it is able to assure its clients of the phone's usability in the distant future.Japanese mobile operator KDDI and Y! Mobile have both said they will bring a halt to the launch of Huawei's newest smartphones, according to the Associated Press.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A US flag, Huawei logo, and two Huawei smartphones flashing red2. Huawei logo, Google Android system, a logo of Gmail, Youtube and Google Map3. Vodafone icon, EE icon, a Huawei smartphone 4. KDDI icon, Y! Mobile icon and a huawei smartphone with its logo on it, 5. A blocking sign then appears on top of itVOICEOVER (in English): "In response to the US decision to impede Huawei's use of US software or components, countries in Asia and Europe have decided to suspend orders of Huawei smartphones.""CNN reports the Chinese company is no longer allowed to use Google's Android system in its new devices.""As a result, Huawei users won't be able to access apps that depend on Google, such as Gmail, Youtube and Google Maps.""The US Commerce Department has issued a temporary reprieve to allow Google's Android system to service existing Huawei smartphones for the next 90 days.""According to The Verge, major carriers in the UK such as Vodafone and EE have also suspended orders of Huawei devices.""The Verge cites Marc Allera, CEO of the BT Group which owns EE, as saying that the company wouldn't launch new Huawei smartphones until it is able to assure its clients of the phone's usability in the distant future.""According to the Associated Press, Japanese mobile operator KDDI and Y! Mobile have both said they will bring a halt to the launch of Huawei's newest smartphones."SOURCES: CNN, The Verge, The Associated Press, The New York Timeshttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/22/tech/huawei-phone-launch-delay/index.htmlhttps://www.theverge.com/2019/5/22/18635313/huawei-phones-dropped-uk-carrier-ee-5g-mate-20-launchhttps://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/3011363/japans-biggest-phone-companies-mull-pulling-huawei-handsetshttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/22/business/huawei-google-japan-britain.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 04:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/24/3833728/3833728_FD457E56A28A41089356B7AA0007541B_190524_3833728_Major_mobile_carriers_suspend_Huawei_smartphone__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, huawei, huawei smartphones, china, US, EE, Vodafone, KDDI, Y! Mobile, huawei ban, Huawei P30 lite, Mate 20X, Mate X folding handset, mobile networks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3835321</guid>
      <title>NASA details plans to return to the moon by 2024</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA plans to launch three Artemis moon missions as well as five other separate launches to build a lunar orbit station in the next five years, according to NASA's website.Artemis 1 is an uncrewed flight set to be launched in 2020 and will test the spacecraft's capabilities of reaching lunar orbit.Artemis 2 will be a manned mission and is expected to be launched two years later. It would take a different route than the previous flight and its target is to take a space crew around the moon.Around the same time, NASA will be sending parts of a lunar orbital station named the Gateway to the moon via private companies.The Gateway will consist of a power and propulsion element and a small habitat module.Artemis 3 will take a space crew and dock at the Gateway, before the crew makes its way down to the moon via a lander.According to NASA, all three Artemis missions will be launched by NASA's Space Launch System on the Orion spacecraft.NASA said this is part of its plan to ultimately make its way from the moon to the Red Planet to make human exploration of Mars a reality. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Artemis rockets on white podiums2. Artemis 1 and 2 in space3. The lunar orbital station, the Gateway is shown being built4. The Artemis 3 docking at the Gateway, and a lander on the moonVOICEOVER (in English): "According to NASA's website, the U.S. space agency plans to launch three Artemis moon missions as well as five other separate launches to build a lunar orbit station in the next five years.""Artemis 1 is an uncrewed flight set to be launched in 2020 and will test the spacecraft's capabilities of reaching lunar orbit.""Artemis 2 will be a manned mission and is expected to be launched two years later. It would take a different route than the previous flight and its target is to take a space crew around the moon.""Around the same time, NASA will be sending parts of a lunar orbital station named the Gateway to the moon via private companies.""The Gateway will consist of a power and propulsion element and a small habitat module.""Artemis 3 will take a space crew and dock at the Gateway, before the crew makes its way down to the moon via a lander."SOURCES: Phys.org, NASA, The New York Times https://phys.org/news/2019-05-nasa-unveils-artemis-moon-mission.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/artemis/https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/themis/news/artemis-orbit.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/sites/default/files/atoms/files/20170724-ppe-rfi-industry-forum-v5.pdfhttps://www.nasa.gov/themis-and-artemishttps://www.nasa.gov/specials/moon2mars/https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/13/science/trump-nasa-moon-mars.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 11:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/27/3835321/3835321_0BB55B7C5EA34908923C1BC648260DD9_190527_3835321_NASA_details_plans_to_return_to_the_moon_by_2024_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, NASA, artemis, moon mission, artemis 2024, lunar mission, space, astronauts, moon, space mission, artemis mission nasa, artemis nasa, artemis 2, artemis 3, space launch system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3835881</guid>
      <title>At least 14 injured in Japan knife attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA mass stabbing in the city of Kawasaki, Japan on Tuesday morning has left over a dozen school children wounded and one child dead, Japanese broadcaster NHK reports.An elementary school girl and a man in his 30s were believed to have died in the attack, according to The Japan Times.As many as 16 other school children were injured in the attack while waiting at a bus stop, NHK reports. According to Kyodo News, two other adults were also wounded.The news agency cites police as saying that two of the school girls and a woman in her 40s suffered serious injuries because of the attack.The suspect was a man in his 50s, police told Kyodo News. He was seen holding knives in both hands. Police say the suspect stabbed victims before stabbing himself in the neck. Officers later found two knives that were believed to be used during the attack.The children were believed to be students at Cartitas Elementary School. However, according to The Japan Times, officials at the elementary school could not immediately confirm if the victims were their students. They added that they are still gathering information. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1.The city where the attack took place on the map of Japan and 16 school children on lying on the ground, with one of them dead2. An adult male and an elementary school girl believed to have died in the attack3. The victims of the attack waiting at the bus stop4. The suspect holding two knives and two police officers finding the knives where the attack took place VOICEOVER (in English): "A mass stabbing in the city of Kawasaki, near Tokyo on Tuesday morning has left over a dozen school children wounded and at least one dead.""According to The Japan Times, an elementary school girl and a man in his 30s were believed to have died in the attack.""Japanese broadcaster NHK reports 16 other school children were injured in the attack while waiting at a bus stop.""According to Kyodo News, two other adults were also wounded.""The news agency cites police as saying that two of the school girls and a woman in her 40s suffered serious injuries because of the attack.""The suspect was a man in his 50s, police told Kyodo News. He was seen holding knives in both hands.""Police say the suspect stabbed victims before stabbing himself in the neck.""Officers later found two knives that were believed to be used during the attack."SOURCES: Kyodo News, NHK World, Japan Times The Guardian, BBC News, https://english.kyodonews.net/news/2019/05/cd2e013a9973-urgent-11-including-elementary-school-children-stabbed-in-city-near-tokyo.htmlhttps://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20190528_10/https://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20190528_19/https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/05/28/national/crime-legal/11-reported-stabbed-kawasaki-including-elementary-school-children/#.XOydSZgzZjUhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/28/japan-mass-stabbing-children-among-injured-in-attack-kawasakihttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-48428695***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/28/3835881/3835881_47EBF958FE224A0CB2BFF1CE7D1B1C90_190528_3835881_At_least_14_injured_in_Japan_knife_attack_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, japan, japan stabbing, japan stabbing attack, japan knife attack, japan knife attack 2019, japan stabbing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3835680</guid>
      <title>Music streaming maybe contributing to climate change: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDownloading and streaming music on online platforms is contributing significantly to greenhouse gas emissions, according to a new study by the Universities of Glasgow and Oslo.Researchers converted the amount of plastic production and electricity generation to represent the amount of resources and energy being used to download and stream music online, referring to them as greenhouse gas equivalents.Music streaming in the U.S. was estimated to have produced between 200 million to 350 million kilograms of greenhouse gas in 2016, according to a University of Glasgow news release. That is the approximate amount of greenhouse gas emissions generated by what is needed to transmit and store digital music files.According to the news release, this is an increase from 140 million kilograms of greenhouse gas equivalents in 1977, 136 million kilograms in 1988, and 157 million kilograms in 2000.Dr Kyle Devine, who led the study, was quoted by the University of Glasgow news release as saying : "From a carbon emissions perspective  the transition towards streaming recorded music from internet-connected devices has resulted in significantly higher carbon emissions than at any previous point in the history of music."Devine told The Rolling Stone that the figure does not include the carbon footprint of data storage and processing in data centers or the amount of electricity needed to power a digital device.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Music icons entering a folder, and a factory releasing greenhouse gas emissions2. US map, phone with music on it and a red measurement bar3. Plastic CD case, electricity icon and music icon4. Graph depicting greenhouse gas equivalent ratesVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study by the Universities of Glasgow and Oslo has found that downloading and streaming music on online platforms is contributing significantly to greenhouse gas emissions.""According to a University of Glasgow news release, music streaming in the U.S. was estimated to have produced between 200 million to 350 million kilograms of greenhouse gas in 2016.""That is the approximate amount of greenhouse gas emissions generated by what is needed to transmit and store digital music files.""Researchers converted the amount of plastic production and electricity generation to represent the amount of resources and energy being used to download and stream music online, referring to them as greenhouse gas equivalents.""According to the news release, this is an increase from 140 million kilograms of greenhouse gas equivalents in 1977, 136 million kilograms in 1988, and 157 million kilograms in 2000."SOURCES: Rolling Stone, University of Glasgow, Citizen Bravo, Spotify Sustainability Report 2017, Live for Live Music, MIT Press,https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-features/environmental-impact-streaming-music-835220/https://www.gla.ac.uk/news/headline_643297_en.htmlhttp://eprints.gla.ac.uk/183249/http://www.citizenbravo.com/research.htmlhttp://q4live.s22.clientfiles.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/540910603/files/doc_downloads/govDocs/Spotify-index-presentation-0702.pdfhttps://liveforlivemusic.com/news/digital-music-greenhouse-gas/https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/decomposed***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 07:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/28/3835680/3835680_247B957F8CB04771888FAF1204AAB3A6_190528_3835680_Music_streaming_maybe_contributing_to_climate_ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, carbon emissions, greenhouse gases, music, playlist, global warming, climate change,  music playlist, carbon footprint, music carbon footprint, songs, streaming music]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3836409</guid>
      <title>McDonald's creates McHives to raise decreasing bee population awareness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs part of a country-wide push to raise sustainability awareness in Sweden, various McDonald's franchises are installing bee hives called McHives on their rooftops. According to Greenpeace, honey bees perform 80 percent of all pollination. Seventy out of the top 100 human food cropswhich provide 90 percent of the world's nutritionare pollinated by bees.    However, overuse of pesticides and climate change are now causing global bee populations to decline. According to AdWeek, McDonald's in a partnership with marketing firm Nord DDB commissioned the project to raise awareness by creating bee hives that look like miniature replicas of McDonald's stores. The idea of a fully-functioning beehive began at one store in Sweden and has now expanded to five in the country. The hives were built by designer Nickals Nilsson. They are built to scale and include the McDonald's sign, a drive-thru, and patio seating.     McDonald's marketing director in Sweden Christoffer Rnnblad said, "we have a lot of really devoted franchisees who contribute to our sustainability work, and it feels good that we can use our size to amplify such a great idea as bee hives on the rooftops."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. McHive2. Bees pollinating flowers and crops, pesticide use and climate change have affected bee populations3. McHive on top of McDonald's store4. McHive exterior and interior makeupVOICEOVER (in English): "As part of a country-wide push to raise sustainability awareness in Sweden, various McDonald's franchises are installing beehives called McHives on their rooftops." "According to Greenpeace, honey bees perform 80 percent of all pollination. Seventy out of the top 100 human food cropswhich provide 90 percent of the world's nutritionare pollinated by bees."    "However, overuse of pesticides and climate change are now causing global bee populations to decline." "According to AdWeek, McDonald's in a partnership with marketing firm Nord DDB commissioned the project to raise awareness by creating beehives that look like miniature replicas of McDonald's stores." "The idea of a fully-functioning beehive began at one store in Sweden and has now expanded to five in the country." "The hives were built by designer Nickals Nilsson. They are built to scale and include the McDonald's sign, a drive-thru, and patio seating."     SOURCES: Adweek, Business Insiderhttps://www.adweek.com/brand-marketing/the-worlds-smallest-mcdonalds-illustrates-the-scale-of-a-declining-bee-population/https://www.businessinsider.sg/mcdonalds-opens-worlds-smallest-restaurant-for-bees-2019-5/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 12:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/29/3836409/3836409_302E9CEEA9324C85BCE30D399FB19DEA_190529_3836409_McDonald_s_creates_McHives_to_raise_decreasing_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, McDonald's McHives, McHives, McHive bee awareness, McHives bee population awareness, McDonald's, bees, bee hives]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3836389</guid>
      <title>iPhone apps use hidden trackers to share data without users' consent</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA privacy test conducted by Washington Post columnist Geoffrey Fowler has found that popular iPhone apps are using trackers and sharing user data, sometimes including sensitive information like email, phone number, location, and IP address.In a single week, Fowler encountered 5,400 data trackers, mostly within apps, which according to privacy firm Disconnect would send out 1.5 gigabytes of data in a month.In most cases, users are not aware that this is happening, or that the trackers are even present.Trackers can have different purposes. Some analyze user behavior in order to let apps improve performance, create targeted ads, or help identify fraud.But according to Disconnect Chief Technology Officer Patrick Jackson, there is a lack of transparency. Often, trackers don't anonymize data or limit retention time, and users aren't given clear information on where collected data is going or who it's shared with. According to Fowler, it's especially disappointing coming from Apple, which claims its software and hardware are "designed to provide advanced security and privacy at every level of the system.He suggested that Apple require apps to label when they are using third-party trackers, or add privacy controls to give users more visibility.In the meantime, concerned iOS users can turn off 'Background App Refresh' in settings, or use a VPN to limit the data that apps are able to send to third party companies.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. iPhone apps using trackers to share user data2. 5,400 trackers found in a week; trackers send out 1.5 gigabytes of data in a month3. Trackers serve different purposes4. Trackers don't give clear information on where data is going or who it's shared withVOICEOVER (in English): "A privacy test conducted by Washington Post columnist Geoffrey Fowler has found that popular iPhone apps are using trackers and sharing user data, sometimes including sensitive information like email, phone number, location, and IP address.""In a single week, Fowler encountered 5,400 data trackers, mostly within apps, which according to privacy firm Disconnect would send out 1.5 gigabytes of data in a month.""In most cases, users are not aware that this is happening, or that the trackers are even present.""Trackers can have different purposes. Some analyze user behavior in order to let apps improve performance, create targeted ads, or help identify fraud.""But according to Disconnect Chief Technology Officer Patrick Jackson, there is a lack of transparency. Often, trackers don't anonymize data or limit retention time, and users aren't given clear information on where collected data is going or who it's shared with. SOURCES: Washington Posthttps://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/05/28/its-middle-night-do-you-know-who-your-iphone-is-talking/?utm_term=.d277f6dbc85e***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 11:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/29/3836389/3836389_746DD157875B4C8683592C45D972D33C_190529_3836389_iPhone_apps_use_hidden_trackers_to_share_data_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, iphone, iphone apps, ios apps, app trackers, iphone app trackers, personal data, apple apps, user data, privacy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3836281</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover new plastic-eating bacteria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have found tiny microbes that are able to break down plastic waste found in the ocean, according to a study published in Science Magazine.The bacteria has been named Ideonella Sakaiensis.[a][b]In a separate study, researchers from the Technical University of Crete experimented with the bacteria. They collected samples of weathered plastic such as polyethylene and polystyrene debris from two different beaches in Greece.According to The European Scientist, polyethylene is commonly used to make plastic bags while polystyrene is typically used in food packaging.The researchers immersed both types of plastic in saltwater from the sea, according to Science Magazine.One batch had naturally-occurring ocean microbes added to the water, while the other had bacteria enhanced with carbon-eating microbe strains. The plastic-consuming microbes were used to speed up the chemical reactions normally required to break down plastic.After five months, the scientists weighed the plastic debris and found that the polyethylene had a weight reduction of 7 percent, while the polystyrene had a weight reduction of 11 percent.According to the study, the microbes could offer an attempt at solving the problem of plastic pollution. However, more research would be needed to see how effective the bacteria would be on a larger scale.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The bacteria Ideonella Sakaiensis[c][d] being pulled out from the ocean2. The plastic-eating microbe on a podium, two beaches and an inset of polyethylene and polystyrene 3. The bacteria breaking down the plastic in salt water4. The amount of plastic the bacteria was able to break downVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in Science Magazine, scientists have found tiny microbes that are able to break down plastic waste found in the ocean.""The bacteria has been named Ideonella Sakaiensis.[e][f]""In a separate study, researchers from the Technical University of Crete experimented with the bacteria. "They collected samples of weathered plastic such as polyethylene and polystyrene debris from two different beaches in Greece.""According to Science magazine, the researchers immersed both types of plastic in saltwater from the sea.""One batch had naturally-occurring ocean microbes added to the water, while the other had bacteria enhanced with carbon-eating microbe strains.""The plastic-consuming microbes were used to speed up the chemical reactions normally required to break down plastic.""After five months, the scientists weighed the plastic debris and found that the polyethylene had a weight reduction of 7 percent, while the polystyrene had a weight reduction of 11 percent."SOURCES: European Scientist, Science Magazine, Journal of Hazardous Materialshttps://www.europeanscientist.com/en/environment/can-plastic-eating-bacteria-help-solve-the-plastic-pollution-problem/https://science.sciencemag.org/content/351/6278/1196https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/05/these-tiny-microbes-are-munching-away-plastic-waste-oceanhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0304389419305060?via%3Dihub***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 09:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/05/29/3836281/3836281_9EEB4F40C17C45A680CC400229FE5123_190529_3836281_Scientists_discover_new_plastic_eating_bacteria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, bacteria, ocean, sea, plastic-eating bacteria, plastic-eating bacteria in the ocean, polyethylene]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3837753</guid>
      <title>7 dead, 21 missing in Budapest boat accident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least seven people are dead and 21 others missing after their tour boat capsized in Hungary.The Guardian reports that 33 South Koreans and two Hungarians were onboard a sightseeing boat called The Mermaid for an hour-long tour on Budapest's Danube river Wednesday night, despite poor weather.CCTV footage released by police shows the Mermaid and a 443-feet-long cruise ship called the Viking both travelling North on the river.""While approaching the pillars of the Magrit bridge, the Mermaid steered left into the path of the larger ship, and was hit from behind.According to the head of Budapest's disaster management office, the Mermaid capsized and sank just seven seconds later. The BBC reports that witnesses saw people in the water screaming for help.Seven people have been rescued, including one that was pulled from the water two miles south of the accident site. Seven are confirmed dead, while 21 others are still missing. CNN reports that none were wearing life jackets.According to police, rescue efforts were hampered by the rain and fast current on the Danube. Authorities have extended the search for the missing far downstream, even into Serbia, where the Danube flows, according to the L.A. Times.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nationality, number of passengers on tour boat2. Sightseeing boat hit from behind by larger cruise ship3. Sightseeing boat sinking; people in the water4. Rescue operation; number of rescued, dead, missingVOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports that 33 South Koreans and two Hungarians were onboard a sightseeing boat called The Mermaid for an hour-long tour on Budapest's Danube river Wednesday night, despite poor weather.""CCTV footage released by police shows the Mermaid and a 443-feet-long cruise ship called the Viking both travelling North on the river.""While approaching the pillars of the Magrit bridge, the Mermaid steered left into the path of the larger ship, and was hit from behind.""According to the head of Budapest's disaster management office, the Mermaid capsized and sank just seven seconds later.""The BBC reports that witnesses saw people in the water screaming for help.""Seven people have been rescued, including one that was pulled from the water two miles south of the accident site. Seven are confirmed dead, while 21 others are still missing.""CNN reports that none were wearing life jackets."SOURCES: The Guardian, BBC, CNN, L.A. Timeshttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/30/budapest-danube-boat-capsized-people-missinghttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-48468701https://edition.cnn.com/2019/05/29/europe/hungary-sightseeing-boat-sinks-on-danube-river/index.htmlhttps://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-hungary-south-korean-tourists-boat-sinks-20190530-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 19:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/06/01/3837753/3837753_B440808B9A1347D9B39C86A875ADC31B_190601_3837753_7_dead__21_missing_in_Budapest_boat_accident_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hungary boat accident, budapest boat accident, budapest boat crash, budapest boat tragedy, tourist boat, tour boat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
