<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 19:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3758238</guid>
      <title>Manchester New Year's Eve stabbings 'a terrorist investigation'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPolice are treating the stabbing of three people, including a police officer, on New Year's Eve at the Manchester Victoria railway station as a terrorist investigation. The stabbings occurred around 20:50 GMT when a 25-year-old suspect attacked a man and woman in their 50s, according to the Greater Manchester Police. The woman suffered injuries to her face and stomach, while the man sustained wounds to his stomach. A British Transport Police officer, who responded to the scene, was also stabbed in the shoulder. All three victims' injuries were described as "serious" but not life-threatening. The police officer was released from the hospital on Tuesday. According to witnesses,  police used pepper spray and a Taser to detain the attacker, who had been resisting arrest. Six or seven police officers were seen on top of the suspect, before he was finally arrested. According to the BBC, two knives were recovered at the scene and a residence is being searched in the Cheetham Hill area.  The attacker is currently being held on the suspicion of attempted murder. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of the attack2. Injuries suffered by victims3. Police used pepper spray and a taser 4. Police restraining the suspectVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Greater Manchester Police, the New Year's Eve stabbings occurred around 20:50 GMT when a 25-year-old suspect attacked a man and woman in their 50s at the Manchester Victoria railway station."  "The woman suffered injuries to her face and stomach, while the man sustained wounds to his stomach." "A British Transport Police officer, who responded to the scene, was also stabbed in the shoulder." "According to witnesses,  police used pepper spray and a Taser to detain the attacker, who had been resisting arrest." "Six or seven police officers were seen on top of the suspect, before he was finally arrested." "According to the BBC, two knives were recovered at the scene and a residence is being searched in the Cheetham Hill area."  SOURCES: BBC, CNNhttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-manchester-46728702https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-manchester-46724322https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/31/europe/manchester-stabbing/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 13:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/02/3758238/3758238_E386C577E4C040E89AC9BA10100419A2_190102_3758238_Manchester_New_Year_s_Eve_stabbings__a_terrorist_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, manchester stabbing, manchester new year's eve stabbings, new year's eve attack, UK new year's eve stabbing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3758232</guid>
      <title>Combating threat from deepfakes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAdvances in artificial intelligence software has led to the proliferation of fake digital images and videos referred to as "deepfakes."According to Neimen Lab, deepfakes use several techniques including faceswaps and  grafting a lip-syncing mouth or expression onto someone's face. According to MIT Technology Review, the technology behind deepfakes are called generative adversarial networks, or GANs. Media outlets like the Wall Street Journal are now training their journalists to detect deepfakes by finding older versions of footage using reverse image search engines like Google Images and Tineye. Reporters can also use video editing programs to look at clips frame-by-frame to look for distortions in the video. According to MIT Technology Review, experts say this is just the beginning for GANs. In the future algorithms will become more refined and harder to identify as fakes.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of a deepfake video2. Making a deepfake video3. Journalist scanning for fake images4. Journalist using video editing program to scan videoVOICEOVER (in English): "Advances in artificial intelligence software has led to the proliferation of fake digital images and videos referred to as 'deepfakes.'""According to Neimen Lab, deepfakes use several techniques including faceswaps and  grafting a lip-syncing mouth or expression onto someone's face." "According to MIT Technology Review, the technology behind deepfakes are called generative adversarial networks, or GANs." "Media outlets like the Wall Street Journal are now training their journalists to detect deepfakes by finding older versions of footage using reverse image search engines like Google Images and Tineye." "Reporters can also use video editing programs to look at clips frame-by-frame to look for distortions in the video." SOURCES: Nieman Lab, MIT Technology Reviewhttp://www.niemanlab.org/2018/12/fighting-the-reality-of-deepfakes/https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612501/inside-the-world-of-ai-that-forges-beautiful-art-and-terrifying-deepfakes/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 13:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/02/3758232/3758232_CA81CBFCC39E4F438ECA8F1A3B1A8639_190102_3758232_Combating_threat_from_deepfakes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Deepfakes, Deepfake video, Deepfake image, GANs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3758914</guid>
      <title>Indonesia tsunami volcano loses two-thirds of its height</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Indonesian volcano which caused a tsunami that killed more than 400 people last week now measures only 110 meters after losing two-thirds of its height.Anak Krakatau is a stratovolcano located in the Sunda Strait. Stratovolcanoes form through the accumulation of layers of viscous lava and ash through multiple eruptions.According to Volcano Discovery, the volcano has been active since around 1928. Its eruptions are strombolian.According to Science Magazine, strombolian eruptions occur when gas inside the volcano form bubbles called gas slugs. Gas slugs then rise through the magma column and throw magma into the air when they burst.Indonesia's Center for Volcanology and Geological Disaster Mitigation has analyzed images of the volcano from a number of radar satellites, including the European Union's Sentinel-1 constellation, the German TerraSAR-X platform, and Japan's Space agency. These show Anak Krakatoa, which used to stand at roughly 340 meters high, now just measuring 110 meters. According to AFP, the steady eruptions caused rock and ash from the volcano to gradually slide into the sea causing it to lose about 150 and 180 million cubic meters of material. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction Anak Krakatau location2. Depiction of strombolian eruptions 3. Representation of satellites photographing Anak Krakatau4. Depiction of landslide caused by Anak Krakatau eruption VOICEOVER (in English): "Anak Krakatau is a stratovolcano located in the Sunda Strait. Stratovolcanoes form through the accumulation of layers of viscous lava and ash through multiple eruptions.""According to Volcano Discovery, the volcano has been active since around 1928. Its eruptions are strombolian.""According to Science Magazine, strombolian eruptions occur when gas inside the volcano form bubbles called gas slugs. Gas slugs then rise through the magma column and throw magma into the air when they burst.""Indonesia's Center for Volcanology and Geological Disaster Mitigation has analyzed images of the volcano from a number of radar satellites, including the European Union's Sentinel-1 constellation, the German TerraSAR-X platform, and Japan's Space agency." "These show Anak Krakatoa, which used to stand at roughly 340 meters high, now just measuring 110 meters." "According to AFP, the steady eruptions caused rock and ash from the volcano to gradually slide into the sea causing it to lose about 150 and 180 million cubic meters of material." "Anak Krakatau, whose name translates to "Child of Krakatoa",  was formed around 1928 in the crater left by Krakatoa, the infamous volcano whose massive eruption in 1883 triggered a period of global cooling."SOURCES: Volcano Discovery, Science Magazine, AFP. https://www.volcanodiscovery.com/es/krakatau.htmlhttp://science.sciencemag.org/content/317/5835/227https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/indonesian-tsunami-volcano-lost-two-thirds-its-height-doc-1bv62n3***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 14:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/03/3758914/3758914_FAD26F69883941AA843F7710977C07AD_190103_3758914_Indonesia_tsunami_volcano_loses_two_thirds_of_it_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Indonesia, Indonesia tsunami volcano, Indonesia volcano, Indonesia tsunami, Anak Krakatau, Krakatau volcano, Krakatau, volcano explosion, Indonesia volcano video, Krakatau video, Krakatau volcano video, Sunda Strait, Java, Sumatra, the guardian, eruption, tsunami, tsunami Indonesia, earthquake, wave, volcano, volcanic, java sea, tsunami 2018, Indonesian, collapse, lava, ash, pyroclastic flow, strombolic eruption]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3758650</guid>
      <title>China builds massive radio antenna facility</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's new experimental radio antenna facility has been built on land that is 3,700 sq km in size and could possible be used for the Chinese military.The radio antenna will have the ability to emit extremely low frequency radio waves, called ELF waves, the South China Morning Post reports.The facility was built in the Huazhong region in central China.The World Health Organization has previously linked ELF waves to cancer.These radio waves will be emitted at a frequency of 0.1 to 300 hertz.They could be picked up by Chinese military submarines that are hundreds of meters deep in the ocean. However, the radio antenna could also be used to detect earthquakes and minerals.The project is a part of China's 11th five-year-plan, which Beijing uses to set targets, guidelines and policy goals for the coming years.China is downplaying the importance of the radio antenna facility in order to avoid causing public alarm, according to the South China Morning Post.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of China with a giant radio antenna2. The radio antenna emitting radio waves3. The radio waves being picked by an underground submarine4. The antenna could also be used to detect earthquakes and mineralsVOICEOVER (in English): "China's new experimental radio antenna facility has been built on land that is 3,700 sq km in size.""The South China Morning Post reports the radio antenna will have the ability to emit extremely low frequency radio waves, called ELF waves.""These radio waves will be emitted at a frequency of 0.1 to 300 hertz.""They could be picked up by Chinese military submarines that are hundreds of meters deep in the ocean.""However, the radio antenna could also be used to detect earthquakes and minerals."SOURCES: The South China Morning Post, The Drive, https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2180071/chinas-new-antenna-five-times-size-new-york-city-it-also-cancerhttp://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/25728/chinas-new-york-city-sized-earthquake-warning-system-sounds-more-like-way-to-talk-to-subs***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 08:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/03/3758650/3758650_AA19BF0DACE449E69881D6862E1567D8_190103_3758650_China_builds_massive_radio_antenna_facility_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, experimental radio antenna, wireless electromagnetic method project, WEM, wireless electromagnetic method project china, radio antenna, radio antenna facility, submarines, ELF waves]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3758485</guid>
      <title>Car carrier vessel catches on fire in the Pacific Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Panamanian car carrier ship was traveling from Japan to Hawaii when a fire suddenly broke out on New Year's Eve.The 650-foot vessel Sincerity Ace was around 2,000 miles northwest of Oahu at the time of the incident, Hawaii News Now reports.The Coast Guard, the Navy and two other commercial vessels rushed to the car carrier and managed to rescue 16 out of 21 crew members.The ship remains adrift at sea while rescuers rush to save the remaining crew members.Two crew members are still missing, while three others were located in the water and found unresponsive and "unable to grab onto life-saving equipment," according to the Honolulu Star-Advertiser.Rescuers are currently dealing with winds of up to 17 miles-per-hour and waves of up to 15 to 18 feet in length.In a statement, the Coast Guard did not specify what caused the fire on the car carrier.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dotted line from Japan to Hawaii and the carrier ship2. The carrier ship is on fire while the Coast Guard, Navy, and two other commercial vessels are shown going over to the carrier ship3. Three unresponsive victims under the sea and life-saving equipment4. The winds and waves at seaVOICEOVER (in English): "A car carrier ship was traveling from Japan to Hawaii when a fire suddenly broke out on New Year's Eve.""Hawaii News Now reports the 650-foot Panamanian vessel Sincerity Ace was around 2,000 miles northwest of Oahu at the time of the incident.""The Coast Guard, the Navy and two other commercial vessels rushed to the car carrier and managed to rescue 16 out of 21 crew members.""According to the Honolulu Star-Advertiser, two crew members are still missing, while three others were located in the water and found unresponsive and 'unable to grab onto life-saving equipment.'""Rescuers are currently dealing with winds of up to 17 miles-per-hour and waves of up to 15 to 18 feet in length."SOURCES: Hawaii News Now, Star Advertiser, http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2018/12/31/coast-guard-commercial-vessels-responding-large-fire-aboard-car-carrier-off-oahu/https://www.staradvertiser.com/2019/01/01/breaking-news/two-missing-three-unresponsive-after-fire-on-ship-headed-to-hawaii/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 03:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/03/3758485/3758485_B519F0ADEF6E4DE2BCCEBCEBD2AC67F0_190103_3758485_Car_carrier_vessel_catches_on_fire_in_the_Pacifi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, hawaii, fire, US coast guard, sincerity ace, sincerity ace fire, sincerity ace fire update, sincerity ace fire hawaii, car carrier, ship on fire at sea, pacific ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3759330</guid>
      <title>U.S. to hold missile drills off Okinawa base</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. military is expected to conduct its first missile drill this year near Japan's Okinawa Island to counter China.The U.S. plans to deploy surface-to-ship missiles during the drill, according to a report in Japan's Sankei newspaper cited by AFP.A mobile rocket launcher will also be tested as a countermeasure to threats from China's surface-to-sea ballistic missiles, Sankei reported.The drills come as Chinese vessels continue to sail the waters near Okinawa where many U.S. troops are stationed.Chinese military doctrine calls for the nation's armed forces to gain martine superiority within and be able to project power beyond what it calls the "first island chain," which links Okinawa, Taiwan and the Philippines.The U.S. is holding the drill to counter an increasingly assertive China as the country continues to rapidly build up its military and increase its naval activism in the region.Beijing insists that its maritime activities are only for self-defense.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. U.S. flag and Okinawa on a map2. Surface-to-ship missile3. A mobile rocket launcher and Chinese surface-to-sea ballistic missiles4. Two Chinese vessels sailing in the waterVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. military is expected to conduct its first missile drill this year near Japan's Okinawa Island to counter China.""According to a report in Japan's Sankei newspaper cited by AFP, the U.S. plans to deploy surface-to-ship missiles during the drill.""A mobile rocket launcher will also be tested as a countermeasure to threats from China's surface-to-sea ballistic missiles, Sankei reported.""The drills come as Chinese vessels continue to sail the waters near Okinawa where many U.S. troops are stationed."SOURCES: AFP, Straits Times, U.S. Department of Defensehttps://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/2180505/us-plans-conduct-first-missile-drill-near-divisive-okinawa-basehttps://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/eyeing-china-us-to-hold-missile-drill-in-japans-okinawa-reporthttps://media.defense.gov/2018/Aug/16/2001955282/-1/-1/1/2018-CHINA-MILITARY-POWER-REPORT.PDF***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 08:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/04/3759330/3759330_8A6E09DC2EA84F84AE6115B5404E32D2_190104_3759330_U_S__to_hold_missile_drills_off_Okinawa_base_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, japan, china, missile drill, okinawa us base, chinese ballistic weapons, okinawa us military base, first island chain, surface-to-ship missiles, mobile rocket launcher, surface-to-sea ballistic missiles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3759130</guid>
      <title>China's war on air pollution is causing ground pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's dramatic decrease of particulate matter has triggered a rise in ground-level ozone pollution.China has managed to reduce levels of fine particulate matter emissions by roughly 40 percent in just four years.However, research from Harvard's School of Engineering and Applied Sciences and the Nanjing University of Information Science and Technology shows this quick fall has triggered a rise in ground-level ozone pollution.According to the paper published in PNAS, researchers studied roughly 1,000 sites in China over the past five years. Their findings showed an increase of surface ozone levels in urban clusters of China, particularly Beijing and Shanghai. According to the Environmental Protection Agency, ground-level ozone is one of the main components of smog.Ground-level ozone is created by chemical reactions between oxides of nitrogen, known as NOX, and volatile organic compounds, or VOCs, under the presence of heat and sunlight.The study indicates that particulate matter, known as PM 2.5, acts as an absorbing agent of the radicals that make up ozone pollution.Its sharp decrease has left more radicals available to generate ground-level ozone. Researchers said in an article on the Harvard school's website that "extra efforts are needed to reduce NOx and VOC emissions in order to stem the tide of ozone pollution."According to the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, ground-level ozone is linked to aggravation of pulmonary diseases, lung and throat irritation, and higher probabilities of contracting a respiratory illness.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of China reducing gas emissions by 40 percent2. Depiction of cities in China studied in the paper3. Representation of oxides of nitrogen and volatile organic compounds floating reacting to heat and generating ground-level ozone pollution4. Representation of PM 2.5 absorbing oxides of nitrogen and volatile organic compoundsVOICEOVER (in English): "China has managed to reduce levels of fine particulate matter emissions by roughly 40 percent in just four years.""However, research from Harvard's School of Engineering and Applied Sciences and the Nanjing University of Information Science and Technology shows this quick fall has triggered a rise in ground-level ozone pollution.""According to the paper published in PNAS, researchers studied roughly 1,000 sites in China over the past five years. Their findings showed an increase of surface ozone levels in urban clusters of China, particularly Beijing and Shanghai." "According to the Environmental Protection Agency, ground-level ozone is one of the main components of smog.""Ground-level ozone is created by chemical reactions between oxides of nitrogen, known as NOX, and volatile organic compounds, or VOCs, under the presence of heat and sunlight.""The study indicates that particulate matter, known as PM 2.5, acts as an absorbing agent of the radicals that make up ozone pollution.""Its sharp decrease has left more radicals available to generate ground-level ozone. Researchers said in an article on the Harvard school's website that 'extra efforts are needed to reduce NOx and VOC emissions in order to stem the tideSOURCES: Harvard's School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, PNAS, EPA, CDChttps://www.seas.harvard.edu/news/2019/01/grad-student-profile-buse-aktashttps://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/12/26/1812168116https://www.epa.gov/ground-level-ozone-pollution/ground-level-ozone-basics#effectshttps://ephtracking.cdc.gov/showAirHealth***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/04/3759130/3759130_6B790530AF9A4996A2D9EE542ED03ACD_190104_3759130_China_s_war_on_air_pollution_is_causing_ground_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china pollution, air pollution, ozone pollution, China, Beijing, china air quality, china air pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3760747</guid>
      <title>What is African Swine Fever?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan and other countries in Asia are currently under high alert for African swine fever as the outbreak continues to rise in China.China continues to loosen rules amid the outbreak to ensure the supply of pork in the country ahead of the Lunar Year of the Pig, according to a Reuters report.African Swine Fever is caused by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family, according to the World Organisation for Animal Health.Symptoms include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen and legs, and diarrhea. In serious cases, it can cause death within 6 to 13 days.The disease is spread through direct contact with infected pigs. It could also be spread through indirect contact if the pigs consume contaminated food waste.China has already reported more than 90 cases of African Swine Fever since August last year.The deadly virus could survive in processed pork for a few months. It could also survive for years in frozen pig carcasses, according to the Guardian.China previously banned the transport of pigs from outbreak regions, but continues to allow pigs from unaffected regions to be freely transported to other areas in the country.Beijing also banned the use of food waste and pig blood in the production of pig feed in September 2018.African Swine Fever is fatal for pigs but the disease does not harm humans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A pig and an inset of the Asfarviridae virus2. Symptoms of African Swine fever3. How African Swine fever is spread4. Virus in processed pork and frozen pig carcassVOICEOVER (in English): "African Swine Fever is caused by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family, according to the World Organisation for Animal Health.""Symptoms include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen and legs, and diarrhea. In serious cases, it can cause death within 6 to 13 days.""The disease is spread through direct contact with infected pigs. It could also be spread through indirect contact if the pigs consume contaminated food waste.""According to the Guardian, the deadly virus could survive in processed pork for a few months. It could also survive for years in frozen pig carcasses."SOURCES: Reuters, Farm Journal's Pork, World Organisation for Animal Health, The Guardian https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-swinefever-regulation/china-eases-pig-transport-ban-to-ensure-supplies-amid-african-swine-fever-idUSKCN1OQ0O2https://www.porkbusiness.com/article/african-swine-fever-virus-discovered-animal-feed-products-chinahttps://www.porkbusiness.com/article/china-loosens-ban-african-swine-fever-ensure-pork-supplyhttp://www.oie.int/en/animal-health-in-the-world/animal-diseases/african-swine-fever/https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/oct/24/what-is-african-swine-fever-and-how-does-it-spread***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 08:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/07/3760747/3760747_A650689010FD4CFFAB01EE568873E8F1_190107_3760747_What_is_African_Swine_Fever__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Satire, China, African swine fever, pork, pigs, pork products, african swine fever china, african swine flu china, african swine fever outbreak in china, african swine fever symptoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3760646</guid>
      <title>New biologger designed to track sperm whale's behavior</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapanese researchers have developed a biologger that can be attached to a sperm whale's body.The device will use robotic technology to gather valuable information regarding the mammal's biology and behavior. The team behind the technology is comprised of researchers from Yamagata University and Teikyo University of Science. The biologger is powered by water currents generated as the whale swims. It uses flexible suction cups to cling onto and travel along the whale's body.The device has a so far successfully traveled across a flat surface at a depth of roughly 500 meters.The team plans to conduct its first experiments in the ocean around the Ogasawara islands, an area known to be inhabited by dolphins and whales, located 1,000 kilometers south of Tokyo.According to the science news website, TechXplore, the team's main objective is to capture video of sperm whales hunting and eating a giant squid.In order to achieve this, the rover will use its suction cups to travel to an area close to the whale's mouth. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of biologger on sperm whale.2. Depiction of the biologger's energy source and mode of operation3. Depiction of location of biologger experimentation4. Representation of spermwhale hunting down a giant squidVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from Yamagata University and Teikyo University of Science, in Japan have developed a biologger that can be attached to a sperm whale's body.""The device will use robotic technology to gather valuable information regarding the mammal's biology and behavior.""The biologger is powered by water currents generated as the whale swims. It uses flexible suction cups to cling onto and travel along the whale's body.""The device has a so far successfully traveled across a flat surface at a depth of roughly 500 meters.""The team plans to conduct its first experiments in the ocean around the Ogasawara islands, an area known to be inhabited by dolphins and whales, located 1,000 kilometers south of Tokyo.""According to the science news site, TechXplore, the team's main objective is to capture video of sperm whales hunting and eating a giant squid""In order to achieve this, the rover will use its suction cups to travel to an area close to the whale's mouth." SOURCES: TechXplorehttps://techxplore.com/news/2018-12-roving-biologger-sperm-whale-body.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 06:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/07/3760646/3760646_BBF583F8767842F7A268D07E8606900E_190107_3760646_New_biologger_designed_to_track_sperm_whale_s_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sperm whale, biologger, whale rover, giant squid, Japan, colossal squid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3760607</guid>
      <title>China probe touches down on far side of moon in historic landing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina's lunar probe has made history as the first spacecraft to touch down on the far side of the moon.Xinhua reports that the Chang'e 4 lunar craft lifted off from the Xichang Satellite launch center in Sichuan province on December 8, carrying a lander and a rover. It entered lunar orbit four days later.At 10:26 a.m. local Beijing time on January 3, the spacecraft landed in the South Pole-Aitken Basin, the moon's largest and oldest impact crater.According to CNN, the rover separated from the lander several hours after touchdown, and is expected to roam and explore the Von Karman crater.According to Space.com, the six-wheeled rover is equipped with a panoramic camera and a visible and near-Infrared imaging spectrometer.The lander is outfitted with a landing camera, terrain camera, and a low-frequency spectrometer. It will conduct low-frequency radio astronomy observations and see whether plants can grow in the low-gravity environment. It will also explore whether there is water or other resources at the poles.The New York Times reports that the probe has sent back the first close-up image of the moon's far side back to Earth using the relay satellite Queqiao.China's future space missions include sending a Chang'e 5 spacecraft to the moon next year that will return to Earth with samples, according to the Washington Post. A crewed mission is also in the works and slated for the early 2030s.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chang'e 4 launches from Sichuan province on December 8 with lander and rover2. Chang'e 4 enters lunar orbit3. Chang'e 4 lands on the far side of the moon4. Rover separates from lander after touchdown5. Features of the rover6. Features of the lander7. Lander's tasks on the far side of the moon8. Chang'e 4 communicating with ground control via relay satelliteVOICEOVER (in English): "The Chang'e 4 lunar craft lifted off from the Xichang Satellite launch center in Sichuan province on December 8, carrying a lander and a rover.""Chinese state media reports that it entered lunar orbit four days later.""At 10:26 a.m. local Beijing time on January 3, the spacecraft landed in the South Pole-Aitken Basin, the moon's largest and oldest impact crater.""CNN reports that several hours after touchdown, the rover separated from the lander on the moon's surface and is expected to roam and explore the Von Karman crater.""According to Space.com, the six-wheeled rover is equipped with a panoramic camera and a visible and near-Infrared imaging spectrometer.""The lander, meanwhile, is outfitted with a landing camera, terrain camera, and a low-frequency spectrometer.""It will conduct low-frequency radio astronomy observations and see whether plants can grow in the low-gravity environment. It will also explore whether there is water or other resources at the poles.""The New York Times reports that the probe has sent back the first close-up image of the moon's far side back to Earth using the relay satellite Queqiao."SOURCES: Xinhua, CNN, BBC, Washington Post, New York Times, Business Insider, Space.comhttp://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-01/03/c_137717597.htmhttps://edition.cnn.com/2019/01/02/health/china-lunar-rover-far-moon-landing-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-46724727https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/chinese-spacecraft-makes-first-landing-on-moons-far-side/2019/01/02/e2152ebe-0f0d-11e9-8f0c-6f878a26288a_story.html?utm_term=.2d5ead49e8bfhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/02/world/asia/china-change-4-moon.htmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/china-far-side-moon-landing-change4-site-map-2019-1https://www.space.com/42665-china-launches-moon-far-side-lander-rover.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 05:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/07/3760607/3760607_19C9BB701D36478BB665B5C31044BE57_190107_3760607_China_probe_touches_down_on_far_side_of_moon_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china moon mission, china lunar mission, china lunar probe, far side of the moon, dark side of the moon, chang'e 4, chang'e 4 spacecraft, china lands on moon, historic landing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3760579</guid>
      <title>Breath tester for cancer detection trialed in the UK</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Cancer Research UK Cambridge Center is launching a two-year clinical trial of a new breath test device that aims to identify molecules linked to certain cancers.According to a press release, the procedure will be tested on 1,500 participants including cancer patients and healthy participants.The technology is called Breath Biopsy and was developed by Owlstone Medical, a company dedicated to developing non-invasive cancer detection technology.The device used in these tests is called ReCIVA Breath Sampler. It analyzes molecules called Volatile Organic Compounds, or VOCs, present in exhaled breath.Cells regularly produce VOCs as part of their normal metabolic processes. Researchers participating in the trial believe the presence of cancerous cells could cause identifiable changes in VOC patterns. The ReCIVA is designed to detect these alterations.Participants will need to breathe into the device for 10 minutes. Samples of the participants' breath containing VOCs are collected in the device's Breath Biopsy Cartridge and then sent to a laboratory in Cambridge for analysis. The trial will be testing patients suspected to have esophageal, stomach, kidney, bladder, prostate, liver and pancreatic cancer.The results of the trials are expected to be published by 2021.David Crosby, head of early detection research at Cancer Research UK, said in the press release: "Technologies such as this breath test have the potential to revolutionize the way we detect and diagnose cancer in the future."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of doctor introducing ReCIVA to patient2. Representation of ReCIVA analyzing Volatile Organic Compounds3. Representation of ReCIVA detecting abnormal VOC patterns4. Representation of types of cancer to be analyzed in the trial VOICEOVER (in English): "The Cancer Research UK Cambridge Center is launching a two-year clinical trial of a new breath test device that aims to identify molecules linked to certain cancers.""According to a press release, the procedure will be tested on 1,500 participants including cancer patients and healthy participants.""The technology is called Breath Biopsy and was developed by Owlstone Medical,  a company dedicated to developing non-invasive cancer detection technology.""The device used in these tests is called ReCIVA Breath Sampler. It analyzes molecules called Volatile Organic Compounds, or VOCs, present in exhaled breath.""Cells regularly produce VOCs as part of their normal metabolic processes. Researchers participating in the trial believe the presence of cancerous cells could cause identifiable changes in VOC patterns. The ReCIVA is designed to detect these alterations.""Participants will need to breathe into the device for 10 minutes. Samples of the participants' breath containing VOCs are collected in the device's Breath Biopsy Cartridge and then sent to a laboratory in Cambridge for analysis." "The trial will be testing patients suspected to have esophageal, stomach, kidney, bladder, prostate, liver and pancreatic cancer.SOURCES: Cancer Research UK, Owlstone Medical https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/about-us/cancer-news/press-release/2019-01-02-clinical-trial-launches-to-develop-breath-test-for-multiple-cancers?_ga=2.44264422.372133073.1546566153-707109807.1546566153https://www.owlstonemedical.com/products/reciva/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 04:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/07/3760579/3760579_B99B23D1EC714EC2883A7698DD1854C4_190107_3760579_Breath_tester_for_cancer_detection_trialed_in_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cancer, cancer detection, cancer research, UK, Cancer Research UK, Cancer Research UK Cambridge Center, ReCIVA, Cambridge, Breath Biopsy, owlstone medical]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3761620</guid>
      <title>U.S. destroyer sailing near disputed islands causes complaints from China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has lodged stern complaints with the U.S. after an American navy vessel conducted patrols near disputed islands in the South China Sea.According to the spokesperson for the U.S. Pacific fleet, the USS McCampbell sailed within 12 nautical miles of the China-claimed Paracel Islands as part of a "freedom of navigation" operation. It was reportedly done to "challenge excessive maritime claims." China responded by dispatching military aircraft and naval vessels to identify the U.S. destroyer and warn it to leave the area.According to Al Jazeera, Chinese foreign ministry spokesman Lu Kang claims the U.S. ship "violated Chinese and international law, infringed on Chinese sovereignty, and undermined peace and stability."The South China Sea has long been contentious. Several countries have competing claims based on their exclusive economic zones, but China claims the entire body based on historic rights, using a nine-dash line to demarcate its territory.Since 2013, China has been building artificial islands in both the Paracels and Spratlys to bolster its claim.Washington has also expressed opposition over Beijing's militarization of the South China Sea, and its addition of military installations like radars and airstrips to islands and reefs.China has defended the construction as necessary for self defense, alleging that the U.S. is the one to blame for heightening tensions in the area with their patrols.This latest incident comes as talks between the two sides get underway in Beijing, following a 90-day truce on a bitter trade war that saw import tariffs imposed on hundreds of billions of dollars worth of goods.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. USS McCampbell sails 12 nautical miles within the Paracel Islands2. China dispatches military aircraft and vessels3. Chinese military aircraft and vessels intercept USS McCampbell4. Competing claims over the South China Sea 5. China building artificial islands in the South China Sea6. China adding military installations on artificial islands and reefsVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the spokesperson for the U.S. Pacific fleet, the USS McCampbell sailed within 12 nautical miles of the China-claimed Paracel Islands as part of a 'freedom of navigation' operation. It was reportedly done to 'challenge excessive maritime claims.'" "China responded by dispatching military aircraft and naval vessels to identify the U.S. destroyer and warn it to leave the area.""According to Al Jazeera, Chinese foreign ministry spokesman Lu Kang claims the U.S. ship 'violated Chinese and international law, infringed on chinese sovereignty, and undermined peace and stability.'""The South China Sea has long been contentious. Several countries have competing claims based on their exclusive economic zones, but China claims the entire body based on historic rights, using a nine-dash line to demarcate its territory.""Since 2013, China has been building artificial islands in both the Paracels and Spratlys to bolster its claim.""Washington has also expressed opposition over Beijing's militarization of the South China Sea, and its addition of military installations like radars and airstrips to islands and reefs."SOURCES: Reuters, Al Jazeerahttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/2181011/us-warship-sails-near-disputed-paracels-south-china-sea-tradehttps://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/01/warship-sails-south-china-sea-trade-talks-beijing-190107181145316.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 16:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/09/3761620/3761620_619ECB2507F54FE5851ED9A2963E4034_190109_3761620_U_S__destroyer_sailing_near_disputed_islands_cau_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, south china sea, south china sea conflict, south china sea dispute, sino us tensions, china us disputes, freedom of navigation, maritime patrol, uss mccampbell]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3761271</guid>
      <title>The science behind itch-induced scratching</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA recent study published in the journal Neuron reveals that a small category of neurons located in an area of the brain called the periaqueductal gray tracks itch-evoked scratching behavior in mice.  Researchers from the Chinese Academy of Sciences studied periaqueductal gray neurons of freely moving mice that were induced to scratch through injections containing histamine, or chloroquine. Histamine is an organic compound involved in itch perception and chloroquine is a medication used to treat malaria.The team then studied the itch-induced scratching behavior by observing the activity of a set of neurons that produce a neurotransmitter called tachykinin 1 or Tac1 which produces glutamate and neuropeptides.Scientists observed that when Tac-1 neurons were eliminated itch-induced scratching also decreased.Stimulating these neurons, on the other hand, resulted in spontaneous scratching behavior even without using histamine and chloroquine injections.Scientists participating in the study will continue to investigate which molecules in the Tac1 can be targeted by drugs. This would allow for the development of a drug that could be used to treat patients with chronic itch.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of neurons analyzed from mouse's head2. Representation of histamine and chloroquine injections used to induce  itch-evoked scratching behavior in mice3. Representation of Tac-1 neurons4. Representation of Tac-1 neurons being eliminated resulting in reduced itch-induced scratchingVOICEOVER (in English): "A recent study published in the journal Neuron reveals that a small category of neurons located in an area of the brain called the periaqueductal gray tracks itch-evoked scratching behavior in mice. " "Researchers from the Chinese Academy of Sciences studied periaqueductal gray neurons of freely moving mice that were induced to scratch through injections containing histamine, or chloroquine." "Histamine is an organic compound involved in itch perception and chloroquine is a medication used to treat malaria.""The team then studied the itch-induced scratching behavior by observing the activity of a set of neurons that produce a neurotransmitter called tachykinin 1 or Tac1 which produces glutamate and neuropeptides.""Scientists observed that when Tac-1 neurons were eliminated itch-induced scratching also decreased.""Stimulating these neurons, on the other hand, resulted in spontaneous scratching behavior even without using histamine and chloroquine injections."SOURCES: Neuron, TheJournal.iehttps://www.cell.com/neuron/fulltext/S0896-6273(18)31001-8https://www.thejournal.ie/how-the-brain-tells-you-to-scratch-an-itch-4379201-Jan2019/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 07:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/08/3761271/3761271_5F26E1C7EC314C38960757EF72850790_190108_3761271_The_science_behind_itch_induced_scratching_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Chinese Academy of Sciences, itch, scratch, itch induced scratching, itch, scratch, nervous system, inflammation, histamine, immune system, itching in mice, tac1, chloroquine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3762197</guid>
      <title>One dead, two missing after explosion rips through oil tanker in Hong Kong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn explosion ripped through an oil tanker off the coast of Hong Kong, killing one and leaving two others unaccounted for.According to the South China Morning Post reports, the Aulac Fortune is a 472-foot oil tanker with a 25-member Vietnamese crew. It unloaded oil cargo in Dongguan, China on Sunday, and stopped one nautical mile from Hong Kong's Lamma Island to refuel while en route to Thailand.While connecting hoses with an oil barge on Tuesday morning, crew members reportedly heard three explosions on the tanker.As fire broke out on the tanker's deck, sailors fell or jumped into the sea to escape the growing blaze.It took firefighters five hours to extinguish the flames on the tanker. One man died and seven others were injured, among them a Singaporean crew on the oil barge. Two are still missing.Yiu Men-yeung, Fire Services Department's division commander for marine and diving, told the South China Morning Post that there was no risk of the vessel sinking or of an oil leak, despite it tilting 30 degrees.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Aulac Fortune oil tanker crew count and route2. Oil tanker explodes while refueling with oil barge3. Oil tanker in flames, sailors jumping off the ship4. Oil tanker flames extinguished, number of casualtiesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Aulac Fortune is a 472-foot oil tanker with a 25-member Vietnamese crew. It unloaded oil cargo in Dongguan, China on Sunday, and stopped one nautical mile from Hong Kong's Lamma Island to refuel while en route to Thailand.""The South China Morning Post reports that while connecting hoses with an oil barge on Tuesday, crew members reportedly heard three explosions on the tanker.""As fire broke out on the tanker's deck, sailors fell or jumped into the sea to escape the growing blaze.""It took firefighters five hours to extinguish the flames on the tanker. One man died and seven others were injured, among them a Singaporean crew on the oil barge. Two are still missing."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, New York Timeshttps://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/society/article/2181128/emergency-crews-battle-oil-tanker-blaze-hong-kongs-lammahttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/08/world/asia/hong-kong-oil-tanker-fire.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 16:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/10/3762197/3762197_84C7422427444B3AA62DED0F9CA31723_190110_3762197_One_dead__two_missing_after_explosion_rips_throu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, oil tanker fire, oil tanker explosion, aulac fortune, tanker explosion, tanker fire, oil tanker catches fire, oil tanker on fire, lamma island, hong kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3761907</guid>
      <title>Sahara desert climate alters every 20,000 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study by MIT researchers suggests that the Sahara desert may have once flourished with nature.Their analysis of marine sediment from the West African coast suggests that the Sahara's climate alters between dry and wet every 20,000 years. The researchers believe this "climatic pendulum" is caused by changes to Earth's axis as it rotates around the sun.This in turn affects the amount of sunlight the Earth receives during different seasons.As the planet tilts to receive maximum sunlight, it intensifies periods of monsoon rain which results in a "greener" Sahara. When the Earth tilts toward an angle that doesn't allow it to receive as much sunlight, the Sahara gets a more arid climate.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A green Sahara desert with plants and animals2. Inset of ocean sediments and we see the Sahara desert turning green3. Earth rotating in space4. The Earth tilts toward the sun, which results in rain and the desert turns green5. The Earth tilts away from the sun, which turns the desert dry and aridVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study by MIT researchers suggests that the Sahara desert may have once flourished with nature.""Their analysis of marine sediment from the West African coast suggests that the Sahara's climate alters between dry and wet every 20,000 years.""The researchers believe this 'climatic pendulum'  is caused by changes to Earth's axis as it rotates around the sun.""As the planet tilts to receive maximum sunlight, it intensifies periods of monsoon rain which results in a 'greener' Sahara.""When the Earth tilts toward an angle that doesn't allow it to receive as much sunlight, the Sahara gets a more arid climate."SOURCES: Phys.org, MIT, Science Advances, https://phys.org/news/2019-01-sahara-swung-lush-conditions-years.htmlhttp://news.mit.edu/2019/study-regulating-north-african-climate-0102http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/5/1/eaav1887***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 08:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/09/3761907/3761907_65438A71FF8E4DD88056F7A88DF6C379_190109_3761907_Sahara_desert_climate_alters_every_20_000_years_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, US, sahara desert, dry climate, wet climate, sahara desert climate, sahara desert climate cycle, sahara desert lush, sahara desert 20000 years ago]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3761783</guid>
      <title>NASA reveals plans of the first planetary defense mission in history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA's Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART, is the first planetary defense mission in history. Its main objective is to demonstrate a kinetic impact on an asteroid.According to NASA, DART's target is a 150-meter moonlet called Didymos B, a small satellite orbiting a larger near-Earth asteroid called Didymos.The asteroid binary is located roughly 11 million kilometers from Earth. The spacecraft will be guided by an onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system. DART will crash against the moonlet at a speed of roughly 6 kilometers per second. Its objective is to change the speed and direction of the incoming object.The spacecraft is scheduled to launch in June 2021 and expected to hit the asteroid by October 2022.In 2013 a small 18-meter-wide meteor crashed into the Earth's atmosphere and entered over Chelyabinsk, Russia, creating a shockwave that hit six cities across the country.According to NASA, this event is proof of the importance of carrying out preventive planetary defense missions in space.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the Double Asteroid Redirection Test spacecraft2. Depiction of the asteroid binary Didymos3. Representation of the spacecraft using its onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system to detect the asteroid 4. Representation of the spacecraft crashing into the asteroidVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA's Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART, is the first planetary defense mission in history. Its main objective is to demonstrate a kinetic impact on an asteroid.""According to NASA, DART's target is a 150-meter moonlet called Didymos B, a small satellite orbiting a larger near-Earth asteroid called Didymos.""The asteroid binary is located roughly 11 million kilometers from Earth. The spacecraft will be guided by an onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system." "DART will crash against the moonlet at a speed of roughly 6 kilometers per second. Its objective is to change the speed and direction of the incoming object.""The spacecraft is scheduled to launch in June 2021 and expected to hit the asteroid by October 2022."SOURCES: NASAhttp://dart.jhuapl.edu/News-and-Resources/18-05389_DART_NASA-Compliant_FS-v9.pdfhttps://www.nasa.gov/planetarydefense/darthttp://dart.jhuapl.edu/Mission/index.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 04:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/09/3761783/3761783_57A9C3AB09A9443EA9E4CEE06A81786F_190109_3761783_NASA_reveals_plans_of_the_first_planetary_defens_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, planetary defense, NASA, DART, asteroid, meteor, double asteroid redirection test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3762740</guid>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg misses oral arguments recovering from lung surgery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSupreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg is missing oral arguments as she recovers at home from lung surgery.  According to Chief Justice John Roberts, Ginsburg did not attend oral arguments, but will participate in the cases and rulings by using the briefs and oral arguments, Reuters reported. Ginsburg underwent a pulmonary lobectomy on Dec. 21 at Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center in New York to remove two cancerous nodules in her left lung and was released from the hospital on Christmas Day. According to Health, the procedure removes one-half to one-third of the lung. The lung tissue removed does not regenerate, but the upper portion of the lungs helps to compensate. According to Raja Flores, MD, chair of thoracic surgery for Mount Sinai Health System and director of the thoracic surgical oncology program at the Tisch Cancer Institute at Mount Sinai taking to Health, it can take patients anywhere from a few weeks to three months to recover from a pulmonary lobectomy. Patients are trained practice deep breathing and coughing exercises to help the lungs re-expand post-operation. Some may also need additional oxygen while recovering in the hospital.This was Ginsburg's third cancer diagnosis. She broke three ribs in a November fall, which led physicians to discover the cancer in her lung. According to a statement from the Supreme Court, there is currently no signs of any cancer in Ginsburg's body and that no further treatment is needed at this time.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ginsburg had two cancerous nodules removed in pulmonary lobectomy2. Pulmonary lobectomy3. Patient recovering from pulmonary lobectomy4. Patient practicing deep breathing and coughing exercisesVOICEOVER (in English): "Ginsburg underwent a pulmonary lobectomy on Dec. 21 at Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center in New York to remove two cancerous nodules in her left lung and was released from the hospital on Christmas Day." "According to Health, the procedure removes one-half to one-third of the lung. The lung tissue removed does not regenerate, but the upper portion of the lungs helps to compensate." "It can take patients anywhere from a few weeks to three months to recover from a pulmonary lobectomy." "Patients are trained practice deep breathing and coughing exercises to help the lungs re-expand post-operation. Some may also need additional oxygen while recovering in the hospital."SOURCES: Reuters, Healthhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-ginsburg/u-s-top-courts-ginsburg-misses-oral-arguments-again-idUSKCN1P21M2https://www.health.com/condition/lung-cancer/ruth-bader-ginsburg-surgery***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 12:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/10/3762740/3762740_9F8B644B1E3443FDB2F42538CA804693_190110_3762740_Ruth_Bader_Ginsburg_misses_oral_arguments_recove_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Ruth Bader Ginsburg, Ruth Bader Ginsburg lung surgery, Ruth Bader Ginsburg pulmonary lobectomy, pulmonary lobectomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3762515</guid>
      <title>India ready for world's biggest religious festival</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIndia is all set for Kumbh Mela, the biggest religious festival in the world, beginning on January 15.The Indian town of Prayagraj, originally known as Allahabad, is getting ready for the annual Kumbh Mela festivities. Prayagraj will be the largest temporary city in the world during the festival, according to CNBC TV18.The festival of Kumbh Mela has also been added to UNESCO's list of "Intangible Cultural Heritage of Humanity," according to Times Now News.The Kumbh Mela celebrations takes place near the Triveni Sangam, which is where three sacred rivers in Hinduism meet together. People usually bathe in the water to wash off their sins.Preparations have been made so that devotees can pray at the "Akshay Vat," which is a sacred fig tree in Hinduism."Hindu monks that live in seclusion, often attend the Kumbh Mela to interact with the public and chant vedic mantras and play spiritual music.As many as 800 special trains will run to the city in order to prepare for the event, according to Times Now News. Airlines such as Air India have also announced flights to the holy city.The Kumbh Mela takes place over 55 days and will last until March 30.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hindu saints marching at the Kumbh Mela2. The Triveni Sangam and a saint bathing in the river3. Akshay Vat, a sacred fig tree for Hindus4. Hindu monks marching and playing musicVOICEOVER (in English): "The Indian town of Prayagraj, originally known as Allahabad, is getting ready for the annual Kumbh Mela festivities which is set to begin on January 15.""The Kumbh Mela celebrations takes place near the Triveni Sangam, which is where three sacred rivers in Hinduism meet together. "People usually bathe in the water to wash off their sins.""Preparations have been made so that devotees can pray at the 'Akshay Vat,' which is a sacred fig tree in Hinduism.""Hindu monks that live in seclusion, often attend the Kumbh Mela to interact with the public and chant vedic  mantras and play spiritual music."SOURCES: Times Now News, NDTV, Live Mint, India.com, CNBC, https://www.timesnownews.com/india/article/kumbh-mela-2019-largest-temporary-city-of-world-uttar-pradesh-prayagraj-yogi-adityanath/343604https://www.timesnownews.com/india/article/kumbh-mela-prayagraj-ardh-kumbh-mela-2019-important-dates-how-to-reach-where-to-stay-all-you-need-to-know-kumbh-mela-2019-map-kumbh-mela-date-and/342354https://www.ndtv.com/allahabad-news/for-kumbh-2019-prayagraj-to-have-worlds-largest-temporary-city-1974408https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/up-minister-says-rs-4-300-crore-set-aside-for-kumbh-mela-preparations-1973243https://www.livemint.com/Opinion/5UCi9CpfeEfjCpdOIbSx0M/Opinion-The-Kumbh-Mela-Indias-first-smart-city-and-more.htmlhttps://www.india.com/news-travel/what-to-expect-at-the-maha-kumbh-mela-happening-in-prayagraj-3510110/https://www.cnbctv18.com/market/data/kumbh-mela-2019-millions-expected-at-worlds-biggest-festival-1883211.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 07:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/10/3762515/3762515_6813C4E8D87D46D18CC758036BB45B05_190110_3762515_India_ready_for_world_s_biggest_religious_festiv_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, india, kumbh mela, world's largest religious festival, india kumbh mela, kumbh mela 2019, holy indian town, indian religious festival, prayagraj, prayagraj kumbh mela, prayagraj kumbh mela 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3762462</guid>
      <title>Trump wall could threaten wildlife and environment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA study from Stanford University published in the journal BioScience reports that the construction of a border wall between the US and Mexico could have serious consequences for the wildlife and environment surrounding the area.The US-Mexico border crosses through six eco-regions. These areas are home to diverse flora and fauna including 62 species tagged as critically endangered, endangered, or vulnerable by the International Union for Conservation of Nature.The wall will mainly degrade landscape connectivity, preventing species from reaching resources, mates and affecting migration. The report states that the wall would disconnect 346 species from half of their habitat including the endangered Peninsular bighorn sheep, the Sonoran pronghorn and the Mexican gray wolf.According to a report from the Center for Biological Diversity, the population of Mexican gray wolves is critically endangered growing by only four wolves from 2014 to 2017.Apart from affecting wildlife, the wall will also affect the flow of three major rivers: the Rio Grande, Colorado, and Tijuana Rivers.This also affects between 100 and 500 rivers and streams connected to them.A study by the University of Texas at Austin released in July last year reported that the wall could threaten the Tamaulipan thornscrub ecosystem, the endangered wildflower Zapata bladderpod, and the threatened whiskerbush cactus.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map showing US-Mexico border and iconographic depiction of endangerment of wildlife and plant life2. Map showing six ecoregions that cover the US-Mexico border3. Representation of construction of the border wall4. Representation of endangered species affected by the border wall5. Representation of Mexican Gray Wolf6. Map showing the Rio Grande, Tijuana and Colorado rivers and their tributaries7. Representation of endangered plant species affected by the border wall8. Representation of alternatives that will allow for wildlife movementVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study from Stanford University published in the journal BioScience, the construction of a border wall between the US and Mexico could have serious consequences for the wildlife and environment surrounding the area.""The US-Mexico border crosses through six eco-regions. These areas are home to diverse flora and fauna including 62 species tagged as critically endangered, endangered, or vulnerable by the International Union for Conservation of Nature.""The wall will mainly degrade landscape connectivity, preventing species from reaching resources, mates and affecting migration." "The report states that the wall would disconnect 346 species from half of their habitat including the endangered Peninsular bighorn sheep, the Sonoran pronghorn and the Mexican gray wolf.""According to a report from the Center for Biological Diversity, the population of Mexican gray wolves is critically endangered growing by only four wolves from 2014 to 2017.""Apart from affecting wildlife, the wall will also affect the flow of three major rivers: the Rio Grande, Colorado, and Tijuana Rivers.""This also affects between 100 and 500 rivers and streams connected to them.""A study by the University of Texas at Austin released in July last year reported that the wall could threaten the Tamaulipan thornscrub ecosystem, the endangered wildflower Zapata bladderpod, and the threatened whiskerbush cactus.""Researchers from this study suggest alternatives that could allow for wildlife movements such as wildlife crossings and electronic sensors."  SOURCES:  BioScience, Phys.orghttps://academic.oup.com/bioscience/article/68/10/740/5057517https://phys.org/news/2018-03-border-wall-texas-animals-scientists.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 06:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/10/3762462/3762462_8E957EAD1548400E9EF2EF6EC3DFF52D_190110_3762462_Trump_wall_could_threaten_wildlife_and_environme_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, President Trump, Trump border wall, US southern border wall, border wall wildlife, border wall plantlife]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3762390</guid>
      <title>BP finds a billion barrels of oil in the Gulf of Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBP discovered a billion barrels of oil as well as two new oilfields in the Gulf of Mexico, the company said in a press release on Tuesday.The British multinational oil and gas company found a billion barrels of oil at the offshore Thunder Horse oil field in the Gulf of Mexico using a new seismic imaging technique known as Full Waveform Inversion.Full Waveform Inversion uses advanced algorithms to create improved models of the Earth's subsurface by generating seismic wave simulations and comparing these with existing recorded data, BP explained in a press release in April of 2017.These models are used to create high-quality images of oil and gas reservoirs.The company also announced the approval of Atlantis Phase 3, a US$1.3 billion project that includes the construction of a new subsea production system located 150 miles south of New Orleans and covering roughly 2 kilometers.According to Tuesday's statement by BP, the company has expanded its production in the Gulf of Mexico by more than 60 percent.It aims to grow its production from 300,000 barrels of oil equivalent per day to 400,000 barrels of oil equivalent per day over the next decade.BP has been the biggest investor in the Deepwater Gulf of Mexico for the past 10 years, the company said.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Representation of Thunder Horse oil field location2. Representation of Full Waveform Inversion seismic imaging technique 3. Representation of subsea production system to be built in New Orleans4. Representation of increase of BP's oil productionVOICEOVER (in English): "British multinational oil and gas company BP has found a billion barrels of oil at the offshore Thunder Horse oil field in the Gulf of Mexico using a new seismic imaging technique known as Full Waveform Inversion.""Full Waveform Inversion uses advanced algorithms to create improved models of the Earth's subsurface by generating seismic wave simulations and comparing these with existing recorded data." "These models are used to create high-quality images of oil and gas reservoirs.""The company also announced the approval of Atlantis Phase 3, a US$1.3 billion project that includes the construction of a new subsea production system located 150 miles south of New Orleans and covering roughly 2 kilometers.""According to a statement by BP, the company has expanded its production in the Gulf of Mexico by more than 60 percent.""It aims to grow its production from 300,000 barrels of oil equivalent per day to 400,000 barrels of oil equivalent per day over the next decade."SOURCES: BPhttps://www.bp.com/content/dam/bp/business-sites/en/global/corporate/pdfs/news-and-insights/press-releases/bp-plans-for-significant-growth-in-deepwater-gulf-of-mexico.pdfhttps://www.bp.com/en/global/corporate/news-and-insights/press-releases/bp-takes-leap-forward-in-seismic-imaging-technology.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 05:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/10/3762390/3762390_710294083A7B42F4891DA175BF490E47_190110_3762390_BP_finds_a_billion_barrels_of_oil_in_the_Gulf_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, BP, BP oil production, oil rig, Atlantis Phase 3, Thunder Horse oil field]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3762296</guid>
      <title>Monarch butterfly populations decline by 86 percent in a year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANConservation groups have reported an 86 percent decline in the populations of the iconic monarch butterfly in California.Data from an animal conservation group called Xerces Society revealed that counts of overwintering monarch butterflies found in California had plummeted from 148,000 in 2017 to just 20,456 in 2018.According to research published in the Biological Conservation journal, monarch butterflies have a 72 percent risk of becoming extinct in 20 years.Several factors contribute to the dramatic decrease in monarch butterfly populations including habitat loss, pesticide use, and climate change.According to National Geographic, rising levels of carbon dioxide may be contaminating milkweed  a flowering plant that is the sole food source of the monarch caterpillar.Increasing temperatures may also affect the monarch butterfly's migration route, pushing butterflies to travel further up north and affecting summer breeding areas.Xerces Society is encouraging people to help restore the monarch butterfly population by planting nectar sources and milkweed and reducing pesticide use.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Graphical depiction of decrease in monarch butterfly populations2. Representation of monarch butterfly at risk of extinction3. Representation of elements influencing monarch butterfly extinction4. Representation of pesticide damaging milkweed flowersVOICEOVER (in English): "Data from an invertebrate animal conservation group called Xerces Society revealed that counts of overwintering monarch butterflies found in California had plummeted from 148,000 in 2017 to just 20,456 in a year.""According to research published in the Biological Conservation journal, monarch butterflies have a 72 percent risk of becoming extinct in 20 years.""Several factors contribute to the dramatic decrease in monarch butterfly populations including habitat loss, pesticide use, and climate change.""According to National Geographic, rising levels of carbon dioxide may be contaminating milkweed  a flowering plant that is the sole food source of the monarch caterpillar.""Increasing temperatures may also affect the monarch butterfly's migration route, pushing butterflies to travel further up north and affecting summer breeding areas."SOURCES: Xerces Society, Biological Conservation, National Geographichttps://xerces.org/2018/11/29/critically-low-monarch-population-in-california/https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2018/12/monarch-butterflies-risk-extinction-climate-change/https://www.westernmonarchcount.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/Western-monarch-PVA_Schultz-et-al.-2017.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/10/3762296/3762296_9BEC4557DA774CDE890AAFA9ECC17F22_190110_3762296_Monarch_butterfly_populations_decline_by_86_perc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, monarch butterfly]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3763273</guid>
      <title>Chile's Aculeo Lagoon dries up for the first time in 2,000 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChile's Aculeo lagoon, a body of water that used to cover 12 square kilometers located in Paine, Chile, has completely dried up for the first time in 2,000 years.According to researchers from the University of Chile, the disappearance of the body of water is due to urban and agricultural expansion as well as climate change and severe droughts.Data from Chile's National Statistics Institute shows that Paine's population has increased by 45 percent from 2002 to 2017.These communities have depleted the lagoon's water by building deep wells and extracting underground water from the aquifer.Also, agricultural activities in the area consisting mainly of  fruit plantations have extracted underground water and water directly from the lagoon 24 hours a day at a rate of up to 16 liters per minute.Pablo Garcia, a lead researcher from University of Chile said to Chilean newspaper Publimetro, "There was no territorial planning here, the municipality authorized the use of the land without considering whether there was enough water to sustain it."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Aculeo Lagoon location2. Causes of drought3. Water depletion due to urban expansion4. Water depletion due to agricultural activityVOICEOVER (in English): "Chile's Aculeo lagoon, a body of water that used to cover 12 square kilometers located in Paine, Chile, has completely dried up for the first time in 2,000 years.""According to researchers from the University of Chile, the disappearance of the body of water is due to urban and agricultural expansion as well as climate change and severe droughts.""Data from Chile's National Statistics Institute shows that Paine's population has increased by 45 percent from 2002 to 2017.""These communities have depleted the lagoon's water by building deep wells and extracting underground water from the aquifer.""Also, agricultural activities in the area consisting mainly of  fruit plantations have extracted underground water and water directly from the lagoon 24 hours a day at a rate of up to 16 liters per minute."SOURCES: Publimetro Chilehttps://www.publimetro.cl/cl/noticias/2018/06/26/dramatico-time-lapse-satelital-muestra-se-seco-la-laguna-aculeo.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 10:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/11/3763273/3763273_448360A305F54C2198BF5A981F9D4561_190111_3763273_Chile_s_Aculeo_Lagoon_dries_up_for_the_first_tim_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, laguna aculeo, aculeo lagoon, aculeo lagoon dries up, Chile, chile lagoon, drought, climate change, laguna de aculeo, laguna de aculeo chile, laguna de aculeo, gobierno de chile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3763159</guid>
      <title>Lack of deep sleep linked to early signs of Alzheimer's</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study has linked poor quality sleep to higher levels of a brain protein believed to cause Alzheimer's.Researchers from the Washington University School of Medicine studied the link between tau and sleep levels by recruiting 119 people over 60, most of whom were cognitively healthy.According to the study published in Science Translational Medicine, subjects' sleep patterns were monitored for a week using portable EEG monitors and wristwatch-like sensors.Tau and amyloid beta levels were also measured using either PET brain scans or spinal fluid sampling.The results show that those who had fewer hours of slow-wave sleep had higher volumes of the tau protein in their brain.Slow-wave sleep is the deepest phase of non-rapid eye movement sleep. This stage of the sleep cycle is also thought to be important for memory consolidation.According to study author Brendan Lucey, those who showed increased tau pathology slept more at night and napped during the day, but were not getting good quality sleep.While the findings are significant, the study is unclear on whether poor quality sleep is a cause or consequence of pathological changes in the brain.Researchers suggest, however, that sleep disruptions may be an effective tool for doctors to spot patients in the earliest stages of cognitive decline.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tau and amyloid beta proteins in the brain2. Protein build-up causes plaques in the brain3. Sleep patterns monitored using EEG monitor and wrist sensor4. Tau and amyloid beta levels measures using PET scan or spinal tap5. Less slow-wave sleep linked to higher volume of tau proteins in the brain6. Explanation of slow-wave sleep7. People with higher tau proteins slept more, but didn't get quality sleepVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists have long believed that the neurodegenerative disorder Alzheimer's results from the build-up of tau and amyloid beta proteins in the brain.""The proteins accumulate and form plaques and tangles, which can contribute to the degradation of neurons.""Researchers from the Washington University School of Medicine studied the link between tau and sleep levels by recruiting 119 people over 60, most of whom were cognitively healthy.""Subjects' sleep patterns were monitored for a week using portable EEG monitors and wristwatch-like sensors.""Tau and amyloid beta levels were also measured using either PET brain scans or spinal fluid sampling.""The results show that those who had fewer hours of slow-wave sleep had higher volumes of the tau protein in their brain.""Slow-wave sleep is the deepest phase of non-rapid eye movement sleep. This stage of the sleep cycle is also thought to be important for memory consolidation.""According to study author Brendan Lucey, those who showed increased tau pathology slept more at night and napped during the day, but were not getting good quality sleep."SOURCES: Science Daily, Science Translational Medicinehttps://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/01/190109142704.htmhttp://stm.sciencemag.org/content/11/474/eaau6550***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 08:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/11/3763159/3763159_B6513F0EBE5C4013A8BFA72419645FEE_190111_3763159_Lack_of_deep_sleep_linked_to_early_signs_of_Alzh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, alzheimers, alzheimer's, slow wave sleep, sleep, tau, tau protein, amyloid beta, amyloid protein, quality sleep, deep sleep]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3763143</guid>
      <title>India's supreme court to hear controversial Ayodhya case</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Indian Supreme Court is expected to hear the controversial Ayodhya case on Jan 29.The case concerns a highly contentious plan to build a Hindu temple on the ruins of a mosque from the Mughal era. The site has been disputed between Hindus and Muslims ever since it was built in the 16th Century.Supporters of the current government are pushing for a temple of the hindu god Ram to be built in place of the ruins of Babri Masjid, especially since elections are to take place in May, Reuters reports. This was one of the key promises Prime Minister Narendra Modi made during his previous election campaign, according to BBC News.Babri Masjid was built in the city of Ayodhya during the Mughal era. Hindu mobs tore it down in 1992. This triggered communal riots in the country and killed around 2,000 people. Today the site is in ruins, with a tiny makeshift Ram temple in its place.Hindus claim the mosque was built on the site of the birthplace of Lord Ram. However, several Hindu nationalists want to build a fully fledged temple of Ram in its place.The Allahabad High Court previously ruled that the land should be divided in three parts, reported the Times of India.  One for the Hindu deity, one for a Hindu-nationalist group and one for the Sunni Waqf Board. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ayodhya on a map.1. Babri masjid then and now2. A tiny Ram temple in its place3. A large Ram temple in the place of the mosque4. The Babri Masjid in ruins and a pie chart VOICEOVER (in English): "Babri Masjid was built in the city of Ayodhya during the Mughal era. "Hindu mobs tore it down in 1992. ""Today the site is in ruins, with a tiny makeshift Ram temple in its place.""However, several Hindu nationalists want to build a fully fledged temple of Ram in its place.""According to Times of India, the Allahabad High Court previously ruled that the land should be divided in three parts."That is one for the Hindu deity, one for a Hindu-nationalist group and one for the Sunni Waqf Board."SOURCES: BBC News, Reuters, Times of India, https://www.bbc.com/news/blogs-trending-34974029https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion/indias-top-court-to-name-panel-to-weigh-demand-for-temple-on-disputed-site-idUSKCN1OY0AI?feedType=RSS&feedName=worldNews&utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+Reuters%2FworldNews+%28Reuters+World+News%29https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/ayodhya-case-justice-lalit-recuses-himself-next-hearing-on-january-29/articleshow/67467061.cms***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 08:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/11/3763143/3763143_E4EC4ECA41984057AD7778DA2BC0FED0_190111_3763143_India_s_supreme_court_to_hear_controversial_Ayod_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, india, indian supreme court, ayodhya, ram mandir, ram mandir ayodhya fight, ram mandir babri masjid, babri masjid,hindu temple, mosque]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3762926</guid>
      <title>Robot dogs could soon be used to deliver packages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANContinental AG showcased a new driverless vehicle with delivery robot dogs this week at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas, TechCrunch reports.The Continental Urban Mobility Experience, or CUbE, will be able to drive on streets by itself and arrive outside a person's doorstep, the company said in a press release. Delivery robot dogs will then be deployed from the vehicle for the last step of the process, according to the press release. The delivery robots will be able to run up to a person's doorstep to deliver their package.The automated vehicle will be able to carry multiple robot dogs and handle deliveries to several houses at once, the company said.Continental AG is a German manufacturing company best known for creating brake systems and tires, among other things, for the automotive industry.The company's press release said this system addresses the need for unique and efficient delivery methods to cope with the increasing popularity of online shopping.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The driverless vehicle and the delivery robot dog2. The vehicle driving itself on the street3. The delivery robot dog comes out of the driverless vehicle4. The delivery robot delivers a package to a person's front doorVOICEOVER (in English): "Continental AG showcased a new driverless vehicle with delivery robot dogs this week at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas, TechCrunch reports.""The Continental Urban Mobility Experience, or CUbE, will be able to drive on streets by itself and arrive outside a person's doorstep, the company said in a press release.""The company says delivery robot dogs will then be deployed from the vehicle for the last step of the process." "The delivery robots will be able to run up to a person's doorstep to deliver their package."SOURCES: TechCrunch, Continental AG, https://techcrunch.com/2019/01/07/robot-delivery-dogs-deployed-by-self-driving-cars-are-coming/?utm_source=tcfbpage&sr_share=facebookhttps://www.continental-corporation.com/en/press/press-releases/ces2019-157096***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 03:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/11/3762926/3762926_B748116CCBEB4E5A8DD6CF5F6AF0B54D_190111_3762926_Robot_dogs_could_soon_be_used_to_deliver_package_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, robot delivery dogs, autonomous robot dogs, robots, driverless vehicles, Continental, Continental Urban Mobility Experience, delivery robots, technology, robot delivery service, autonomous vehicle technology, automated goods delivery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3764672</guid>
      <title>Britain plans to set up naval base in Southeast Asia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe South China Morning Post reports that the UK's foreign and defense ministers have said Britain is planning to establish a permanent naval base in Southeast Asia.The location of the base will likely be in Brunei, although Singapore is also being considered.According to an opinion piece in the Washington Examiner, establishing a naval base in Brunei would allow the UK to support the Americans in "corralling Chinese forces" by limiting their movement and offering force replenishment.They can also provide strike power by deploying Astute-class submarines at the base. Powerful torpedos and a high-capability sonar system allows the submarines to "complement U.S. Virginia-class counterparts in threatening the enemy while unseen."Brunei is already host to a British Army base, where an infantry battalion of Royal Gurkha Rifles are stationed, along with an Army Air Corps Flight of Bell 212 helicopters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. British naval base in Brunei2. Astute-class submarine deployed at naval base3. Existing British military base in Brunei4. Franco-British carrier strike group5. U.S. freedom of navigation in the South China Sea6. China claims in the South China Sea7. Chinese-built artificial islands in the South China Sea8. British military hardwareVOICEOVER (in English): "According to an opinion piece in the Washington Examiner, establishing a naval base in Brunei would allow the UK to support the Americans in 'corralling Chinese forces' by limiting their movement and offering force replenishment.""They can also provide strike power by deploying Astute-class submarines at the base. Powerful torpedos and a high-capability sonar system allows the submarines to 'complement U.S. Virginia-class counterparts in threatening the enemy while unseen.'""Brunei is already host to a British Army base, where an infantry battalion of Royal Gurkha Rifles are stationed, along with an Army Air Corps Flight of Bell 212 helicopters.""According to a British Ministry of Defense document, a Franco-British carrier strike group may also be deployed in the early 2020s." "The UK's HMS Queen Elizabeth and HMS Prince of Wales, and France's Charles de Gaulle will rotate as the formation's primary warship.""The move is set to complement Washington's strategy of asserting freedom of navigation in the Indo-Pacific region, particularly in the South China Sea.""But Beijing will likely see it as a threat, especially since the country claims the entire South China Sea as its own, and has militarized several disputed islands in the region.""According to CNN, a naval base in Asia may also serve as a 'showroom' for military hardware and could result in big arms deals that would benefit the UK's post-Brexit economy."SOURCES: South China Morning Post, Washington Examiner, Asia Times, CNN, British Ministry of Defencehttps://www.scmp.com/comment/insight-opinion/asia/article/2181540/new-british-naval-base-southeast-asia-could-stokehttps://sg.news.yahoo.com/britain-planned-naval-southeast-asia-120338262.htmlhttps://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/how-britain-will-support-america-with-a-new-naval-base-in-southeast-asiahttp://www.atimes.com/article/uks-hopes-of-indo-pacific-strike-group-with-france-premature/http://www.atimes.com/article/new-global-britain-sets-naval-sights-on-asia/https://edition.cnn.com/2019/01/03/asia/britain-military-bases-asia-intl/index.htmlhttps://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/742817/UKFR_MilitaryCooperationA5.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 10:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/14/3764672/3764672_27EC171F99C648A4927C70469456E113_190114_3764672_Britain_plans_to_set_up_naval_base_in_Southeast__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, british navy, naval base, british naval base brunei, global britain, uk naval base asia, south china sea, carrier strike group, royal british navy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3764588</guid>
      <title>Green Darner Dragonfly annual migratory cycle revealed for the first time ever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team from the University of Maryland Baltimore County is the first to determine the annual migratory cycle of the green darner dragonfly.According to the paper published in the journal Biology Letters, researchers employed stable-hydrogen isotope analysis on wing samples of more than 800 dragonflies from eight different countries spanning 140 years. The wings analyzed were from specimens caught in the wild and from specimens preserved in museums.The researchers found it takes three generations of green darners to complete an annual migratory cycle.The first migration occurs between February and March. Dragonflies depart from southern United States, Mexico and the Caribbean by May they reach the upper Midwest. The first generation lays its eggs there and dies.Dragonflies from the second generation head South again once they reach maturity and deposits another batch of eggs when they arrive at their destination.The third and last generation does not migrate but produces another batch of eggs that will restart the cycle once again the following spring.Researchers have not yet understood how migratory insects know what path to take during their migration cycles. Although climate change may pose a threat to this natural process.Researchers participating in the study stated, "further research is needed to determine how a changing climate may alter the migratory schedules and annual cycle of dragonflies and other migratory insects." RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Green Darner dragonfly in its natural habitat 2. Chemical analysis of the dragonfly's wings 3. Dragonflies migrate from southern United States, Mexico and the Caribbean to the upper Midwest4. Dragonflies return to the south to lay eggs and restart the cycle VOICEOVER (in English): "A team from the University of Maryland Baltimore County is the first to determine the annual migratory cycle of the green darner dragonfly." "According to the paper published in the journal Biology Letters, researchers employed stable-hydrogen isotope analysis on wing samples of more than 800 dragonflies from eight different countries spanning 140 years." "The wings analyzed were from specimens caught in the wild and from specimens preserved in museums.""The researchers found it takes three generations of green darners to complete an annual migratory cycle.""The first migration occurs between February and March. Dragonflies depart from southern United States, Mexico and the Caribbean by May they reach the upper Midwest. The first generation lays its eggs there and dies.""Dragonflies from the second generation head South again once they reach maturity and deposits another batch of eggs when they arrive at their destination.""The third and last generation does not migrate but produces another batch of eggs that will restart the cycle once again the following spring."SOURCES: Biology Lettershttps://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsbl.2018.0741***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 09:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/14/3764588/3764588_0D23E282F0774980BE50BCE92BA4B536_190114_3764588_Green_Darner_Dragonfly_annual_migratory_cycle_re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Dragonfly migration, University of Maryland Baltimore County, annual migratory cycle, dragonfly annual migratory cycle, green darner dragonfly, green darner dragonfly migration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3764523</guid>
      <title>Germany and Russia's Nordstream 2 pipeline explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRussia and Germany plan to build an energy pipeline that will bypass Ukraine, according to DW. The pipeline, named "Nord Stream 2", will be 1,200 kilometers long. It is planned to connect Europe to natural gas reserves in northern Russia, according to offshoretechnology.com.The project is being led by Russia and is expected to bypass Ukraine and run under the Baltic Sea. DW reports Germany and Russia both want to expand the pipeline from the existing Nord Stream 1. Both nations also want to double its current capacity.According to RT, the pipeline will carry natural gas from Russia to Europe and could provide up to 70 percent of Europe's gas needs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Nord Stream 2 pipeline1.Europe and northern Russia on a map1.Inset of natural gas reserves in Russia2. Russian flag, Ukranian flag and the Baltic Sea on a map3. Nord Stream pipeline 1 and 2 on a map4.The Nord Stream 2 pipeline4. Inset of natural gas4. European Union flag and a vertical measurement barVOICEOVER (in English): "The Nord Stream 2 pipeline will be 1,200 kilometers long." "It is planned to connect Europe to natural gas reserves in northern Russia, according to offshoretechnology.com.""The project is being led by Russia and is expected to bypass Ukraine and run under the Baltic Sea.""DW reports Germany and Russia both want to expand the pipeline from the existing Nord Stream 1. Both nations also want to double its current capacity.""According to RT, the pipeline will carry natural gas from Russia to Europe and could provide up to 70 percent of Europe's gas needs."SOURCES: RT, DW, Nord-Stream 2 website, Off Shore Technology, Reuters,https://www.rt.com/business/448369-us-threatens-nord-stream-partners/https://www.dw.com/en/nord-stream-2-gas-pipeline-what-is-the-controversy-about/a-44677741https://www.nord-stream2.com/https://www.offshore-technology.com/projects/nord-stream-2-pipeline/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-russia-pipeline/us-sanctions-against-nord-stream-2-wrong-solution-germanys-maas-idUSKCN1P42IH***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 07:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/14/3764523/3764523_495410F8A510498A8033496660CC5819_190114_3764523_Germany_and_Russia_s_Nordstream_2_pipeline_expla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, russia, germany, nord stream 2 pipeline, EU, European Union, nord stream 2 gas pipeline, nord stream 2 controversy, nord stream 2 news, nord stream 2 pipeline explainer, nord stream 2 pipeline map]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3764374</guid>
      <title>Dental floss could be linked to toxic chemicals, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANCertain types of dental floss may increase the amount of toxic chemicals present in the body, according to a new study published in the Journal of Exposure Science & Environmental Epidemiology.Researchers in the study, led by the Silent Spring Institute in collaboration with the Public Health Institute in Berkeley, California, tested for the presence of PFAS in six different dental flosses.To do this, the researchers examined the blood samples of 178 middle-aged female participants.The study found that women who flossed using Oral-B Glide had higher levels of PFAS, or polyfluoroalkyl substances, present in the body than women who used other brands of floss.In a statement to USA Today, Oral-B said they didn't find the toxic chemical in their floss and said their dental floss "undergoes thorough safety testing."The company added: "The safety of the people who use our products is our top priority."PFAS are typically found in food packaging, cleaning products and drinking water, according to the EPA.This is the first study to link dental floss to PFAS, according to the study.PFAS could build up over time and may cause health problems. PFAS has previously been linked to thyroid disease, high cholesterol and decreased fertility, according to the EPA.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dental floss and a male medical body2. Dental floss, PFAS and a test tube with a blood sample3. Oral-B Glide, PFAS and a measurement bar4. Where PFAS is typically foundVOICEOVER (in English): "Certain types of dental floss may increase the amount of toxic chemicals present in the body, according to a new study published in the Journal of Exposure Science & Environmental Epidemiology.""The researchers tested for the presence of PFAS in six different dental flosses.""To do this, the researchers examined the blood samples of 178 middle-aged female participants.""The study found that women who flossed using Oral-B Glide had higher levels of PFAS, or polyfluoroalkyl substances, present in the body than women who used other brands of floss.""According to the EPA, PFAS are typically found in food packaging, cleaning products and drinking water.""This is the first study to link dental floss to PFAS."SOURCES: Journal of Exposure Science & Environmental Epidemiology, EPA, USA Today, Silent Spring Institutehttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41370-018-0109-yhttps://www.epa.gov/pfas/basic-information-pfashttps://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/01/09/oral-b-glide-floss-toxic-pfas-chemicals-study/2530661002/https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-01/ssi-dfa010819.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 03:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/14/3764374/3764374_7D7D8D7AEE7E47109B0E7C7A50198C38_190114_3764374_Dental_floss_could_be_linked_to_toxic_chemicals__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, floss, dental floss, oral-b, oral-b glide floss, PFAS, PFAS chemicals, PFAS chemicals dental floss, dental floss linked to PFAS, polyfluoroalkyl, polyfluoroalkyl effects, polyfluoroalkyl chemicals, toxic chemicals, polyfluoroalkyl substances]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3765290</guid>
      <title>Less than six hours sleep per night may increase heart disease risk, study says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANPeople who sleep less than six hours a night might have an increased risk of cardiovascular disease compared to those who sleep seven to eight hours, according to a new study published in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology.  According to UPI, the study published on Jan. 14 found that chronic lack of sleep or poor sleep quality were associated with increased chances of atherosclerosis, a condition where fatty plaque accumulates in the arteries which can lead to heart attack or stroke. For the study, lead researcher Jose Ordovas from the National Center for Cardiovascular Research in Madrid and his team tracked around 4,000 Spanish adults using coronary ultrasound and CT scans to monitor artery health. Participants did not have a prior history of heart disease at the start of the study and had an average age of 46. Researchers was unable to prove cause and effect, but they found people who slept less than six hours a night were 27 percent more likely to have body-wide atherosclerosis than those who slept seven to eight hours a night. The study also found that women who slept more than eight hours a night had an increased chance of atherosclerosis. Adults with poor-quality sleep were also 34 percent more likely to have atherosclerosis, compared to individuals with good-quality sleep. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People who sleep less than 6 hours a night have increased heart disease risk2. Atherosclerosis3. Participants monitored with CT scans and coronary ultrasound; people who slept less than 6 hours have higher rates of atherosclerosis4. People with poor quality sleep and women who slept more than 8 hours had higher rates of atherosclerosisVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a new study published in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology on Jan 14, people who sleep less than six hours a night might have an increased risk of cardiovascular disease compared to those who sleep seven to eight hours."  "According to UPI, the study found that chronic lack of sleep or poor sleep quality were associated with increased chances of atherosclerosis, a condition where fatty plaque accumulates in the arteries which can lead to heart attack or stroke." "Researchers tracked around 4,000 Spanish adults using coronary ultrasound and CT scans to monitor artery health." "They were unable to prove cause and effect, but found people who slept less than six hours a night were 27 percent more likely to have body-wide atherosclerosis than those who slept seven to eight hours a night." "Adults with poor-quality sleep were also 34 percent more likely to have atherosclerosis, compared to individuals with good-quality sleep." "The study also found that women who slept more than eight hours a night had an increased chance of atherosclerosis." SOURCES: UPIhttps://www.upi.com/Health_News/2019/01/14/Study-Less-than-six-hours-sleep-per-night-increases-risk-for-heart-disease/8491547500288/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 10:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/15/3765290/3765290_00EDD00F65B24C1B9FFFCC723F96CCDE_190115_3765290_Less_than_six_hours_sleep_per_night_may_increase_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sleep, sleep study, sleep heart disease, sleep heart disease risk, healthy sleep, unhealthy sleep]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3765168</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk shares images of Mars-bound rocket, Starship.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANLast Thursday SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk shared new images of the Starship.According to the images shared on Musk's Twitter account last Thursday, the Starship prototype, called Starship Hopper, has a shiny steel finish with a nine-meter tank diameter.Musk also mentioned that the prototype will be used in suborbital vertical take-off and landing tests, also known as suborbital "hops". The first orbital prototype is scheduled to be finished by June this year.The orbital version of the Starship will be launched with a giant rocket called the Super Heavy Rocket and will have the capacity to carry up to 100 passengers. Musk said this version will have "thicker skins that will not wrinkle and a smoothly curving nose section." The final version of the Starship and Super heavy Rocket will also carry out long-distance travel around Earth.According to SpaceX, it will take them only 25 minutes to travel from Los Angeles to New York and less than 40 minutes to complete a flight from London to Hong Kong. Flights on those routes last 5 and a half hours and almost twelve hours respectively.SpaceX hopes to launch a manned mission to Mars as soon as 2024. Japanese billionaire, Yusaku Maezawa, is the company's first private customer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Model of Starship prototype2. Starship prototype dimensions3. Suborbital vertical take-offs and suborbital hops4. Starship passenger capacity and space travelVOICEOVER (in English): "Last Thursday SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk shared new images of the Starship.""According to the images shared on Musk's Twitter account last Thursday, the Starship prototype, called Starship Hopper, has a shiny steel finish with a nine-meter tank diameter.""Musk also mentioned that the prototype will be used in suborbital vertical take-off and landing tests, also known as suborbital "hops". "The first orbital prototype is scheduled to be finished by June this year.""The orbital version of the Starship will be launched with a giant rocket called the Super Heavy Rocket and will have the capacity to carry up to 100 passengers." "Musk said this version will have "thicker skins that will not wrinkle and a smoothly curving nose section." "SOURCES: Space.com, SpaceXhttps://www.space.com/42979-spacex-starship-test-vehicle-photo.htmlhttps://www.spacex.com/mars***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 08:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/15/3765168/3765168_88D5CDF6622A4A3A86D9CCDB46561306_190115_3765168_Elon_Musk_shares_images_of_Mars_bound_rocket__St_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Elon Musk, SpaceX, interplanetary travel, mars, missions to mars, spacex mars, spacecraft, space race]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3765135</guid>
      <title>Scientists build space probe that uses steam for propulsion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists are building a space probe that could extract water from asteroids and travel indefinitely in space.Researchers from the University of Central Florida have developed a spacecraft that could generate steam for propulsion by extracting water from asteroids or other planets.The project is a collaboration between NASA, the University of Central Florida and Honey Bee Robotics, according to the University of Central Florida's news release.The spacecraft is called the World Is Not Enough, or WINE, and would be the size of a microwave oven.The probe would extract water from other terrestrial planets and use deployable solar panels to create enough energy to generate steam.The space probe would then be able to visit places with low gravity and water such as the Moon, Pluto and Europa to refuel and mine.Theoretically speaking, the space probe could go on to explore space forever, as long as it doesn't run out of fuel.In the university's news release, Phil Metzger, UCF's planetary research scientist said: "WINE was designed to never run out of propellant so [that] exploration will be less expensive."The team is currently seeking partners to continue creating the space probe.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The moon, inset of water and the space probe generating steam2. The spacecraft with a measurement line underneath3. The space probe using solar panels to generate steam and propelling itself4. The Moon, Pluto and EuropaVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the University of Central Florida have developed a spacecraft that could generate steam for propulsion by extracting water from asteroids or other planets.""The spacecraft is called the World Is Not Enough, or WINE, and would be the size of a microwave oven.""The probe would extract water from other terrestrial planets and use deployable solar panels to create enough energy to generate steam.""The space probe would then be able to visit places with low gravity and water such as the Moon, Pluto and Europa to refuel and mine."SOURCES: University of Central Florida News release, New Atlas, https://today.ucf.edu/steam-powered-asteroid-hoppers-developed-ucf-collaboration/https://newatlas.com/steam-powered-space-probes/58015/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 07:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/15/3765135/3765135_02CE0EE265264868BC3EBD2FD085E895_190115_3765135_Scientists_build_space_probe_that_uses_steam_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, space probe, steam-powered space probe, steam-powered space probe prototype, World Is Not Enough spacecraft, New Horizon space probe, WINE space project, water propelled spacecraft, steam-powered spacecraft prototype]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3766054</guid>
      <title>Nairobi hotel attacked by suspected Somali militants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAt least six people were killed on Tuesday when suspected militants attacked a luxury hotel complex in Nairobi, according to France 24. According to Kenyan Police Chief Joseph Boinnet, the attack began around 3 p.m. local time when gunmen threw bombs destroying three vehicles in the I&M Bank parking lot.The gunmen then entered the lobby of the Dusit hotel, where one blew himself up.  Gunfire and explosions could be heard throughout the compound, reported BBC. The government said all buildings had been secured by late Tuesday. According to the BBC, local media report that around 30 people are being treated at Nairobi hospitals. According to the BBC, the Somali-based militant group al-Shabab has claimed responsibility for the attack.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dusit D2 hotel2. Three vehicles being destroyed in parking lot3. Gunman blowing himself up4. Gunman firing weapon, hotel secured later by governmentVOICEOVER (in English): "According to France 24, at least six people were killed on Tuesday when suspected militants attacked the five-star Dusit hotel complex in Nairobi." "According to Kenyan Police Chief Joseph Boinnet, the attack began around 3 p.m. local time when gunmen threw bombs destroying three vehicles in the I&M Bank parking lot.""The gunmen then entered the lobby of the Dusit hotel, where one blew himself up."  "According to the BBC, gunfire and explosions could be heard throughout the compound." "The government said all buildings had been secured by late Tuesday." SOURCES: France 24, BBChttps://www.france24.com/en/20190115-gunfire-blasts-reported-upscale-hotel-complex-westlands-nairobi-kenya-somalia-shabaabhttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-46880375***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 16:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/17/3766054/3766054_61A1857AF74D46E799D445923FF400EF_190117_3766054_Nairobi_hotel_attacked_by_suspected_Somali_milit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Nairobi attack, Nairobi Dusit hotel, DusitD2 hotel, ah-Shabab, al-Shabab Nairobi attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3765791</guid>
      <title>How is foie gras made?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Supreme court has rejected a challenge to California's 2004 ban on foie gras, the Los Angeles Times reports.Foie gras was outlawed in California after animals rights groups fought for a ban on the french delicacy, the New York Times reports. Even though foie gras was banned in 2004, full enforcement of the ban only started in 2012. Legal challenges resulted in it being suspended and reinstated numerous times over the past six years in California, according to SFGate.Now, it is illegal to sell or produce foie gras in California as the U.S. Supreme Court declined to hear the case against the ban.Violators of the ban will be fined up to US$1,000 if they are caught selling foie gras.To make foie gras, a metal tube is forced down the throat of a duck or a goose to enable forced feeding. This process is called "gavage," according to One Green Planet.org.The animals are then force-fed grain until their liver fattens to 10 times its size. The animals are eventually then slaughtered and their liver is cooked into a pate.The Animal Legal Defense Fund's staff attorney Kelsey Eberly told SFGate that they were "absolutely thrilled" at the Supreme Court's decision to not hear the case against the ban.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Metal tube, duck, foie gras2. Duck being force fed  2. Duck's liver expanding3. Pate on plateVOICEOVER (in English): "To make foie gras, a metal tube is forced down the throat of a duck or a goose to enable forced feeding. "This process is called 'gavage,' according to One Green Planet.org.""The animals are then force-fed grain until their liver fattens to 10 times its size.""The animals are eventually then slaughtered and their liver is cooked into a pate."SOURCES: Inhabitat, LA Times, One Green Planet, SF Gate, https://inhabitat.com/foie-gras-ban-in-california-stands-after-court-battle/https://www.latimes.com/food/la-fo-re-foie-gras-ban-20190114-story.htmlhttps://www.onegreenplanet.org/animalsandnature/foie-gras-ban-in-california-upheld-by-supreme-court/https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/California-s-foie-gras-ban-upheld-though-chefs-13514763.php***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 08:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/16/3765791/3765791_CEB6E13D9A7141B7BD5C2C9B30AEFC22_190116_3765791_How_is_foie_gras_made__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, foie gras, how foie gras is made, foie gras pate, duck, geese, foie gras explainer,  what is foie gras, fatty liver, fatty liver foie gras, french delicacy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3765628</guid>
      <title>Rescuers search for two-year-old who fell down borehole in Spain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to El Pais, rescuers are still searching for a toddler who fell down a well in southern Spain.Around 2 p.m. on Sunday, two-year-old Yulen walked away from his family while playing in a mountainous area in Malaga, Spain, and fell down a narrow well. The family heard his cries shortly after the fall, but have not heard or seen anything since.The hole is only 10 inches wide, too narrow to fit an adult. But it is believed to be 328 feet deep. It was bored in December during water prospection works, and left uncovered.Rescuers lowered a camera into the well and found the bag of sweets and cup he was holding in a layer of compacted wet sand about 250 feet down.According to the Mirror, emergency services have yet to locate the boy and fear he may be beneath the sand.The spokesman for the Civil Guard told Spanish broadcaster TVE that efforts are being made to widen the well while also digging a separate shaft to try and connect to it. A third alternative is an excavation from the side of the mountain.Elias Bendodo, who is president of the Provincial Council of Malaga, said rescuers will not stop until they find the toddler.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boy falls into narrow, deep well in Malaga, Spain2. Dimensions of well 3. Rescuers find bag of sweets, cup, but fear boy is beneath a layer of wet sand4. Plans for rescueVOICEOVER (in English): "Around 2 p.m. on Sunday, two-year-old Yulen walked away from his family while playing in a mountainous area in Malaga, Spain, and fell down a narrow well.""The family heard his cries shortly after the fall, but have not heard or seen anything since.""The hole is only 10 inches wide, too narrow to fit an adult. But it is believed to be 328 feet deep. It was bored in December during water prospection works, and left uncovered.""Rescuers lowered a camera into the well and found the bag of sweets and cup he was holding in a layer of compacted wet sand about 250 feet down.""According to the Mirror, emergency services have yet to locate the boy and fear he may be beneath the sand.""The spokesman for the Civil Guard told Spanish broadcaster TVE that efforts are being made to widen the well while also digging a separate shaft to try and connect to it.""A third alternative is an excavation from the side of the mountain."SOURCES: El Pais, NBC, The Guardian, Mirrorhttps://elpais.com/politica/2019/01/13/actualidad/1547396956_895011.htmlhttps://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/Boy-Falls-Down-Well-Spain-504323791.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/14/rescuers-search-for-toddler-who-fell-into-110-metre-well-in-spainhttps://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-boy-2-falls-down-13853395***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 04:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/16/3765628/3765628_51323753DD1A4C48B353D95544AD3D82_190116_3765628_Rescuers_search_for_two_year_old_who_fell_down_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, boy falls down well, boy falls into hole, borehole accident, well accident, borehole, deep well, narrow well, spanish toddler, rescue mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3765586</guid>
      <title>Denmark to build nine artificial islands off the coast of Copenhagen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Danish government and greater Copenhagen mayors have revealed plans to build artificial islands using surplus soil from construction projects, according to a report by New Atlas.The Urban Power architecture and planning firm has designed the project, called "Holmene," which calls for the creation a total of nine artificial islands 10 km off the coast of Copenhagen by 2040.The islands will be built one by one, with the government hoping to start construction on the first island by 2022.The government plans to finance the project by selling plots on the islands to different businesses.Soil from construction projects as well as imported Swedish surplus soil will be used to create the islands, according to Holmene's website.One of the islands would house a waste water conversion plant as well as windmills to store energy, Deutsche Welle reports. Some of the other islands would be used for recreational purposes, according to the project's website.The project would ease the problem of land shortage in Denmark by creating 3 million square meters of new land for Denmark, Deutsche Welle reports.This would result in 17 kilometers of new coastline, 700,000 square meters of nature and space for upto 380 new businesses, Deutsche Welle reports.Danish chamber of commerce Brian Mikkelsen, saying this to TV2 televisionThe artificial islands are projected to bring in more than $8 billion in economic activity.The Guardian quotes Brian Mikkelsen, head of the Danish chamber of commerce, as telling TV2 television he thinks the project "could become a sort of European Silicon Valley."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The artificial islands on a map2. The artificial islands being built one by one3. The soil that would be used to create the islands4.  An island with a waste water conversion plant, windmills and a recreational parkVOICEOVER (in English): "The Urban Power architecture and planning firm has designed the project, called 'Holmene,' which calls for the creation a total of nine artificial islands 10 kilometers off the coast of Copenhagen by 2040.""The islands will be built one by one, with the government hoping to start construction on the first island by 2022.""Soil from construction projects as well as imported Swedish surplus soil will be used to create the islands, according to Holmene's website.""One of the islands would house a waste water conversion plant as well as windmills to store energy, Deutsche Welle reports.""While some of the other islands would be used for recreational purposes, according to the project's website."SOURCES: Deutsche Welle, Holmene, Urban Power, https://www.dw.com/en/denmark-plans-silicon-valley-on-9-artificial-islands-off-copenhagen/a-46986197http://holmene.com/Nyt-erhvervsomraade/FAQhttp://www.urbanpower.dk/holmene.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/16/3765586/3765586_6E51841540874B44BFDC92AA22DDABD0_190116_3765586_Denmark_to_build_nine_artificial_islands_off_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, denmark, copenhagen, artificial islands, building artificial islands, copenhagen artificial islands, denmark artificial islands, Holmene project, denmark to build nine artificial islands off copenhagen, creating artificial islands]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3766666</guid>
      <title>Georgia man charged with plotting attack on White House</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Georgia man was charged on Wednesday with plotting a terrorist attack on the White House, according to the Washington Post. Hasher Jallal Taheb, 21, is accused of attempting to damage or destroy the White House by means of fire or an explosive, according to a criminal complaint filed in federal court in Atlanta, reports the Washington Post. According to the complaint, the FBI started investigating Taheb in March after an unidentified citizen informed authorities that he had "become radicalized, changed his name and made plans to travel abroad." According to court papers, an FBI informant and an undercover FBI agent then befriended Taheb, and through conversations, the suspect told them his plan to "blow a hole in the White House" so the three could carry out an attack with guns and grenades. On Wednesday, Taheb, the informant and the undercover agent met in a Buford, Georgia parking lot to exchange their cars for guns, an antitank weapon and explosives, according to the criminal complaint. According to officials, the weapons were all rendered inert as part of the sting operation. Taheb was arrested after the transaction was completed.  According to the Washington Post it is unclear if Taheb has obtained a lawyer.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Taheb charged with plotting attack on White House2. FBI began investigating Taheb after a tip from an unidentified citizen3. Taheb  planning to exchange his car for weapons4. Taheb being arrestedVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the Washington Post, a Georgia man was charged on Wednesday with plotting a terrorist attack on the White House." "According to a criminal complaint filed in federal court in Atlanta, Hasher Jallal Taheb is accused of attempting to damage or destroy the White House by means of fire or an explosive." "The complaint said the FBI started investigating Taheb in March after an unidentified citizen informed authorities that he had 'become radicalized, changed his name and made plans to travel abroad.'" "According to court papers, an FBI informant and an undercover FBI agent then befriended Taheb, and through conversations, the suspect told them his plan to 'blow a hole in the White House' so the three could carry out an attack with guns and grenades." "According to the criminal complaint, Taheb, the informant and the undercover agent met on Wednesday in a Buford, Georgia parking lot to exchange their cars for guns, an antitank weapon and explosives." "According to officials, the weapons were all rendered inert as part of the sting operation.""Taheb was arrested after the transaction was completed."  SOURCES: Washington Post, The Atlanta Journal-Constitutionhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/georgia-man-charged-with-plotting-to-attack-the-white-house/2019/01/16/d6050e46-19df-11e9-88fe-f9f77a3bcb6c_story.html?noredirect=on&utm_term=.abdbb42cbe03https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-cumming-man-threatened-attack-white-house-authorities-say/REYZfPSsBFUeiJTIPkYaWN/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/17/3766666/3766666_FDBFF991A95D46DF8DF0B7CA4B9AD8F5_190117_3766666_Georgia_man_charged_with_plotting_attack_on_Whit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, White House attack plot, Georgia man White House plot, Hasher Jallal Taheb, Cummings man arrested White House plot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3766254</guid>
      <title>CERN unveils proposal to build new bigger and more powerful particle accelerator.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers at CERN revealed a conceptual plan for a new particle accelerator called the Future Circular Collider, or FCC.It would be located in Geneva and would have a circumference of roughly 100 kilometers. That's almost four times bigger than the Large Hadron Collider or LHC.The conceptual design report predicts it would take approximately 20 years to design and build the new collider. The report highlights the importance of building it at the right time to ensure the continuation of particle research after the LHC stops operating in 2035.According to the report, the collider would be built in phases. During its early stages, it would collide electrons and positrons. Later it would collide electrons against the nuclei of lead atoms.The team hopes that by 2050 the FCC will be able to carry out proton-proton collisions with an energy of 100 teraelectronvolts[a]. That is seven times the energy capacity of the LHC.Plans for the collider also include a radiofrequency acceleration system, large scale cryogenic plants and 16 tesla high-field accelerator magnets. It took 1,300 scientists based at 150 universities worldwide five years to develop this conceptual project.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location and size of Future Circular Collider  2. First stage and second stage of Future Circular Collider3. Proton-proton collision; 100 teraelectronvolts of energy4. Extra uses of Future Circular Collider  VOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at CERN revealed a conceptual plan for a new particle accelerator called the Future Circular Collider, or FCC.""It would be located in Geneva and would have a circumference of roughly 100 kilometers. That's almost four times bigger than the Large Hadron Collider or LHC.""The conceptual design report predicts it would take approximately 20 years to design and build the new collider.""According to the report, the collider would be built in phases. "During its early stages, it would collide electrons and positrons. Later it would collide electrons against the nuclei of lead atoms.""The team hopes that by 2050 the FCC will be able to carry out proton-proton collisions with an energy of 100 teraelectronvolts[b]. "That is seven times the energy capacity of the LHC.""Plans for the collider also include a radiofrequency acceleration system, large scale cryogenic plants and 16 tesla high-field accelerator magnets."SOURCES: CERN, Nature, The Guardian, BBC, Phys.org, The Vergehttp://fcc-cdr.web.cern.ch/http://fcc-cdr.web.cern.ch/webkit/https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-00173-2https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jan/15/cern-draws-up-plans-for-collider-four-times-the-size-of-large-hadronhttps://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-46862486https://phys.org/news/2019-01-cern-vision-next-generation-particle-collider.htmlhttps://www.theverge.com/2019/1/15/18183828/cern-physics-particle-accelerator-hadron-collider***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/17/3766254/3766254_C4A94D9DB48C497FB55C99F1FFD894AB_190117_3766254_CERN_unveils_proposal_to_build_new_bigger_and_mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, cern, switzerland, geneva, large hadron collider, higgs boson, particle physics, particle colliders, particle accelerators, future circular collider, particle collider]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3767359</guid>
      <title>Prince Philip uninjured in car collision</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Guardian reports that the Duke of Edinburgh escaped unharmed after being involved in a car crash in Norfolk.Witnesses told the BBC that the accident near Sandringham estate occurred as Prince Philip drove his Range Rover out of a driveway and onto the A149 shortly before 3 p.m. on Thursday.A Kia travelling south collided with the Range Rover, causing it to overturn and slide across the road, ultimately landing on the driver's side.According to the Guardian, the 97-year-old Duke of Edinburgh was helped out of his vehicle by eyewitnesses. He was shaken, but uninjured. The female driver of the Kia suffered cuts, while the female passenger sustained an arm injury. Both needed hospital treatment but have since been discharged.A Norfolk police spokesman said the two drivers were breath tested as part of force policy, and received negative readings.Buckingham Palace put out a statement three hours after the incident saying the Duke had seen a doctor as a precaution and had been confirmed to be unharmed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Prince Philip driving Range Rover near Sandringham estate2. Kia collides with Range Rover, causes it to overturn3. Prince Philip uninjured, helped out of vehicle; women in Kia suffered minor injuries4. Both drivers test negative on breath testVOICEOVER (in English): "Witnesses told the BBC that the accident near Sandringham estate occurred as Prince Philip drove his Range Rover out of a driveway and onto the A149 shortly before 3 p.m. on Thursday.""A Kia travelling south collided with the Range Rover, causing it to overturn and slide across the road, ultimately landing on the driver's side.""According to the Guardian, the 97-year-old Duke of Edinburgh was helped out of his vehicle by eyewitnesses. He was shaken, but uninjured. "The female driver of the Kia suffered cuts, while the female passenger sustained an arm injury. Both needed hospital treatment but have since been discharged.""A Norfolk police spokesman said the two drivers were breath tested as part of force policy, and received negative readings."SOURCES: BBC, The Telegraph, The Guardian, Norfolk Policehttps://www.bbc.com/news/uk-46912691https://www.telegraph.co.uk/royal-family/2019/01/17/prince-philip-car-crash-near-sandringham/https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/jan/17/prince-philip-involved-in-car-accident-near-sandringhamhttps://www.norfolk.police.uk/news/latest-news/17-01-2019/sandringham-collision-statement***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 16:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/19/3767359/3767359_EA60CB435C2C472496606070CD497FEA_190119_3767359_Prince_Philip_uninjured_in_car_collision_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, car crash, car accident, collision, car collision, Prince Philip car crash, Duke of Edinburgh, Prince Philip, range rover, royal family, British royal family]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3767308</guid>
      <title>Saturn rings are relatively young compared to planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have used new measurements to calculate the mass of Saturn's rings to estimate their age, which is 10 to 100 million years old, according to Berkeley News.  One of the last things the Cassini spacecraft did before plunging into Saturn's atmosphere in 2017 was to travel between the planet and its rings, acting as a gravity probe.  NASA programmed Cassini to perform 22 dives between the planet and the rings, with earth-based radio telescopes measuring the spacecraft's velocity to within a fraction of a millimeter per second. Based on how much Cassini's flight path was deflected by the gravity of the rings, researchers were able to make an accurate estimate of Saturn ring mass. Previous research has shown a relationship between the mass of the rings and their age. Lower mass would point to a younger age, because the rings are initially made of ice and are bright, but over time become contaminated and darkened by interplanetary debris. With that estimate, scientist calculated that the rings are relatively recent, having originated between 100 million years to 10 million years ago. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cassini traveling between Saturn and its rings2. Cassini performing 22 dives between Saturn and rings3. Cassini flight path affected by ring and planet gravity4. Saturn's ringsVOICEOVER (in English): "One of the last things the Cassini spacecraft did before plunging into Saturn's atmosphere in 2017 was to travel between the planet and its rings, acting as a gravity probe."  "NASA programmed Cassini to perform 22 dives between the planet and the rings, with earth-based radio telescopes measuring the spacecraft's velocity to within a fraction of a millimeter per second." "Based on how much Cassini's flight path was deflected by the gravity of the rings, researchers were able to make an accurate estimate of Saturn ring mass." "Previous research has shown a relationship between the mass of the rings and their age. Lower mass would point to a younger age, because the rings are initially made of ice and are bright, but over time become contaminated and darkened by interplanetary debris." "With that estimate, scientist calculated that the rings are relatively recent, having originated between 100 million years to 10 million years ago." SOURCES: Berkeley News https://news.berkeley.edu/2019/01/17/saturn-hasnt-always-had-rings/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/18/3767308/3767308_D615A53F865C43B5AE529831AF0BB3D7_190118_3767308_Saturn_rings_are_relatively_young_compared_to_pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Saturn, Saturn's rings, Saturn rings age, Saturn rings mass, Cassini]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3767080</guid>
      <title>Tesla may power Greek islands using new microgrids</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTesla may soon be collaborating with Greece to help modernize its power grids by using advanced energy storage technology.According to Electrek, Tesla has presented Greek officials a proposal to reduce the country's fossil fuel dependency and aid the transition to renewable energy sources. The proposal suggests the creation of a microgrid composed of energy storage systems to power remote Greek islands that are not connected to the country's main power grid.Tesla's previous microgrid projects have been powered by Powerpacks. Tesla Powerpacks are rechargeable batteries that store energy from renewable sources.The Powerpack can store large amounts of energy off-grid and are made to function as large-scale supplemental power systems.Government authorities are reportedly considering conducting a pilot project on the Island of Limnos in the Aegean Sea.A large array of solar panels would be installed in order to power energy storage facilities during the day. The energy stored would be used during the night.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Collaboration between Tesla and Greece; remote Greek islands not connected to main power grid2. Tesla's Powerpack energy storage system3. Pilot project in Greek Island of Limnos4. Solar panel and energy storage system installationVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Electrek, Tesla has presented Greek officials a proposal to reduce the country's fossil fuel dependency and aid the transition to renewable energy sources, also known as RES." "The proposal suggests the creation of a microgrid composed of energy storage systems to power remote Greek islands that are not connected to the country's main power grid.""Tesla's previous microgrid projects have been powered by Powerpacks. Tesla Powerpacks are rechargeable batteries that store energy from renewable sources.""The Powerpack can store large amounts of energy off-grid and are made to function as large-scale supplemental power systems.""Government authorities are reportedly considering conducting a pilot project on the Island of Limnos in the Aegean Sea.""A large array of solar panels would be installed in order to power energy storage facilities during the day. The energy stored would be used during the night."SOURCES: Elektrek, Big Think, Capital.gr, Futurism https://electrek.co/2019/01/14/tesla-microgrid-solar-batteries-power-greek-island/https://bigthink.com/technology-innovation/tesla-energy-storage-greek-islands?rebelltitem=1#rebelltitem1http://www.capital.gr/epixeiriseis/3337012/reuma-sti-limno-me-mpataries-teslahttps://futurism.com/teslas-powerpacks-greece***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/18/3767080/3767080_5584C0CCAD944E7D978C89D0008E8F7F_190118_3767080_Tesla_may_power_Greek_islands_using_new_microgri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Tesla, Greece, microgrid, renewable energy, energy storage system, Tesla powerpack, Earth energy, renewable energy storage system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3766855</guid>
      <title>China to launch Mars mission next year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has reiterated is plans to send a space probe, a lander and an orbiter to Mars in 2020 on the heels of landing a mission on the far side of the moon, state-run media agency Xinhua reports.Wu Yanhua, deputy chief of the China National Space Administration, made the announcement in a press conference on Monday, Xinhua reports.The mission is being called the Mars Global Remote Sensing Orbiter and Small Rover, or HX-1.According to the State Council of the People's Republic of China's website, China's Mars 2020 mission will be launched on a Long March-5 carrier rocket from the Wenchang Spacecraft Launch Site in Hainan province.A lander along with an orbiter and a rover will be deployed to the Red Planet. The lander is designed to operate for three Martian months. It will touch down on the northern hemisphere of Mars and will contain a rover that has six wheels and four solar panels that will explore Mars.The rover will feature a remote sensing camera as well as a ground penetrating radar and is expected to collect Martian soil and bring it back to Earth by 2030, according to Futurism.com.The news comes after the success of China's moon mission earlier this month.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of a rocket taking off, a lander, an orbiter and a rover2. The lander touching down on Mars3. The lander contains a rover4. Features of the roverVOICEOVER (in English): "China's Mars 2020 mission will be launched on a Long March-5 carrier rocket from the Wenchang Spacecraft Launch Site in Hainan province.""A lander along with an orbiter and a rover will be deployed to the Red Planet.""The lander will touch down on the northern hemisphere of Mars, according to the State Council of the People's Republic of China's website.""The lander will contain a rover that has six wheels and four solar panels and will be able to explore Mars by itself.""The rover will contain a remote sensing camera as well as a ground penetrating radar and is expected to collect Martian soil and bring it back to Earth by 2030, according to Futurism.com."SOURCES: Futurism, State Council of the People's Republic of China, Xinhua, Business Insiderhttps://futurism.com/china-mission-to-mars-2020http://english.gov.cn/news/video/2016/08/24/content_281475424665899.htmhttp://english.cas.cn/newsroom/mutimedia_news/201608/t20160824_166702.shtmlhttps://www.businessinsider.com/china-mars-spacecraft-launch-2020-rover-sample-return-2019-1http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-01/14/c_137743306.htm***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 03:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/18/3766855/3766855_D307190C1E4143AFBB6E0F4CD39ABDA1_190118_3766855_China_to_launch_Mars_mission_next_year_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, mars, mars mission, china mars mission, mars lander mission, china mars lander, chinese mars mission, space, space exploration, china space mission, martian soil]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3767466</guid>
      <title>Taiwan plans large-scale military drills</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTaiwan's Ministry of National Defense has announced plans for crucial military drills to to defend against China.The Taiwanese military drills are to be divided into four major parts this year, Focus Taiwan reports. This first part of the drills consists of a month of combat readiness training, followed by a month of live-fire exercises in the second quarter.Taiwan's military also plans to hold drills of joint anti-landing operations as well as joint anti-airbourne exercises in the third and fourth quarter.Taiwan also plans to upgrade its existing 144 F-16 A/B fighter jets by spending around US$3.64 billion, reports DW.The announcement comes after Chinese President Xi Jinping explained China would use military force to bring Taiwan back under their control if necessary. The Chinese military is becoming increasingly aggressive, with more Chinese naval vessels and fighter jets holding exercises near Taiwan, reports Focus Taiwan.Speaking in a Focus Taiwan report, Taiwan's military spokesperson Chen Chung-Chi stressed that the drills are being held to prepare against invasion from the PRC.Business Insider reports, the People's Liberation Army carried out 18,000 military drills last year alone.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Soldiers in the field and a live fire drill2. Anti-landing operations taking place3. Anti-airbourne exercises taking place4. F-16 fighter jetVOICEOVER (in English): "Focus Taiwan reports that the Taiwanese military drills are to be divided into four major parts this year.""This first part of the drills consists of a month of combat readiness training, followed by a month of live-fire exercises in the second quarter.""Taiwan's military also plans to hold drills of joint anti-landing operations...""...as well as joint anti-airbourne exercises in the third and fourth quarter.""DW reports Taiwan also plans to upgrade its existing 144 F-16 A/B fighter jets by spending around US$3.64 billion."SOURCES: Focus Taiwan, Deutsche Welle, Business Insider, http://focustaiwan.tw/news/aipl/201901090005.aspxhttp://focustaiwan.tw/news/aipl/201802220026.aspxhttps://www.dw.com/en/taiwan-prepares-to-hold-large-scale-military-drills-to-deter-china/a-47107430https://www.businessinsider.com/taiwan-is-changing-up-combat-drills-in-preparation-for-war-with-china-2019-1***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 02:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/19/3767466/3767466_3573445C1E9347BCA5E4C6A28F189969_190119_3767466_Taiwan_plans_large_scale_military_drills_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, taiwan, china, military drills, military drills in taiwan, cross-strait relations, taiwan china relations, taiwan china conflict, taiwan military drill, taiwan china conflict, live fire drill]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3768605</guid>
      <title>Mexico pipeline blast kills at least 79 people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMexican officials say at least 79 people were killed in a fuel pipeline blast last Friday in the town of Tlahuelilpan, in Hidalgo state. According to Reuters, suspected fuel thieves punctured the Tula-Tuxpan pipeline a few miles from one of the country's main refineries on Friday, causing a large jet of fuel to rise into the air.  According to authorities, around 800 people scrambled to fill up containers from the 23-foot (7 meter) gasoline geyser.   A few hours later, the geyser erupted in flames in a powerful explosion.During a press conference, Pemex chief executive Octavio Romero said the company was aware of a leak along the pipeline at around 16:50 local time. According to BBC, locals said President Andrs Manuel Lpez Obrador's new policy to crack down on fuel theft has created shortages.  Mexico says fuel theft cost the country about US$3 billion just last year. President Lpez Obrador has said he will continue his anti-theft policy until the illegal practice was stopped.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tula-Tuxpan pipeline2. Gas geyser shooting from pipeline3. Pipeline explosion4. Fuel theft cost Mexico US$3 billion last yearVOICEOVER (in English):"Mexican officials say at least 79 people were killed in a fuel pipeline blast last Friday in the town of Tlahuelilpan, in Hidalgo state." "According to Reuters, suspected fuel thieves punctured the Tula-Tuxpan pipeline a few miles from one of the country's main refineries on Friday, causing a large jet of fuel to rise into the air."  "According to authorities, around 800 people scrambled to fill up containers from the 23-foot gasoline geyser."   "A few hours later, the geyser erupted in flames in a powerful explosion." "Mexico says fuel theft cost the country about US$3 billion just last year."   SOURCES: Reuters, BBChttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-fuel-theft-blast/focus-sharpens-on-mexico-fuel-theft-plan-after-blast-kills-79-idUSKCN1PE08Chttps://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-46929950***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 10:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/21/3768605/3768605_F1F88017A9AF4B7EB334F7DF0E255382_190121_3768605_Mexico_pipeline_blast_kills_at_least_79_people_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Mexico pipeline blast, Mexico pipeline explosion, Mexico fuel theft, Tlahuelilpan pipeline explosion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3768529</guid>
      <title>NASA reveals images testing Space Launch System rocket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has unveiled photographs of the hydrogen tank that will power its Space Launch System rocket.According to NASA, the hydrogen tank for the Space Launch System rocket was loaded into a test stand at NASA's Marshall Space Flight Center in Huntsville, Alabama on Jan. 14.Hydraulic cylinders installed in the test stand will push and pull the tank, mimicking the pressure it would have to withstand during lift-off and flight. The SLS rocket tank is a 61-meter tall liquid hydrogen tank and is eight-meters in diameter. Its design allows it to hold over two million liters of supercooled liquid nitrogen.The tank will feed the rocket's RS-25 engines with cryogenic liquid hydrogen and liquid oxygen producing almost nine million pounds of maximum thrust. The launch vehicle is designed to carry NASA's Orion spacecraft as well as other cargo into deep space for exploration.The SLS rocket is one of the most powerful rockets designed by NASA. It will boost Orion at a speed of almost 40,000 kilometers per hour out of Earth's orbit. That's roughly, 11,000 kilometers per hour faster than the International Space Station travels around Earth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. NASA's Space Launch System rocket tank tests2. Dimensions and capacity of Space Launch System tank3. Tank feeding Space Launch System rocket engines4. Space Launch System rocket launching Orion to spaceVOICEOVER (in English): "The hydrogen tank for NASA's Space Launch System rocket was loaded into a test stand at NASA's Marshall Space Flight Center in Huntsville, Alabama on Jan. 14.""According to a NASA report, hydraulic cylinders installed in the test stand will push and pull the tank, mimicking the pressure it would have to withstand during lift-off and flight.""The SLS rocket tank is a 61-meter tall liquid hydrogen tank and is eight-meters in diameter. Its design allows it to hold over two million liters of supercooled liquid nitrogen.""The tank will feed the rocket's RS-25 engines with cryogenic liquid hydrogen and liquid oxygen producing almost nine million pounds of maximum thrust.""The launch vehicle is designed to carry NASA's Orion spacecraft as well as other cargo into deep space for exploration."SOURCES: NASA, V3https://www.nasa.gov/exploration/systems/sls/index.htmlhttps://www.nasa.gov/audience/forstudents/5-8/features/nasa-knows/what-is-orion-58.htmlhttps://www.v3.co.uk/v3-uk/news/3069512/nasas-liquid-hydrogen-tank-to-undergo-tests-at-marshall-space-flight-centre***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 09:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/21/3768529/3768529_635DCD386F7F43569095C2E73CFB94E2_190121_3768529_NASA_reveals_images_testing_Space_Launch_System__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Space Launch System, NASA, Orion, space travel, space, space exploration, Marshall Space Flight Center, mission to Mars, NASA rocket to Mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3768516</guid>
      <title>Harvard scientist continues to claim Oumuamua is an alien probe directed to Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA strange space object called Oumuamua has been a topic of debate among scientists and astronomers, with one Israeli Harvard professor claiming it is likely an alien probe.Oumuamua is a reddish interstellar object that was first seen using the Pan-STARRS telescope at Haleakala Observatory, Hawaii on October 2017, as it passed by Earth at 156,428 kilometers per hour.Its odd shape and unusual level of acceleration have made it an object of speculation among the astronomic community.Oumuamua, whose name comes from a Hawaiian word meaning "scout" or "messenger sent from the distant past to reach out to us", is the first interstellar object observed in the Solar System. It is 400 meters long and roughly 40 meters wide.Scientists are debating whether or not the object is an asteroid or a comet with some even suggesting it has extraterrestrial origins. According to a theoretical paper written by Israeli Harvard Professor Abraham Loeb published in The Astrophysical Journal Letters, states that the object is likely a space probe that passed by our solar system.The hypothesis suggests it is powered by lightsail energy, also known as solar sail technology, and that its reddish color might be a layer of interstellar dust.The paper suggests a second hypothesis claiming the object's random trajectory might mean it is an alien probe intentionally passing by Earth's vicinity.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Oumuamua model traveling through space.2. Oumuamua length and width3. Hypothesis of Oumuamua being powered by solar sails4. Oumuamua passing close to EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Oumuamua is a reddish interstellar object that was first seen using the Pan-STARRS telescope at Haleakala Observatory, Hawaii on October 2017, as it passed by Earth at 156,428 kilometers per hour.""Its odd shape and unusual level of acceleration have made it an object of speculation among the astronomic community.""Oumuamua, whose name comes from a Hawaiian word meaning "scout" or "messenger sent from the distant past to reach out to us", is the first interstellar object observed in the Solar System. It is 400 meters long and roughly 40 meters wide.""Scientists are debating whether or not the object is an asteroid or a comet with some even suggesting it has extraterrestrial origins. ""According to a theoretical paper written by Israeli Harvard Professor Abraham Loeb published in The Astrophysical Journal Letters, states that the object is likely a space probe that passed by our solar system.""The hypothesis suggests it is powered by lightsail energy, also known as solar sail technology, and that its reddish color might be a layer of interstellar dust.""The paper suggests a second hypothesis claiming the object's random trajectory might mean it is an alien probe intentionally passing by Earth's vicinity."SOURCES: The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Wired, The Guardianhttp://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.3847/2041-8213/aaeda8/methttps://www.wired.com/story/is-oumuamua-an-alien-spaceship-sure-except-no/https://www.theguardian.com/science/shortcuts/2018/nov/07/oumuamua-alien-spaceship-scientists-harvard-professors***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 09:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/21/3768516/3768516_C20BDE9287B847B9B5D0FB118C1D3087_190121_3768516_Harvard_scientist_continues_to_claim_Oumuamua_is_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Oumuamua, Harvard, alien spacecraft, oumuamua trajectory, solar system, interstellar object, oumuamua interstellar object]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3768486</guid>
      <title>3D-printed rockets could soon be launched into space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANRelativity Space's 3D printed rocket could be launching from Cape Canaveral before the end of 2020.Relativity Space made different parts for their new rocket, Terran-1, using their 3D printer Stargate, according to the company's website.The Terran-1 would take around 60 days to print. When all the parts are put together, the rocket would be around 100-feet tall. It would also be able to carry a payload of nearly 2,750 pounds.Relativity Space has also received permission from the U.S. Air Force to launch Terran-1 at Cape Canaveral in Florida.The company is hoping to launch the 3D-printed rocket by the end of 2020.If the launch is successful, the company could get to lease the site for up to 20 years, according to Business Insider.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Terran-1 rocket and Stargate, a 3D printer2. The rocket from bottom to top and its payload3. Launch Complex 164. Terran-1 rocket being launchedVOICEOVER (in English): "Relativity Space made different parts for their new rocket, Terran-1, using their 3D printer Stargate, according to the company's website.""All in all, the Terran-1 would take around 60 days to print. "When all the parts are put together, the rocket would be around 100-feet tall." "It would also be able to carry a payload of nearly 2,750 pounds.""Relativity Space has also received permission from the U.S. Air Force to launch Terran-1 at Cape Canaveral in Florida.""The company is hoping to launch the 3D-printed rocket by the end of 2020."SOURCES: Futurism.com, Quartz, Business Insider, Florida Today, Relativity Spacehttps://futurism.com/air-force-grants-launch-site-3d-printed-rocket-relativity-spacehttps://qz.com/1526158/rocket-start-up-relativity-leased-a-launch-pad-from-the-us-air-force/https://www.businessinsider.com/relativity-space-rockets-launchpad-cape-canaveral-2019-1https://www.floridatoday.com/story/tech/science/space/2019/01/17/relativity-launch-rockets-cape-canaveral/2603166002/https://www.relativityspace.com/mission***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/21/3768486/3768486_E2552F09D12744E790F0225BB8D1513F_190121_3768486_3D_printed_rockets_could_soon_be_launched_into_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, us air force,  rocket, 3d printed rockets, us air force rocket flight 3d, cape canaveral, relativity space, rocket 3d printer, relativity space rocket, Launch Complex 16, Terran-1 rocket]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3768316</guid>
      <title>Vietnam's new international airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVietnam's new Long Thanh Airport is being built in order to reduce traffic at Tan Son Nhat Airport in Ho Chi Minh City.This is a joint venture between The Airports Corporation of Vietnam and different firms from Japan, France, and Vietnam, according to Nhan Dan Online.Long Thanh International Airport will be built in Vietnam's southern province of Dong Nai, according to Vietnam News.vn.The airport will cover an area of 5,580 hectares and will undergo three stages of construction.However, according to Vietnam Investment Review, the airport will be built over six communes in the area.This means people living in the area will have to be relocated and resettled to other areas and given a compensation package.The airport is being designed by South Korean architectural firm Heerim, and will feature a roof that has been made to look like a lotus.A runway and a passenger terminal will be built in its first phase of construction which is slated to start next year, according to Vietnam Net.A passenger lounge along with parking areas for planes will also be built along with other auxiliary constructions.According to Vietnam Investment Review, the airport will be able to hold up to 100 million passengers and five million tons of cargo once it becomes operational in 2025.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The outer design of the new international airport2. Focus on the roof of the airport3. Runway, passenger terminal4. Passenger lounge, airplane parking VOICEOVER (in English): "Long Thanh International Airport will be built in Vietnam's southern province of Dong Nai, according to Vietnam News.vn.""The airport will cover an area of 5,580 hectares and will undergo three stages of construction.""The airport is being designed by South Korean architectural firm Heerim, and will feature a roof that has been made to look like a lotus.""A runway and a passenger terminal will be built in its first phase of construction which is slated to start next year, according to Vietnam Net.""A passenger lounge along with parking areas for planes will also be built along with other auxiliary constructions."SOURCES: Vietnam News.vn, Heerim, Vietnam Investment Review, Nhan Dan, Vietnam Net, https://vietnamnews.vn/society/449252/contract-signed-for-feasibility-study-for-long-thanh-airport.html#masVRDJ9es22EOIH.97http://www.heerim.com/project/view?id=1117&lang=enhttps://www.vir.com.vn/government-urges-site-clearance-for-long-thanh-airport-49692.htmlhttps://www.vir.com.vn/dong-nai-to-hand-over-land-for-long-thanh-airport-63787.htmlhttp://en.nhandan.org.vn/travel/item/6769802-long-thanh-among-cnn-list-of-16-most-exciting-airport-projects.htmlhttps://english.vietnamnet.vn/fms/society/215233/work-on-long-thanh-airport-project-to-start-by-end-2020.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 03:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/21/3768316/3768316_BC6D92ECFD1D4148B91CA1B2AF745915_190121_3768316_Vietnam_s_new_international_airport_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, vietnam, vietnam airport, Long Thanh airport, Long Thanh airport vietnam, Long Thanh international airport, vietnam to build new international airport, Long Thanh airport project, vietnam international airport, new airport vietnam, Heerim, Dong Nai, Dong Nai Vietnam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3769091</guid>
      <title>Recycled boat sails to bring awareness about pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA recycled boat is set to sail the seas to raise awareness about marine plastic pollution.The sail boat is around 10 meters long and is made of more than 10 tons of recycled plastic such as flip-flops, plastic bottles and bags, according to its website.The sailboat will set out on Jan 24 from the Lamu Islands, Kenya and sail 500 kilometers.The boat, nicknamed Flipflopi, is expected to stop by in various towns such as Mombasa, Diani and Watamu among other cities before it reaches its final destination of Stone Town, Zanzibar.The journey would take 12 to 14 days, according to its website.The sailboat will stop by in different towns to teach local residents about recycling and reusing plastic, according to Geek.com.The Flipflopi plans sail the seas again in 2021 when it will sail along the coast of Kenya, Tanzania, Mozambique and reach its destination of South Africa for 3 to 4 months.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The recycled sailboat and pollution in the ocean2. What the sailboat is made out of3. The sailboat sailing 4. Map of where the sailboat is expected to sailVOICEOVER (in English): "According to Geek.com, a recycled boat is set to sail to raise awareness about marine plastic pollution.""According to its website, the sailboat is around 10 meters long and is made of more than 10 tons of recycled plastic such as flip-flops, plastic bottles and bags."[CUT 3]"The vessel will set out on Jan. 24 from the Lamu Islands, Kenya and sail 500 kilometers.""The boat, nicknamed Flipflopi, is expected to stop by in various towns such as Mombasa, Diani and Watamu among other cities before it reaches its final destination of Stone Town, Zanzibar." "The journey will take 12 to 14 days."SOURCES: Geek.com, Flip Flopi Expedition, UN Environment, https://www.geek.com/news/this-boat-made-from-30000-flip-flops-will-set-sail-to-raise-awareness-about-plastic-pollution-1770373/http://www.theflipflopi.com/the-flipflopi-dhow/https://www.unenvironment.org/interactive/beat-plastic-pollution/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 08:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/22/3769091/3769091_94285BA62B11462A914B94AF23A5B158_190122_3769091_Recycled_boat_sails_to_bring_awareness_about_pol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, boat, plastic pollution, boat made of flip flops, sail boat, sail boat flip flops, recycled plastic boat, recycled plastic boat kenya, recycling plastic, lamu, kenya, flipflopi expedition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3768934</guid>
      <title>Scientists grow human blood vessels in lab for the first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists at the University of British Columbia have grown a pair human blood vessels for the first time.Scientists used stem cells to grow organoids in a petri dish, according to a study published in the journal Nature.The organoids were then planted in mice and had a survival rate of more than 95 percent.The researchers observed that the organoids had developed into human blood vessels with arteries and capillaries after six months.The research team from UBC used this same technique to study the impact of diabetes on these lab-grown blood vessels, according to New Atlas.Diabetes causes the membrane that surrounds the blood vessels to expand and decreases the amount of oxygen and nutrients delivered to the cells and tissue.This in turn increases the risk of health problems such as heart attacks, kidney failure and blindness.The researchers found that none of the current anti-diabetic medications helped in curing the flawed blood vessels.However, they did find an enzyme inhibitor which could help in preventing the membrane from expanding."This discovery could be beneficial in treating diabetes in the future.The researchers say the lab-grown blood vessels could help in finding treatments and determine the cause for different vascular disease such as Alzheimer's disease, wound healing problems and diabetes.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Stem cells, a petri dish and organoids2.  The organoids being planted in mice and a measurement bar3. The organoid turning into human blood vessels and a calendar icon4. Depiction of Alzheimer's disease, wound healing problems and diabetesVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a study published in the journal Nature, scientists used stem cells to grow organoids in a petri dish.""The organoids were then planted in mice and had a survival rate of more than 95 percent.""The researchers observed that the organoids had developed into human blood vessels with arteries and capillaries after six months.""The researchers say the lab-grown blood vessels could help in finding treatments and determine the cause for different vascular disease such as Alzheimer's disease, wound healing problems and diabetes."SOURCES: New Atlas, University of British Columbia news release, Nature Journal, https://newatlas.com/stem-cells-blood-vessels/58095/https://news.ubc.ca/2019/01/16/scientists-grow-perfect-human-blood-vessels-in-a-petri-dish/https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-018-0858-8***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 04:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/22/3768934/3768934_DFED003C54664FC78A1A232ACD2C89E7_190122_3768934_Scientists_grow_human_blood_vessels_in_lab_for_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, lab-grown human blood vessels, human blood vessels, grow blood vessels, blood vessels grown in lab, diabetes, organoids]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3768821</guid>
      <title>Japan launches satellite to test artificial meteor showers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA satellite from a Japanese aerospace company called Astro Live Experiences, or ALE, has successfully entered Earth's orbit after being launched into space on Jan. 18. According to a press release by the company, it's first satellite will gather data on the environment of the Earth's atmosphere in order to determine the feasibility of creating an artificial meteor shower.The satellite was launched by the Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency on the Epsilon-4 rocket along with six other tech demo satellites. According to The Japan Times, the cost per launch of the Epsilon-4 is $50 million.The satellite is designed to imitate a meteor shower by firing small 1-centimeter metal pellets at high-speed into the Earth's atmosphere.The space venture company states that the pellets will not cause any damage to existing satellites or air crafts because they will completely burn up at 60 to 80 kilometers above ground. Airplanes fly at an altitude of 10 kilometers.During a meteor shower show, the pellets will travel one-fifth of the way around Earth before entering the atmosphere. On average, five to twenty pellets will be released, each of which will remain visible for roughly three to ten seconds.The company hopes to create its first artificial meteor shower show above the city of Hiroshima. According to ALE, the shower will be visible to over 6 million people in an area of up to 200 kilometers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Satellite launches on the Epsilon-4 into Earth's orbit2. Satellite shoots metallic pellets; pellets enter the Earth's atmosphere3. Satellite orbiting Earth; demonstration of meteor shower4. Location of the meteor showerVOICEOVER (in English): "A satellite from a Japanese aerospace company called Astro Live Experiences, or ALE, has successfully entered Earth's orbit after being launched into space on Jan. 18.""According to a press release by the company, the satellite is designed to imitate a meteor shower by firing small 1-centimeter metal pellets at high-speed into the Earth's atmosphere.""During a meteor shower show, the pellets will travel one-fifth of the way around Earth before entering the atmosphere. On average, five to twenty pellets will be released, each of which will remain visible for roughly three to ten seconds.""The company hopes to create its first artificial meteor shower show above the city of Hiroshima. According to ALE, the shower will be visible to over 6 million people in an area of up to 200 kilometers."SOURCES: Astro Live Experiences, The Japan Times, Fast Company, Futurism, CNEThttp://star-ale.com/en/https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/01/18/national/japan-launches-epsilon-rocket-carrying-seven-satellites-including-one-supposed-generate-fake-meteor-shower/#.XEUnV2gzaUkhttps://www.fastcompany.com/90293194/the-worlds-first-artificial-meteor-shower-is-set-to-fly-over-japan-tonighthttps://futurism.com/sourcing-parts-quantum-computers-difficulthttps://www.cnet.com/news/first-artificial-meteor-shower-might-outshine-natural-shooting-stars/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 01:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/22/3768821/3768821_63C318DFCF2B415DB52AD291C5779EFF_190122_3768821_Japan_launches_satellite_to_test_artificial_mete_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Astro Live Experiences, Japan, meteor shower, fake meteor shower, japan fake meteor shower, ALE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3769808</guid>
      <title>Europe could be looking to mine the moon by 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe European Space Agency will be working with local companies in Europe to prepare for an upcoming lunar mission.Ariane Group, a Paris-based rocket company, said it has signed a one-year contract with the European Space Agency to prepare for a moon mission by 2025.The European Space Agency will work with Ariane Group and PTScientists, a German startup to build a lunar lander for the mission.The European Space Agency plans to mine regolith, or moon rock, from the moon's surface in the next six years, according to The Telegraph.Regolith covers the entire surface of the moon and is made up of clay, glass fragments, mineral as well as chemical compounds such as iron oxide from which oxygen, water and fuel could be extracted.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The moon and the lunar lander appearing on the surface of the moon2. Regolith from the moon 3. What regolith is made out of4. What the scientists plan to extract out of regolithVOICEOVER (in English): "The European Space Agency will work with Ariane Group and PTScientists, a German startup, to build a lunar lander for the mission.""According to The Telegraph, the European Space Agency plans to mine regolith, or moon rock, from the moon's surface in the next six years.""Regolith covers the entire surface of the moon and is made up of clay, glass fragments, mineral..""..as well as chemical compounds such as iron oxide from which oxygen, water and fuel could be extracted."SOURCES: The Telegraph, European Space Agency Press Release, The Washington Posthttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/21/european-space-agency-wants-mine-moon-2025/http://spaceref.com/news/viewpr.html?pid=53602https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/europe/europeans-contemplating-moon-mission-by-2025/2019/01/21/c7bb1230-1d9b-11e9-a759-2b8541bbbe20_story.html?noredirect=on&utm_term=.c23dccee146c***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 10:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/23/3769808/3769808_A1B6C4560E794C3A81B5E2CDDD8DCF65_190123_3769808_Europe_could_be_looking_to_mine_the_moon_by_2025_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, europe, moon, mining the moon, european space agency, regolith, moon rock, mining moon rock, moon regolith]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3769742</guid>
      <title>Chinese construction in Tibet have military implications for India</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Print reports that China's various infrastructure projects in Tibet could have military implications for India.China is building the G-6 expressway to connect Beijing to Lhasa, the capital of Tibet. While the Beijing to Xining portion is completed, the 546-kilometer stretch between Xining and Lhasa is still under construction.From Lhasa, a 75-kilometer long, four-lane road is also being built to provide direct access to Tsedang, via huge twin tunnels that will cut across the mountain range.The infrastructure for a Tibetan railway line from Lhasa to Nyingchi is also underway. The railway line is reportedly being laid, with stations being built in Gonggar, Dranang, Tsedang, and Nyingchi.Satellite images published by The Print also reveal an underground facility constructed by the Chinese People's Liberation Army just 50 kilometers from the Indian border and 60 kilometers from the Indian Army's forward post.The projects have strategic implications for the PLA, allowing convoys to cover the 3,725-kilometer distance between Beijing and Lhasa in four days or less.But the large number of strategic routes may negatively impact India, as they could face serious difficulties in any future confrontation with China, according to a commentary from the Observer Research Foundation.The Indian vice chief of army staff has voiced serious concerns about the lack of funding for the Army, pointing to Chinese infrastructural development along the northern borders to seek more resource allocation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. G-6 expressway from Beijing to Lhasa, direct road connecting Lhasa to Tsedang2. Tibetan railway line from Lhasa to Nyingchi3. Chinese underground facility near Indian border4. Strategic implications for Chinese People's Liberation Army5. Military implications for Indian ArmyVOICEOVER (in English): "China is building the G-6 expressway to connect Beijing to Lhasa, the capital of Tibet. While the Beijing to Xining portion is completed, the 546-kilometer stretch between Xining and Lhasa is still under construction.""From Lhasa, a 75-kilometer long, four-lane road is also being built to provide direct access to Tsedang, via huge twin tunnels that will cut across the mountain range.""The infrastructure for a Tibetan railway line from Lhasa to Nyingchi is also underway. The railway line is reportedly being laid, with stations being built in Gonggar, Dranang, Tsedang, and Nyingchi.""Satellite images published by The Print also reveal an underground facility constructed by the Chinese People's Liberation Army just 50 kilometers from the Indian border and 60 kilometers from the Indian Army's forward post.""The projects have strategic implications for the PLA, allowing convoys to cover the 3,725-kilometer distance between Beijing and Lhasa in four days or less.""But the large number of strategic routes may negatively impact India, as they could face serious difficulties in any future confrontation with China, according to a commentary from the Observer Research Foundation."SOURCES: The Print, Observer Research Foundationhttps://theprint.in/security/satellite-images-show-china-is-building-underground-facility-50-km-from-india-border/179792/https://theprint.in/security/chinas-new-move-in-tibet-is-beijing-lhasa-high-speed-road-that-can-move-troops-superfast/167364/https://theprint.in/security/china-gives-big-push-to-road-rail-infrastructure-in-areas-bordering-india/138856/https://www.orfonline.org/research/india-is-still-losing-to-china-in-the-border-infrastructure-war-44595/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 09:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/23/3769742/3769742_3FF0C9060E0C4FBC93BE6171E280915B_190123_3769742_Chinese_construction_in_Tibet_have_military_impl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, chinese infrastructure, tibet expressway, tibetan railway, G6 expressway, china underground facility, PLA, indian army, india military]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3769643</guid>
      <title>Scientists find ancient life buried underneath Antarctic ice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have discovered remains of tiny sea creatures deep beneath the ice in Antarctica, according to a report published in Nature.Scientists in Antarctica have drilled beneath a frozen Antarctic lake and discovered signs of ancient aquatic life as part of the expedition SALSA, or Subglacial Antarctic Lakes Scientific Access.The scientists used a hot water bore to drill through the ice.Remains of tiny sea animals such as crustaceans and a tardigrade, also known as water bears, were discovered in the Subglacial Lake Mercer.The remains of these species were found preserved underneath a kilometer of Antarctic ice.David Harwood, a micropaleontologist at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln involved with the project, said they didn't expect to find ancient life buried underneath the ice.Slawek Tulaczyk, a glaciologist at the University of California, Santa Cruz who was not part of the research team, told Nature that the nothing like this ever been discovered beneath the glacial ice.Tulaczyk said the sea creatures probably lived in ponds and streams in the Transantarctic Mountains when the climate was warmer.He explained the sea creatures the river could have washed down the creatures from the mountains to the lake.The animals may have been in the lake when ice sheets started to form over it and froze them over.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Subglacial Lake Mercer2. Ice being drilled 3. Remains of sea animals found beneath the ice4. A measurement line depicting where the species were found frozenVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists in Antarctica have drilled beneath a frozen Antarctic lake and discovered signs of ancient aquatic life as part of the expedition SALSA, or Subglacial Antarctic Lakes Scientific Access.""According to a report published in Nature, the scientists used a hot water drill to bore through the ice.""Remains of tiny sea animals such as crustaceans and a tardigrade, also known as water bears, were discovered in the Subglacial Lake Mercer.""The remains of these species were found preserved underneath a kilometer of Antarctic ice."SOURCES: Nature, Fox News, Subglacial Antarctic Lakes Scientific Accesshttps://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-00106-zhttps://www.foxnews.com/science/scientists-exploring-antarctic-buried-under-ice-find-surprising-signs-of-ancient-lifehttps://salsa-antarctica.org/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 07:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/23/3769643/3769643_A05427BE8CCB487C873987512E5AB0E2_190123_3769643_Scientists_find_ancient_life_buried_underneath_A_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, antarctica, antarctic lake, sheets of ice, preserved animals, animal remains, Subglacial Lake Mercer, ancient life buried underneath the ice, antarctic ice, crustaceans, tardigrade, water bears, ancient aquatic life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3769491</guid>
      <title>Scientists alarmed at rate magnetic North Pole is moving</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe magnetic North Pole is moving at an alarming rate and forcing researchers to update a navigational model. According to The Washington Post, almost half of the employees from the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, which is responsible for updating the World Magnetic Model, are on furlough due to the government shutdown, as the Democrat-controlled House of Representatives refuses to fund U.S. President Donald Trump's $5 billion border wall.Earth's poles naturally shift and change due to unpredictable flows of molten liquid iron at the Earth's core caused by the planet's rotation. This liquid's movement creates the Earth's magnetic field. However, an article posted in the journal Nature shows that the Earth's magnetic North Pole has been moving at an unprecedented rate. The movement began in the mid-1990s and it is now headed towards Siberia at roughly 55 kilometers per year.Scientists from the NOAA and the British Geological Survey study and update the World Magnetic Model every five years.However, due to the dramatic movement, the model needs to be updated earlier than scheduled. The current government shutdown has forced the NOAA to postpone the update from January 15 to January 30.This model is necessary for accurate civilian and military navigation. According to the report, the abrupt changes may be due to a geomagnetic pulse that occurred beneath South America in 2016.In 2017, Phil Livermore a geophysicist from the University of Leeds detected a high-speed jet of liquid iron beneath Canada that seemed to be weakening the magnetic field in that area. Livermore believes this could be linked to the current changes in the earth's magnetic field.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Flow of Earth's core2. Movement of magnetic North Pole over the years3. Geomagnetic pulse in South America in 20164. Jet of liquid iron beneath Canada VOICEOVER (in English): "Earth's poles naturally shift and change due to unpredictable flows of molten liquid iron at the Earth's core caused by the earth's rotation. This liquid's movement creates the earth's magnetic field." "However, an article posted in the journal Nature shows that the Earth's magnetic North Pole has been moving at an unprecedented rate." "The movement began in the mid-1990s and the magnetic North Pole is now headed towards Siberia at roughly 55 kilometers per year.""According to the report, the abrupt changes may be due to a geomagnetic pulse that occurred beneath South America in 2016.""In 2017, Phil Livermore a geophysicist from the University of Leeds detected a high-speed jet of liquid iron beneath Canada that seemed to be weakening the magnetic field in that area. SOURCES: Nature, Reuters, The Washington Post, Maritime Executive https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-00007-1https://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-north/shifting-north-magnetic-pole-forces-unprecedented-navigation-fix-idUSKCN1P51UEhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2019/01/17/north-pole-is-moving-shutdown-means-we-arent-keeping-up/?utm_term=.a7c734b372d2https://www.maritime-executive.com/article/magnetic-north-pole-shifting-rapidly-and-unpredicatably   ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 02:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/23/3769491/3769491_EE55004226A24C5297364BCBADF70A8B_190123_3769491_Scientists_alarmed_at_rate_magnetic_North_Pole_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Trump, north magnetic pole, trump shutdown, NOAA, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, north pole moving, north pole shift, wandering pole]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3770608</guid>
      <title>Carbon capture system turns CO2 into usable electricity and hydrogen fuel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists have developed a new carbon capture system that absorbs CO2 and produces useable electricity and hydrogen fuel, according to New Atlas. Researchers from Georgia Tech and Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology designed the device using the ocean's carbon sink ability as inspiration, and published their results in the journal Science in Nov. 2018. According to New Atlas, the device is called the Hybrid Na-CO2 System and is in essence a large liquid battery. A sodium metal anode is place in an organic electrolyte, while the cathode is placed in an aqueous solution. The two liquids are separated by a sodium Super Ionic Conductor membrane. When carbon dioxide is pumped into the aqueous electrolyte, it reacts with the cathode, turning the solution more acidic, which then generates electricity and creates hydrogen. During testing, the system reported a CO2 conversion efficiency of 50 percent and was able to run for over 1,000 hours without damage to the electrodes. Another benefit of the system is that no CO2 is released during the process. The leftover CO2 from the electrolyte is recovered as baking soda. For carbon capture systems to become practical however, they would need to be produced at a much larger scales in order to have an impact on reducing levels of atmospheric CO2. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. CO2 being captured to make electricity and hydrogen2. Hybrid Na-CO2 System parts3. Hybrid Na-CO2 System processVOICEOVER (in English): "According to New Atlas, scientists have developed a new carbon capture system that absorbs CO2 and produces useable electricity and hydrogen fuel." "The device is called the Hybrid Na-CO2 System and is in essence a large liquid battery." "A sodium metal anode is place in an organic electrolyte, while the cathode is placed in an aqueous solution. The two liquids are separated by a sodium Super Ionic Conductor membrane." "When carbon dioxide is pumped into the aqueous electrolyte, it reacts with the cathode, turning the solution more acidic, which then generates electricity and creates hydrogen." SOURCES: New Atlas, Sciencehttps://newatlas.com/hybrid-co2-capture-hydrogen-system/58145/https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S258900421830186X?via%3Dihub ***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/24/3770608/3770608_6E1164AACAF142DCA50494CAEFAC351B_190124_3770608_Carbon_capture_system_turns_CO2_into_usable_elec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, carbon capture, carbon capture system, carbon sequestration, Hybrid Na-CO2 System, carbon dioxide, global warming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3770595</guid>
      <title>Planetary collision that created moon made life possible on Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANMost of Earth's vital elements for life mostly likely came from a planetary collision that also created the moon more than 4.4 billion years ago, according to a Rice University study published in the journal Science Advances. For life to occur on a planet, volatile elements including carbon, nitrogen and sulfur must be present. According to the study, a catastrophic collision between Earth while it was still forming and a Mars-sized object with volatile elements could explain how these elements were introduced. Researchers used a combination of high-temperature, high-pressure experiments to mimic these conditions in the lab. The results were then fed into computer simulations that were able to determine the size and chemical composition of the impacting planet.  The team conclude that Earth's volatiles arrived from a collision with an embryonic planet that had a sulfur-rich core.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Planetary collision with Earth2. Life on a planet must have carbon, nitrogen and sulfur3. Mar-sized planetary embryo elemental makeup 4. Mar-sized planetary embryo introducing volatiles to Earth after collisionVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a Rice University study published in the journal Science Advances, most of Earth's vital elements for life mostly likely came from a planetary collision that also created the moon more than 4.4 billion years ago." "For life to occur on a planet, volatile elements including carbon, nitrogen and sulfur must be present." "According to the study, a catastrophic collision between Earth while it was still forming and a Mars-sized object with volatile elements could explain how these elements were introduced." "Researchers used a combination of high-temperature, high-pressure experiments to mimic these conditions in the lab." "The results were then fed into computer simulations that were able to determine the size and chemical composition of the impacting planet."  "The team conclude that Earth's volatiles arrived from a collision with an embryonic planet that had a sulfur-rich core." SOURCES: Phys.orghttps://phys.org/news/2019-01-planetary-collision-moon-life-earth.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 13:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/24/3770595/3770595_A3990049F7D249ACB0C8F4E2D963B8B6_190124_3770595_Planetary_collision_that_created_moon_made_life__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, Earth formation, planetary collision, Proto Earth, Earth volatiles, Earth volatile elements]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3770480</guid>
      <title>Facebook and Airbus test internet drones in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook is working with aeronautics company Airbus on drone-based connectivity, according to German publication Netzpolitik. According to a document obtained by Netzpolitik through a Freedom of Information request, test flights for an Airbus Zephyr drone with a Facebook payload were scheduled for November and December 2018 in Australia.The two companies previously met with European regulators in April 2018 to discuss providing connectivity using Zephyr drones. One European Commission official noted in an email that it could be deployed in a smart cities approach.The Zephyr is a 'High Altitude Pseudo Satellite,' or HAPS, that charges its batteries via solar panels and can stay operative for weeks.Facebook and Airbus are reportedly testing the Model S, which has a 25-meter wingspan. TechCrunch reports that it operates at an altitude of 20 kilometers, and uses millimeter-wave radio to broadcast to the ground.The project is similar to Facebook's Aquila drone program, which aimed to provide internet connectivity to remote parts of the world. It was dropped in 2018 after years of development.Though it's clear that Airbus and Facebook met with the Australian Civil Aviation Safety Authority to discuss the test flights, it's unclear if they actually took place.A Facebook spokesperson told Netzpolitik, 'We continue to work with partners on High Altitude Platform System connectivity. We don't have further details to share at this time.' Airbus did not respond to a request for comment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Airbus and Facebook drone test flights in Australia2. Connectivity using Zephyr drones, can be deployed in smart cities approach3. Zephyr drone using solar power, can stay operative for weeks4. Zephyr S model wingspan, other features5. Facebook Aquila drone programVOICEOVER (in English): "According to a document obtained by Netzpolitik through a Freedom of Information request, test flights for an Airbus Zephyr drone with a Facebook payload were scheduled for November and December 2018 in Australia.""The two companies previously met with European regulators in April 2018 to discuss providing connectivity using Zephyr drones. One European Commission official noted in an email that it could be deployed in a smart cities approach.""The Zephyr is a 'High Altitude Pseudo Satellite' or HAPS that charges its batteries via solar panels and can stay operative for weeks.""Facebook and Airbus are reportedly testing the Model S, which has a 25-meter wingspan. TechCrunch reports that it operates at an altitude of 20 kilometers, and uses millimeter-wave radio to broadcast to the ground.""The project is similar to Facebook's Aquila drone program, which aimed to provide internet connectivity to remote parts of the world. It was dropped in 2018 after years of development."SOURCES: Netzpolitik, TechCrunchhttps://netzpolitik.org/2019/facebook-and-airbus-hold-secretive-drone-tests-in-the-australian-bush/https://cdn.netzpolitik.org/wp-upload/2019/01/Facebook-Airbus-Zephyr-Test-Wyndham-Australia-Meeting-documents-FOI.pdfhttps://techcrunch.com/2019/01/21/facebook-airbus-solar-drones-internet-program/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 10:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/24/3770480/3770480_02545B03B2F74F959014687B27EF04F5_190124_3770480_Facebook_and_Airbus_test_internet_drones_in_Aust_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, internet drone, facebook drone, airbus drone, zephyr drone, zephyr s drone, drone connectivity, test flight, facebook, airbus, internet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3770332</guid>
      <title>New Chinese app to track those in debt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new program on Tencent-owned social media app WeChat has been launched in the northern Hebei province that tracks debtors, according to a report in the state-run China Daily newspaper.The program, whose name translates as "A Map of Deadbeat Debtors," was introduced on Jan. 16 by the Higher People's Court of Hebei. The program allows users in Hebei province to find if there are any debtors within 500 meters.Users are able to see the precise location of the debtors in the area. The China Daily says the program also allows users to "whistle-blow on debtors capable of paying their debts."It is not clear if the app lists names, photos or any other identification marks of the debtors.The China Daily says the app will "create a socially credible environment." The program is a part of China's new social credit system that is currently being rolled out by Beijing and will become mandatory in 2020.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. WeChat app on a smartphone and map of China with the Chinese flag2. The program finding debtors within a certain area3. The program precisely locating the debtors in the areaVOICEOVER (in English): "The state-run China Daily newspaper reports that a new program on Tencent-owned social media app WeChat has been launched in the northern Hebei province that tracks debtors.""The program, whose name translates as 'A Map of Deadbeat Debtors,' was introduced on Jan. 16 by the Higher People's Court of Hebei. The program allows users to find if there are any debtors within 500 meters.""Users are able to see the precise location of the debtors in the area. The China Daily says the program also allows users to 'whistle-blow on debtors capable of paying their debts.'"SOURCES: Business Insider, China Daily, South China Morning Post  https://www.businessinsider.com/china-app-shows-map-of-people-in-debt-for-social-credit-system-report-2019-1http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/201901/16/WS5c3edfb8a3106c65c34e4d75.htmlhttps://www.scmp.com/news/china/economy/article/2114768/china-create-national-name-and-shame-system-deadbeat-borrowers***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 08:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/24/3770332/3770332_0656BAA5C1A848498245B8FC6B294C65_190124_3770332_New_Chinese_app_to_track_those_in_debt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, app, debt, technology, chinese technology, chinese technology 2019, map of deadbeat debtors app, map of deadbeat debtors china, china social credit system, china debt app, china social credit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3770307</guid>
      <title>Researcher's study method for memory recovery for Alzheimer's patients</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research claims it has successfully reversed memory loss in an animal model of Alzheimer's.New research published in the journal Brain has discovered that memory loss in Alzheimer's found in animals was linked to epigenetics. Epigenetics are alterations found in gene expressions that are not derived from DNA sequences.A team of scientists from the University at Buffalo studied mouse models that carried Alzheimer's Disease as well as post-mortem brain tissues from patients with Alzheimer's.Scientists discovered that a process linked to epigenetics called repressive histone modification affected memory loss in Alzheimer's patients.The abnormal histone modifications detected reduce glutamate receptors. This leads to loss in synaptic function and memory deficiency. The animals were injected three times with special compounds made to inhibit the histone modifier that was causing memory loss. Results showed that the animals recovered glutamate receptor expression and function in the frontal cortex. These improvements lasted for a week.According to the Alzheimer's Association, every 65 seconds someone in the United States develops the disease.Currently, roughly 5.7 million Americans are living with Alzheimer's dementia.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Epigenetics explanation.2. Analysis of animal model Alzheimer's and post-mortem brain tissues from patients with Alzheimer's3. Histone modification link to memory loss4. Rats get injections of special compounds to fight histone modification linked to memory lossVOICEOVER (in English): "New research published in the journal Brain has discovered that memory loss in Alzheimer's found in animals was linked to epigenetics.""Epigenetics are alterations found in gene expressions that are not derived from DNA sequences.""A team of scientists from the University at Buffalo studied mouse models that carried Alzheimer's Disease as well as post-mortem brain tissues from patients with Alzheimer's.""Scientists discovered that a process linked to epigenetics called repressive histone modification affected memory loss in Alzheimer's patients.""The abnormal histone modifications detected reduce glutamate receptors. This leads to loss in synaptic function and memory deficiency. ""The animals were injected three times with special compounds made to inhibit the histone modifier that was causing memory loss.""Results showed that the animals recovered glutamate receptor expression and function in the frontal cortex. These improvements lasted for a week."SOURCES: Brain, University at Buffalo, Futurism, Alzheimer's Associationhttps://academic.oup.com/brain/advance-article/doi/10.1093/brain/awy354/5298257#129958788http://www.buffalo.edu/news/releases/2019/01/013.htmlhttps://futurism.com/the-byte/reverse-memory-loss-alzheimers-patientshttps://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/facts-figures***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 07:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/24/3770307/3770307_D142E179496A4B598460421366CD22B8_190124_3770307_Researcher_s_study_method_for_memory_recovery_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, alzheimer's, alzheimer's disease, alzheimer's cure, alzheimer's treatment, alzheimer's drugs, nerve cells, brain shrinkage, alzheimer's brain, histone methylation, epigenetics, memory, glutamate receptor, histones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3770220</guid>
      <title>Scientists use optogenetics to erase memories of drug addiction from rats</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA team of researchers has successfully erased cocaine-related memories in rats using optogenetics. Researchers from the University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine made rats addicted to cocaine by giving them an infusion of cocaine each time the rats pressed a lever. The infusion would be accompanied by a tone and a light.According to the paper published in the journal Cell Reports, the rats would then associate the tone and light with the cocaine high and would exhibit drug-seeking behavior by repeatedly pressing the lever.The team studied electrical recordings from rat brain tissue and found essential connections between the medial geniculate nucleus and the lateral amygdala. These connections created memories that associated the cocaine high with external cues.The team then used a biological technique called optogenetics to erase memories related to cocaine use. Optogenetics uses light to alter cell behavior. It allows scientists to turn neurons on or off selectively. Rats that had memories related to cocaine erased pressed the lever fewer times than those who did not go through the optogenetic procedure. These rats also resisted the drug even when placed in a different environment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Rats in the experiment receive cocaine infusion and audio-visual stimulation when they press a lever2. Scientists study connections between the medial geniculate nucleus and the lateral amygdala3. Scientists use optogenetics to erase memories of cocaine in the rats' brains4. Rats that are subjected to optogenetics press lever fewer timesVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine made rats addicted to cocaine by giving them an infusion of cocaine each time the rats pressed a lever. The infusion would be accompanied by a tone and a light.""According to the paper published in the journal Cell Reports, the rats would then associate the tone and light with the cocaine high and would exhibit drug-seeking behavior by repeatedly pressing the lever.""The team studied electrical recordings from rat brain tissue and found essential connections between the medial geniculate nucleus and the lateral amygdala. These connections created memories that associated the cocaine high with external cues.""The team then used a biological technique called optogenetics to erase memories related to cocaine use. Optogenetics uses light to alter cell behavior. It allows scientists to turn neurons on or off selectively." "Rats that had memories related to cocaine erased pressed the lever fewer times than those who did not go through the optogenetic procedure. These rats also resisted the drug even when placed in a different environment."SOURCES: Cell Reports, University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine, Futurism https://www.cell.com/cell-reports/fulltext/S2211-1247(18)32080-1https://www.upmc.com/media/news/012219-cocaine-relapsehttps://futurism.com/the-byte/erasing-memories-cocaine-use-drug***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/24/3770220/3770220_9A9EB43416374B2186E3F0128C95DE42_190124_3770220_Scientists_use_optogenetics_to_erase_memories_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, optogenetics, drug addiction, drug abuse, relapse, addiction, cocaine, memory]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3771358</guid>
      <title>U.S. to aid Venezuela opposition by cutting off revenue to Maduro</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANReuters reports that the U.S. is backing Venezuela's opposition leader and interim president, and wants to ensure the country's oil revenues go to him.Nicolas Maduro had been inaugurated as President of Venezuela following a re-election vote largely regarded as fraudulent.Opposition leader Juan Gaido claimed Maduro's rule is illegitimate, and swore himself in as interim president on the basis that he is head of the National Assembly.According to France24, Guaido told a crowd of thousands that he would install a transitional government and hold free elections.He is backed by the U.S. and Canada, Argentina, Colombia, and Brazil, and several other countries.Mexico is choosing not to intervene, while Russia and Turkey have openly criticized the U.S. stance as an example of American colonialism.Reuters reports that according to national security adviser John Bolton, the U.S. is focusing on cutting off Maduro's revenue sources, which are primarily from oil exports, and divert them to Guaido.Despite international support, Guaido is not recognized by Venezuela's armed forces. He also has no influence on day-to-day administration, which includes distributing food and medicine to the populaceMaduro has responded to the Trump administration's support of Guaido by severing diplomatic ties with the U.S. He gave American diplomats 72 hours to leave the country, but Washington has refused to comply.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nicolas Maduro inauguration, Juan Guaido sworn in as interim president2. Guaido aims to hold free elections, supported by U.S., Canada, and other countries3. U.S. wants to disconnect Maduro oil revenue, divert it to Guaido4. Guaido not recognized by Venezuela armed forcesVOICEOVER (in English): "Nicolas Maduro had been inaugurated as President of Venezuela following a re-election vote largely regarded as fraudulent.""Opposition leader Juan Gaido claimed Maduro's rule is illegitimate, and swore himself in as interim president on the basis that he is head of the National Assembly.""According to France24, Guaido told a crowd of thousands that he would install a transitional government and hold free elections.""He is backed by the U.S. and Canada, Argentina, Colombia, and Brazil, and several other countries.""Reuters reports that according to national security adviser John Bolton, the U.S. is focusing on cutting off Maduro's revenue sources, which are primarily from oil exports, and divert them to Guaido.""Despite international support, Guaido is not recognized by Venezuela's armed forces. He also has no influence on day-to-day administration, which includes distributing food and medicine to the populace."SOURCES: Reuters, Los Angeles Timeshttps://www.reuters.com/article/venezuela-politics/wrapup-1-u-s-seeks-to-cut-off-revenues-for-venezuelas-maduro-aid-opposition-idUSL1N1ZO10Uhttps://www.latimes.com/nation/la-fg-venezuela-us-20190124-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/26/3771358/3771358_EA70B85EC8D0437F8FE14EF4F7DDD787_190126_3771358_U_S__to_aid_Venezuela_opposition_by_cutting_off__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, venezuela, venezuela president, venezuela opposition, interim president, nicolas maduro, juan guaido, venezuela oil, venezuela oil, oil revenue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3771185</guid>
      <title>How climate change and global warming can cause colder winters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANClimate change and global warming cause extreme temperature fluctuations, these are causing unusually cold winters in some regions in the US. The terms "weather" and "climate" are not interchangeable. Weather refers to daily variations in temperature, precipitation, wind and other variables. According to the NOAA, climate is the average weather conditions of an area over at least a 30-year period."Global warming refers to the gradual increase of the Earth's average temperature. The sudden rise in temperature in recent years is primarily attributed to the increasing presence of greenhouse gases caused by human activity. These gases include carbon dioxide, methane, nitrous oxide and ozone.Climate change refers to changes in weather patterns in Earth over an extended period of time. These changes are natural, however, activities including fossil fuel combustion, land use, deforestation, and agriculture magnify these changes.Research published in 2018 in Nature Communications explained that the record-breaking cold weather and polar vortex disruptions are caused by Arctic warming. Fast flowing air currents located in the Earth's northern hemisphere called jet streams are responsible for weather fluctuations around the globe.These winds move from east-to-west and are pushed by the difference in temperature between Arctic and tropical air. Higher temperatures in the Arctic make the jetstream move further south. This fluctuation causes places located to the south of the Arctic to experience colder winters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Difference between weather and climate2. Explanation of global warming3. Explanation of climate change4. Arctic warming intensified causing polar vortex fluctuationsVOICEOVER (in English): "The terms "weather" and "climate" are not interchangeable. Weather refers to daily variations in temperature, precipitation, wind etc.""And, according to the NOAA, climate is the average weather conditions of an area over at least a 30-year period.""Global warming refers to the gradual increase of the Earth's average temperature. The sudden rise in temperature in recent years is primarily attributed to the increasing presence of greenhouse gases caused by human activity.""These gases include carbon dioxide, methane, nitrous oxide, and ozone.""Climate change refers to changes in weather patterns in Earth over an extended period of time.""These changes are natural, however, activities including fossil fuel combustion, land use, deforestation, and agriculture magnify these changes.""A research published in 2018 in Nature Communications explained that the record-breaking cold weather and polar vortex disruptions are caused by Arctic warming.""Fast flowing air currents located in the Earth's northern hemisphere called jet streams are responsible for weather fluctuations around the globe.""These winds move from east-to-west and are pushed by the difference between Arctic and tropical air.""Higher temperatures in the Arctic make the jetstream move further south. This fluctuation causes places located to the South of the Arctic to experience colder winters."SOURCES: National Geographic, Rutgers Today, Nature, Scientific American, Accuweather, Science Advanceshttps://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2019/01/climate-change-colder-winters-global-warming-polar-vortex/https://news.rutgers.edu/news/warm-arctic-means-colder-snowier-winters-northeastern-us-study-says/20180309#.XElgQmgzaUmhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-018-02992-9https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/earthtalks-global-warming-harsher-winter/https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/what-are-jet-streams-and-how-do-they-influence-the-weather-we-experience/70003416http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/4/10/eaat3272***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 12:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/25/3771185/3771185_809480633366442BA3939CD31B5CF483_190125_3771185_How_climate_change_and_global_warming_can_cause__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, global warming, climate change, polar vortex, jet stream, extream weather, weather fluctuation, green house gases]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3771160</guid>
      <title>Search for Spanish toddler hit by setback</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe rescue mission to save a two-year-old boy from a well in Spain has encountered some unexpected problems.Julen Rosello, a two-year-old boy, was with his family when he walked away and unexpectedly fell down a narrow well on January 13, The Guardian reports.The well is around 25 centimeters wide and is believed to be 100 meters deep. Rescuers found the boy's bag of sweets and a cup when they lowered a camera down around 75 meters into the well.The Spanish Civil Guard stated that rescuers did attempt to widen the hole, reported NBC, citing TVE.They reportedly attempted this while also trying to dig an alternate shaft in order to connect the two tunnels and rescue the baby. The rescuers have now finished digging a second vertical shaft in an effort to reach the boy, El Pais reports. They were originally planning to go down using a cage to dig a horizontal tunnel into the first shaft.However, the cage got stuck 40 meters down the shaft. They were aiming to reach 60 meters depth. A rescue team are now planning to dig 4 meters to connect with the first shaft. Each of them will work in 40 to 60 minute shifts. It will take around 24 hours for them to connect to the first borehole, according to El Pais.Rescuers have yet to locate the boy. They have only managed to find strands of hair with DNA that matches his.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boy falls into a well 2. Dimensions of the well 3. Bag of sweets and a cup found by the rescuers4. Original rescue plans5. The second tunnel6. A cage which was supposed to go down the second tunnel7. Where the cage got stuck 8. New rescue plans VOICEOVER (in English): "The Guardian reports the two-year-old boy named Julen Rosello was with his family when he walked away and unexpectedly fell down a narrow well on January 13.""The well is around 25 cm wide and is believed to be 100m deep.""Rescuers found the boy's bag of sweets and a cup when they lowered a camera down around 75m into the well.""Citing TVE, NBC reports that the Spanish Civil Guard said that rescuers did attempt to widen the hole."Reportedly, they attempted this while also trying to dig an alternate shaft in order to connect the two tunnels and rescue the baby.""El Pais reports the rescuers have now finished digging a second vertical shaft in an effort to reach the boy.""The rescuers were originally planning to go down using a cage to dig a horizontal tunnel into the first shaft.""However, the cage got stuck 40 meters down the shaft. They were aiming to reach 60 meters depth.""A rescue team are now planning to dig 4 meters to connect with the first shaft." "Each of them will work in 40 to 60 minute shifts.""According to El Pais, it will take around 24 hours for them to connect to the first borehole."SOURCES: El Pais, NBC, The Guardian, The Local ES, https://elpais.com/elpais/2019/01/23/inenglish/1548231368_142142.htmlhttps://elpais.com/elpais/2019/01/22/media/1548176417_593093.htmlhttps://elpais.com/elpais/2019/01/22/inenglish/1548161678_636501.htmlhttps://elpais.com/elpais/2019/01/22/inenglish/1548144373_303448.htmlhttps://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/Boy-Falls-Down-Well-Spain-504323791.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/14/rescuers-search-for-toddler-who-fell-into-110-metre-well-in-spainhttps://www.thelocal.es/20190121/everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-mission-to-rescue-two-year-old-julen***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 11:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/25/3771160/3771160_3E82E8250477462BA51422ACD8D49A5B_190125_3771160_Search_for_Spanish_toddler_hit_by_setback_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, spain, spanish toddler, Julen Rosell, julen rosell rescue, spanish toddler rescue, Julen Rosell update, toddler well rescue, toddler falls into a well]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3771074</guid>
      <title>New research debunks link between solar cycle and North Atlantic winter weather</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearch published in Nature Geoscience presents new evidence that debunks the existence of a correlation between solar activity and winter weather in the North.The North Atlantic Oscillation is a key driver of winter weather patterns in the Northern hemisphere. A positive NAO is linked to mild and wet winters in Europe, while a negative NAO indicates a snowy and cold winters.According to Columbia University, published research in recent years claims the NAO is linked to the solar cycle, a periodic, 11-year change during which the sun's activity increases then ebbs.The theory indicates that the connection between the two is strong enough to inform predictions of the NAO by up to a decade in advance.But using computer modeling and extended observations, scientists at Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory and Columbia's School of Engineering found no evidence of any correlation prior to 1960. The apparent correlation had been due to atmospheric variability, and not the sun.The correlation theory would have proven advantageous to Northern hemisphere societies, as it would have allowed them to plan for intense flooding and storms.But the research debunking the link is also important for future climate research, now that it appears the causes for decadal weather changes lie elsewhere.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Atlantic Oscillation2. 11-year solar cycle3. Correlation theory between solar cycle and North Atlantic Oscillation4. Correlation theory debunkedVOICEOVER (in English): "The North Atlantic Oscillation is a key driver of winter weather patterns in the Northern hemisphere. A positive NAO is linked to mild and wet winters in Europe, while a negative NAO indicates a snowy and cold winters.""According to Columbia University, published research in recent years claims the NAO is linked to the solar cycle, a periodic, 11-year change during which the sun's activity increases then ebbs.""The theory indicates that the connection between the two is strong enough to inform predictions of the NAO by up to a decade in advance.""But using computer modeling and extended observations, scientists at Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory and Columbia's School of Engineering found no evidence of any correlation prior to 1960.""The apparent correlation had been due to atmospheric variability, and not the sun."SOURCES: Columbia Universityhttps://blogs.ei.columbia.edu/2019/01/22/debunking-solar-cycle-north-atlantic-winter-weather-connection/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 10:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/25/3771074/3771074_6B97E9FA041D4D40807807205B7F8FF8_190125_3771074_New_research_debunks_link_between_solar_cycle_an_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, solar cycle, north atlantic oscillation, NAO, sun cycle, sunspot cycle, correlation theory, theory debunked, winter weather, north atlantic winter, europe winter, weather pattern, climate]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3770868</guid>
      <title>China monitors its citizens using AI-embedded CCTV cameras</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina has developed CCTV cameras embedded with artificial intelligence to track the movements of civilians across the country.The program, Ensemble Net, was trained using clips from CCTV footage and is supposedly 90 percent accurate, New Scientist reports.The system will be able to scan body shapes and facial features. It will then scan the database to see if it finds a match.The program will also be able to identify a person in disguise or if their back is faced towards the camera.The AI-powered CCTV cameras have already been used by Chinese authorities to track down fugitives, CNet reports.China plans to have over 600 million AI-powered CCTV cameras by 2020, according to Q Daily, a Chinese online publication.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of China, CCTV camera, and a CCTV camera surveilling people2. CCTV footage and a measurement bar3. A man's body and facial features being scanned4. The same man in a disguise and with his back faced towards the cameraVOICEOVER (in English): "New Scientist reports China has developed CCTV cameras embedded with artificial intelligence to track the movements of civilians across the country.""The program, Ensemble Net, was trained using clips from CCTV footage and is supposedly 90 percent accurate.""The system will be able to scan body shapes and facial features. It will then scan the database to see if it finds a match.""Apparently the program will also be able to identify a person in disguise or if their back is faced towards the camera."SOURCES: New Scientist, CNet, Q Daily https://www.newscientist.com/article/2191558-chinese-army-ai-can-track-people-across-different-cctv-cameras/https://www.cnet.com/news/ai-powered-cctv-cameras-in-china-catch-another-wanted-fugitive/https://www.qdaily.com/articles/47431.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/25/3770868/3770868_2C83651608E245A8992D8664186AF600_190125_3770868_China_monitors_its_citizens_using_AI_embedded_CC_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, china, facial recognition, artificial intelligence, CCTV cameras, china surveillance, china surveillance state, china surveillance system, china surveillance cameras, china social credit, chinese surveillance, chinese surveillance system, china ai, china cctv, total surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3772415</guid>
      <title>Climate change affecting soil's ability to absorb CO2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new research paper by Columbia University's School of Engineering studied how fluctuations in the Earth's hydrological cycle caused by climate change can affect the ability of soil to trap carbon dioxide.Currently, the ocean and other terrestrial biospheres are absorbing roughly 50 percent of carbon dioxide emissions.According to the paper published in the journal Nature, they analyzed data from four Earth system models to look for reductions in net biome productivity caused by changes in soil moisture. Net biome productivity or NBP refers to the net gain or loss of carbon from a region over a period of time. Results from the study showed that the land was only absorbing half as much carbon dioxide as it could have been due to changes in soil moisture.If extreme weather events continue to affect the Earth's hydrological cycle, the land's ability to absorb carbon dioxide will be reduced causing even more extreme weather due to carbon dioxide overload in the atmosphere.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Climate change disrupting Earth's hydrological cycle; percentage of CO2 absorbed by Earth2. Analysis of Earth models; explanation of net biome productivity3. Earth only absorbing half as much as it could be4. Extreme weather caused by rise in CO2 emissionsVOICEOVER (in English): "A new research paper by Columbia University's School of Engineering studied how fluctuations in the Earth's hydrological cycle caused by climate change can affect the capability of soil to trap carbon dioxide emissions.""Currently, the ocean and other terrestrial biospheres are absorbing roughly 50 percent of carbon dioxide emissions.""According to the paper published in the journal Nature, they analyzed data from four Earth system models to look for reductions in net biome productivity caused by changes in soil moisture.""Net biome productivity or NBP refers to the net gain or loss of carbon from a region over a period of time." "Results from the study showed that the land was only absorbing half as much carbon dioxide as it could have been due to changes in soil moisture.""If extreme weather events continue to affect the Earth's hydrological cycle, the land's ability to absorb carbon dioxide will be reduced causing even more extreme weather due to carbon dioxide overload in the atmosphere."SOURCES: Nature, Columbia University, Yale Universityhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-018-0848-xhttps://engineering.columbia.edu/press-releases/climate-change-tipping-pointhttp://climatecommunication.yale.edu/publications/climate-change-in-the-american-mind-december-2018/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 08:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/28/3772415/3772415_6A8B4265A26349A18434E6D95E71CDD1_190128_3772415_Climate_change_affecting_soil_s_ability_to_absor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, climate change, carbon dioxide emissions, CO2,  fossil fuel emissions, global warming, hydrological cycle, extreme weather]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3773144</guid>
      <title>Volvo builds a sustainable sea wall to fight plastic pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANVolvo is working on what it calls Living Seawalls which mimic the structure of mangrove roots, to recreate habitats for marine life that were once supported by mangrove trees.It is building one Living Seawall in Sydney, Australia, where half of the coastline is now comprised of artificial seawalls.Volvo is working with the Sydney Institute of Marine Science and Reef Design Lab to build the Living Seawall, which will be made up of a total of 50 3D-printed tiles. The tiles will be reinforced with recycled plastic fibers.These tiles are designed to mimic the root structure of native mangrove trees in Sydney, and it is hoped they will provide a habitat for marine life that was lost when mangrove forests gave way to artificial coastlines.The artificial seawall will be able to attract filter-feeding organisms which will aid in absorbing and filtering out toxic pollutants, according to Volvo's website.The Living Seawall will be installed on the existing seawall structure in Sydney Harbor.Humans produce around 300 million tonnes of plastic waste every year, according to the UN.Australians produce 3 million tons of plastic every year  of which only 12 percent is recycled, according to WWF Australia.Items such plastic water bottles, grocery bags and straws all end up in the ocean on a daily basis, according to EcoWatch.Volvo says researchers will observe the seawall for the next 20 years as it improves biodiversity and water quality.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. A living seawall tile and a living seawall being enforced with recycled plastic fibers2. A living seawall tile, Mangrove trees and the deep ocean3. Closeup of the living seawall 4. The living seawall being installedVOICEOVER (in English): "Volvo is working with the Sydney Institute of Marine Science and Reef Design Lab to build the Living Seawall, which will be made up of a total of 50 3D-printed tiles.""The tiles will be reinforced with recycled plastic fibers.""These tiles are designed to mimic the root structure of native mangrove trees in Sydney, and it is hoped they will provide a habitat for marine life that was lost when mangrove forests gave way to artificial coastlines." "According to Volvo's website, the artificial seawall will be able to attract filter-feeding organisms which will aid in absorbing and filtering out toxic pollutants.""The Living Seawall will be installed on the existing seawall structure in Sydney Harbor."SOURCES: Inhabitat, The Sydney Morning Herald, UN Environment.org, Volvo Cars, WWF Australia, EcoWatch, https://inhabitat.com/volvo-creates-the-living-seawall-in-sydney-to-help-with-plastic-pollution/https://www.smh.com.au/national/nsw/changing-the-game-on-plastic-20180604-p4zjbh.htmlhttps://www.unenvironment.org/interactive/beat-plastic-pollution/https://www.volvocars.com/au/About/Australia/Living-Seawallhttps://www.wwf.org.au/get-involved/plastics#gs.23LiQibGhttps://www.ecowatch.com/22-facts-about-plastic-pollution-and-10-things-we-can-do-about-it-1881885971.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/29/3773144/3773144_17891013EF6D4E3ABF61ED6CFDA137EC_190129_3773144_Volvo_builds_a_sustainable_sea_wall_to_fight_pla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  australia, volvo, living seawall, plastic pollution, ocean microplastics, seawall structure, artificial sea wall, marine life, biodiversity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3772967</guid>
      <title>Chinese scientists clone gene-edited monkeys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists in China have successfully cloned monkeys with genetic disease symptoms, according to two papers published in National Science Review.Science China Press reports that researchers from the Chinese Academy of Sciences used the CRISPR-Cas9 method on in-vitro fertilized monkey embryos. With no BMAL1 to help manage their circadian rhythm, the resulting monkeys exhibited "a wide range of circadian disorder phenotypes."After taking a fibroblast from the gene-edited monkey, scientists used somatic cell nuclear transfer to replace the nucleus of a monkey egg cell with the fibroblast nucleus.Three hundred and twenty-five embryos were implanted in 65 surrogate monkeys. This resulted in 16 pregnancies but only five live births.All five cloned monkeys carried the altered BMAL1 gene introduced in the donor monkey. They also showed the same circadian disorder symptoms, such as reduced sleep, increased night activity, increased anxiety and depression, and schizophrenia-like behaviors.The Chinese team claims the identical specimens could be useful in studying disease pathogenesis and treatment. Cloning genetically altered animals could also reduce the number needed for research.But the experiment raises many ethical concerns, especially with regard to animal rights. A video showing the five monkeys behaving erratically has been widely described as disturbing.According to Futurism, scientists are also questioning whether insight gleaned from such research would even translate to humans, since many animal studies do not.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Scientists use CRISPR Cas9 to alter BMAL1 gene in monkey embryo2. Gene-edited monkey cloned using somatic cell nuclear transfer3. 325 embryos implanted in 65 surrogate monkeys result in 16 pregnancies, 5 live births4. Monkey clones all have altered BMAL1 gene, exhibit circadian disorder symptomsVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers from the Chinese Academy of Sciences used the CRISPR-Cas9 method on in-vitro fertilized monkey embryos.""With no BMAL1 to help manage their circadian rhythm, the resulting monkeys exhibited 'a wide range of circadian disorder phenotypes.'""After taking a fibroblast from the gene-edited monkey, scientists used somatic cell nuclear transfer to replace the nucleus of a monkey egg cell with the fibroblast nucleus.""Three hundred and twenty-five embryos were implanted in 65 surrogate monkeys. This resulted in 16 pregnancies but only five live births.""All five cloned monkeys carried the altered BMAL1 gene introduced in the donor monkey.""They also showed the same circadian disorder symptoms, such as reduced sleep, increased night activity, increased anxiety and depression, and schizophrenia-like behaviors."SOURCES: National Science Review, Science China Press, Futurismhttps://academic.oup.com/nsr/advance-article/doi/10.1093/nsr/nwz002/5290357https://academic.oup.com/nsr/advance-article/doi/10.1093/nsr/nwz003/5290358https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-01/scp-gdm012119.phphttps://futurism.com/the-byte/cloned-monkeys-gene-edited-chinese***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 06:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/19/01/29/3772967/3772967_33C579E3DEF640A0A0FEFAE5B7BE48D2_190129_3772967_Chinese_scientists_clone_gene_edited_monkeys_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, monkey clones, cloned monkey, gene edited monkeys, gene editing, CRISPR, CRISPR cas9, china gene editing, china cloning, somatic cell nuclear transfer, circadian disorder, genetic disorder, ethics, china, biomedical research]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
