<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3559512</guid>
      <title>Doctors may have found virus behind illness paralyzing children</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDoctors have long been puzzled by polio-like illness that's been causing paralysis in kids, but now that mystery may have finally been solved.According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, acute flaccid myelitis or AFM is a rare condition that causes inflammation in the spinal cord. Symptoms include facial and eyelid drooping, difficulty swallowing, muscle weakness, and paralysis.The U.S. had an outbreak of the disease in 2014, with 120 confirmed cases, and then again in 2016, with 149 people infected.Though tests of their spinal fluid yielded nothing, patients with AFM tested positive for a respiratory virus known as enterovirus D68, reports KUNC.Repeated experiments on infected mice showed that EV-D68 killed nerve cells in the spinal cord, which resulted in partial paralysis.While the findings are significant and could help doctors figure out how to control the disease, many unanswered questions remain.Direct evidence from infected human tissue is needed to officially confirm the link between the disease and the virus. Until such time, health officials are hoping there won't be another resurgence of the crippling illness.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Symptoms of acute flaccid myelitis2. Confirmed cases of acute flaccid myelitis in 2014 and 20163. EV-D68 found in respiratory systems of children with AFM4. EV-D68 injected in mice caused paralysis after killing nerve cells in the spinal cord VOICEOVER (in English): "Acute flaccid myelitis or AFM is a rare condition that causes inflammation in the spinal cord. Symptoms include facial and eyelid drooping, difficulty swallowing, muscle weakness, and paralysis.""The U.S. had an outbreak of the disease in 2014, with 120 confirmed cases, and then again in 2016, with 149 people infected.""Though tests of their spinal fluid yielded nothing, patients with AFM tested positive for a respiratory virus known as enterovirus D68.""Repeated experiments on infected mice showed that EV-D68 killed nerve cells in the spinal cord, which resulted in partial paralysis."SOURCES: KUNC, Centers for Disease Control and Preventionhttp://www.kunc.org/post/colorado-researchers-home-cause-mystery-illnesshttps://www.cdc.gov/acute-flaccid-myelitis/afm-surveillance.htmlhttps://www.cdc.gov/acute-flaccid-myelitis/about-afm.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 17:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/03/3559512/3559512_AC2C57E8B40442A19BFCC259D421135D_180303_3559512_Doctors_may_have_found_virus_behind_illness_para_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/516/DE7/516DE7D7F12A4CEB9E7496704C6BDD6B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, paralysis, acute flaccid myelitis, AFM, polio, polio like illness, spine paralysis, mystery illness, ev-d68, enterovirus d68, enterovirus, kids disease, respiratory disease]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3559219</guid>
      <title>Minnesota toddler allergic to water</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn 18-month-old girl suffers from a condition where she is allergic to water, including her own sweat and tears. Ivy Angerman, from Hastings, Minnesota, was diagnosed with aquagenic urticaria in October, People reported.  It's an extremely rare condition where hives form on the skin when it comes in contact with water. Urticaria can break out for several reasons, including food allergies, a reaction to very hot or very cold temperatures, scratching or rubbing. Currently, the only treatment for aquagenic urticaria is taking antihistamines before being exposed to water. Those who have the condition are also advised to wear moisture-wicking clothing and keep an even keel temperature to prevent sweating. It can also help to take quick shower and to never bath.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Toddler being diagnosed with condition2. Breakouts can be caused by food allergies, temperature changes, scratching and rubbing3. Condition is treated with antihistamines4. Sufferers should wear moisture wicking clothing, keep temp stable and take quick showersVOICEOVER (in English): "Ivy Angerman, from Hastings, Minnesota, was diagnosed with aquagenic urticaria in October, an extremely rare condition where hives form on the skin when it comes in contact with water." "Urticaria can break out for several reasons, including food allergies, a reaction to very hot or very cold temperatures, scratching or rubbing." "Currently, the only treatment for aquagenic urticaria is taking antihistamines before being exposed to water." "Those who have the condition are also advised to wear moisture-wicking clothing and keep an even keel temperature to prevent sweating. It can also help to take quick shower and to never bath."SOURCES: People, Global Newshttp://people.com/human-interest/minnesota-toddler-allergic-water/https://globalnews.ca/news/4053937/toddler-allergic-to-water/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 10:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/02/3559219/3559219_ED3183A219AB496A97F82A23146376B0_180302_3559219_Minnesota_toddler_allergic_to_water_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FF5/3F7/FF53F7213074416183891107E7A2D5DE_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, allergy, allergic to water, water allergy, aquagenic urticaria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3559211</guid>
      <title>Study finds Asian tick infestation in New Jersey sheep</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANU.S. health officials last month reported an infestation of Asian ticks on a New Jersey sheep.Samples from the 12-year-old Icelandic sheep were provided to the Hunterdon County Health Department in August, 2017. The animal's owner, reports NPR, found ticks on her arms during a shearing session.Officials believed them to be deer ticks initially, but further analysis determined they were Asian ticks. They collected over 1,000 from the sheep's paddock and hundreds from the animal itself, according to NPR. The animal and property were treated with chemicals. A follow-up visit by county workers found no remaining ticks.Details of the infestation were published in the Journal of Medical Entomology.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of farmer discovering tick infestation2. Depiction of health officials visiting sheep paddock and finding tick infestation3. Depiction of tick analysis, tick distribution and sheep travel history4. Depiction of ticks being removed from area and sheep with chemicalsVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: NPR, Medical Entomology, Southern Monitoring Serviceshttps://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2018/02/27/588408433/asian-ticks-mysteriously-turned-up-on-a-new-jersey-sheephttps://academic.oup.com/jme/advance-article/doi/10.1093/jme/tjy006/4840594https://www.smsl.co.nz/site/southernmonitoring/files/NZB/Ha%20longicornis%20Profile.pdf***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 10:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/02/3559211/3559211_92FF080729144913A7E53A6E8767066B_180302_3559211_Study_finds_Asian_tick_infestation_in_New_Jersey_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CDA/332/CDA3324C36624FFAA7DA71332D621CCD_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  new jersey, asian tick, what is a tick]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3559629</guid>
      <title>New species of tardigrade found in Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers have found a new species of Tardigrade in a Tsuruoka City, Japan parking lot.After the initial finding in Japan, researchers were unable to identify which type of tardigrade it was. Writing in the journal PLOS One, scientists designated the creature as Macrobiotus shonaicus.  According to Newsweek, 20 new species are found annually.They bare resemblance to some other species of tardigrade, but the new species is noted for its unique eggs. These have lengthy tentacles and a solid exterior.The research was carried out by scientists in Japan and Poland.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Tardigrade moving2. Tardigrade analysis3. Tardigrade eggs4. Tardigrade mouth VOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: PLOS One, Newsweekhttp://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0192210#sec001http://www.newsweek.com/tardigrades-species-825333***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 02:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/03/3559629/3559629_16DE20E18F824CD18DBD91D26FB9E970_180303_3559629_New_species_of_tardigrade_found_in_Japan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1FF/8A5/1FF8A593F0CF461282708F83E312C349_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  tardigrade, macrobiotus shonaicus, tardigrade eggs, japan tardigrade]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3561191</guid>
      <title>Internet-connected devices could be hacked to mine digital currency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANInternet-connected devices could be at risk from hijacking by hackers and used to mine cryptocurrencies, according to cybersecurity firm Avast. Avast ran a demonstration at the Mobile World Congress in Barcelona, Spain which had several devices hijacked to run cryptocurrency mining software, CNBC reported. Based on their calculations, if hackers could attack 15,000 devices, they could be used to mine $1,000 worth of Monero digital cash in four days. A theoretical attack would start with hackers taking over a network of devices and then using that combined computing power to mine digital currency. Unlike Bitcoin, which requires substantial computing power to mine, Monero can be mined using a network of internet-connected devices.Monero has grown in popularity among criminals as it advertises itself as being one of the most anonymous digital coins available. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Internet-connected devices could be hacked for mining digital money2. 15,000 devices could be used to mine for Monero3. Depiction of theoretical hacking attack4. Bitcoin takes more computing power to mine than MoneroVOICEOVER (in English): "Internet-connected devices, like smartphones and TVs, could be at risk from hijacking by hackers and used to mine cryptocurrencies." "According to Avast cybersecurity firm, 15,000 internet-connected devices could be used to mine $1,000 worth of Monero digital cash in four days." "A theoretical attack would start with hackers taking over a network of devices and then using that combined computing power to mine digital currency." "Unlike Bitcoin, which requires substantial computing power to mine, Monero can be mined using a network of internet-connected devices."SOURCES: CNBChttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/03/01/thousands-of-iot-devices-can-be-hacked-to-mine-cryptocurrency-avast.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 12:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/05/3561191/3561191_C3700F9BD2184512A454828C04A923E0_180305_3561191_Internet_connected_devices_could_be_hacked_to_mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6ED/E11/6EDE11DAF12949B681DEB87CEECC43EF_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, digital currency, internet of things, internet connected devices, cryptocurrency mining]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3560907</guid>
      <title>Why space debris cannot be photographed in photos of the Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThere's thousands of debris floating around Earth, but none show up in images of the planet.Writing in 2013, NASA reported there was half-a-million pieces of space debris floating near Earth.These comprise old satellites, rockets and spacecraft parts. Whenever a spacecraft photographs the entire planet, or just a partial shot, the image is typically taken from thousands of kilometers away. Space debris aren't visible at this distance.Closer spacecraft also shoot photos of Earth. The International Space Station (ISS) is around 400 km above the planet but even at this range, space debris appear as miniscule.Much of these objects vary in size, but one of the largest spacecraft near Earth is the ISS. It measures 109 meters at its widest points, while the planet itself is over 12,000 kilometers in diameter. Meaning, even that is just 0.00085% the size of Earth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of space debris near Earth 2. Depiction of satellite taking photo of Earth3. Depiction of ISS over Earth4. Depiction of ISS and EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Writing in 2013, NASA reported there was half-a-million pieces of space debris floating around Earth.""This is a mix of old satellites, rockets, spacecraft and spacecraft parts.""Whenever a spacecraft photographs the entire planet the image is typically taken from thousands of kilometers away.""Space debris aren't visible at this distance.""Closer spacecraft also shoot photos of Earth.""The International Space Station is around 400 km above the planet, but even at this range, space debris are often miniscule.""Much of the debris vary in size, but one of the largest spacecraft near Earth is the ISS.""It measures 109 meters at its widest points, while the planet itself is over 12,000 kilometers in diameter.""Meaning, even that is just 0.0008% the size of Earth."SOURCES: NASA, Popular Mechanics, Popular Science, Quartz https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/station/news/orbital_debris.htmlhttps://www.popularmechanics.com/space/satellites/g2951/7-of-the-biggest-things-put-in-space/https://www.popsci.com/space-junk-why-cant-we-see-satellites-in-images-earthhttps://qz.com/458826/behold-nasas-first-image-in-decades-of-the-whole-earth/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 05:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/05/3560907/3560907_E4CC634B869442E58604941F9B7AAAB8_180305_3560907_Why_space_debris_cannot_be_photographed_in_photo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9B7/474/9B747479BEB74D6B871F57A530D4FAA2_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, NASA, space junk, space garbage, international space station, ISS, photographing Earth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3561980</guid>
      <title>Long term depression can cause brain inflammation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA new study suggests that untreated depression could lead to brain inflammation. Researchers from the Centre for Addiction and Mental Health discovered people with untreated depression for more than a decade had more brain inflammation than those who had untreated depression for a shorter period, Science Alert reported. The study was published on Feb. 26 in The Lancet Psychiatry. The study looked at 80 participants: 25 people with untreated depression for more than 10 years, 25 people with untreated depression for less than 10 years, and 30 people as a control group without depression. Using positron emission tomography or PET brain imaging, the team looked for translocator proteins, an inflammation marker produced by the body's microglia  central nervous system immune cells.  Scientists found people suffering from longer terms of untreated depression had 30 percent higher levels of the translocator protein. Long-term depression sufferers also had higher levels of inflammation compared with the control group. The next step will be to collect more data, but researchers hope this will lead to new approaches in how depression is treated, specifically medications that target inflammation. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People with untreated depression for 10+ years had more brain inflammation2. Researchers used PET imaging to look for inflammation markers3. People with longer terms of untreated depression had more inflammation markers4. People with depression had more inflammation than people withoutVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers found people with untreated depression for more than a decade had more brain inflammation than those who had untreated depression for a shorter period.""Using positron emission tomography or PET brain imaging, scientists looked for translocator proteins, an inflammation marker produced by the body's microglia."  "Scientists found people suffering from longer terms of untreated depression had 30 percent higher levels of the translocator protein." "Long-term depression sufferers also had higher levels of inflammation compared with people without depression." SOURCES: Science Alert, The Lancethttps://www.sciencealert.com/depression-could-cause-long-term-brain-changeshttp://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366%2818%2930048-8/fulltext***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/06/3561980/3561980_2652929D077149209747F3088840CC8F_180306_3561980_Long_term_depression_can_cause_brain_inflammatio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DBD/8B0/DBD8B0C429A04EFA9C8E4540EE62FA07_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Depression, depression treatment, depression brain inflammation, inflammation, inflammation and depression]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3561969</guid>
      <title>Study finds selfies make the nose appear 30% wider</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNew research has found that selfies make people's noses appear larger than they actually are.CNN reports that 55% of plastic surgeons in a 2017 poll reportedly had patients who wanted surgery to look better in selfies, which have been known to distort people's features.Using mathematical modelling, a Rutgers University study found that selfies taken from the standard portrait distance of 5 feet produced no distortion on the subject's nose.But those taken from just 12 inches away made the nose appear 30% wider in men, and 29% in women.This is due to perspective. With a camera close to the subject, the nose looks larger as it's nearer to it than the rest of the face. But further away, the facial features are at a similar distance from the camera, and appear flat and proportionate.The good news is that there are devices that will enable a photo to be taken at the proper distance, and apps to enhance one's features. The bottom line is that there are are easier and cheaper ways to look good in a selfie than getting a nose job.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Patients wanting surgery to help them look better in selfies2. Depiction of a selfie taken from a regular portrait distance of 60 inches 3. Selfie taken 12 inches from the face makes the nose appear wider4. Why the nose looks bigger in a selfieVOICEOVER (in English): "55% of plastic surgeons in a 2017 poll reportedly had patients who wanted surgery to look better in selfies, which have been known to distort people's features.""Using mathematical modelling, a Rutgers University study found that selfies taken from the standard portrait distance of 5 feet produced no distortion on the subject's nose.""But those taken from just 12 inches away made the nose appear 30% wider in men, and 29% in women.""This is due to perspective. With a camera close to the subject, the nose looks larger as it's nearer to it than the rest of the face. But further away, the facial features are at a similar distance from the camera, and appear flat and proportionate."SOURCES: JAMA Facial Plastic Surgery, CNN, National Posthttps://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamafacialplasticsurgery/article-abstract/2673450?redirect=true#qld180002r2https://edition.cnn.com/2018/03/01/health/selfies-make-noses-look-bigger-study/index.htmlhttp://nationalpost.com/news/selfies-make-noses-look-30-per-cent-bigger-but-thats-no-reason-for-plastic-surgery***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 12:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/06/3561969/3561969_CDBC14DEF280473689E839A3BE6DE791_180306_3561969_Study_finds_selfies_make_the_nose_appear_30__wid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BBC/BEB/BBCBEBA124874DC28CB83F4ABB60E660_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, selfie, selfie distortion, selfie nose, nose distortion, bigger nose, plastic surgery, nose surgery, rhinoplasty]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3561861</guid>
      <title>North Korea suspected to have made up to $200 million from Bitcoin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea has found a way to earn money despite intense global pressure over its nuclear capabilities.Reuters reports that the U.S. will be imposing sanctions on 28 ships, 27 companies, and one person believed to be helping North Korea, in a bid to pressure the regime to give up on developing weapons.But according to former National Security Agency official Priscilla Moriuchi, the North is earning millions through cryptocurrency, and may be turning it into cash or goods to fund their nuclear and ballistic missiles program.The North Koreans reportedly obtained 11,000 Bitcoins through mining and hacking in 2017, which is valued between $120 to 210 million.Evidence suggests they have cyber operations setup in several foreign locations, including China, India, and Southeast Asia.The reclusive nation is believed to be behind multiple cyber attacks in recent years, like the Wanna Cry ransomware, the Bank of Bangladesh theft, and a South Korean cryptocurrency heist.With the North Koreans capitalizing on the anonymity of cryptocurrency, experts believe more international regulation is crucial in blocking their shadowy activities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. US sanctions on ships servicing North Korea2. North Korea using cryptocurrency to fund nuclear program3. North Korea obtained 11,000 bitcoins through mining and hacking in 20174. Hacker cells operating out of China, India, and Southeast AsiaVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. will be imposing sanctions on 28 ships, 27 companies, and one person believed to be helping North Korea, in a bid to pressure the regime to give up on developing weapons.""But a new report now says the North is earning millions through cryptocurrency, and  may be turning it into cash or goods to fund their nuclear and ballistic missiles program.""The North Koreans reportedly obtained 11,000 Bitcoins through mining and hacking in 2017, which is valued between $120 to $210 million.""Evidence suggests they have cyber operations setup in several foreign locations, including China, India, and Southeast Asia."SOURCES: Reuters, Telegraph, Korea Times, Voxhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles-trump/u-s-imposes-more-north-korea-sanctions-trump-warns-of-phase-two-idUSKCN1G71RDhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/03/05/north-korea-may-have-made-much-200-million-bitcoin-according/https://www.koreatimes.co.kr/www/nation/2018/03/103_245053.htmlhttps://www.vox.com/world/2018/2/28/17055762/north-korea-sanctions-bitcoin-nuclear-weapons***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 10:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/06/3561861/3561861_BAF4C8D6F03149828E808956D872A165_180306_3561861_North_Korea_suspected_to_have_made_up_to__200_mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E06/135/E06135B537CD4121903820CF35B10509_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, north korea, bitcoin, north korea sanctions, nuclear program, north korea nuclear, cryptomining, hacking, hackers, north korean hackers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3561605</guid>
      <title>China uses predictive policing to detain Xinjiang  ethnic minorities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is using big data to target ethnic minorities in Xinjiang, detaining them on the basis that they may someday threaten the government.Human Rights Watch reports that Beijing has been using surveillance cameras with facial recognition technology, wifi sniffers, and police checkpoints to monitor the country's Uyghur population.Data from these sources, as well as existing health, banking and other records, feeds into the Integrated Joint Operations Platform, a system that uses predictive policing to flag down potential threats.Authorities personally visit flagged individuals and gather more information about their families and ideological situation, but can take into custody anyone deemed suspicious, whether or not they've committed a crime.Most detainees are sent to political education centers, where they are reportedly indoctrinated in Chinese socialist ideology.Reports estimate that roughly 120,000 people are being held indefinitely, without charge or trial, inside the camps.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China monitoring Xinjiang residents using CCTV, wifi sniffers, police checkpoints2. Information transmitted to database, which issues predictive warnings based on data3. Authorities conducting visits to flagged individuals, taking take them into custody 4. Detained individuals taken to political education centersVOICEOVER (in English): "Beijing has been using surveillance cameras with facial recognition technology, wifi sniffers, and police checkpoints to monitor the country's Uighur population.""Data from these sources, as well as existing health, banking and other records, feeds into the Integrated Joint Operations Platform, a system that uses predictive policing to flag down potential threats.""Authorities personally visit flagged individuals to gather more information, but can take into custody anyone deemed suspicious, whether or not they've committed a crime.""Most detainees are sent to political education centers, where they are reportedly indoctrinated in Chinese socialist ideology."SOURCES: Human Rights Watch, Reutershttps://www.hrw.org/news/2018/02/26/china-big-data-fuels-crackdown-minority-regionhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-rights-xinjiang/big-data-predictions-spur-detentions-in-chinas-xinjiang-human-rights-watch-idUSKCN1GB0D9***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 05:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/06/3561605/3561605_B113F68D37724995B3E5909ABF685ABC_180306_3561605_China_uses_predictive_policing_to_detain_Xinjian_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E05/21B/E0521B8B0FFB4666BF177A02C2B738A7_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, predictive policing, china surveillance, china surveillance state, china predictive policing, xinjiang, uighurs, uyghurs, china uighurs, profiling, IJOP, integrated joint operations platform, china police database]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3562778</guid>
      <title>3D-printed prosthetic limbs used to treat war amputees</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDoctors looking to 3D technology to provide prosthetic access to poor and wounded refugees in the Middle East.Mdecins Sans Frontires, or Doctors Without Borders, has been working with a hospital in Amman, Jordan to help upper-limb amputees from war-torn nations.Before designing a prosthetic limb, the team assesses each patient and makes a scan of their stumps.They use flexible thermoplastic polyurethane to 3D-print the socket and hand, and a firmer plastic to create the forearm. The 3D printed prosthetics take only 24 hours to design and produce and costs only a fraction of the normal price at $20.When the parts have been assembled together, the limb can be painted to match the patient's skin tone.Doctors make sure the lightweight prosthetic limb fits comfortably on the stump, ensuring patients will be able to use it long-term, according to their needs. Doctors Without Borders is still improving the process, but wants to expand to other missions in the future.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Doctors without Borders helping war-wounded patients in Jordan2. Prosthesis for upper-arm amputees designed based on patient needs3. Depiction of 3D-printed prosthetic parts 4. Customizable prosthetic parts coming together5. Patient fitted with prosthetic armVOICEOVER (in English): "Doctors Without Borders has been working with a hospital in Amman, Jordan to help upper-limb amputees from war-torn nations.""Before designing a prosthetic limb, the team assesses each patient and makes a scan of their stumps.""They use flexible thermoplastic polyurethane to 3D-print the socket and hand, and a firmer plastic to create the forearm.""When the parts have been assembled together, the limb can be painted to match the patient's skin tone."SOURCES: Doctors Without Borders, New Atlashttp://rsp.msf-me.org/en/index.htmlhttps://www.msf.org.uk/video/innovation-3d-printed-prosthetic-limbs-refugeeshttps://newatlas.com/3d-printed-prostheses-syria/53685/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 13:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/07/3562778/3562778_4D3FF8CC7E094DBFB89A449C8B247F7A_180307_3562778_3D_printed_prosthetic_limbs_used_to_treat_war_am_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EF6/7B0/EF67B0AF295148F3BD76A7D966D03C11_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, prosthesis, prosthetics, prosthetic arm, prosthetic limbs, 3D printed prosthetics, 3D printing, Syria, war, war wounded, Doctors without borders, medecins sans frontieres]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3562572</guid>
      <title>The best way to charge your smartphone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTime reports that modern smartphones use lithium-ion batteries that charge fast but also get used up quickly because of the sheer amount of mobile activity they power.People tend to drain their phone batteries before plugging them in overnight. Fortunately, most are equipped with chips that protect against overcharging.Still, it's unwise to leave a device plugged once its battery is full, since trickle charges can heat up the phone, stressing and wearing down the battery.Experts recommend charging the phone before it empties completely, and not bringing it to a full charge. Plugging it in occasionally throughout the day ensures the battery retains its capacity longer.Batteries also don't do well in extreme heat or extreme cold, so make sure it's not exposed to either.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lithium-ion batteries charge fast, but also drain quickly due to phone activity2. Batteries protected from overcharging when plugged in overnight3. Trickle charges during overnight charging can reduce battery capacity4. How best to charge smartphonesVOICEOVER (in English): "Modern smartphones use lithium-ion batteries that charge fast but also get used up quickly because of the sheer amount of mobile activity they power.""People tend to drain their phone batteries before plugging them in overnight. Fortunately, most are equipped with chips that protect against overcharging.""Still, it's unwise to leave a device plugged once its battery is full, since trickle charges can heat up the phone, stressing and wearing down the battery.""Experts recommend charging the phone before it empties completely, and not bringing it to a full charge. Plugging it in occasionally throughout the day ensures the battery retains its capacity longer."SOURCES: Battery University, http://batteryuniversity.com/learn/article/charging_lithium_ion_batterieshttp://time.com/4949569/mobile-phone-charge-overnight/https://www.pcmag.com/news/357987/charging-your-phone-overnight-battery-myths-debunkedhttp://www.businessinsider.com/the-best-way-to-charge-your-iphone-2016-7?utm_content=buffer0401f&utm_medium=social&utm_source=facebook.com&utm_campaign=buffer-ti***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 09:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/07/3562572/3562572_1763D3B33E55491E9B23225F72D8E553_180307_3562572_The_best_way_to_charge_your_smartphone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/011/E7E/011E7E936BFC44748F480D250F9A8378_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, battery, phone battery, smartphone, charging, overnight charging, lithium ion, lithium ion battery, mobile phone, phone maintenance, battery maintenance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3562563</guid>
      <title>US Navy awards laser weapon systems contract</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Navy has awarded a $150 million contract for two high-power laser weapons systems by 2020.  Lockheed Martin has agreed to provide the navy with a high-energy laser and integrated optical-dazzler with surveillance (HELIOS) system, Naval Technology reported. The HELIOS system combines a laser weapon, long-range intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance (ISR) and counter-unmanned aerial system (counter-UAS) capabilities. It's designed to counter drones and small boats, as well as provide long-range ISR capabilities to decision-makers. The current contract represents the first phase in the navy's surface laser weapon system program, and will see Lockheed Martin supply two laser systems for testing purposes. The first unit will be integrated onto an Arleigh-Burke-class destroyer, while the second unit will be used for land testing at the White Sands Missile Range. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Lockheed Martin will provide navy with 2 HELIOS systems2. HELIOS combines 3 systems in one3. HELIOS can counter drones, small boats and provide long-range ISR4. The navy will integrate one unit on a destroyer and one on landVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. Navy has awarded a $150 million contract to Lockheed Martin for two HELIOS weapons systems by 2020." "The HELIOS system combines a laser weapon, long-range intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance  ISR  and counter-unmanned aerial system capabilities." "It's designed to counter drones and small boats, as well as provide long-range ISR capabilities to decision-makers." "The first unit will be integrated onto an Arleigh-Burke-class destroyer, while the second unit will be used for land testing at the White Sands Missile Range." SOURCES: Naval Technologyhttps://www.naval-technology.com/news/us-navy-awards-150m-contract-delivery-laser-weapon-systems/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 09:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/07/3562563/3562563_CE9AC937BFF5402CB76786696B677CFE_180307_3562563_US_Navy_awards_laser_weapon_systems_contract_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7C0/9E2/7C09E25FD87C4B768B9907A23FF5E625_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, US Navy, Lockheed Martin HELIOS system, high-energy laser, HELIOS system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3563454</guid>
      <title>Japanese banks set to use Ripple-powered payments app</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANJapan's financial industry is embracing innovation by looking to blockchain technology to facilitate its payments platform.CNBC reports that the Japan Bank Consortium, comprised of 61 member banks, is set to release MoneyTap, a Ripple-powered smartphone app that will allow customers to settle transactions in real time.The country's current system for cash transfers is limited. Transactions can only be processed on weekdays, from 8:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m., and comes with high fees.With MoneyTap, customers can make payments and transfers using only a bank account, phone number, or QR code.Transactions go through the cloud-based Ripple Connect platform. Processing is instant and available 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, for a fraction of the normal cost.The app will go live in the later half of 2018, starting with three major banks, followed by a staggered rollout of the rest of the consortium.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Japan Bank Consortium to release app using Ripple blockchain technology2. Japan's current cash transfer system is limited3. MoneyTap app allows customers to make instant payments4. Fund transfers go through RC Cloud platformVOICEOVER (in English): "The Japan Bank Consortium is set to release MoneyTap, a Ripple-powered smartphone app that will allow customers to settle transactions in real time.""The country's current system for cash transfers is limited. Transactions can only be processed on weekdays, from 8:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m., and comes with high fees.""With MoneyTap, customers can make payments and transfers using only a bank account, phone number, or QR code.""Transactions go through the cloud-based Ripple Connect platform. Processing is instant and available 24 hours a day, seven days a week, for a fraction of the normal cost."SOURCES: Ripple, CNBC, Bloomberghttps://ripple.com/insights/ripple-powered-mobile-app-provide-demand-domestic-payments-japan/https://www.cnbc.com/2017/03/01/japanese-banks-plan-to-adopt-blockchain-for-payments.htmlhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-03-07/ripple-develops-blockchain-payments-app-with-61-japanese-banks***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 12:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/08/3563454/3563454_61EABCD65ACE494FAC798ABA82A40B52_180308_3563454_Japanese_banks_set_to_use_Ripple_powered_payment_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A0/97D/1A097D2A98AA434DAE8FBB5941F5FF57_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, blockchain, ripple, Japan bank consortium, blockchain technology, Japan payment, rc cloud, ripple connect, cash transfer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3564417</guid>
      <title>Bones found in 1940 may have belonged to Amelia Earhart</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe disappearance of Amelia Earhart has always been shrouded in mystery, but a new study may have answers as to what really happened.The Washington Post reports that Amelia Earhart vanished over the Pacific Ocean in 1937. Three years later, skeletal remains suspected to be hers were recovered on Nikumaroro Island in present-day Kiribati.A physician in Fiji examined the bones in 1940 and determined that the remains belonged to a European male.The bones have since been lost, but recent analysis of the skeletal measurements using modern techniques reveals the bones were in fact female.Measurements of the arm and leg bones were determined to be a match to Earhart's estimated size and build, making it likely that the remains were hers.The data shows the bones were more similar to the ill-fated pilot than 99% of individuals in a large sample, though without a way to examine the actual bones, it's difficult to determine an actual match with 100% certainty.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Bones found on Nikumaroro Island near where Amelia Earhart's plane disappeared2. Initial bone examination in 1940s determined the bones were a male's3. Modern forensic analysis of bones reveals they are female4. Bone lengths indicate a height and build similar to Amelia Earhart VOICEOVER (in English): "Amelia Earhart vanished over the Pacific Ocean in 1937. Three years later, skeletal remains suspected to be hers was recovered on Nikumaroro Island.""A physician in Fiji examined the bones in 1940 and determined that the remains belonged to a European male.""The bones have since been lost, but recent analysis of the skeletal measurements using modern techniques reveals the bones were in fact female.""Measurements of the arm and leg bones were determined to be a match to Earhart's estimated size and build, making it likely that the remains were hers."SOURCES: University of Tennessee-Knoxville, NPR, Washington Post https://news.utk.edu/2018/03/07/researcher-new-forensic-analysis-indicates-bones-were-amelia-earharts/https://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2018/03/08/591950171/new-research-claims-bones-found-80-years-ago-on-pacific-atoll-likely-amelia-earhhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/retropolis/wp/2018/03/07/bones-discovered-on-a-pacific-island-belong-to-amelia-earhart-a-new-forensic-analysis-shows/?utm_term=.20c98ef9bd39***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/10/3564417/3564417_E43C723BD47D4B26B5D41ACBFE330B58_180310_3564417_Bones_found_in_1940_may_have_belonged_to_Amelia__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4A0/97C/4A097C7A7C4A44A497CD982B62C8397E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, amelia earhart, bones, bone analysis, nikumaroro bones, skeleton, skeletal remains, nikumaroro island, forensic analysis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3564141</guid>
      <title>$8 billion LNG pipeline backed by Taliban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANConstruction on the Afghan section of an $8 billion natural gas pipeline that will connect Turkmenistan through Afghanistan to Pakistan and India began last month with the backing of the Taliban, according to Reuters.   The endorsement of the Taliban is vital as the pipeline will run through many areas under its control, Bloomberg reported. The Taliban "deems it its responsibility to revive foundational economic and reconstruction work in the country and asks international construction companies to help the Afghans in this regard, Taliban spokesman Zabihullah Mujahid said in a statement last month, according to Bloomberg. The TAPI pipeline is expected to carry an annual 33 billion cubic meters of gas along an 1,800 kilometer route. It is expected to create thousands of jobs and generate more than $400 million a year in revenue for the Afghan government. The Afghan section of the pipeline, with around 804 kilometers controlled by the Taliban, is expected to be completed in two years.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The proposed TAPI pipeline2. Pipeline running through Taliban controlled area3. TAPI pipeline expected to carry 33 billion cubic meters annually4. Depiction of pipeline under constructionVOICEOVER (in English): "Construction on the Afghan section of an $8 billion natural gas pipeline that will connect Turkmenistan through Afghanistan to Pakistan and India began last month with the backing of the Taliban.""The endorsement of the group is vital as the pipeline will run through about 804 kilometers of Taliban controlled areas."  "The TAPI pipeline is expected to carry an annual 33 billion cubic meters of gas along an 1,800 kilometer route." "It is expected to create thousands of jobs and generate more than $400 million a year in revenue for the Afghan government." SOURCES: Reuters, Bloomberghttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkmenistan-afghanistan-gas-pipeline/leaders-launch-start-of-afghan-section-of-tapi-gas-pipeline-idUSKCN1G70PUhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-03-08/a-7-5-billion-pipeline-has-surprise-patrons-taliban-militants***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 10:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/09/3564141/3564141_BD77542CEFFC4797B6EB84D10AC25FB9_180309_3564141__8_billion_LNG_pipeline_backed_by_Taliban_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AA6/B1C/AA6B1C28E9994CB381BEDD02ACB7BDB9_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, TAPI pipeline, LNG pipeline, Taliban backing TAPI pipeline, Afghanistan LNG pipeline]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3564054</guid>
      <title>What is carbon capture and storage?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe U.S. Congress' recently passed budget bill includes incentives to support CCS, or carbon capture and storage.The CCS Association reports that fossil fuels supply most of the world's energy needs, but harnessing them emits large quantities of carbon dioxide that can cause irreversible environmental damage.One solution to combat this is carbon capture and storage, which works by first separating carbon dioxide from other gases at industrial facilities.The captured CO2 is transported using underground pipelines or via ships to suitable storage sites.It is then injected into rock formations several kilometers below the surface of the Earth, where pressure and temperature conditions keep it in a liquid state.CCS can capture up to 90% of carbon emissions from fossil fuels, but experts believe it's most effective alongside other strategies, such as improving energy efficiency and switching to renewable energy.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Burning fossil fuels emits massive amounts of carbon dioxide2. Depiction of capturing carbon dioxide3. Depiction of transporting carbon dioxide4. Depiction of storing carbon dioxideVOICEOVER (in English): "Fossil fuels supply most of the world's energy needs, but harnessing them emits large quantities of carbon dioxide that can cause irreversible environmental damage.""One solution to combat this is carbon capture and storage, which works by first separating carbon dioxide from other gases at industrial facilities.""The captured CO2 is transported using underground pipelines or via ships to suitable storage sites.""It is then injected into rock formations several kilometers below the surface of the Earth, where pressure and temperature conditions keep it in a liquid state."SOURCES: Carbon Capture and Storage Association, Global CCs Institutehttp://www.ccsassociation.org/what-is-ccs/https://www.globalccsinstitute.com/understanding-ccs/what***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 09:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/09/3564054/3564054_01C0FD4BE5494294BCAF0ABAB48548EF_180309_3564054_What_is_carbon_capture_and_storage__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8AB/020/8AB020263C314CABA542C00F6153D51B_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, carbon capture and storage, carbon capture, ccs, carbon emissions, climate change, global warming, fossil fuel, renewable energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3564003</guid>
      <title>Goal-line technology to be used at the 2018 FIFA World Cup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANGoal-line technology could be back again at the 2018 FIFA World Cup Russia.  Here's a guide at two different goal-line systems that will help referees to decide a goal has been score or not. The camera system uses several cameras that have been installed high up within the stadium to determine whether the whole ball has crossed the goal line. The magnetic system tracks the receptors in the ball and the magnetic fields created through underground cables to calculate and determine a goal has been scored. The goal-line technology automatically registers the goal and instantly alert the referee to the fact that the football has crossed the goal line. The technology will be able to avoid shocking decisions like the disallowed goal between England and Germany in the 2006 World Cup in Germany. The following goal-line tech systems have been approved by Fifa and the International Football Association Board (IFAB) for use: GoalRef, Hawk-Eye, and GoalControl-4D. The technology passed its inaugural trial during the 2012 FIFA Club World Cup Japan. It has since been used at several major tournaments, and most recently the English premier league and the German Bundesliga. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Explaining the camera based goal-line technology.2. Explaining the magnetic field based goal-line technology.3. The technology will alert the referee as soon as a football has crossed the goal line.4. The system can avoid controversial goal decisions.VOICEOVER (in English): "The camera system uses several cameras that have been installed high up within the stadium to determine whether the whole ball has crossed the goal line.""The magnetic system tracks the receptors in the ball and the magnetic fields created through underground cables to calculate and determine a goal has been scored.""The goal-line technology automatically registers the goal and instantly alert the referee to the fact that the football has crossed the goal line.""The technology will be able to avoid shocking decisions like the disallowed goal between England and Germany in the 2010 World Cup in Germany."SOURCES: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Goal-line_technologyhttps://football-technology.fifa.com/en/standards/goal-line-technology/https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2014/jun/16/world-cup-goalline-technology-football-brazil-2014***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 08:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/09/3564003/3564003_E51EB097C3434CF4BAC897A0B03E68B3_180309_3564003_Goal_line_technology_to_be_used_at_the_2018_FIFA_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7D3/C2C/7D3C2C7142684564ADC796E2BF6E5298_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, goal line technology, world cup goal line tech, goal-line tech soccer, goal-line tech football, russia world cup, world cup 2018, world cup technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566306</guid>
      <title>China tests 1,000 kilometer per hour super-maglev train</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChinese researchers have developed the world's first testing platform for a new maglev train that can run at ultra-high speeds.China Central Television reports that China's super-maglev train uses magnetic levitation technology and vacuum tube transport to run at speeds of 1,000 kilometers per hour, faster than narrow-body Boeing 737 or Airbus A320 jets.To test their prototype, Southwest Jiaotong University scientists led by Professor Deng Xigang constructed a test car and a 45-meter loop with a load capacity of up to one ton.The superconducting maglev system inside the loop allows the test car to be constantly levitated 20 millimeters above the track, according to a study published in the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Transactions on Power Delivery journal.Deng and his team are currently conducting trials and aims to complete 400 kilometer per hour runs within the year.They will still need to conduct 1,000 kph trial runs, tackle safety standards, and deal with high construction and maintenance costs before any super-maglev trains can enter commercial service.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China prototype train running on maglev tech and vacuum tube transport2. Maglev test loop with 1-ton load capacity3. Test car constantly levitated at 20 millimeters off the track4. 400 kph tests to be completed this yearVOICEOVER (in English): "China's super-maglev train combines maglev technology and vacuum tube transport to run at speeds of 1,000 kilometers per hour, faster than narrow-body Boeing or Airbus jets.""To test their prototype, scientists at Southwest Jiaotong University in Chengdu constructed a test car and a 45-meter loop with a load capacity of up to one ton.""The superconducting maglev system inside the loop allows the test car to be levitated 20 millimeters above the track.""The team is currently conducting trials and aims to complete 400 kilometer per hour runs within the year."SOURCES: Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, China Central Televisionhttp://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/7456207/?part=1http://big5.cctv.com/gate/big5/news.cctv.com/2018/03/04/ARTI6ls85I8e1VSun3M4TAni180304.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 17:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/13/3566306/3566306_E3DAE6ED44264274B32198AA011E618B_180313_3566306_China_tests_1_000_kilometer_per_hour_super_magle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9E8/544/9E854414B70742B0B7A044FACF2BA3A1_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, super-maglev, maglev, maglev test loop, maglev train, maglev technology, vacuum tube transport, China, Southwest Jiaotong University]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566099</guid>
      <title>Virginia dentists keep dying of rare lung disease, CDC doesn't know why</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOfficials at the U.S. Centers for Disease Control are trying to figure out why dentists in Virginia have been dying of a rare form of lung disease. The CDC has identified nine dentists or dental workers who were diagnosed with idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis, or IPF, all of whom were treated at the same specialty clinic in Virginia, the agency said in its Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report.Of the nine cases, seven have died, the report said. Around 200,000 people in the U.S. have IPF at any one time, according to the American Thoracic Society. Citing a review in the journal Industrial Health, the CDC said that dental professionals were 23 times more likely to have IPF than the rest of the population. IPF causes scarring of the lungs and can be treated, but not cured. Over time, sufferers have difficulty getting oxygen to the body's organs. Doctors still don't know what causes IPF. Patients usually live three to five years after being diagnosed. Signs of IPF include shortness of breath, a chronic and dry cough, weight loss, fatigue, joint and muscle pains and clubbed fingers or toes. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Nine dental workers have been diagnosed with IPF2. Around 200,000 people in the U.S. have IPF at any one time, dentists were 23 times more likely to have IPF than rest of population3. IPF causes scarring in the lungs4. IPF symptomsVOICEOVER (in English): "Officials at the CDC have identified nine dentists or dental workers who were diagnosed with idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis, or IPF, all of whom were treated at the same specialty clinic in Virginia. Of the nine cases, seven have died.""Around 200,000 people in the U.S. have IPF at any one time. Dental professionals are 23 times more likely to have IPF than the rest of the population, according to research cited by the CDC." "IPF causes scarring of the lungs and can be treated, but not cured. Over time, sufferers have difficulty getting oxygen to the body's vital organs like the heart and brain." "Signs of IPF include shortness of breath, a chronic and dry cough, weight loss, fatigue, joint and muscle pains and clubbed fingers or toes." SOURCES: Centers for Disease Control, American Thoracic Society, Industrial Healthhttps://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/67/wr/mm6709a2.htm?s_cid=mm6709a2_whttps://www.thoracic.org/patients/lung-disease-week/2015/pulmonary-fibrosis-week/general-info.phphttps://www.jstage.jst.go.jp/article/indhealth/45/5/45_5_611/_articlehttp://www.newsweek.com/dentists-mysteriously-dying-lung-disease-idiopathic-pulmonary-fibrosis-cdc-838559***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 11:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/12/3566099/3566099_6B260F3C8B3C4BC2B0A5A7B7D011170B_180312_3566099_Virginia_dentists_keep_dying_of_rare_lung_diseas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4E7/298/4E7298092B80467984F99B9931565A66_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dentists lung disease, dentists IPF, idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis, dentists diagnosed IPF]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566090</guid>
      <title>Ice crystals in diamond show water may lay deep below Earth's surface</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists analyzing diamonds have found that small pockets of water may exist deep in the Earth's mantle.  Geologists unearthed impure diamonds from mines in southern Africa, Zaire, Sierra Leone and China, according to a report published in the journal Science. The diamonds were then sent to the Argonne National Lab in Illinois for analysis in the Advanced Photon Source synchrotron particle accelerator. Mineralogist Oliver Tschauner from the University of Nevada in Las Vegas and his colleagues found more than a dozen diamonds with a distinct form of crystallized water known as ice VII. Ice VII has been studied in labs, but these samples are the first known natural samples. Because of the team's discovery, ice VII has been classified as a new mineral. The ice crystals suggest pockets of watery fluid may be present deep in the Earth's mantle, despite the high temperatures. The scientists estimated the diamonds were formed at depths between 610 and 800 kilometers below the Earth's surface. Researchers were unable to determine the exact location of the pockets or how common they could be. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Impure diamonds were collected from southern Africa, Zaire, Sierra Leone and China2. Ice VII crystals were found in the diamonds3. Pockets of water may exist deep in Earth's mantle4. The diamonds were formed at depths between 610 and 800 kms below Earth's surfaceVOICEOVER (in English): "Geologists unearthed impure diamonds from mines in southern Africa, Zaire, Sierra Leone and China and discovered they contained ice crystals, which means pockets of water may exist deep in the Earth's mantle.""Researchers found more than a dozen diamonds with a distinct form of crystallized water known as ice VII." "The ice crystals suggest pockets of watery fluid may be present deep in the Earth's mantle, despite the high temperatures." "The scientists estimated the diamonds were formed at depths between 610 and 800 kilometers below the Earth's surface." SOURCES: Science, Nature, Gizmodohttp://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/03/pockets-water-may-lay-deep-below-earth-s-surfacehttps://www.nature.com/articles/nature25972https://gizmodo.com/ice-crystals-in-diamonds-reveal-pockets-of-water-deep-i-1823610904***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 11:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/12/3566090/3566090_19FE2FE010024CE886D3E4601DC30540_180312_3566090_Ice_crystals_in_diamond_show_water_may_lay_deep__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0B6/857/0B6857F3E5444554B73EFA8B5C591EA5_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[water below earth, water below the earth's surface, mantle, water in the mantle, water inside earth, Earth's mantle, water pockets in Earth's mantle, water in mantle, Ice 7, Ice VII, ice crystals in diamonds, science, News]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566876</guid>
      <title>China's Tiangong-1 space station set to re enter Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn out-of-control space station is set to fall to Earth within a few weeks, but experts say the likelihood of it hitting anyone in the process is very slim.The Guardian reports that China's Tiangong-1 space station has been orbiting uncontrolled since 2016, and has sped up its descent towards Earth in recent months.According to the European Space Agency, reentry is estimated to occur between March 29 and April 9, with the impact point anywhere between 43 degrees north and 43 degrees south latitudes.The 9.4-ton space station is expected to burn up as it enters the atmosphere, and may be visible from Earth as a bright streak in the sky.Experts say a small amount of debris may survive reentry and fall to Earth, but the probability of it hitting anyone and causing harm is extremely low.To date, only one person has ever been struck by falling space debris, but wasn't injured, according to a report from the Aerospace Corporation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Tiangong-1 space station's uncontrolled descent toward Earth2. Estimated date and location of reentry3. Tiangong-1 burning up during reentry4. Depiction of pieces of debris falling to EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "China's Tiangong-1 space station has been orbiting uncontrolled since 2016, and has sped up its descent towards Earth in recent months.""Reentry is estimated to occur between March 29 and April 9, with the impact point anywhere between 43 degrees north and 43 degrees south latitudes.""The 9.4-ton space station is expected to burn up as it enters the atmosphere, and may be visible from Earth as a bright streak in the sky.""Experts say a small amount of debris may survive reentry and fall to Earth, but the probability of it hitting anyone and causing harm is extremely low."SOURCES: European Space Agency, Aerospacehttp://blogs.esa.int/rocketscience/2018/01/16/tiangong-1-frequently-asked-questions-2/http://www.aerospace.org/cords/reentry-predictions/tiangong-1-reentry/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 11:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/13/3566876/3566876_E77796D7DBCD4061A9E709F325DA2A1F_180313_3566876_China_s_Tiangong_1_space_station_set_to_re_enter_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/22D/485/22D485514E7343A3A37DD9AB028B4206_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, tiangong space station, tiangong crash, space station falling, china space station falling, china space station crash, tiangong, tiangong 1, china space station, space station crash, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566837</guid>
      <title>Pen diagnoses cancer 'in seconds'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists at the University of Texas have developed a handheld device that can detect cancer in 10 seconds.The pen is aimed for use by medical professionals during surgery. After a tissue sample is taken, the surgeon uses a pen connected to a mass spectrometer and foot pump to begin analysis. The pump sends water through the pen the via tubing and forms a droplet.This absorbs molecules from the tissue, and is then sent back up the tubing for analysis. The machine then investigates the molecules for signs of cancer and provides diagnosis in seconds.The device was showcased this week at the South by Southwest festival in Austin, Texas.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Pen being used by surgeon during surgery2. How the pen analyses cancer3. Pen moving around different areas of the tissueVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: MasSpec Pen, University of Texas, Texas Medical Center, Science Mag, Fox Newshttps://www.masspecpen.comhttps://eberlin.cm.utexas.edu/masspec-pen/http://www.tmc.edu/news/2018/03/solutions-pen-detects-cancer-real-time/http://stm.sciencemag.org/content/9/406/eaan3968http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/03/12/sxsw-scientists-tout-pen-technology-that-detects-cancer-in-20-seconds.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 10:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/13/3566837/3566837_A4515197611946BA974E25D658BB7709_180313_3566837_Pen_diagnoses_cancer__in_seconds__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A9F/089/A9F089AB01A244B390A0B78ED386F1D9_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, sxsw 2018, quick cancer diagnosis, masspec pen, mass spectrometry, cancer research, cancer treatment, cancer story, cancer story animation, university of texas, university of texas austin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566794</guid>
      <title>Former spy poisoned by Russian nerve agent, says Theresa May</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANBritish Prime Minister Theresa May said on Monday it was "highly likely" Russian ex-double spy Sergei Skripal and his daughter were poisoned using a military-grade nerve agent, according to Reuters.  Skripal and his daughter, Yulia, were discovered slumped over on a park bench in Salisbury on March 4. They are in critical, but stable condition in the hospital, according to BBC. In front of parliament on Monday, May identified the chemical used in the attack as a group of nerve agents known as Novichok. The name means "newcomer" in Russian and refers to a group of advanced chemical agents secretly developed by the Soviet Union in the 1970s and 1980s, according to BBC. One of the chemicals  A-230  can kill a person within minutes and is reportedly five to eight times deadlier than VX nerve gas.Some come in liquid form, while other exist in a solid state. Some are also binary weapons, meaning they are stored separately, but when mixed produce the lethal nerve agent. Novichok agents were designed to evade detection by international insectors.   The Foreign Office has called on Russia's ambassador to provide an explanation by Tuesday. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Spy and daughter were poisoned with Novichok nerve agent2. Scientists working in a laboratory3. A-230 nerve agent can kill someone in minutes4. Novichok nerve agents come in liquid, solid and binary formsVOICEOVER (in English): "British Prime Minister Theresa May said on Monday it was "highly likely" Russian ex-double spy Sergei Skripal and his daughter were poisoned using military-grade nerve agents called Novichok.""The name means "newcomer" in Russian and refers to a group of advanced chemical agents secretly developed by the Soviet Union in the 1970s and 1980s.""One of the chemicals  A-230  can kill a person within minutes and is reportedly five to eight times deadlier than VX nerve gas.""Some come in liquid form, while other exist in a solid state. Some are also binary weapons, meaning they are stored separately, but when mixed produce the lethal nerve agent." SOURCES: Reuters, BBC, NPRhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-russia/uks-may-says-highly-likely-russia-behind-nerve-attack-on-spy-idUSKCN1GO0MShttp://www.bbc.com/news/uk-43377856https://www.npr.org/sections/parallels/2018/03/12/592964624/nerve-agent-found-in-u-k-is-rare-and-definitely-russian***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 10:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/13/3566794/3566794_2D7E0BA30C714FE1BDE01E00EE44BC42_180313_3566794_Former_spy_poisoned_by_Russian_nerve_agent__says_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1DB/444/1DB44459C31A4A20B926DBF25C17B463_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nerve agent, Novichok, Novichok nerve agents, Sergei Skripal, Russian nerve agents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566775</guid>
      <title>MIT says nuclear fusion is only 15 years away</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANResearchers from MIT say nuclear fusion is only 15 years away from becoming a reality.  A team at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology working with newly formed company Commonwealth Fusion Systems says it will build a working fusion power plant in 15 years, thanks to a new superconducting material that recently became commercially available. The MIT Energy Initiative announced the project in a statement published March 9 on its website. The collaboration between MIT and Commonwealth Fusion Systems plans to use the new superconducting steel tape coated with a yttrium-barium-copper oxide to make smaller, more powerful magnets that can be used in fusion reactors. The new magnets will double the magnetic field of a fusion reactor, which means more power can be produced with a smaller device. The smaller size will reduce costs and complexity, making future fusion power plants easier to build. The researchers say they will be able to create the first fusion reactor that produces more energy than is required to get the fusion reaction going, the university said in a statement published on MIT News.The planned fusion experiment, called SPARC, is set to be 1/65th the volume of the International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor project currently being built in France, according to Guardian. "This is an important historical moment: Advances in superconducting magnets have put fusion energy potentially within reach, offering the prospect of a safe, carbon-free energy future," MIT President L. Rafael Reif said in the statement to MIT News. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. MIT fusion reactor2. Plan to use new superconductor to make smaller, more power magnets to be used in fusion reactors 3. MIT fusion reactor cross section4. Depiction of fusion reactionVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology working with a newly formed private company say they will build a working fusion power plant in 15 years, thanks to a new superconducting material that recently became commercially available.""The material is a new superconducting steel tape coated with a yttrium-barium-copper oxide. The team, working with MIT spin-off Commonwealth Fusion Systems, plans to use the tape to make smaller, more powerful magnets that can be used in fusion reactors." "The new magnets will double the magnetic field of a fusion reactor, which means more power can be produced with a smaller device.""The smaller size will reduce costs and complexity, making future fusion power plants easier to construct."SOURCES: Fast Company, Guardian, Inhabitathttps://www.fastcompany.com/40541615/this-mit-project-says-nuclear-fusion-is-15-years-away-no-really-this-time?utm_source=feedly&utm_medium=webfeedshttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/mar/09/nuclear-fusion-on-brink-of-being-realised-say-mit-scientistshttps://inhabitat.com/mit-claims-that-clean-limitless-nuclear-fusion-energy-is-just-15-years-away/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 09:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/13/3566775/3566775_00AB814346FA47F281EAD441B0E3E172_180313_3566775_MIT_says_nuclear_fusion_is_only_15_years_away_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/178/637/17863738569B4CAFB11E1F7E90BC0591_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Nuclear fusion, MIT nuclear fusion, superconductor, superconducting tape, MIT fusion device]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3566710</guid>
      <title>Russia test launches new hypersonic missile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Russians have test-launched a new hypersonic missile that's been described by President Vladimir Putin as an ideal weapon.The Russian News Agency reports that the Kinzhal missile was launched from a MiG-31 interceptor jet that took off from an airfield in the Southern Military District.Video footage released by the country's Defense Ministry shows the missile detaching from the jet in mid air.The Kinzhal hypersonic missile travels at 10 times the speed of sound, with a range of over 2,000 kilometers.The launch was reportedly successful, with the missile hitting the preset target.The Kinzhal is part of a new line of weapons unveiled during Putin's recent state of the nation address, that can reportedly outmaneuver U.S. defenses.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Russian Kinzhal missile and MiG-31 aircraft2. Aircraft deploying Kinzhal missile3. Missile 10 times faster than the speed of sound, with 2,000 km range4. Depiction of Kinzhal missile hitting targetVOICEOVER (in English): "Russia's Kinzhal missile was launched from a MiG-31 interceptor jet that took off from an airfield in the Southern Military District.""Video footage released by the country's Defense Ministry shows the missile detaching from the jet in mid air.""The Kinzhal hypersonic missile travels at 10 times the speed of sound, with a range of over 2,000 kilometers.""The launch was reportedly successful, with the missile hitting the preset target."SOURCES: Russian News Agency, BBC, The Guardianhttp://tass.com/defense/993439http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-43362213https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/11/russia-hypersonic-kinzhal-missile-launch***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 08:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/13/3566710/3566710_54D52CE5DF4E48A48EA4396934C93217_180313_3566710_Russia_test_launches_new_hypersonic_missile_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B5C/C0D/B5CC0D77A8584A5699FFE9A74B4CCA50_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, russia missile, missile, kinzhal, kinzhal missile, hypersonic missile, missile launch, missile test launch, russia, russian weapons, putin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3567702</guid>
      <title>US may get rare glimpse of Northern Lights due to solar storm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANSome parts of the U.S. may get a rare glimpse of the northern lights, as a solar storm fires up the planet's auroras this week.According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, a minor geomagnetic storm will hit Earth from March 14 to 15.Solar winds from the Sun's coronal hole are set to stream out into space and cause a slight disturbance to our planet's geomagnetic field. Charged solar particles interacting with the earth's atmosphere results in an amplified display of the Aurora Borealis, or Northern Lights.The storm allows the lights to be visible in lower latitude areas, like Michigan and Maine in the northeastern U.S. It's also expected to have a minor impact on power grids and satellite operations.Space reports that over the weekend, several news outlets inaccurately warned of a massive solar disturbance that can cause power outages, prompting some to panic.In response, the NOAA's Space Prediction Center claims the storm, known as "G1" is the lowest severity on a scale of five, and shouldn't be cause for concern.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Minor solar storm to hit Earth on March 14 and 152. Charged particles from Sun's coronal hole interacting with Earth's geomagnetic field3. Depiction of amplified northern lights 4. Aurora visible from northern US; minimal effects on power grid and satellite communicationsVOICEOVER (in English): "The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration has forecast that a minor geomagnetic storm will hit Earth from March 14 to 15.""Solar winds from the Sun's coronal hole are set to stream out into space and cause a slight disturbance to our planet's geomagnetic field.""Charged solar particles interacting with the earth's atmosphere results in an amplified display of the Aurora Borealis, or Northern Lights.""The storm allows the lights to be visible in lower latitude areas, like Michigan and Maine in the northeastern U.S. It's also expected to have a minor impact on power grids and satellite operations."SOURCES: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, Space, The Weather Networkhttps://www.swpc.noaa.gov/news/g1-watch-14-and-15-march-2018-utc-dayshttps://www.space.com/39965-solar-storm-amps-up-northern-lights-march-2018.htmlhttps://www.theweathernetwork.com/news/articles/auroras-across-canada-northern-lights-possible-weekend-coronal-hole-solar-wind-equinox-cracks/97302***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 11:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/14/3567702/3567702_523E43C36CE84D8EAA926E48C1442868_180314_3567702_US_may_get_rare_glimpse_of_Northern_Lights_due_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EF5/FBD/EF5FBD8BD7DF4E04B3BD0F56CFEDCD9C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, northern lights, solar storm, geomagnetic storm, aurora borealis, coronal hole, G1 storm, power grid, satellite communications]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3567500</guid>
      <title>Flying taxi trials get go ahead in New Zealand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn autonomous "air taxi" designed by Larry Page-backed Kitty Hawk has been approved for trials in Christchurch, New Zealand. Cora, an autonomous flying vehicle by Silicon Valley firm Kitty Hawk, has been approved for trials in Christchurch, New Zealand, reported the New Zealand Herald. The all-electric aircraft takes off vertically, similar to a helicopter and can carry two people. According to CNN, Cora can fly at speeds of over 150 km per hour and operates autonomously. The aircraft also has a travel range of over 100 km.According to Stuff.co.nz, it's hoped that Cora will operate commercially in New Zealand within three to six years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Cora and New Zealand 2. Depiction of Cora taking off3. Depiction of Cora in flight4. Depiction of Cora landingVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Cora, Stuff, New Zealand Herald, CNNhttps://cora.aerohttps://www.stuff.co.nz/technology/102203642/air-taxi-trials-possible-in-six-years-as-tech-company-trials-flying-vehicle-in-canterburyhttp://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&objectid=12012006http://money.cnn.com/2018/03/13/technology/flying-taxi-cora-kitty-hawk-google/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 08:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/14/3567500/3567500_46C1FB8EFFBA41C6B94F8466B63D2187_180314_3567500_Flying_taxi_trials_get_go_ahead_in_New_Zealand_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0B3/C9D/0B3C9D0C0C0949EA956CB0EF65F0C544_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, the flying car, cora, google, flying car new zealand, flying taxi service, air taxi service]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3568586</guid>
      <title>Fan ID: How tickets at the 2018 World Cup will work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFans attending the 2018 World Cup in Russia will need a "Fan ID" in addition to standard match tickets.According to information from the Fan ID and FIFA websites, the document can only be got after buying official tickets from FIFA, then by applying for the document at a seperate website or at a distribution center in Russia. Successful applicants, are notified by email or text and the ID is sent by mail, or collected from a center.The document allows visa-free entry to Russia for 10 days prior to the document holder's first match and 10 days after their last match. Fan ID and ticket holders will also be able to travel between cities for free using trains and other public transport.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of fan presenting Fan ID and ticket at world cup match2. Depiction of how fan ID is got3. Depiction of visa-free travel and duration of stay4. Depiction of transportation between Russian citiesVOICEOVER (in English): "To enter stadiums during the 2018 World Cup in Russia, fans will need to present a 'Fan ID' in addition to their normal ticket.""Reportedly, these are designed to nullify touting and for security purposes.""Fan IDs can only be acquired after buying official tickets from FIFA, then by applying for the ID at a seperate website or at a distribution center in Russia.""Successful applicants are notified by email or text, and the ID is sent by mail, or collected from a center."  "The document allows visa-free entry to Russia for 10 days prior to the document's first match and 10 days after their last match.""Fan ID and ticket holders will also be able to travel between cities for free using trains and other public transport."SOURCES: FIFA, Fan-ID, ESPNhttp://www.fifa.com/worldcup/organisation/fan-id/index.htmlhttps://www.fan-id.ruhttp://global.espn.com/football/world-cup-soccer/4/blog/post/3408421/world-cup-100-days-out-russia-face-challenges-like-racism-fan-safety-and-price-gouging***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 10:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/15/3568586/3568586_12AF3037A03D41D1A7B49EAF9A886166_180315_3568586_Fan_ID__How_tickets_at_the_2018_World_Cup_will_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/336/AC6/336AC6BABEDE4FF7A90AE9B5476F22DE_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, fan id russia 2018, fan id, world cup fan id, world cup tickets, russia 2018, vladimir putin, fifa fan id, russia fan id, russia, how does fan id work]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3568429</guid>
      <title>Austin startup can 3D print cheap houses in less than 24 hours</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA construction tech company is using 3D-printing to provide houses for the 1.2 billion people in the world without adequate housing.Wired reports that Texas startup Icon unveiled a proof-of-concept model house at the annual SXSW innovation festival in Austin. The 650-square-foot structure featured a living room, bedroom, bathroom, and curved porch.Using traditional building methods, a community of a hundred houses will take roughly eight months to complete. But with an industrial-sized Vulcan 3D printer, Icon claims it a single-storey home can be constructed using cement in only 12 to 24 hours.Each 600 to 800 square foot home costs $10,000 to build, but the company is working to drop it to just $4,000.Icon is working with housing charity New Story to bring the printer to El Salvador, where it plans to build a community of 3D printed houses within the year.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Traditional way of building houses2. Houses 3D printed in less than a day3. Size and cost of each 3D printed house4. First model house unveiled in Austin VOICEOVER (in English): "Using traditional building methods, a community of a hundred houses will take roughly eight months to complete.""But with an industrial-sized Vulcan 3D printer, Texas startup Icon claims it can construct a single-storey home using cement in only 12 to 24 hours.""Each 600 to 800 square foot home costs $10,000 to build, but the company is working to drop it to just $4,000.""A proof-of-concept model house unveiled in Austin features a living room, bedroom, and bathroom, along with a curved porch."SOURCES: Icon, Wired, World Resources Institutehttps://www.iconbuild.com/https://www.wired.com/story/new-story-3-d-printed-house/http://www.wri.org/wri-citiesforall/news/2017/07/release-12-billion-people-living-cities-lack-access-affordable-and-secure-housing***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 07:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/15/3568429/3568429_54F705F882D64553863426B78F3E6882_180315_3568429_Austin_startup_can_3D_print_cheap_houses_in_less_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C54/A4C/C54A4CA053F34FA8BDABFA756A5A18D9_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, house, 3d printed house, 3d printer, 3d printing, cheap houses, affordable houses, homeless, homelessness, global housing, vulcan printer, icon, new story, el salvador]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3568244</guid>
      <title>Doctors find air pocket in man's brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDoctors treating an elderly man who was having trouble with balance were surprised to find a 3.5-inch air pocket in the patient's brain. The 84-year-old man had been complaining to his primary care doctor in Northern Ireland about recurrent falls and three days of left arm and leg weakness, according to a report in the journal BMJ Case Reports.Physicians were worried the patient may have been suffering from some form of stroke, but he was not displaying any visual or speech impairments and did not seem confused or have facial weakness, according to the report.  A brain scan revealed a 3.5-inch long pocket of air, also known as a pneumatocele, in the man's right frontal lobe, behind the frontal sinus and above the cribriform plate. An MRI on the man's brain also revealed a small benign bone tumor in the man's paranasal sinuses, that was eroding through the base of the skull, causing air to leak into the cranial cavity, according to the report. Doctors concluded that the air pressure from the air cavity may have caused a small stroke in the patient's frontal lobe. Due to his old age, surgery was ruled out. He was instead given medication to prevent a secondary stroke. After a 12-week follow up visit, the man said he no longer had any left-side muscle weakness, the journal reported.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Patient complaining about falling and left-side complications 2. Brain scan revealing air pocket3. MRI scan revealing benign tumor in paranasal sinuses4. Pressure from air pocket may have caused small strokeVOICEOVER (in English): "An 84-year-old man had been complaining to his doctor in Northern Ireland about recurrent falls and three days of left arm and leg weakness.""A brain scan revealed a 3.5-inch long pocket of air, also known as a pneumatocele, in the man's right frontal lobe.""An MRI on the man's brain also revealed a small benign bone tumor in the man's paranasal sinuses, that was eroding through the base of the skull, causing air to leak into the cranial cavity.""Doctors concluded that the air pressure from the air cavity may have caused a small stroke in the patient's frontal lobe. Due to his old age, surgery was ruled out. He was instead given medication to prevent a secondary stroke."SOURCES: CNN, BMJ Case Reportshttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/03/13/health/brain-air-pocket-patient/index.htmlhttp://casereports.bmj.com/content/2018/bcr-2017-222892.full?sid=dc43cb***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 03:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/15/3568244/3568244_6F2DEEEBA13B4B0E9200E3683ADE6736_180315_3568244_Doctors_find_air_pocket_in_man_s_brain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E7F/5B6/E7F5B677B4FB49638C47A8A7B510321F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, air pocket in brain, brain air pocket, pneumocephalus, stroke, partial stroke]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3569429</guid>
      <title>Ford recalls 1.38 million cars for loose steering wheels</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFord Motor Co. announced on Wednesday it is recalling 1.38 million vehicles in North America for possible loose steering wheel bolts.The defect has connected to at least two accidents and one potential injury, according to Ford.  The automaker said the recall includes 2014 through 2018 Ford Fusion cars and Lincoln MKZ vehicles built at plants in Michigan and Mexico, according to Reuters. Car dealers will replace the steering wheel bolt with a longer bolt. The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration began a preliminary investigation in October into 841,000 Ford cars over detachable steering wheels while vehicles were in motion. The latest recall affects 1.3 million cars in the U.S., around 62,000 in Canada and about 14,000 in Mexico, according to USA Today. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ford Fusion with steering bolt2. Ford Fusion and Lincoln MKZ vehicles are being recalled, fitted with longer bolts3. Depiction of steering wheel coming loose during driving4. Number of vehicles to be recalled in US, Canada and MexicoVOICEOVER (in English): "Ford Motor Co. announced on Wednesday it is recalling 1.38 million vehicles in North America for possible loose steering wheel bolts.""The automaker is recalling 2014 through 2018 Ford Fusion and Lincoln MKZ cars built at plants in Michigan and Mexico. Dealers will replace the steering wheel bolt with a longer bolt.""The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration began a preliminary investigation in October into 841,000 Ford cars over detachable steering wheels while vehicles were in motion." "The latest recall affects 1.3 million cars in the U.S., around 62,000 in Canada and about 14,000 in Mexico."SOURCES: Reuters, USA Todayhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-ford-recall/ford-recalls-1-38-million-vehicles-for-loose-steering-wheel-bolts-idUSKCN1GQ1QWhttps://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2018/03/14/ford-recall-fusion-lincoln-mkz-steering-wheel/423395002/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 09:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/16/3569429/3569429_3B9B16F49EDF45E48437CF757D62E4A7_180316_3569429_Ford_recalls_1_38_million_cars_for_loose_steerin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5CF/350/5CF35079EE3043899CEC00BD3EF626DE_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Ford recall, Ford steering wheel recall, Ford loose steering wheels, Ford loose steering wheel bolts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3569326</guid>
      <title>NASA planning deep-space station near the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA says it plans to build a station for astronauts orbiting the moon. The project is called the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway.   The space agency's fiscal year 2019 budget request calls for launching the first element of the Gateway, the power and propulsion module, into space in 2022, according to Space.com. The station would be complete after two additional launches by 2025 to add habitation, logistics and airlock functions. The Gateway could be put in a Near Rectilinear Halo Orbit, an orbit in cislunar space that could be used as a staging area for future missions. The platform's position would let astronauts control telerobots on the moon's surface that could be used to explore craters as well as carry out other experiments. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Gateway station in space2. The Gateway station is set to be completed in 20253. Gateway station in Near Rectilinear Halo Orbit4. Depiction of astronaut controlling telerobot from Gateway stationVOICEOVER (in English): "NASA says it plans to build a station for astronauts orbiting the moon. The project is called the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway."   "NASA's 2019 fiscal year budget request calls for launching the first element  the power and propulsion module  into space in 2022. Two additional launches by 2025 to add habitation, logistics and airlock functions would complete the station.""The Gateway could be put in a Near Rectilinear Halo Orbit, an orbit in cislunar space that could be used as a staging area for future missions." "The platform's position would let astronauts control telerobots on the moon's surface that could be used to explore craters as well as carry out other experiments." SOURCES: Space.comhttps://www.space.com/39985-nasa-lunar-orbital-platform-gateway-science-plan.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 08:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/16/3569326/3569326_44E40BC837EC4801BBD3E45A2B4A15F0_180316_3569326_NASA_planning_deep_space_station_near_the_moon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BBD/4DC/BBD4DCBBA78942A89D308AB7C0F41D2E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, NASA Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway, deep-space outpost, Lunar missions, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3569178</guid>
      <title>Identical twins no longer share same DNA after one spends a year in space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANIdentical NASA twin astronauts Scott and Mark Kelly no longer share the same DNA after the former spent a year in space.According to NASA, scientists compared the twins' DNA and RNA via whole-genome sequencing. They found that 7% of Scott's DNA had changed into so-called space-genes.His immune system, bone formation and eyesight all went under changes, reported Live Science.Telomeres, caps on chromosomes, typically shorten as a person ages. Kelly's lengthened, according to NASA, but returned to normal two days after he returned to Earth.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of DNA sequencing2. Depiction of DNA sequencing continued and change percentage3. Depiction of changes in Kelly4. Depiction of telomeresVOICEOVER (in English): "Following his year in space, scientists compared the DNA and RNA of Scott Kelly with his identical twin brother Mark via whole-genome sequencing.""They found that 7% of Kelly's DNA had changed into so-called space-genes.""As well as that, Kelly's immune system, bone formation and eyesight all went under changes during his year in space.""Telomeres, caps on chromosomes, typically shorten as a person ages.""NASA found Kelly's lengthened spending a year aboard the International Space Station.""They returned to normal two days after he returned to Earth."SOURCES: NASA, CNN, Live Sciencehttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/nasa-twins-study-investigators-to-release-integrated-paper-in-2018https://edition.cnn.com/2018/03/14/health/scott-kelly-dna-nasa-twins-study/index.htmlhttps://www.livescience.com/62000-scott-kelly-dna-twin-study.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 05:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/16/3569178/3569178_B6636B5E87B34381AEB59D2F139E5BF0_180316_3569178_Identical_twins_no_longer_share_same_DNA_after_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EFF/B2B/EFFB2BA3D0D44581B6BEDC52B126B982_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ex twins, identical twins not identical, nasa, space dna, dna and your body, weird science twins, strange science stories, weird science stories, strange science facts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3571451</guid>
      <title>Oklahoma to execute inmates with nitrogen gas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANOklahoma plans to use nitrogen gas to execute death row prisoners, though the details of the procedure have yet to be finalized.The state plans to use the gas to induce nitrogen hypoxia, a fatal state where the brain and body are deprived of oxygen.According to the U.S. Chemical Safety Board, 78% of the air humans breathe contain nitrogen. The lower the oxygen content, the deadlier nitrogen becomes.  As the oxygen content lowers to 16%, the brain tells the body to breathe faster and deeper. Anything below 10% oxygen content can be fatal.Speaking to Reuters, the Death Penalty Information Center said it would take 7 minutes for a 32-kg pig to die from nitrogen hypoxia. Other countries known to use gas during executions were Nazi Germany, North Korea and the USSR.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of nitrogen hypoxia2. Depiction of regular oxygen and nitrogen content in air3. Depiction of nitrogen impact on the body as oxygen content lowers4. Depiction of time it take for a pig to die via nitrogen hypoxiaVOICEOVER (in English): "Oklahoma plans to use nitrogen gas to induce hypoxia in prisoners awaiting execution, though the details of the procedure have yet to be finalized.""Hypoxia is a fatal state where the brain and body are deprived of oxygen.""According to the U.S. Chemical Safety Board, 78% of the air humans breathe contain nitrogen.""The lower the oxygen content, the deadlier nitrogen becomes.""As the oxygen content lowers to 16%, the brain tells the body to breathe faster and deeper.""Anything below 10% oxygen content can be fatal.""Speaking to Reuters, the Death Penalty Information Center said it would take 7 minutes for a 32-kg pig to die from nitrogen hypoxia."SOURCES: Reuters, U.S. Chemical Safety Board, Death Penalty Information Center, https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oklahoma-executions/oklahoma-to-become-first-u-s-state-to-use-nitrogen-gas-for-executions-idUSKCN1GQ3CThttp://www.csb.gov/assets/1/19/Nitrogen_Asphyxiation_Bulletin_Training_Presentation.pdfhttp://www.csb.gov/assets/1/19/SB-Nitrogen-6-11-031.pdfhttps://deathpenaltyinfo.org/node/7042***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 10:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/19/3571451/3571451_DB716BA2112549B4A92F698480C474E9_180319_3571451_Oklahoma_to_execute_inmates_with_nitrogen_gas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BB4/5D2/BB45D29638D54C5BB70B106938F7348E_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nitrogen gas execution, oklahoma nitrogen gas, nitrogen hypoxia, death penalty, lethal injection, oklahoma, prisoner execution, nitrogen gas, nitrogen execution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3571253</guid>
      <title>U.S. Department of Defense funding time crystal studies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANTime crystal research is to get funding from the U.S. Department of Defense.DoD agency DARPA announced it would be funding several projects at universities in January.Regular crystals are made up of structured atoms in a shape. If touched, a crystal won't break apart. The structure remains rigid, even when moved. It generally maintains its shape. Time crystals also feature an atomic structure, except these aren't solid. The structure is constantly moving, repeating it through time. Researchers say these the world's first non-equilibrium matter, reports the Daily Mail, or more simply, a matter where forces are not balanced.According to Gizmodo, the research is classified but may have applications in atomic clocks and also, potentially, quantum computing.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of regular crystal2. Depiction of time crystal3. Depiction of forces within regular crystals and time crystalsVOICEOVER (in English): "Regular crystals are made up of structured atoms in a shape. If touched, a crystal won't break apart.""The structure remains rigid, even when moved. It generally maintains its shape.""Time crystals also feature an atomic structure, except these aren't solid.""The structure is constantly moving, repeating it through time.""Researchers say these the world's first non-equilibrium matter, or more simply, a matter where forces are not balanced."SOURCES: DARPA, Gizmodo, Daily Mailhttps://www.darpa.mil/news-events/2018-01-18https://gizmodo.com/darpa-is-funding-time-crystal-research-1823745090http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-5507453/DARPA-launches-research-program-study-time-crystals.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 06:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/19/3571253/3571253_86A5CA5CB3B6492E957455DBC003CDCE_180319_3571253_U_S__Department_of_Defense_funding_time_crystal__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/54A/AA1/54AAA16CFC274852B2C0FBCEEB0C063D_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, time crystals, what are time crystals, space-time crystals, DARPAm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572053</guid>
      <title>NASA plans to use nukes to blow up giant asteroid Bennu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNASA has come up with a plan to save us all should a large space rock ever hit the planet.According to the Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, the massive asteroid Bennu, which is taller than the Empire State building and larger than five football fields, is currently orbiting the sun 54 million miles from Earth.It is classified as a "potentially hazardous" object, with a 1 in 2,700 chance of crashing into the planet on September 21, 2135.The spacecraft HAMMER, or Hypervelocity Asteroid Mitigation Mission for Emergency Response, would be able to use an impactor to change the trajectory of smaller rocks.But for a large asteroid like Bennu, HAMMER would have to deploy a nuclear device to destroy it before it reaches Earth.NASA has been monitoring the enormous space rock since it was discovered in 1999, and has sent out a space probe to take samples.Bennu is one of 10,000 near-Earth objects it has detected, though only 2,500 of these are estimated to be as large.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Asteroid Bennu currently orbiting sun2. Asteroid Bennu has a 1 in 2,700 chance of hitting Earth on September 25, 21353. Depiction of HAMMER impactor changing a small asteroid's trajectory4. Depiction of HAMMER deploying nuclear warhead to destroy asteroidVOICEOVER (in English): "The massive asteroid Bennu, which is taller than the Empire State building and larger than five football fields, is currently orbiting the sun 54 million miles from Earth.""It is classified as a 'potentially hazardous' object, with a 1 in 2,700 chance of crashing into the planet on September 25, 2135.""The spacecraft HAMMER, or Hypervelocity Asteroid Mitigation Mission for Emergency Response, would be able to use an impactor to change the trajectory of smaller rocks.""But for a large asteroid like Bennu, HAMMER would have to deploy a nuclear device to destroy it before it reaches Earth."SOURCES: Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, Space, The Telegraphhttps://www.llnl.gov/news/scientists-design-conceptual-asteroid-deflector-and-evaluate-it-against-massive-potentialhttps://www.space.com/39925-hammer-spacecraft-dangerous-asteroid-nuclear-bomb.htmlhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/03/15/nasa-draw-plans-huge-spacecraft-blow-doomsday-asteroid/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/20/3572053/3572053_B125CF0A5E384D4D92F204F34F32EB6E_180320_3572053_NASA_plans_to_use_nukes_to_blow_up_giant_asteroi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D92/126/D9212616F7B944EA949DD26C560CC135_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, asteroid, bennu, asteroid collision, HAMMER, nukes, nuclear warhead, asteroid hitting earth, asteroid bennu, killer asteroid, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572024</guid>
      <title>Strongest ever radio burst recorded by astronomers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAstronomers recorded strongest ever fast radio burst from outer space using the Parkes Observatory radio telescope in Australia earlier this month.According to Inquisitr, signal FRB 180309 was heard by the telescope on March 9. It's signal-to-noise ratio was 4 times larger than the previous strongest signal. Astronomers don't know what it is, but some speculate it could be anything from stars colliding to interstellar travel, according to a report by the Search for Extraterrestrial at University of California, Berkeley.Details of the signal were published on the website Astronomer's Telegram.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of radio burst travelling toward Earth2. Depiction of radio burst being recorded by satellite3. Depiction of theoretical radio burst originVOICEOVER (in English): "The strongest ever fast radio burst ever recorded by astronomers hit Earth earlier this month.""Scientists say signal FRB 180309 was heard on March 9." "It's signal-to-noise ratio was 4 times larger than the previous strongest signal.""Astronomers don't know what it is, but some speculate it could be anything from stars colliding to interstellar travel."SOURCES: Inquisitr, Astronomer's Telegram, SETI at UC Berkeley, https://www.inquisitr.com/4831620/fast-radio-bursts-recently-detected-by-astronomers-includes-strongest-in-over-a-decade/http://www.astronomerstelegram.org/?read=11387http://seti.berkeley.edu:8000/parkes-frb/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 06:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/20/3572024/3572024_4781FC721C414FB98E23F6D874FF87A2_180320_3572024_Strongest_ever_radio_burst_recorded_by_astronome_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4DE/2A2/4DE2A25FF75343D79404DC84B93B20CC_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, astronomy, radio burst, fast radio burst, radio telescope, extraterrestrial life, interstellar travel, neutron star collision]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572016</guid>
      <title>Facebook facing backlash over Cambridge Analytica data misuse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook is facing calls for regulation from congress after reports a political consultant gained inappropriate access to 50 million users' data beginning in 2014. The company disclosed the news in a blog post last Friday. American and British lawmakers are demand on Sunday Facebook explain how so many profiles were harvested without the social network notifying users, according to the New York Times. According the New York Times and the Observer, Cambridge Analytica used personal information taken without permission early in 2014 to build a system that could profile US voters, in order more effectively target them with personalized political ads. The data has not been deleted despite Facebook's demands beginning in 2015. Around 270,000 people allowed a researcher to use their personal data, who also scraped the data of all their friends as well, until the end of 2015. The researcher then sold the data to Cambridge Analytica. Cambridge Analytica worked on Trump's 2016 campaign. According to Reuters, a Trump campaign official said it used Republican data sources for voter information, not Cambridge Analytica. Facebook is claiming Cambridge Analytica and researchers were in breach of policy and that it was exploring legal action. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Facebook data breach2. Depiction of Cambridge Analytica using FB data to make political ads3. Researcher using data on 270,000 users to access all their friends too4. The user data was then sold to Cambridge AnalyticaVOICEOVER (in English): "Facebook is facing calls for regulation from congress after reports that a political consultant gained inappropriate access to 50 million users' data beginning in 2014." "Cambridge Analytica used personal information taken without permission early in 2014 to build a system that could profile US voters, in order more effectively target them with personalized political ads." "Around 270,000 people allowed a researcher to use their personal data, who also scraped the data of all their friends as well, until the end of 2015." "The researcher then sold the data to Cambridge Analytica. Cambridge Analytica worked on Trump's 2016 campaign, however, a Trump campaign official said it used Republican data sources for voter information, not Cambridge Analytica." SOURCES: Reuters, New York Times, Guardianhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-cambridge-analytica-regulati/facebook-critics-want-regulation-investigation-after-data-misuse-idUSKCN1GU01Ahttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/03/18/us/cambridge-analytica-facebook-privacy-data.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/mar/17/cambridge-analytica-facebook-influence-us-election***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 06:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/20/3572016/3572016_1375E407A0DE4DA6942D0A89CBDEDDF7_180320_3572016_Facebook_facing_backlash_over_Cambridge_Analytic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9A9/94E/9A994ED7B1194278B96508AD7F9B55DF_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Facebook, Facebook data misuse, Facebook user data misuse, Cambridge Analytica]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572949</guid>
      <title>Scientists plan to revive northern white rhino using IVF techniques</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe death of the last male northern white rhino may mean probable extinction for the subspecies, but scientists are working on a plan to save them.The New York Times reports that Sudan, the world's last male northern white rhino died in Kenya on Monday, leaving the only two females, neither of which is can carry a pregnancy to term.The best plan to carry on the species is through in-vitro fertilization, using eggs extracted from the surviving females, and stored sperm from dead males.The fertilized egg would be implanted in a surrogate southern white rhino, the species' closest living relative, which would carry the calf to term.If successful, scientists hope to use the procedure to create a herd of five to fifteen rhinos, that would eventually be returned to their natural habitat, according to the Chicago Tribune.With the IVF method costing as much as $9 million, conservationists hope to raise enough money and implement it before it's too late.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Last male northern white rhino dies2. Egg cells to be extracted from living females, combined with frozen white rhino sperm3. Fertilized egg implanted in surrogate southern white rhino4. If successful, herd of 5 to 15 rhinos to be returned to natural habitatVOICEOVER (in English): "Sudan, the world's last male northern white rhino died in Kenya on Monday, leaving the only two females, neither of which has been able to carry a pregnancy to term.""The best plan to carry on the species is through in-vitro fertilization, using eggs extracted from the surviving females, and stored sperm from dead males.""The fertilized egg would be implanted in a surrogate southern white rhino, the species' closest living relative, which would carry the calf to term.""If successful, scientists hope to use the procedure to create a herd of five to 15 rhinos, that would eventually be returned to their natural habitat."SOURCES: New York Times, Chicago Tribune, WJLAhttps://www.nytimes.com/2018/03/20/science/rhino-sudan-extinct.htmlhttp://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/science/ct-northern-white-rhino-sudan-dies-20180320-story.htmlhttp://wjla.com/news/nation-world/the-last-male-northern-white-rhino-has-died-could-his-sperm-save-the-subspecies***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 10:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/21/3572949/3572949_7EB7F803F5E946FDB86BFC73A043BE43_180321_3572949_Scientists_plan_to_revive_northern_white_rhino_u_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/25B/A90/25BA908AD83B4798B8DA4D3D983B5FE0_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, northern white rhino, white rhino, sudan the white rhino, last white rhino, white rhino dies, save the rhino, sudan, in vitro fertilization, southern white rhino]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572941</guid>
      <title>Unexploded package at FedEx facility could help in hunt for Austin bomber</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs a string of explosions in Austin has left two dead and four injured, an unexploded package found on Tuesday could help investigators in their search for a suspected serial bomber. A fifth parcel bomb detonated shortly after midnight on Tuesday at a FedEx center in Schertz, Texas, when the package went off on a conveyor belt, injuring one person. Later Tuesday morning, a second suspicious package was found at another FedEx facility near Austin and was "disrupted by law enforcement," according to CBS News.  FBI officials say the package "contained an explosive device," while emergency dispatch audio reported there were nails and metals in the parcel.  The FBI said in a news release on Tuesday that all six packages were connected. There have been three types of bombs used: hand delivered, tripwire and delivered.Investigators will now study the unexploded device to look for clues and signatures that could help lead to the bomb maker. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of the five explosions2. An suspicious package was found at a FedEx facility3. The package contained an explosive device, nails and metal4. The six packages are all connectedVOICEOVER (in English): "As a string of explosions in Austin has left two dead and four injured, an unexploded package found on Tuesday could help investigators in the hunt for a serial bomber." "Later Tuesday morning, a second suspicious package was found at another FedEx facility near Austin and "disrupted by law enforcement." "FBI officials say the package "contained an explosive device," while emergency dispatch audio reported there were nails and metals in the parcel."  "The FBI said in a news release on Tuesday that all six packages were connected. There have been three types of bombs used: hand delivered, tripwire and delivered."SOURCES: CBS News, Reuters, Voxhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/fedex-explosion-serial-bomber-schertz-san-antonio-austin-texas-today-2018-03-20/https://www.reuters.com/article/us-texas-blast/fifth-texas-parcel-bomb-blast-leaves-u-s-investigators-baffled-idUSKBN1GW136https://www.vox.com/2018/3/19/17139366/austin-texas-bombings***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 10:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/21/3572941/3572941_55406B9DF83E4FFEB4F26FBD3BEBA395_180321_3572941_Unexploded_package_at_FedEx_facility_could_help__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/47C/B30/47CB30F83FDA4A7883EA29D49D845171_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Austin bombings, Texas bombings, Austin parcel bombs, Austin package bombs, Austin FedEx bombs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572766</guid>
      <title>What would happen if Russia attacked deep sea data cables?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: NONELate last year Britain's top military officer warned that Russia poses a threat to the country's internet and communication networks.Trade, business, communication and nations rely largely on deep sea data cables to function. These global links connect the planet's information.Britain's top military officer warned NATO must safeguard them as a priority due to threat presented by Russia's Navy, according to a December 2017 BBC report. In international waters, the cables are in a legally gray area, meaning an attack on them may not trigger NATO collective defence.The cables can be easily destroyed via small explosives, according to the Center for International Maritime Security. If successful, and attack could damage a country's economy and bring their communications network to a halt.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of global subsea data cables2. Depiction of data cable construction3. Depiction of data cable explosion4. Depiction of data cable damage and implicationsVOICEOVER (in English): "Trade, business, communication and nations rely largely on deep sea data cables to function.""These global links connect the planet's information.""But they're very vulnerable.""In December 2017, Britain's top military officer warned NATO must safeguard them as a priority due to threat presented by Russia's Navy.""In international waters, the cables are in a legally gray area, meaning an attack on them may not trigger NATO collective defence.""And the cables can be easily destroyed via small explosives, according to the Center for International Maritime Security.""If successful, an attack could damage a country's economy and bring their communications network to a halt."SOURCES: CIMSEC, Lawfare, BBC, Submarine Cable Map,http://cimsec.org/undersea-cables-challenges-protecting-seabed-lines-communication/35889https://lawfareblog.com/evaluating-russian-threat-undersea-cableshttp://www.bbc.com/news/uk-42362500https://www.submarinecablemap.com***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 07:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/21/3572766/3572766_A6BA3A7C08844CF6A1F024F740EA48D3_180321_3572766_What_would_happen_if_Russia_attacked_deep_sea_da_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0C6/2FD/0C62FDB4FF894B9D9F196D286E1F4206_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Russian Navy, russian submarines, UK, NATO, internet down, deep sea data cable attack, deep sea cables]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572689</guid>
      <title>The risks visitors could face at 2018 World Cup in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANWith the 2018 FIFA World Cup coming in Russia, security measures are going to be tightened.According to IHS Markit, officials predict fights between rival fans and police are more likely to take place in the host cities, meaning there will be an elevated likelihood of injuries and collateral damage done to property.Visitors of non-white racial backgrounds are likely to become targets of individual attacks by football fans or radical groups.With limited legal assistance, minor crimes like pickpocketing, theft and robberies will likely be underreported by Russian authorities.There is also heightened risk of cyberattacks with the intent of breaching the information security of corporate visitors.Despite the security concerns and the recent death of a Spanish police officer when hooligans rioted before Spartak Moscow's Europa League match at Athletic Bilbao, FIFA said it has "complete trust" in the security arrangements for the 2018 World Cup.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of violent events between fans and police in host cities.2. Depiction of visitors of non-white racial background attacked by fans or radical groups.3. Depiction of minor crimes like pickpocketing, theft, and robberies.4. Depiction of cyberattacks against corporate visitors.VOICEOVER (in English): "Officials predict fights between rival fans and police are more likely to take place in the host cities, meaning there will be an elevated likelihood of injuries and collateral damage done to property.""Visitors of non-white racial backgrounds are likely to become targets of individual attacks by football fans or radical groups.""With limited legal assistance, minor crimes like pickpocketing, theft and robberies will likely be underreported by Russian authorities.""There is also heightened risk of cyberattacks with the intent of breaching the information security of corporate visitors."SOURCES: http://www.janes.com/article/75065/foreign-visitors-to-2018-fifa-world-cup-in-russia-face-elevated-injury-risks-collateral-damage-to-propertyhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/2018/02/22/police-officer-dies-football-fans-clash-ahead-match-athletic/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 05:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/21/3572689/3572689_D00CE1F6BE7746E383F01377BB3E65E1_180321_3572689_The_risks_visitors_could_face_at_2018_World_Cup__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A89/6EA/A896EAD7F9AD47C3ABE4FE1E5F75F152_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, world cup security, world cup russia, world cup risks, world cup danger, world cup security measures, russia security measures, 2018 world cup russia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572678</guid>
      <title>China to restrict travel rights of people with poor 'social credit'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANChina is curbing the transportation rights of people with poor "social credit."Effective May 1, the country will ban citizens with low social credit scores from using flight and rail transport for one year.According to Reuters, those banned include individuals who lied about terrorism, caused trouble on flights as well as people who used out-of-date tickets, or smoked on trains. Also affected are people who didn't pay fines and employers not paying social insurance.China's yet-to-be finalized social credit system operates on the doctrine of "once untrustworthy, always restricted", reported Reuters.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of travel restrictions2. Depiction of those restricted from travel3. Depiction of social credit system VOICEOVER (in English): "Effective May 1, the People's Republic of China will ban citizens with low social credit scores from using flight and rail transport for one year.""Those prohibited include people who caused trouble on flights, as well as individuals who used out-of-date tickets, or those who were caught smoking on trains.""Also affected are people who didn't pay fines and businesses who did not pay their employees' social insurance." SOURCES: Reuters, The Telegraphhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-credit/china-to-bar-people-with-bad-social-credit-from-planes-trains-idUSKCN1GS10Shttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/china-travel-ban-bad-social-credit-from-planes-trains/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 05:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/21/3572678/3572678_8D7644AB89D141B986B0EA062E841450_180321_3572678_China_to_restrict_travel_rights_of_people_with_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3AC/C2D/3ACC2DF68F034F6183E40BD5CF144BD1_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, china, social credit china, travel ban, social credit scores, life in china, government surveillance, prc, communist state]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3572658</guid>
      <title>Uber halts self-driving tests after fatal crash in Arizona</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA female pedestrian was struck and killed by an Uber autonomous vehicle in Tempe, Arizona on Sunday night. The fatality is believed to be the first known death by an autonomous test vehicle. The company has halted self-driving tests in Tempe, San Francisco, Pittsburgh and Toronto.  The crash occurred near Mill Avenue and Curry Road around 10 p.m., according to police. The Uber vehicle was reportedly traveling northbound at around 40 mph when a woman walking a bicycle outside of the crosswalk was struck.The woman, 49-year-old Elaine Herzberg, was transported to the hospital where she died from her injuries, according to ABC 15.  Tempe Police say the SUV was in autonomous mode and vehicle operator, 44-year-old Rafaela Vasquez, was behind the wheel at the time of the accident. The National Transportation Safety Board is opening an investigation and sending investigators to Tempe.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Uber self-driving vehicle2. Uber self-driving vehicle traveling down street before accident3. A woman being struck by the Uber self-driving vehicle4. Uber is halting self-driving tests in Tempe, SF, Pittsburgh and TorontoVOICEOVER (in English): "A female pedestrian was struck and killed by an Uber autonomous vehicle in Tempe on Sunday night. The fatality is believed to be the first known death by an autonomous test vehicle." "The Uber vehicle was reportedly traveling northbound at around 40 mph in autonomous mode with a backup driver behind the wheel around 10 p.m.""That's when a woman walking a bicycle outside of the crosswalk was struck by the Uber SUV. The woman was transported to the hospital where she died from her injuries.""In response, Uber has stopped self-driving tests in Tempe, San Francisco, Pittsburgh and Toronto."  SOURCES: ABC 15, Verge, Bloomberghttps://www.abc15.com/news/region-southeast-valley/tempe/tempe-police-investigating-self-driving-uber-car-involved-in-crash-overnighthttps://www.theverge.com/2018/3/19/17139518/uber-self-driving-car-fatal-crash-tempe-arizonahttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-03-19/uber-autonomous-car-involved-in-fatal-crash-in-arizona?utm_content=politics&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=socialflow-organic&cmpid%3D=socialflow-twitter-politics&utm_source=twitter***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/21/3572658/3572658_C32CB69B11534EB6B76AABC83CFDAB6E_180321_3572658_Uber_halts_self_driving_tests_after_fatal_crash__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/43B/431/43B4313E799A41EAA9F0FAB94B016F28_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Uber autonomous car crash, Uber autonomous vehicle crash, Uber autonomous crash, Uber autonomous fatal crash, Uber self driving fatal crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3573709</guid>
      <title>Protecting your personal data on Facebook</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANFacebook has been taking criticism for its latest scandal involving the misuse of personal data with Cambridge Analytica.According to Digital Trends, here are some ways to protect personal data on Facebook without deleting the entire account. The first step is to remove Facebook from connected apps, basically disabling the platform so third-party apps can not access your account or information. Next, users can adjust the amount of data friends and family take with them to other apps, such as birthdate, education, employment and relationships. The third alternative is to shut off Facebook's data collection for advertisements. This includes website and apps use and adds coupled with social actions. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People using Facebook2. Disabling Facebook for third party apps3. Adjusting how much data friends and family can take with them4. Shutting off Facebook data collection for adsVOICEOVER (in English): "Here are some ways to protect personal data on Facebook without deleting the entire account." "The first step is to remove Facebook from connected apps, basically disabling the platform so third-party apps cannot access your account or information." "Next, users can adjust the amount of data friends and family take with them to other apps, such as birthdate, education, employment and relationships.""The third alternative is to shut off Facebook's data collection for advertisements. This includes website and apps use and ads coupled with social actions." SOURCES: Digital Trendshttps://www.digitaltrends.com/social-media/protect-yourself-on-facebook/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 09:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/22/3573709/3573709_62669800A2C2428AA0C4AEB3349AFC4C_180322_3573709_Protecting_your_personal_data_on_Facebook_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/450/632/450632E63AD74078BA2D8508E097F519_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Facebook data, Facebook personal data misuse, Facebook third party apps, third party data]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3573611</guid>
      <title>China testing unmanned tank as part of military modernization</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Chinese have begun trialing a remotely-controlled battle tank as part of plans to upgrade its armed forces.The Global Times reports that China's medium-sized Type 59 tank is equipped with a 100 or 105 millimeter cannon, and typically requires a crew of 4 people to operate.The state is now testing an unmanned version of the tank, with footage from Chinese media showing a soldier remotely driving the vehicle.Type 59 tanks were first used in the 1950s and are due to retire, but can be equipped with with artificial intelligence to turn them to autonomous vehicles.They will be able to work with other unmanned equipment, and integrate information from satellites, aircrafts, or submarines.For now, the unmanned Type 59 tanks still have technical issues, and will likely go through more testing and tweaking before they can be fully combat-capable.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese type 59 tank typically requires 4 crew members to operate2. Chinese testing unmanned tank3. Type 59 tanks can be converted into unmanned vehicles using artificial intelligence4. Unmanned tanks to integrate information from other unmanned equipmentVOICEOVER (in English): "China's medium-sized Type 59 tank is equipped with a 100 or 105 millimeter cannon, and typically requires a crew of 4 people to operate.""The state is now testing an unmanned version of the tank, with footage from Chinese media showing a soldier remotely driving the vehicle.""Type 59 tanks were first used in the 1950s and are due to retire, but can be equipped with with artificial intelligence to turn them to autonomous vehicles.""They will be able to work with other unmanned equipment, and integrate information from satellites, aircrafts, or submarines."SOURCES: Reuters, Global Timeshttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-defence/china-trials-unmanned-tanks-in-latest-modernization-push-idUSKBN1GX03Shttp://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1094292.shtml***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 07:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/22/3573611/3573611_2C535BBD9FAF404BB4CD55560A19054D_180322_3573611_China_testing_unmanned_tank_as_part_of_military__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F98/2A5/F982A59C9BF94DCA85CAB016BC9C58D6_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, unmanned tank, unmanned vehicle, artificial intelligence, type 59 tank, china military, military tech, military technology, china artificial intelligence]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3573575</guid>
      <title>How to protect your cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAs cryptocurrencies have gained in popularity, so have thefts involving digital coins. Hackers have several methods at their disposal to steal cryptocurrencies, including brute forcing, phone-porting, phishing, Ponzi schemes and mining malware, according to Visual Capitalist. When it comes to digital currencies, how secure your digital wallet, your private keys and any systems they use to make transactions is of utmost importance.   Install and run antivirus software on your computers and smartphones. Be careful opening up any suspicious emails, and set up two-factor authentication whenever possible. Encrypt your hard drives and mobile devices, and make backups of them as well. Finding a trustworthy exchange is also important. With a centralized exchange, you allow the exchange to manage the security of your funds on your behalf. Unfortunately, this makes centralized exchanges a perfect target for hackers. Decentralized exchanges allow for direct peer-to-peer cryptotrading, during which the exchange is never in control of your funds. Decentralized exchanges also do not have access to your private keys. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cryptotheft methods2. Digital wallet and private key security importance3. Antivirus software being installed in devices4. Depiction of two factor authenticationVOICEOVER (in English): "Hackers have several methods at their disposal to steal cryptocurrencies, including brute forcing, phone-porting, phishing, Ponzi schemes and mining malware.""When it comes to digital currencies, how secure your digital wallet, your private keys and any systems they use to make transactions is of utmost importance."   "Install and run antivirus software on your computers and smartphones." "Be careful opening up any suspicious emails, and set up two-factor authentication whenever possible." SOURCES: Visual Capitalist, Tom's Guidehttp://www.visualcapitalist.com/problem-crypto-theft/https://www.tomsguide.com/us/how-to-protect-bitcoins,news-26260.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 07:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/22/3573575/3573575_FA6BBA29252F442B896919EE83F42137_180322_3573575_How_to_protect_your_cryptocurrency_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7C9/DF8/7C9DF8BB8701400494A117EF35BB134C_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cryptocurrency, digital currency, cryptotheft, cryptocurrency hackers, bitcoin, bitcoin security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3573569</guid>
      <title>U.S., South Korea push forward with annual military drills</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDespite being delayed by the Pyeongchang Winter Olympics, the annual war games on the democratic side of the Korean Peninsula are pushing through.According to Korea JoongAng Daily, South Korea and the U.S. have announced that joint military drills between the two countries will begin on April 1.The war games consist of two drills. The first, called "Foal Eagle", is a series of field-training exercises combining ground, air, naval, and special operations.The four-week-long program involves 290,000 South Korean and 11,500 American troops.The second drill, called "Key Resolve", is a computer-simulated command post exercise that's set to be held for two weeks starting April 23.This year's war games are more low-key compared to previous years, possibly to avoid provoking North Korea, who has always objected to them.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. US and South Korea to begin joint military exercises on April 12. Depiction of Foal Eagle drill3. 290,000 South Korean and 11,500 US troops involved in Foal Eagle4. Depiction of Key Resolve computer-simulated training programVOICEOVER (in English): "South Korea  and the U.S. have announced that joint military drills between the two countries will begin on April 1.""The war games consist of two drills. The first, called 'Foal Eagle', is a series of field training exercises combining ground, air, naval, and special operations.""The four-week-long program involves 290,000 South Korean and 11,500 American troops.""The second drill, called 'Key Resolve', is a computer-simulated command post exercise that's set to be held for two weeks starting April 23."SOURCES: CNBC, Korea JoongAng Daily, Los Angeles Timeshttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/03/20/us-south-korea-war-games-that-freak-out-north-korea-coming-soon.htmlhttp://koreajoongangdaily.joins.com/news/article/article.aspx?aid=3045884http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-korea-us-military-20180320-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 07:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/22/3573569/3573569_812B794965B344FDB26924E2227CA648_180322_3573569_U_S___South_Korea_push_forward_with_annual_milit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3EE/53D/3EE53DBF56DB40F196C15040FB4335D4_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, US South Korean war games, war games, military drills, joint military exercises, North Korea, South Korea, foal eagle, key resolve]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3574842</guid>
      <title>Gulf of Mexico dead zone may take decades to clear up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe dead zone in the Gulf of Mexico isn't likely to shrink anytime soon, and could even persist for decades, according to a new study.The Guardian reports that dead zones are low-oxygen areas in bodies of water that are harmful to marine life and can lead to massive algal blooms.The hypoxic zones are fed by nitrogen fertilizer, which flows through waterways across America's corn belt and into the Gulf of Mexico.The Gulf Hypoxia Action Plan currently calls for a reduction in nitrogen runoffs in order to shrink the dead zone from 5,000 to 1,950 square kilometers by 2035.But according to a new report from the University of Waterloo, 'legacy' nitrogen that has been accumulating underground and in the groundwater also feeds into the Gulf.It found that even if strict measures were to fully stem annual runoffs, it would still take more than 30 years for the 'legacy' nitrogen to clear up, and for the Gulf to recover.Improving water quality in the Gulf of Mexico requires changes in agricultural practices.More careful application of fertilizers, reduced tillage, and cultivating plants that can stop chemicals from leaching into water are just some methods that can curb nitrogen pollution.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of the low-oxygen dead zone in the Gulf of Mexico2. Dead zone caused by excessive nitrogen runoff from fertilizers3. Depiction of national plan to shrink dead zone by 20354. Depiction of 'legacy' nitrogen underground and in groundwater5. Dead zone will likely take 30 years to clear upVOICEOVER (in English): "Dead zones are low-oxygen areas in bodies of water that are harmful to marine life and can lead to massive algal blooms.""The hypoxic zones are fed by nitrogen fertilizer, which flows through waterways across America's corn belt and into the Gulf of Mexico.""The Gulf Hypoxia Action Plan currently calls for a reduction in nitrogen runoffs in order to shrink the dead zone from 5,000 to 1,950 square kilometers by 2035.""'Legacy' nitrogen that has been accumulating underground and in the groundwater also feeds into the Gulf.""Even if strict measures were to fully stem annual runoffs, it could take more than 30 years for the 'legacy' nitrogen to clear up, and for the Gulf to recover."SOURCES: The Guardian, University of Waterloohttps://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/mar/22/dead-zone-gulf-of-mexico-decades-recover-studyhttps://phys.org/news/2018-03-gulf-mexico-dead-zone-anytime.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/24/3574842/3574842_1186A3625D014022928BF3A2AE2779DD_180324_3574842_Gulf_of_Mexico_dead_zone_may_take_decades_to_cle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CAF/40D/CAF40DC41F774438A9C72E4D920108E2_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, dead zone, gulf of mexico, gulf of mexico dead zone, hypoxic zone, nitrogen fertilizer, nitrogen runoffs, legacy nitrogen, low oxygen, American corn belt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3574414</guid>
      <title>Space Drone that extends satellite life could also be weaponized</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA UK-based space company is planning to launch satellite-servicing drones by 2020, but experts warn these could double as space weapons.The BBC reports that the Space Drone is an 800-pound spacecraft that can dock onto ageing satellites running low on fuel, and helping to stabilize and maneuver them.The drones remain attached for up to five years, before then moving the satellite to a graveyard orbit at the end of its life.Experts believe the space drones can be used to clean up Earth's orbit by directing space debris to the atmosphere to burn up.Theoretically, the drones could also be weaponized and used to hijack active satellites and push them out of orbit.The company that makes the space drones says any technology has the potential to be abused, and claims they can prevent this by retaining control and simply offering their services.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Space drone docks on low fuel satellites to extend their life2. Space drone pushing satellite into graveyard orbit after 5 years3. Space drone used to direct space junk to burn up in the Earth's atmosphere4. Depiction of Space Drone as an outer space tugboat VOICEOVER (in English): "Space Drone is an 800-pound spacecraft that can dock onto aging satellites running low on fuel, and helping to stabilize and maneuver them.""The drones remain attached for up to five years, before then moving the satellite to a graveyard orbit at the end of its life.""Experts believe the space drones can be used to clean up Earth's orbit by directing space debris into the atmosphere to burn up.""Theoretically, the drones could also be weaponized and used to hijack active satellites and push them out of orbit."SOURCES: Effective Space, Space News, BBChttps://www.effective.space/http://spacenews.com/effective-space-signs-first-contract-for-satellite-life-extension-services/http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-43374855***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 08:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/23/3574414/3574414_6F5BF27529914663A92ECBA2692314D8_180323_3574414_Space_Drone_that_extends_satellite_life_could_al_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B79/88A/B7988AD5D9B747C49CAF874D8DD3B34F_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, space drone, old satellites, space junk, space tugboat, outer space tugboat, orbital tugboat, low fuel, graveyard orbit, weaponized satellites, effective space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3577283</guid>
      <title>Study reveals where to sit on plane to avoid getting sick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAccording to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America, human movement around an enclosed space such as an airline cabin can supposedly spread more viruses than recirculated air.Since a person's seat influences their movement, those in the aisle and middle seats are more likely to get up and be exposed to germs. Passengers who pick a window seat and stay there have the least exposure.A study found that on a flight of 150 passengers where one person is sick, only one person on average will become infected.The odds of getting sick are highest among the 11 passengers seated closest to the sick person  three beside, four in front, and four behind.So if you're particular about germs, a window seat might be your best optio. And if you just happen to sit next to someone who has a cold, the overhead air vents might still help ward away those germs.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People moving through airline cabin spreads more germs than recirculated air2. Window seat passengers least likely to come in contact with germs or viruses3. Sick person on a 150-passenger flight infects one other passenger on average4. Positions of those most likely to get sickVOICEOVER (in English): "Human movement around an enclosed space such as an airline cabin can supposedly spread more viruses than recirculated air.""Since a person's seat influences their movement, those in the aisle and middle seats are more likely to get up and be exposed to germs. Passengers who pick a window seat and stay there have the least exposure.""A study found that on a flight of 150 passengers where one person is sick, only one person on average will become infected.""The odds of getting sick are highest among the 11 passengers seated closest to the sick person  three beside, four in front, and four behind."SOURCES: Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of Americahttp://www.pnas.org/content/early/2018/03/13/1711611115http://www.afr.com/lifestyle/travel/world/to-avoid-germs-on-a-plane-consider-booking-a-window-seat-20180321-h0xt06***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 09:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/27/3577283/3577283_56E0739A46244BD7AC2837E1F6F081D2_180327_3577283_Study_reveals_where_to_sit_on_plane_to_avoid_get_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/137/DDD/137DDDF75AEB4C2ABE06583E00541108_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, best seat on plane, window seat, disease transmission, disease, virus transmission, plane germs, germs on planes, viruses on planes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3577273</guid>
      <title>North Korean train in Beijing fuels rumors of Kim Jong Un visit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANUnusually heavy security in China's capital coupled with the arrival of a mysterious train from the North are sparking intense speculation over who came to visit.The Los Angeles Times reports that Japanese news media first noticed the armored train crossing from North Korea into China at the border city of Dandong.Soldiers and police were on hand when the train arrived at Beijing station on Monday, with reports indicating Kim Jong Un was onboard.The 21-car train bears a striking resemblance to the armored train Kim's late father Kim Jong Il used to visit allies in China and Russia.The locomotive reportedly contained a conference room, an audience chamber, and bedrooms, and was fitted with satellite phone connections and a flat screen TV.The news has not been confirmed, but if true, this visit is the reclusive leader's first known trip outside his country since taking power in 2011.Analysts say it's possible Kim may be in town to talk to the Chinese regarding his upcoming meeting with U.S. President Trump.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Armored train seen crossing from North Korea into China2. Train in Beijing station, met by marching soldiers and a limousine motorcade3. 21-car train may be same one used by Kim Jong Il to visit Russia, China4. Facilities, equipment inside the trainVOICEOVER (in English): "Japanese news media first noticed the armored train crossing from North Korea into China at the border city of Dandong.""Soldiers and police were on hand when the train arrived at Beijing station on Monday, with reports indicating Kim Jong Un was on board.""The 21-car train bears a striking resemblance to the armored train Kim's late father Kim Jong Il used to visit allies in China and Russia.""The locomotive reportedly contained a conference room, an audience chamber, and bedrooms, and was fitted with satellite phone connections and a flat screen TV."SOURCES: Bloomberg, CNN, Independent, Los Angeles Timeshttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-03-25/mnuchin-cautiously-hopeful-china-trade-deal-can-be-reachedhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/03/26/asia/north-korea-train-beijing-intl/index.htmlhttps://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/north-korea-train-kim-jong-un-china-beijing-visit-us-talks-guard-asia-latest-a8274591.htmlhttp://www.latimes.com/nation/la-fg-china-kim-20180326-story.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 09:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/27/3577273/3577273_F11ECF6353574B799BD58CDD0C9EA6CE_180327_3577273_North_Korean_train_in_Beijing_fuels_rumors_of_Ki_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/416/A28/416A2893EEE44B83BCBB8BF4DB2B4448_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, north korea, north korea train, kim jong un, north korea visit, armored train, state visit, beijing, kim jong il, north korea armored train]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3577193</guid>
      <title>Suspicious mail found at military, intelligence and FBI buildings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANAn FBI-led Investigation is underway after federal facilities, military, CIA and FBI installations all received suspicious packages on Monday.Fort Belvoir, Fort McNair and the CIA all received packages containing black powder, reports CNN, citing officials. Law enforcement told CNN over 10 devices were found and explosions from the packages would not have resulted in casualties.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of package with suspicious contents being detected2. Depiction of package contents3. Depiction of suspicious package being posted4. Depiction of explosion with no casualties VOICEOVER (in English): "According to CNN, scanners at military and intelligence buildings in Washington, D.C and Virginia detected suspicious packages on Monday.""Ten devices were found in total.""Law enforcement told CNN that the packages all contained black powder. "One at Fort Belvoir in Virginia was found to also contain a fuse and a 'suspected GPS.'""Authorities say the packages were sent via regular mail.""Explosions from the packages would not have resulted in casualties."SOURCES: CNN, NBC, CBShttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/03/26/politics/suspicious-packages-dc-military-installations/index.htmlhttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/six-suspicious-packages-sent-military-intelligence-sites-officials-say-n860236https://www.cbsnews.com/news/suspicious-packages-sent-to-washington-d-c-area-military-bases/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 08:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/27/3577193/3577193_E11A901691E449B6A5AE42ECF3500AF0_180327_3577193_Suspicious_mail_found_at_military__intelligence__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D1F/BEA/D1FBEA54641D478DB0FBF37360B4C15B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, suspicious package, strange mail, powder in the mail, suspicious powder in mail, mail room inspection, military, government, cia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3578056</guid>
      <title>New human organ found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANScientists at New York University have discovered a previously unseen human organ, according to a new study.Called the interstitium, the organ is a system of interconnected lymph fluid pockets that found throughout, according to the research.   Researchers say the interstitium is a body-wide structure of lymph-fluid, collagen and proteins. The organ is also believed to comprise 20 percent of all bodily fluids, according to a CBS report.The study also found that the interstitium had helped cancer cells move from infected areas to other areas of the body via the lymphatic system. NYU pathologist Neil Theise described this as a "waterslide", according to a quote in a New Scientist report on the study. The findings were published in the journal Scientific Reports.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of interstitium being found2. Depiction of interstitium structure3. Depiction of how the interstitium helps cancer moveVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Scientific Reports (Nature), Biomed Research International, New Scientist, National Geographic, Live Science, CBS Miamihttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-23062-6https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4773527/https://www.newscientist.com/article/2164903-newly-discovered-human-organ-may-help-explain-how-cancer-spreads/https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/03/interstitium-fluid-cells-organ-found-cancer-spd/https://www.livescience.com/62128-interstitium-organ.htmlhttp://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/03/27/interstitium-new-organ-human-body/***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 09:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/28/3578056/3578056_3098CA79F94D4F7FBB9CE1DC70818BEC_180328_3578056_New_human_organ_found_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/385/256/3852562ABFB54362A0E6ED465DECE337_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, new human organ found, new human organ, interstitium, new organ, organ discovery, interstitium organ]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3577998</guid>
      <title>China sends massive naval fleet to South China Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANDozens of naval vessels were spotted doing drills in disputed waters, in what experts believe is China showing off its growing military might.Reuters reports that satellite images taken by Planet Labs Inc. on Monday revealed that the Chinese aircraft carrier Liaoning entered a vital trade waterway in the South China Sea, just off Hainan Island.At least 40 ships and submarines were seen flanking the aircraft carrier  an unusually large show of force, according to experts.The massive Chinese fleet was sailing in a line formation headed by the submarines, and accompanied by several aircrafts flying overhead.It's unclear though where the fleet was headed or how long the naval exercises are set to last.Analysts say China may be displaying inter-fleet interoperability, which the navy has been working on. It's also possible they're flexing their muscles in response to a freedom-of-navigation patrol by a U.S. warship last week.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Chinese aircraft carrier Liaoning in South China Sea, off Hainan Island2. 40 ships and submarines accompanying aircraft carrier3. Chinese fleet sailing in a line formation with aircraft flying overheadVOICEOVER (in English): "Satellite images taken on Monday revealed that the Chinese aircraft carrier Liaoning entered a vital trade waterway in the South China Sea, just off Hainan Island.""At least 40 ships and submarines were seen flanking the aircraft carrier  an unusually large show of force, according to experts.""The massive Chinese fleet was sailing in a line formation headed by the submarines, and accompanied by several aircrafts flying overhead."SOURCES: Reutershttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-defence/exclusive-satellite-images-reveal-show-of-force-by-chinese-navy-in-south-china-sea-idUSKBN1H3135***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 08:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/28/3577998/3577998_B1FE7C3382134AB6970CD85C69FA3330_180328_3577998_China_sends_massive_naval_fleet_to_South_China_S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7F2/9C0/7F29C06F3BCB4E26800F393B9143F6C2_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, south china sea, chinese navy, chinese fleet, south sea fleet, liaoning, aircraft carrier, china military drills, war games, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3577831</guid>
      <title>CDC warns of second wave of flu virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThis year's flu season has been one of the worst the U.S. has ever seen, and though it's winding down, we're not in the clear just yet.According to the CDC, cases of the dominant and more serious influenza-A strain have been declining in recent weeks.But another form of the virus, influenza-B, is on the rise, and now makes up for 60% of reported flu cases in the country.Though generally milder, the B-strain virus tends to affect younger children more severely.It's also possible for adults who have gotten sick from the A-strain to also become infected with the B virus within the same season.Since both strains are still active, doctors recommend flu shots for those who are still unvaccinated. Standard hygiene practices should also be followed to keep the viruses at bay.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Influenza-A virus declining2. Influenza-B strain on the rise, accounts for 60% of all cases in the US3. Influenza-B virus can affect children more severely4. People who were affected with influenza A could still get influenza BVOICEOVER (in English): "According to the CDC, cases of the dominant and more serious influenza-A strain have been declining in recent weeks.""But another form of the virus, influenza-B, is on the rise, and now makes up for 60% of reported flu cases in the country.""Though generally milder, the B-strain virus tends to affect younger children more severely.""It's also possible for adults who have gotten sick from the A-strain to also become infected with the B virus within the same season."SOURCES: Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, WKBN, WCVBhttps://www.cdc.gov/flu/weekly/index.htmhttp://wkbn.com/2018/03/26/cdc-warns-of-a-second-wave-of-flu-virus-happening-now/http://www.wcvb.com/article/cdc-warns-of-second-wave-of-flu-virus/19602362***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/28/3577831/3577831_617E36546A614FEF8E1A1BD31B9575D5_180328_3577831_CDC_warns_of_second_wave_of_flu_virus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/33C/D39/33CD390A3ED8484395A8BBB68A99A2DA_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, flu season, flu virus, flu, influenza, influenza virus, influenza A, influenza B, second wave, 2018 flu season, CDC, virus, disease, contagious disease]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3579108</guid>
      <title>Archaeologists find 81 ancient settlements in the Amazon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe Amazon was believed to be largely uninhabited before Europeans arrived in South America, but new research shows this may not be the case.According to a study published in Nature Communications, deforestation in the Amazon has uncovered at least 81 geoglyphs  trenches carved into the ground. They were spotted on satellite images of Brazil's Upper Tapajos Basin.The geoglyphs come in a range of different shapes and sizes, and are believed to date back centuries, from the years 1250 to 1500.Archaeologists examined several locations and found fragments of pottery, stone axes, and fertile dark earth indicative of a long-term human settlement.Researchers used models to estimate that between 1,000 to 1,500 wooden settlements were built in the southern rim of the Amazon alone, housing 500,000 to a million people.This indigenous population was likely wiped out by the outbreak of diseases, and would have been worsened by the arrival of the Europeans.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Discovery of 81 geoglyphs in deforested areas of the Amazon2. Settlements of different shapes and sizes, from years 1250 to 15003. Archaeologists finding fragments that indicate long-term human habitation4. Settlement structures possibly made from woodVOICEOVER (in English): "Deforestation in the Amazon has uncovered at least 81 geoglyphs- trenches carved into the ground that were spotted on satellite images of Brazil's Upper Tapajos Basin.""The geoglyphs come in a range of different shapes and sizes, and are believed to date back centuries, from the years 1250 to 1500.""Archaeologists examined several locations and found fragments of pottery, stone axes, and fertile dark earth indicative of a long-term human settlement.""Researchers used models to estimate that between 1,000 to 1,500 wooden settlements were built in the southern rim of the Amazon alone, housing 500,000 to a million people."SOURCES: Nature Communications, Washington Post, The Guardianhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-018-03510-7https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/speaking-of-science/wp/2018/03/27/archaeologists-discover-81-ancient-settlements-in-the-amazon/?utm_term=.b6e9cc6b8bd9https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/mar/27/lost-amazon-villages-uncovered-by-archaeologists***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/29/3579108/3579108_31CD948CB66640A4B6BD9282904BBE61_180329_3579108_Archaeologists_find_81_ancient_settlements_in_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/356/348/3563481BE89444C4B47815FCAC9B1EAD_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, amazon, ancient settlement, amazon village, lost settlement, lost village, amazon tribe, amazon settlements, amazon rainforest, archaeological find, archaeologists, pre columbian]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3578848</guid>
      <title>Startup to offer man-made shooting star shows</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA Japanese startup wants to offer the world on-demand fake meteor showers.Tokyo-based Astro Live Experience will use a microsatellite to create an artificial shooting star show for the 2020 Olympics. The company now want to make it available on demand.In December, the company plans to launch a to two satellites at an orbit of 220 miles over Earth. The International Space Station orbits at 250 miles. The heights of other the thousands of other satellites in orbit vary."ALE told BuzzFeed they'd do a triple-check with US Strategic Command's satellite trajectory prior to any pellet launch in order to avoid collision with other spacecraft.The problem with that, a retired U.S. Air Force Colonel pointed out, is that spy satellites' trajectories are classified and kept out of the catalog. Meaning, a pellet could theoretically hit one.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of shooting stars2. Depiction of artificial shooting stars over Tokyo3. Depiction of satellite and pellets4. Depiction of satellite and pellet in space5. Depiction of pellets as artificial shooting stars.6. Depiction of December launch7. Depiction of multiple satellites8. Depiction of pellet colliding with satelliteVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Star-ALE, Futurism, BuzzFeed, TechTimes, Christian Science Monitor, Facebook / Now This, Phys.orghttp://star-ale.comhttps://www.buzzfeed.com/danvergano/ale-shooting-star-satellite-meteor?utm_term=.ip31RlK88#.acKV7YA88https://futurism.com/meteor-showers-demand-rich-people/https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/demand-meteor-showers-may-be-way-ncna860466http://www.techtimes.com/articles/160172/20160523/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-pellets-for-japans-man-made-meteor-shower.htmhttp://www.csmonitor.com/Science/2016/0522/Japanese-startup-seeks-to-create-artificial-meteor-showerhttps://www.facebook.com/NowThisNews/videos/1067510883339035/http://phys.org/news/2015-06-star-japan-man-made-meteors.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 09:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/29/3578848/3578848_A30BC766EFC74610AF9D1A4A4BF28A9B_180329_3578848_Startup_to_offer_man_made_shooting_star_shows_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/429/BC1/429BC1528B2545888E3307E002B9372A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  meteor show, Astro Live Experience, fake meteor show, artificial shooting stars, tokyo 2020]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3578618</guid>
      <title>North Korea fires up new nuclear reactor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANNorth Korea has begun testing a new nuclear reactor after claiming to support the idea of a nuclear-free North and setting up a meeting with U.S. President Donald Trump.A newly finished nuclear reactor in North Korea's Yongbyon complex has reportedly come online, after satellite images show its smokestack releasing emissions. The North claims the reactor is meant to produce electricity for civilians, since it has the potential to create enough megawatts to power a small town.Experts point out that the nuclear reactor can also be used to create 20 kilograms of plutonium a year to power its nuclear weapons.To achieve complete denuclearization, the U.S. will have to persuade the North Koreans to give up not just their arsenal, but also facilities that produce nuclear fuel.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. New nuclear reactor in Yongbyon, North Korea goes online 2. Nuclear reactor can generate enough electricity to power a village3. Nuclear reactor can also produce 20kg of plutonium a year4. Both nuclear weapons and facilities must be closed for denuclearization goalVOICEOVER (in English): "A newly finished nuclear reactor in North Korea's Yongbyon complex has reportedly come online, after satellite images show its smokestack releasing emissions. "The North claims the reactor is meant to produce electricity for civilians, since it has the potential to create enough megawatts to power a small town.""Experts point out that the nuclear reactor can also be used to create 20 kilograms of plutonium a year to power its nuclear weapons.""To achieve complete denuclearization, the U.S. will have to persuade the North Koreans to give up not just their arsenal, but also facilities that produce nuclear fuel."SOURCES: New York Timeshttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2018/03/27/world/asia/north-korea-nuclear.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 05:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/29/3578618/3578618_096A588807344E96BAADED282914D7C5_180329_3578618_North_Korea_fires_up_new_nuclear_reactor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F49/E83/F49E838152C34F7E95802217D65A23FF_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, north korea, nuclear reactor, nuclear, nuclear weapons, trump kim talks, yongbyon nuclear complex, denuclearization, donald trump, kim jong un]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3579572</guid>
      <title>US general says country at risk from Russia and China hypersonic weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA U.S. general in charge of the country's nuclear arsenal said the nation currently has no defense against new hypersonic weapons being developed by the Chinese and Russians.Gen. John Hyten, the head of U.S. Strategic Command, said the weapons still need several years of development, but that without missile defense upgrades, the U.S. will be unable to detect them when they are operational, according to CNN. Hypersonic weapons travel at speeds over Mach 5, or 3,806 mph. Hypersonic missiles are launched into space, but then reenter the atmosphere and fly at high speeds on a flight path similar to an aircraft. The lower altitude trajectory make them more difficult for U.S. missile defense satellites and radars to pick them up.  Hyten said the U.S. would need to first upgrade its sensor capabilities as well as develop more effective interceptor missiles with more lethal warheads.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China and Russia are developing hypersonic weapons2. Russian hypersonic missile in flight 3. US upgrading sensor capabilities and more effective interceptorsVOICEOVER (in English): "A U.S. general in charge of the country's nuclear arsenal said the nation currently has no defense against new hypersonic weapons being developed by the Chinese and Russians.""The lower altitude trajectory make them more difficult for U.S. missile defense satellites and radars to pick them up."  "Hyten said the U.S. would need to first upgrade its sensor capabilities as well as develop more effective interceptor missiles with more lethal warheads."  SOURCES: CNNhttps://edition.cnn.com/2018/03/27/politics/general-hyten-hypersonic-weapon-threat/index.html***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 08:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/30/3579572/3579572_7098000E9AC74F478A0BEA5C7887DDEC_180330_3579572_US_general_says_country_at_risk_from_Russia_and__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AA3/D13/AA3D13AA32C24D08B5F2F5A4786D9B3B_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, News, hypersonic weapons, US hypersonic weapons, Russia hypersonic weapons, China hypersonic weapons, hypersonic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3579515</guid>
      <title>FIFA World Cup in Russia will be played on artificial turf</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANThe 2018 Fifa World Cup tournament in Russia will be played on artificial turf for the first time in soccer history, according to turf provider SIS Pitches. Artificial turf is made of synthetic blades in which layers of sand and performance infills are incorporated. Some systems also utilise a shock-absorbing layer underneath the turf.Artificial turf is weather-resistant and does not need sunlight, and is therefore more cost-efficient compared to natural grass. FIFA requirements ensure the turf being used meet playing performance, safety, durability and quality assurance standards. FIFA awards the FIFA Quality mark to turf that meet the standard for amateur pitches, and awards the FIFA Quality Pro mark to turf that been shown to provide the highest playing performance for professional level football.In total, six of the 12 stadiums in Russia to host the games at this summer's World Cup will be outfitted with artificial turf. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Show artificial turf composition2. Show the turf is weather-resistant and more cost-efficient than natural grass3. Show FIFA has requirements to ensure the turf has a certain standards4. Show FIFA Quality mark for amateur pitches and FIFA Quality Pro mark for professional pitchesVOICEOVER (in English): "Artificial turf is made of synthetic blades in which layers of sand and performance infills are incorporated. Some systems also utilise a shock-absorbing layer underneath the turf.""Artificial turf is weather-resistant and does not need sunlight, and is therefore is more cost-efficient compared to natural grass.""FIFA requirements ensure the turf being used meet playing performance, safety, durability and quality assurance standards.""FIFA awards the FIFA Quality mark to turf that meet the standard for amateur pitches, and awards the FIFA Quality Pro mark to turf that been shown to provide the highest playing performance for professional level football."SOURCES: https://football-technology.fifa.com/en/media-tiles/about-football-turfhttps://football-technology.fifa.com/en/media-tiles/fifa-quality-programme-for-football-turfhttps://www.sispitches.com/your-sport/football-pitcheshttp://www.in-cumbria.com/news/Maryport-firm-is-pitch-perfect-49bdcbf4-fe2b-4d4c-b2cb-0f9df5e6d33b-ds***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 07:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/30/3579515/3579515_5E4F6FCF07674BA699D76C81729449AE_180330_3579515_FIFA_World_Cup_in_Russia_will_be_played_on_artif_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/63B/EB4/63BEB41FAD9F49579C1187C2B94D0AB6_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, artificial turfs, artificial turfs soccer, artificial turfs football, artificial turfs world cup, artificial pitch, artificial football pitch, russia world cup pitch]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3579424</guid>
      <title>Man in UK suffering from super-gonorrhoea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For story suggestions or custom animation requests, contact tips@nextanimation.com.tw. Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com to view News Direct's complete archive of 3D news animations.RESTRICTIONS: Broadcast: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWAN Digital: NO USE JAPAN, NO USE TAIWANA man has been diagnosed with a severe case of super-gonorrhea that is resistant to first choice antibiotics. The man picked up the sexually transmitted disease after a sexual encounter with a woman in southeast Asia, according to the BBC. Public Health England says it's the first time the infection was unable to be treated with a combination of azithromycin and ceftriaxone antibiotics. Officials from the World Health Organization and the European Centers for Disease Control say this is a first for the world. The infection is caused by the bacterium Neisseria gonorrhea. It's spread through unprotected sex.Symptoms can include a thick green or yellow discharge from sexual organs, pain urinating and bleeding between periods.If left untreated, it can cause infertility, pelvic inflammatory disease and can be spread to children during pregnancy. Physicians now have the man on one last antibiotic, but will have to wait till next month to see if it worked at combating the infection.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Man being diagnosed with super-gonorrhea2. First choice antibiotics were ineffective against super-gonorrhea3. Gonorrhea symptoms4. Complications caused by untreated gonorrheaVOICEOVER (in English): "A man in the U.K. has been diagnosed with the world's "worst-ever" case of super-gonorrhea that is resistant to first choice antibiotics. The man picked it up after a sexual encounter with a woman in southeast Asia.""Health officials say it's the first time the infection was unable to be treated with a combination of azithromycin and ceftriaxone antibiotics." "The infection is caused by the bacterium Neisseria gonorrhea. It's spread through unprotected sex. Symptoms can include a thick green or yellow discharge from sexual organs, pain urinating and bleeding between periods.""If left untreated, it can cause infertility, pelvic inflammatory disease and can be spread to children during pregnancy." SOURCES: BBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/health-43571120***]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 05:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/18/03/30/3579424/3579424_8A5670635E2D499FB7A480264EA2EABC_180330_3579424_Man_in_UK_suffering_from_super_gonorrhoea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/928/F2D/928F2DD60B3D44E1B36CDD535BF349EC_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, gonorrhoea, super gonorrhoea, azithromycin-resistant gonorrhea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
