<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 19:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3474258</guid>
      <title>World's largest aircraft set to fly luxury tourist trips</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe world's largest aircraft  the Airlander 10  is set to be tested by travel company Henry Cookson Adventures to take tourists on exotic trips around the world. British aerospace company Hybrid Air Vehicles (HAV) is the maker of the Airlander 10. It announced that Henry Cookson Adventures (HCA) will become the first private company to trial the Airlander 10 next year, News Atlas reported. The aircraft is powered by four 325-hp turbocharged diesel engines and uses aerodynamic lift like a fixed-wing aircraft to take off. Helium keeps the Airlander in the air. The airship can carry payloads of up to 10,000 kg and stay in the air for five days at a time with a crew. It also doesn't require a runway.The passenger version of the Airlander 10 is expected to be able to cruise at 80 knots at an altitude of up to 20,000 feet. The Airlander 10 is currently still in its test-flight phase and looking to gain airworthiness certification.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Airlander 10 flying over the Grand Canyon2. The Airlander 10 taking off3. The Airlander 10 can carry up to 10,000 kg and stay in air for five days at a time4. The Airlander 10 can travel at 80 knots at an altitude up to 20,000 feetVOICEOVER (in English): "The world's largest aircraft  the Airlander 10  made by Hybrid Air Vehicles is set to be tested by travel company Henry Cookson Adventures to take tourists on exotic trips around the world." "The aircraft is powered by four 325-hp turbocharged diesel engines and uses aerodynamic lift like a fixed-wing aircraft to take off. Helium keeps the Airlander in the air." "The airship can carry payloads of up to 10,000 kg and stay in the air for five days at a time with a crew. It also doesn't require a runway." "The passenger version of the Airlander 10 is expected to be able to cruise at 80 knots at an altitude of up to 20,000 feet." SOURCES: Telegraph, New Atlashttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/10/26/away-britains-21st-century-airship-company-prepares-launch-new/https://newatlas.com/airlander-10-tourists/51933/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 05:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/01/3474258/3474258_5F92D93548F44512A18E0D51351B6928_171101_3474258_World_s_largest_aircraft_set_to_fly_luxury_touri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C6E/5C0/C6E5C0B2CDF24B7D8746536BC18E47E9_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, airships, world's largest aircraft, Hybrid Air Vehicles, Airlander 10]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3474205</guid>
      <title>New York truck attack kills eight in lower Manhattan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEEight people were killed and 11 others seriously injured Tuesday, when a man deliberately drove a rented truck onto a bike path near World Trade Center in lower Manhattan before crashing into a school bus.The suspect then jumped out of the truck and shouted "Allahu Akbar" before firing a BB or pellet gun, authorities said, according to NBC News. A police officer on patrol in the area returned fire, hitting the suspect in the abdomen. The suspect was taken into custody and transported to the hospital for treatment, according to CNN. The attacker was identified as 29-year-old Uzbek immigrant Sayfullo Habibullaevic Saipov. Officials say he entered the country in 2010. The attack began at 3:05 p.m. when Saipov drove a Home Depot rental truck onto a bike path on West Street near Houston Street.He exited the bike path when he collided with a school bus at Chambers Street, said Police Commissioner James O'Neill, according to NBC News. There were two adults and two children on the bus, O'Neill said. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Location of the truck attack2. The truck driving onto the bike path3. The truck running into the school bus4. The suspect was firing a pellet or BB gun VOICEOVER (in English): "Eight people were killed and 11 others seriously injured Tuesday, when a man deliberately drove a rented truck onto a bike path in lower Manhattan before crashing into a school bus.""The attack began at 3:05 p.m. when the suspect, a 29-year-old Uzbek immigrant, drove a Home Depot rental truck onto a bike path on West Street near Houston Street.""Saipov exited the bike path when he collided with a school bus at Chambers Street. The school bus was carrying two children and two adults." "The suspect then jumped out of the truck and shouted "Allahu Akbar" before firing a BB or pellet gun. A police officer on patrol in the area returned fire, hitting the suspect in the abdomen." SOURCES: NBC News, CNN, CBS Newshttps://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/nyc-terrorist-attack/least-one-person-dead-incident-lower-manhattan-n816166http://edition.cnn.com/2017/10/31/us/new-york-shots-fired/index.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-york-city-terror-attack-truck-crash-lower-manhattan-live-updates/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 04:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/01/3474205/3474205_CADB1F1084A84763AB02E0DE0FFD6DDC_171101_3474205_New_York_truck_attack_kills_eight_in_lower_Manha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/859/D77/859D770AAF244CC388FEFA38D4F3314E_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, NYC truck attack, New York City truck attack, NYC terror attack, Sayfullo Haibibullaevic Saipov]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3474178</guid>
      <title>World's first trackless smart train launched in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONE A city in China has launched a test run for a futuristic urban transport system that's being called the world's first 'smart train'.Described as a cross between a train, tram, and bus, the Autonomous Rail Rapid Transit is a 32-meter electric vehicle that runs at a maximum speed of 70 kilometers per hour, according to Xinhua News.The ART is equipped with sensors to help it read road dimensions as it travels along a virtual track made up of dotted white lines painted on the road.The 'smart train' has three carriages, and is capable of carrying up to 300 passengers.The self-driving system uses rubber tires instead of steel wheels, and can travel up to 25 kilometers after a 10-minute charge.At the moment, the train traverses a 3.1-kilometer route, traveling through four stations in the city of Zhuzhou, in the country's Hunan province.A longer route is being planned, with the transport system aiming to eventually expand to other cities.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. China's Smart Train is a cross between a train, tram, and bus2. Train equipped with sensors, moves along virtual railway tracks3. Smart train can fit up to 300 passengers4. Train can travel 25km after a 10-minute chargeVOICEOVER (in English): "Described as a cross between a train, tram, and bus, the Autonomous Rail Rapid Transit is a 32-meter electric vehicle that runs at a maximum speed of 70 kilometers per hour.""The ART is equipped with sensors to help it read road dimensions as it travels along a virtual track made up of dotted white lines painted on the road."train' has three carriages, and is capable of carrying up to 300 passengers.""The self-driving system uses rubber tires instead of steel wheels, and can travel up to 25 kilometers after a 10-minute charge."SOURCES: Xinhua, Channel News Asiahttp://news.xinhuanet.com/english/2017-10/24/c_136702282.htmhttp://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asiapacific/electric-trackless-trains-launched-in-china-9356606***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 03:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/01/3474178/3474178_9BFAD5671C794EC2AB82E73CFD604178_171101_3474178_World_s_first_trackless_smart_train_launched_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3C6/43E/3C643EA5896C43CBB412E7AE6C68664A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, smart train, china train, ART, autonomous rail rapid transit, train, public transportation, china transportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3475014</guid>
      <title>New York truck attack suspect charged with terrorism offenses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe suspect in Tuesday's truck attack, which left eight people dead in lower Manhattan, has been charged with federal terrorism offenses.  Sayfullo Habibullaevic Saipov, a 29-year-old Uzbekistan native, is charged with providing material support to ISIS and violence and destruction of motor vehicles, acting US Attorney for the Southern District of New York said, according to CNN.Saipov told authorities he was inspired by ISIS videos, a federal criminal complaint stated. Officials said he began planning the attack a year ago and decided to use a truck two months ago. Law enforcement discovered around 90 ISIS propaganda videos, as well as 4,000 images, many of which were ISIS-related on Saipov's cellphone, according to the FBI.   Saipov came into the U.S. from Uzbekistan in 2010 on a diversity immigrant visa, according to the Department of Homeland Security. He was living in Paterson, New Jersey with his wife and three children. A little over six months ago, he became an Uber driver, passing their background check.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The location of the truck attack2. Saipov entering the country on a diversity immigrant visa3. Saipov was living in New Jersey and working as an Uber driver4. ISIS videos and images were found on the suspect's phoneVOICEOVER (in English): "Suspect Sayfullo Saipov has been charged with providing material support to ISIS and violence and destruction of motor vehicles in Tuesday's truck attack which left eight people dead.""Saipov came into the U.S. from Uzbekistan in 2010 on a diversity immigrant visa." "He was living in Paterson, New Jersey with his wife and three children. About six months ago, he became an Uber driver, passing their background check."   "Saipov told authorities he was inspired by ISIS videos. Around 90 ISIS propaganda videos and 4,000 images, mainly ISIS-related were found on the suspect's cellphone."SOURCES: CNN, BBChttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/01/us/new-york-attack/index.htmlhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-41829264***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 06:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/02/3475014/3475014_45284E8F712447DCBDCFF21419956B8F_171102_3475014_New_York_truck_attack_suspect_charged_with_terro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/40A/679/40A6792837A84AF58DDD507C55812237_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, New York terror attack, New York truck attack, Sayfullo Haibibullaevic Saipov, truck attack suspect charged, terrorism charges]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3475004</guid>
      <title>New research suggests Alzheimer's originates outside the brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists have long assumed that Alzheimer's starts in the brain, but new research suggests that might not be the case.According to AAAS, patients with Alzheimer's disease have abnormal deposits of amyloid beta protein in their brain, which smothers the cells and impairs nerve and memory function.Amyloid beta protein can be found in other organs apart from the brain, though because of the blood-brain barrier, the amyloid responsible for Alzheimer's was generally believed to only originate in the brain.To see if this theory was true, researchers at the University of British Columbia used parabiosis to attach a normal mouse to one with high amyloid beta levels. They found that the protein was able to travel to the normal mouse's brain, accumulating and beginning to cause damage. In just 12 months, the normal mouse had effectively 'contracted' Alzheimer's.Scientists suggest that as the blood-brain barrier weakens with age, more amyloid-beta may infiltrate the brain, and contribute to its deterioration.The findings indicate that future drugs might be able to halt the disease by targeting the toxic protein before it ever reaches the brain.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. What Alzheimer's does to the brain2. Amyloid protein responsible for Alzheimer's found in brain and other organs3. Normal mouse attached to mouse with high amyloid protein contracted Alzheimer's4. Blood-brain barrier may weaken with age, causing more amyloid protein to enter brainVOICEOVER (in English): "Patients with Alzheimer's disease have abnormal deposits of amyloid beta protein in their brain, which smothers the cells and impairs nerve and memory function.""Amyloid beta protein can be found in other organs apart from the brain, though because of the blood-brain barrier, the amyloid responsible for Alzheimer's was believed to only originate in the brain.""When researchers used parabiosis to attach a normal mouse to one with high amyloid beta levels, the protein traveled to the normal mouse's brain, effectively causing the animal to 'contract' Alzheimer's in just 12 months.""Scientists suggest that as the blood-brain barrier weakens with age, more amyloid-beta may infiltrate the brain, and contribute to its deterioration."SOURCES: American Association for the Advancement of Science, Medical News Todayhttps://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2017-10/uobc-adm102717.phphttps://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/319928.php***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 06:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/02/3475004/3475004_0C4FCF2D1C734B358F7AD6F26DCBDA31_171102_3475004_New_research_suggests_Alzheimer_s_originates_out_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8D4/336/8D4336598F87408AB65DE1C63228EB51_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, alzheimer's, alzheimers, dementia, alzheimer's cure, amyloid protein, amyloid beta, amyloid beta protein, brain plaque, parabiosis, blood brain barrier]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3475949</guid>
      <title>Big void detected inside Great Pyramid at Giza</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEArchaeologists have identified an empty cavity in Egypt's Great Pyramid, marking the first discovery of a new internal structure in over two hundred years.BBC reports that a nearly 100-feet long void was discovered inside the Great Pyramid in Giza, just above the 153-foot long Grand Gallery.The void was detected using cosmic ray muons, which are high-energy particles that shower the Earth. Muons pass through empty spaces easily, but can be absorbed or deflected by dense materials like solid rock.Three different muography technologies used to measure muons in the pyramid all detected the same void in the same position.But because the technique is low resolution, it's difficult to determine the exact shape or function of the void.Researchers speculate that the void could be one large empty space, or several small ones, possibility used to relieve pressure on the chambers below.The void will need to be investigated further if we want to know what it actually is. Scientists are already considering drilling a small hole and sending in a tiny robot to hopefully get some answers.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Big void discovered inside the Great Pyramid2. Void detected using cosmic ray muons, which pass through empty spaces, but are absorbed or deflected by solid objects3. Three different muography technologies all detected the same void4. Void could be a big empty chamber or several small ones, possibly for pressure-relieving purposesVOICEOVER (in English): "A nearly 100-foot long void was discovered inside the Great Pyramid in Giza, just above the 153-foot long Grand Gallery.""The void was detected using cosmic ray muons, which are high-energy particles that shower the Earth. Muons pass through empty spaces easily, but can be absorbed or deflected by dense materials like solid rock.""Three different muography technologies used to measure muons in the pyramid all detected the same void in the same position.""Researchers speculate that the void could be one large empty space, or several small ones, possibility used to relieve pressure on the chambers below."SOURCES: National Geographic, BBChttps://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/11/great-pyramid-giza-void-discovered-khufu-archaeology-science/http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-41845445***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 09:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/03/3475949/3475949_1DC5D84C053C4010B56237BD7A60B3C1_171103_3475949_Big_void_detected_inside_Great_Pyramid_at_Giza_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/884/19D/88419D15347448049853BB715096BEBD_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, pyramid, great pyramid, giza, void, big void, cosmic ray muons, muons, khufu, pharaoh khufu]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3475707</guid>
      <title>Chemotherapy harms fertility of female cancer patients' grandchildren, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChemotherapy can significantly harm the fertility of female cancer patients' children, new research has shown. Researchers at the University of Utah found the offspring of women who had treatment before becoming pregnant had a 70 percent worse chance of having a child themselves, the Telegraph reported. The effects of chemotherapy drugs has been well documented, but this is the first study to find a negative effect inherited by the next generation. Scientists believe the chemotherapy medication may be altering the genetic expression of inherited germ line cells.Male cancer patients did not pass on the same effect to their offspring, most likely because sperm constantly regenerates, while a woman has all her eggs at birth. Women of reproductive age being treated for cancer are increasingly being encouraged to preserve their eggs cryogenically. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman receiving chemotherapy2. Study found offspring of mothers who had chemotherapy before pregnancy were affected3. Chemotherapy drugs affecting genetic expression4. Eggs being cryogenically frozenVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study has found chemotherapy can significantly harm the fertility of female cancer patients' grandchildren." "Researchers at the University of Utah found the offspring of women who had treatment before becoming pregnant had a 70 percent worse chance of having a child themselves.""Scientists believe the chemotherapy medication may be altering the genetic expression of inherited germ line cells.""Women of reproductive age being treated for cancer are increasingly being encouraged to preserve their eggs cryogenically." SOURCES: The Telegraphhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/11/01/chemotherapy-harms-fertility-female-cancer-patients-grandchildren/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/03/3475707/3475707_5B5C7C1F56464E4F8BF12F9E027F4C9A_171103_3475707_Chemotherapy_harms_fertility_of_female_cancer_pa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/065/A64/065A643ED0E54C6484D064ACB44D3655_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cancer treatments, chemotherapy, chemotherapy side effects, chemotherapy affects female patient grandchildren]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3475651</guid>
      <title>Microchips could be the way of the future</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA tech festival in Melbourne is shining the spotlight on microchips, implanting the 'injectables' into 10 volunteers who will personally test them out.According to The Guardian, the microchip is roughly the size of a grain of rice, and is capable of holding only one access code and limited information.The tiny device is typically injected in between the thumb and forefinger, using a needle as thick as those used in body piercings.Each microchip uses NFC or near-field communication to unlock a specific door, vehicle, or device.The volunteers' chips come preloaded with a 30-day VIP pass for Pause Fest, and will be programmed to unlock the door to their home, gym or work. Alternatively, it can also function as a public transportation pass.When the festival finally comes around in February 2018, the ten volunteers will join a panel and talk about whether they found the chip useful.Developers are already working on a model of microchips that can store multiple access codes, and even be able to handle payments.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Current microchips the size of a rice grain can only store one access code, limited information2. Microchips injected between thumb and forefinger3. Each microchip can be programmed to unlock a specific door or device4. Future microchips can hold multiple access codes and handle paymentsVOICEOVER (in English): "The microchip is roughly the size of a grain of rice, and is capable of holding only one access code and limited information.""The tiny device is typically injected in between the thumb and forefinger, using a needle as thick as those used in body piercings.""Each microchip uses NFC or near-field communication to unlock a specific door, vehicle, or device.""Developers are already working on a model of microchips that can store multiple access codes, and even be able to handle payments."SOURCES: The Guardianhttps://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/nov/01/under-the-skin-how-insertable-microchips-could-unlock-the-future#img-2***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 02:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/03/3475651/3475651_C59A4AB0F6D4484589A7D85026CFBB58_171103_3475651_Microchips_could_be_the_way_of_the_future_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/91A/C4C/91AC4C016270433D81BDA2F2A0DB7C5A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, microchips, microchip, NFC microchip, NFC chip, NFC, chip implant, microchip implant, chip injection, injectables, injectibles, tech festival, Pause Festival, Pause Festival 2018, melbourne tech festival]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3475647</guid>
      <title>Iceland's biggest volcano hit by 4 tremors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Bardarbunga volcano in Iceland was hit by a series of four earthquakes last week.University of Iceland Geophysics Professor Pll Einarsson told British tabloid the Daily Star that the volcano is getting ready to erupt in the next few years.  The volcano is in a normal, non-eruptive state, reported the Daily Star, citing the Icelandic Meteorological Office. When the Eyjafjallajokull volcano erupted in 2010 it caused massive flight chaos, grounding most air traffic to and from Europe for several days.  The ash cloud from that eruption reached nearly 10,000 meters high, meaning planes in the impacted area were unable to fly, reported the BBC.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Bardarbunga volcano2. 2010 eruption ash cloud on globe3. 2010 eruption ash cloud heightVOICEOVER (in English): "The Bardarbunga volcano in Iceland was hit by a series of four earthquakes recently.""University of Iceland Geophysics Professor Pll Einarsson told British tabloid the Daily Star that the volcano is getting ready to erupt in the next few years.""Iceland authorities say the volcano is in a normal, non-eruptive state.""When the Eyjafjallajokull volcano erupted in 2010 it caused massive flight chaos, grounding most air traffic to and from Europe for several days.  "The ash cloud from that eruption reached nearly 10,000 meters high, meaning planes in the impacted area were unable to fly."SOURCES: Daily Star, Yahoo, BBC, Reutershttps://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/656398/iceland-bardarbunga-volcano-eruption-four-earthquakes-2010-eyjafjallaj-kullhttps://uk.news.yahoo.com/icelands-biggest-volcano-erupt-struck-series-earthquakes-144553408.htmlhttp://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/science/nature/8629609.stmhttp://graphics.thomsonreuters.com/RNGS/2010/APR/ASH2.jpg***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 02:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/03/3475647/3475647_DDDC025FEE70497B8FB2019AA9DA660A_171103_3475647_Iceland_s_biggest_volcano_hit_by_4_tremors_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/226/018/2260189995B24ED09B8F5D2AADDBE2C9_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Bardarbunga, Eyjafjallajokull, iceland volcanoes, flights and ashcloud]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3477660</guid>
      <title>North Korea maybe readying for new missile test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENorth Korea maybe preparing for another missile test, South Korean intelligence told Seoul lawmakers last Thursday.Seoul points to increased vehicular movement around a missile research base in Pyongyang as evidence of this, reported Reuters. North Korea last carried out a test in September 2017 at its underground facility in Punggye-ri. That reportedly resulted in an earthquake and several aftershocks.Last week Japanese media outlet TV Asahi reported this created a tunnel collapse and the deaths of 200 people, according to CNN. Pyongyang said this was fake news.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. South Korea and North Korea on map2. Depiction of vehicle movement inside North Korea3. Depiction of North Korea's Punggye-ri test site4. Depiction of explosion and earthquake in Punggye-ri.VOICEOVER (in English): "South Korean intelligence told the country's lawmakers last Thursday that North Korea is making preparations for another missile test.""Seoul points to increased vehicular movement around a missile research base in Pyongyang as evidence of this." "North Korea last carried out a test in September of this year at its underground facility in Punggye-ri.""That reportedly resulted in an earthquake and several aftershocks." "Last week Japanese media outlet TV Asahi reported this created a tunnel collapse and killed 200 people." "However, Pyongyang called this report fake news."SOURCES: CNN, Reutershttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/02/asia/south-korea-north-korea-nuclear-test/index.htmlhttps://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-northkorea-missiles-southkorea/south-korea-spy-agency-sees-signs-of-planned-new-missile-test-by-north-idUKKBN1D20YI***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 08:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/06/3477660/3477660_298AD629309947859C6C1AEF94960B11_171106_3477660_North_Korea_maybe_readying_for_new_missile_test_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FA8/BA2/FA8BA22683834B4AB7198BB46CC03A61_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, kim jong un, donald trump, missile test, dprk, missile test fail, trump in asia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3477592</guid>
      <title>Texas church shooting leaves at least 26 dead, 20 wounded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA church shooting in Sutherland Springs, Texas on Sunday has left 26 people dead and 20 wounded, authorities said. The shooter was a white male dressed in all-black tactical gear and a ballistic vest, according to CNN. He has been identified as Devin Kelley of New Braunfels, ABC New reported. Kelly entered the First Baptist Church and opened fire with a Ruger AR rifle around 11:20 a.m. before fleeing the scene in an SUV, said Wilson County Sheriff Joe Tackitt, according to KSAT. As Kelly was attempting to leave, a local resident used a rifle to engage him. The shooter then fled the church, according to CNN.After a short car chase, authorities found the suspected shooter dead from a gunshot wound inside his truck. Officials are still trying to determine Kelly's cause of death.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Shooter dressed in tactical gear, ballistic vest and armed with Ruger AR rifle2. Shooter entering church3. Shooter fleeing the scene4. Shooter was found dead of a gunshot woundVOICEOVER (in English): "The shooter was a white male armed with a Ruger AR rifle, dressed in all-black tactical gear and a ballistic vest. He has been identified as 26-year-old Devin Kelley of New Braunfels.""Kelly entered the First Baptist Church and opened fire with a Ruger AR rifle around 11:20 a.m., killing at least 26 people and injuring 20 others." "The shooter then fled the scene after exchanging fire with a local resident armed with a rifle.""After a short car chase, authorities found the suspected shooter dead from a gunshot wound inside his truck. Officials are still trying to determine Kelly's cause of death." SOURCES: KSAT, CNN, BBChttps://www.ksat.com/news/shooting-sutherland-springs-church-gunfire-mass-shooting-airlifehttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/05/us/texas-church-shooting/index.htmlhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-41880511***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 07:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/06/3477592/3477592_3664559A6DBA456081A173B456A8A706_171106_3477592_Texas_church_shooting_leaves_at_least_26_dead__2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1F2/EA2/1F2EA2D783CB476EA2C0B017E883AD2D_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Texas church shooting, church shooting, First Baptist Church Sutherland Springs, mass shooting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3477500</guid>
      <title>Ozone hole over Antarctica shrinks to smallest since 1988</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA announced on Thursday that the hole in the Earth's ozone is the smallest it's been for the last 29 years, though not because toxic emissions have gone down.According to NASA, the ozone hole that formed over Antarctica this year measured 7.6 million square miles at its maximum peak on September 11, and is as small as it has been since 1988.Ozone molecules shield the Earth from the sun's UV radiation, but are being depleted by man-made chemicals like bromine and chlorine that are released into the atmosphere.The hole in the ozone has been growing larger over the years, measuring more than 11 million square miles at its highest.Ozone deteriorates more quickly in colder temperatures, and in the presence of polar stratospheric clouds that encourage ozone-eating chemical reactions.This year's weak depletion is largely due to stormy conditions in the upper atmosphere, which warmed temperatures and kept toxic chemicals from destroying the ozone.While the small ozone hole resulted from mostly natural causes, steady improvements such as the banning of ozone-eating chemicals in a 1987 international treaty may have also contributed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ozone hole over Antarctica smallest since 19882. Ozone being depleted by manmade chemicals like bromine and chlorine3. Ozone deteriorates more quickly in colder temperatures4. Smaller ozone hole resulted from a warm winterVOICEOVER (in English): "The ozone hole that formed over Antarctica this year measured 7.6 million square miles at its maximum peak, and is as small as it has been since 1988.""Ozone molecules shield the Earth from the sun's UV radiation, but are being depleted by man-made chemicals like bromine and chlorine that are released into the atmosphere.""Ozone deteriorates more quickly in colder temperatures, and in the presence of polar stratospheric clouds that encourage ozone-eating chemical reactions.""This year's weak depletion is largely due to stormy conditions in the upper atmosphere, which warmed temperatures and kept toxic chemicals from destroying the ozone."SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2017/warm-air-helped-make-2017-ozone-hole-smallest-since-1988***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 05:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/06/3477500/3477500_033E2EAA3B004E4A983B88895A71B392_171106_3477500_Ozone_hole_over_Antarctica_shrinks_to_smallest_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7A5/6D3/7A56D3DFD0D6478090BB6FC811104AC8_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ozone hole, ozone layer, ozone depletion, ozone, global warming, antarctica, warm winter, climate change, UV radiation, sun protection, toxic emissions, emissions, chlorine, bromine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3478514</guid>
      <title>U.S. airline passenger passenger seats are shrinking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe airline interior industry is worth $17 billion and growing, while airline seats are shrinking. Over time, the average width of airline seating on U.S. flights has gradually shrunk, despite the weight of the average American going up, reported the New York Times.Airlines have also decreased pitch, the legroom and space between seating rows, in a bid to accommodate more passengers on flights. Some seating manufacturers have also reduced the thickness of seats.The airline interiors industry is said to be worth $17 billion dollars, and is expected to grow in the coming decade, reported the Economist, citing the Los Angeles Times.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of seat width shrinking.2. Depiction of seat pitch shrinking.3. Airline interior industryVOICEOVER (in English): "Over time, the average width of airline seating on US has gradually shrunk, despite the weight of the average American going up.""Airlines have also decreased the space between rows in a bid to accommodate more passengers on flights."Some eating manufacturers have also reduced the thickness of seats, by removing foam and using other materials.""The airline interiors industry is said to be worth $17 billion dollars, and is expected to grow in the coming decade." SOURCES: New York Times, Economist, Los Angeles Timeshttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/11/06/business/airline-seat.htmlhttps://www.economist.com/blogs/gulliver/2017/10/squeezy-jethttp://beta.latimes.com/business/la-fi-airline-seats-20171001-story.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 10:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/07/3478514/3478514_3E049D9FC4A9418BA2E90CA9E2A20E68_171107_3478514_U_S__airline_passenger_passenger_seats_are_shrin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C21/86E/C2186E0B9D6246F2B87550325FB16452_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, shrinking airline seats, smaller airline seats, more people on planes, smaller seats on planes, airline seating, airline travel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3478336</guid>
      <title>Astronomers find new 'Monster' planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearch led by the University of Warwick has led to the discovery of a giant planet located 600 light years from Earth.Named NGTS-1b, the celestial body is a gas giant around the same size Jupiter. It orbits a star half the size of the Sun."Researchers say this is the largest planet compared to the size of its companion star ever discovered.NGTS-1b orbits the star a 3% of the distance between Earth and the sun. As such, it holds a temperature of 530 degrees centigrade and orbit its star every 2.6 days.The discovery challenges 'formation theory' which posits smaller stars can smaller stars can only form rocky planets, not gas giants.The findings will are set to be reported in Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of planet in space2. Comparison between planet and jupiter3. Planet orbiting star4. Temperature of planetVOICEOVER (in English): "Named NGTS-1b, the celestial body is a gas giant around the same size Jupiter. It orbits a star half the size of the Sun.""Researchers say this is the largest planet compared to the size of its companion star ever discovered.""NGTS-1b orbits the star a 3% of the distance between Earth and the sun.""As such, it holds a temperature of 530 degrees centigrade and orbit its star every 2.6 days.""The discovery challenges 'formation theory' which posits smaller stars can only form rocky planets, not gas giants."SOURCES: University of Warwick, Sci-Newshttps://warwick.ac.uk/newsandevents/pressreleases/monster_planet_discovery/http://www.sci-news.com/astronomy/ngts-1b-hot-jupiter-05385.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 07:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/07/3478336/3478336_AFECFD12DA834C70BB24EA27B9903915_171107_3478336_Astronomers_find_new__Monster__planet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EAA/B88/EAAB88AEC9344551A14577F234525735_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, exoplanet 2017, monster planet, NGTS-1b, formation theory, university of warwick]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3478294</guid>
      <title>Largest ever tropical reforestation wants to plant 73 million trees</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA project in the Amazon rainforest is using a new technique to plant trees in the largest ever tropical reforestation. Conservation International plans to restore 70,000 acres of land cleared for grazing with 73 million trees, Fast Company reported.The trees will be planted in the "arc of deforestation" that stretches across the Brazilian states of Amazonas, Acre, Par and Rondnia, as well as the Xingu watershed. The planting method is called muvuca, which is Portuguese for a small place with many people. The muvuca method involves spreading hundreds of native tree seeds of various species over deforested land. Natural selection then allows the most suited trees to grow and thrive in a much thicker density than plant-by-plant reforestation. Plant-by-plant techniques usually have a density of 160 plants per hectare, while with muvuca, the density is 2,500 species per hectare. Scientists believe after 10 years, it could reach 5,000 trees per hectare.    RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Deforested area being reforested2. The trees are going to be planted in the arc of deforestation3. The project uses the muvuca planting technique4. The muvuca process produces higher tree densities per hectare VOICEOVER (in English): "Conservation International plans to restore 70,000 acres of land cleared for grazing with 73 million trees in the Brazilian Amazon.""The trees will be planted in the "arc of deforestation" that stretches across the Brazilian states of Amazonas, Acre, Par and Rondnia, as well as the Xingu watershed." "The planting method is called muvuca, which is Portuguese for a small place with many people. It involves spreading hundreds of native tree seeds of various species over deforested land." "Plant-by-plant reforestation techniques usually have a density of 160 plants per hectare, while with muvuca, density is 2,500 species per hectare. Scientists believe after 10 years, it could reach 5,000 trees per hectare."    SOURCES: Fast Company, Inhabitat https://www.fastcompany.com/40481305/the-largest-ever-tropical-reforestation-is-planting-73-million-treeshttps://inhabitat.com/73-million-trees-to-be-planted-in-largest-reforestation-project-ever-undertaken/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 07:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/07/3478294/3478294_76ADAA488CE6416692A084A2B60CF85D_171107_3478294_Largest_ever_tropical_reforestation_wants_to_pla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/035/0D6/0350D6D839824C7DB9B346B18D509933_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Amazon, reforestation, reforestation project, muvuca planting method, muvuca]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3478287</guid>
      <title>Finnair begins weighing passengers before flights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFinland's largest airline is now weighing its passengers, but not for the reason you might be thinking.BBC reports that Finnish flag carrier Finnair has begun conducting voluntary passenger weigh-ins at Helsinki airport. Only 180 have volunteered so far, but the airline hopes to weigh as many as 2,000.The aim of the weigh-ins is to update the estimates being used to calculate total weight, since this is used to forecast payload and fuel consumption.Finnair is currently relying on 2009 data from the European Aviation Safety Agency, which lists 85 kilos as the standard weight for males, 67 kilos for females, and 31 for children under 12.But these weights often vary under certain conditions. Men in first class tend to weigh more than average, while the opposite is true for females. Carry-on luggage weight also fluctuates, and is heavier in winter than in summer.Finnair claims surveying its mix of travellers will generate more accurate data that's specific to their airline. It plans to continue with the weigh-ins through Spring 2018.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Finnair conducting voluntary weigh-ins at Helsinki airport2. Weigh-ins aim to update estimates on passenger weight3. Finnair currently using 2009 data from EASA4. Weight varies under certain conditionsVOICEOVER (in English): "Finnish flag carrier Finnair has begun conducting voluntary passenger weigh-ins at Helsinki airport. Only 180 have volunteered so far, but the airline hopes to weigh as many as 2,000. ""The aim of the weigh-ins is to update the estimates being used to calculate total weight, since this is used to forecast payload and fuel consumption.""Finnair is currently relying on 2009 data from the European Aviation Safety Agency, which lists 85 kilos as the standard weight for males, 67 kilos for females, and 31 for children under 12.""But these weights often vary under certain conditions. Men in first class tend to weigh more than average, while the opposite is true for females. Carry-on luggage weight also fluctuates, and is heavier in winter than in summer."SOURCES: BBC, CNBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/business-41835933https://www.cnbc.com/2017/11/02/forget-your-checked-luggage-this-airline-is-weighing-passengers.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 07:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/07/3478287/3478287_0764F6AA6CE54261A83C708F263C2587_171107_3478287_Finnair_begins_weighing_passengers_before_flight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A23/53D/A2353D99AE1845D295AA817FCE0423FA_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, finnair, weigh ins, passenger weight, airline weight, EASA, finland airline, fuel, payload, luggage, luggage weight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3478221</guid>
      <title>What are the Paradise Papers?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA massive new trove of leaked records is shining light on how the world's richest are sheltering their wealth offshore.The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists reports that the Paradise Papers are a leak of 13.4 million papers covering people's finances from 1950 to 2016, mostly from offshore law firm Appleby and the company registries of 19 tax havens.Appleby's clients include both people and companies, from countries like the UK, China, and Hong Kong. The majority, however, are from the U.S., numbering at least 30,000.The leaked documents detail how firms like Appleby help clients stash money and assets in offshore tax havens, to avoid paying high taxes.The expos comes from the same German newspaper that outed last year's Panama Papers, and reveals the secret dealings of numerous individuals and companies, including the Queen of England, and Facebook.The Queen's private estate had invested nearly 10 million pounds in a Cayman Islands fund, some of which had gone to a company accused of exploiting the poor.Facebook and Twitter, meanwhile, received investments that were traced to Russian state institutions. The funds had gone through a business associate of Trump adviser and son-in-law Jared Kushner.Most of these transactions and accounts are perfectly legal, but whether they are fair or moral is another matter entirely.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 13.4 million documents leaked from Appleby and tax haven registries2. Largest number of clients are from the US3. Documents detail how people and companies stash money in offshore tax havens to avoid paying high taxesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Paradise Papers are a leak of 13.4 million papers covering people's finances from 1950 to 2016, mostly from offshore law firm Appleby and the company registries of 19 tax havens.""Appleby's clients include both people and companies, from countries like the UK, China, and Hong Kong. The majority, however, are from the U.S., numbering at least 30,000.""The leaked documents detail how firms like Appleby help clients stash money and assets in offshore tax havens, to avoid paying high taxes."SOURCES: International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, The Guardian, BBChttps://www.icij.org/blog/2017/790/icij-releases-paradise-papers/https://www.theguardian.com/news/2017/nov/05/what-are-the-paradise-papers-and-what-do-they-tell-ushttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-41880153***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 05:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/07/3478221/3478221_5488E5F62724463A81824EFBE53D6E92_171107_3478221_What_are_the_Paradise_Papers__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/965/18A/96518AC5471943B08399D00BF7411EBB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, paradise papers, document leak, leaks, offshore accounts, offshore, offshore services, appleby, taxes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3478980</guid>
      <title>Transgender women may soon be able to give birth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEOne of the world's leading fertility specialists has said that it's now entirely possible for transgendered women to get pregnant, thanks to developments in science.The Telegraph reports that doctors have successfully transplanted wombs in uterine infertile women in recent years, and at least five babies have been born to these transplant recipients since 2014.Experts now believe the same procedure can be conducted on transgendered women who were born male but have undergone sex reassignment surgery.Carrying a live fetus in the transplanted wombs will likely be more complicated, and expectant transgendered women may need hormones to replicate the natural pregnancy changes that occur in women.The male pelvis is also shaped differently than a female's, which means the baby would have to be born via caesarean section.Of course, not everyone is on board with the idea. Some have voiced ethical concerns, since a pregnancy of this nature poses a huge risk to both mother and child.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Uterus transplant on woman resulted in successful birth2. Uterus transplant on transgendered woman3. Transgendered women may need hormone therapy during pregnancy4. Baby to be born via C-section due to differently shaped male and female pelvic bonesVOICEOVER (in English): "Doctors have successfully transplanted wombs in uterine infertile women in recent years, and at least five babies have been born to these transplant recipients since 2014.""Experts now believe the same procedure can be conducted on transgendered women who were born male but have undergone sex reassignment surgery.""Carrying a live fetus in the transplanted wombs will likely be more complicated, and expectant transgendered women may need hormones to replicate the natural pregnancy changes that occur in women.""The male pelvis is also shaped differently than a female's, which means the baby would have to be born via caesarean section."SOURCES: Telegraph, Science Dailyhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/11/04/babies-born-transgender-mothers-could-happen-tomorrow-fertility/https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/09/170918123535.htm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 06:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/08/3478980/3478980_C9064194753E4DAB91D0FC64CAD0A112_171108_3478980_Transgender_women_may_soon_be_able_to_give_birth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/27A/14B/27A14BC6AC0C4AF4BFA61C4DA0D6D27F_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, womb transplant, uterus transplant, transgender woman, transgender, trans woman, sex change, sex reassignment, gender reassignment, pregnancy, male pregnancy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3480053</guid>
      <title>Gene therapy creates new skin to save dying boy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA young patient who lost most of his skin to a genetic disease now has a new chance at life, thanks to a breakthrough therapy that gave him replacement skin.The New York Times reports that the 7-year-old boy was born with junctional epidermolysis bullosa, a condition in which a gene defect causes the skin to become fragile, often tearing and forming blisters.By June 2015, the boy gotten two bacterial infections that destroyed two-thirds of his skin. He was treated with antibiotics, bandages, and even a skin graft from his father, but nothing worked.Doctors decided to use gene therapy on a patch of non blistered skin, and used a virus to carry a corrected version of the defective gene into the skin cells.The engineered cells were grown into sheets of skin and grafted onto the child's body to replace his missing skin.The grafts took and grew, and the patient was discharged by February 2016. His epidermis is currently stable and doesn't blister or itch.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Junctional epidermis bullosa cause and symptoms2. Skin cells engineered using unmutated gene3. Skin cells grown, grafted onto boy's bodyVOICEOVER (in English): "The 7-year-old boy was born with junctional epidermolysis bullosa, a condition in which a gene defect causes the skin to become fragile, often tearing and forming blisters.""Doctors decided to use gene therapy on a patch of non blistered skin, and used a virus to carry a corrected version of the defective gene into the skin cells.""The engineered cells were grown into sheets of skin and grafted onto the child's body to replace his missing skin."SOURCES: Nature, New York Timeshttps://www.nature.com/articles/nature24487.epdfhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/11/08/health/gene-therapy-skin-graft.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 11:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/09/3480053/3480053_1891E1CBA36446028E37697B21A77DB5_171109_3480053_Gene_therapy_creates_new_skin_to_save_dying_boy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6B5/FBF/6B5FBF87C95441B2BE311B5F08A205F9_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, new skin, replacement skin, junctional epidermolysis bullosa, skin condition, genetic disease, skin disease, skin graft, butterfly skin, fragile skin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3479798</guid>
      <title>Gaming keyboard records how many times keys are pressed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONESeveral users of the MantisTek GK2 gaming keyboard have reported a built-in Keylogger that is sending data to an Alibaba server in China. The MantisTex GK2 is a low cost RGB mechanical keyboard produced in China. The issue is being caused by the keyboard's "Cloud Driver," which sends data to IP addresses linked to Alibaba servers, according to Tom's Hardware. The data has been identified as how many times keys have been pressed. Tracking this type of data without user permission could be a violation of privacy laws in the European Union.  To stop the keyboard from sending your key presses to the Alibaba server, make sure the MantisTek Cloud Driver software isn't running in the background. Another method is by blocking the CMS.exe executable in your firewall by adding a new firewall rule for the MantisTek Cloud Driver in your Windows settings.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. MantisTek GK2 keyboards sending data to an Alibaba server2. Keyboard data being sent to a cloud driver3. User shutting down MantisTek Cloud Driver from running in the background4. Changing your firewall settings can also disable the KeyloggerVOICEOVER (in English): "Several users of the MantisTek GK2 gaming keyboard have reported a built-in Keylogger is sending data to an Alibaba server in China." "The issue is being caused by the keyboard's "Cloud Driver," which sends how many times keys are pressed to IP addresses linked to Alibaba servers.""To stop the keyboard from sending your key presses to the Alibaba server, make sure the MantisTek Cloud Driver software isn't running in the background." "Another method is by blocking the CMS.exe executable in your firewall by adding a new firewall rule for the MantisTek Cloud Driver in your Windows settings."  SOURCES: Tom's Hardwarehttp://www.tomshardware.com/news/mantistek-gk2-collects-typed-keys,35850.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 07:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/09/3479798/3479798_67A8CFC6953341909DAAA22E8871ADEF_171109_3479798_Gaming_keyboard_records_how_many_times_keys_are__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FA7/9F8/FA79F878EBC441359A14E60888748A69_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Gaming keyboard, MantisTek GK2 keyboard, MantisTek GK2 Cloud Driver software, Alibaba server]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3479751</guid>
      <title>Geothermal heat source detected underneath West Antarctic ice sheet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONE A new NASA study bolsters the theory that a heat source exists under West Antarctica.Researchers have found evidence that a geothermal heat source called a mantle plume lies deep below Antarctica's Marie Byrd Land, according to NASA.Mantle plumes are narrow upwellings of hot rock that rise up from the Earth's mantle. They spread out like mushroom caps under the crust, causing it to bulge upward.Using a numeric model, the flux of energy from the mantle plume was calculated to be 150 miliwatts, only 50 milliwatts less than the average heat flux under Yellowstone.Researchers say the heat source could explain the melting that creates river and lakes under the West Antarctic ice sheet, but it is not a new or increasing threat.However, global weather changes and rising sea levels can push warm water closer to the ice, causing it to become unstable and collapse  just as it did 11,000 years ago at the end of the last ice age.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mantle plume deep underneath Marie Byrd Land in Antarctica2. Explanation of mantle plumes3. Melting creates lakes and rivers beneath Antarctic ice sheet4. Meltwater causes ice sheets to slide, become unstableVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers have found evidence that a geothermal heat source called a mantle plume lies deep below Antarctica's Marie Byrd Land.""Mantle plumes are narrow upwellings of hot rock that rise up from the Earth's mantle. They spread out like mushroom caps under the crust, causing it to bulge upward.""Researchers say the heat source could explain the melting that creates river and lakes under the West Antarctic ice sheet, but it is not a new or increasing threat.""However, global weather changes and rising sea levels can push warm water closer to the ice, causing it to become unstable and collapse  just as it did 11,000 years ago at the end of the last ice age."SOURCES: NASAhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?release=2017-291#.WgH4u-OBkE8.twitter***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 06:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/09/3479751/3479751_0F05F52056EE4762B063D16F84062BCC_171109_3479751_Geothermal_heat_source_detected_underneath_West__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BD8/CF8/BD8CF85B2A9843358BCDDB471D287E43_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mantle plume, heat source, geothermal, antarctica ice sheet, antarctic ice sheet, west antarctica, marie byrd land, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3479735</guid>
      <title>How Saturn's ocean moon keeps warm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists looking at data pulled from NASA's Cassini spacecraft may have found out how Saturn's ocean moon Enceladus remains geologically active.The research, published in Nature Astronomy, suggests that tidal currents flow through the moon's porous core where rocks rub together and generate heat that warms the ocean. According to the European Space Agency, this tidal heating is primarily caused by the gravitational pull of Saturn.Writing in 2008, the space agency speculated that the deep sea vent theory could apply to life on Enceladus. When applied to Earth, this suggests life originated from chemical, heat and tidal interactions beneath the seabed.NASA previously said Encedalus has all the ingredients for life, reported CNET, citing the space agency.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Cassini spacecraft near Saturn and Enceladus 2. Cross section of Enceladus area.3. Depiction of Saturn and Enceladus4. Depiction of deep sea vent theory on EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists looking at data pulled from NASA's Cassini spacecraft may have found out how Saturn's ocean moon Enceladus remains geologically active.""The research suggests that tidal currents flow through the moon's porous core where rocks rub together and generate heat that warms the ocean.""According to the European Space Agency, this tidal heating is primarily caused by the gravitational pull of Saturn.""NASA previously said the moon has all the ingredients for life.""Writing in 2008, the space agency speculated that the deep sea vent theory could apply to life on Enceladus." "When applied to Earth, this suggests life originated from chemical, heat and tidal interactions beneath the seabed."SOURCES: Nature, NASA, ESA, CNET, Futurismhttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-017-0289-8http://sci.esa.int/cassini-huygens/59739-choblet-et-al-2017/#https://saturn.jpl.nasa.gov/news/3130/powering-saturns-active-ocean-moon/https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/cassini/media/enceladus-f20080326.htmlhttps://www.cnet.com/news/saturn-moon-enceladus-nasa-alien-life-ocean/https://futurism.com/understand-alien-life-survive-saturns-moon/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 06:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/09/3479735/3479735_C2220027B8BD4F5393BA654DBEA2ADA0_171109_3479735_How_Saturn_s_ocean_moon_keeps_warm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5D5/FFE/5D5FFE4B24CA4D5B866550824BE4F649_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, enceladus alien, life on enceladus, enceladus, saturn, nasa, esa, deep sea vent enceladus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3480485</guid>
      <title>Unexpected things that can slow down your WiFi</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONE A UK survey of 2,000 people has found that more than half are positioning routers near objects that can weaken wifi signals.Huffington Post reports that according to Post Office Telecoms, unexpected items can slow down your wifi. One such item are Christmas lights, which create a small electromagnetic field that can interfere with the signal.Routers broadcast radio signals that are picked up by wifi capable devices, but electronic devices interfere with this signal because they compete for frequencies.Wifi also doesn't transmit easily through water, so expect a slow connection when a router is near a fish tank, which has both electrical circuitry and lots of liquid.Experts advise that routers be placed centrally within the house, away from windows or corners, in order to secure a strong wifi signal.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Christmas lights giving off electromagnetic field that interferes with wifi signal2. Electrical devices can weaken wifi signals3. Water in fish tanks can absorb signals from the router4. Router should be centrally located within the houseVOICEOVER (in English): "An unexpected item that can slow down your wifi are Christmas lights, which create a small electromagnetic field that can interfere with the signal.""Routers broadcast radio signals that are picked up by wifi capable devices, but electronic devices interfere with this signal because they compete for frequencies.""Wifi also doesn't transmit easily through water, so expect a slow connection when a router is near a fish tank, which has both electrical circuitry and lots of liquid.""Experts advise that routers be placed centrally within the house, away from windows or corners, in order to secure a strong wifi signal."SOURCES: Huffington Post, CNN, The Guardianhttp://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/why-is-my-wifi-slow-surprising-things-that-could-be-affecting-your-wifi-speed_uk_5a02e6dbe4b04e96f0c68cdfhttp://money.cnn.com/2015/12/01/technology/wifi-internet-christmas-lights-electronics/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/technology/2015/dec/01/christmas-fairy-lights-ruining-wi-fi***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 05:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/10/3480485/3480485_39FD81DA8E6140D89BCE26DDB3E2C80A_171110_3480485_Unexpected_things_that_can_slow_down_your_WiFi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CB3/3C2/CB33C263742B460AB62599121042E94C_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, wifi, wifi signal, wifi connection, internet connection, connectivity, christmas lights, electromagnetic field, electric signals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3482516</guid>
      <title>Disneyland shuts down cooling towers after Legionnaires' outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEDisneyland has shut down two cooling towers after an outbreak of Legionnaires' disease. Orange County health officials said nine people who visited the theme park in September came down with the disease, CNN reported.  Three other people in the Anaheim area also got sick, according to a spokeswoman for the Orange County Health Care Agency. The 12 patients range in age from 52 to 94, according to the L.A. Times. The towers were shut down after Disney was notified by health officials on October 27 about increased Legionnaires' cases, according to CNN. Disney found two of its 18 cooling towers had elevated levels of Legionella bacteria, which were then treated and disinfected. Cooling towers supply cooled water for several uses such as refrigeration or air conditioning, but not for drinking water. Legionnaires disease is a severe lung infection caused by Legionella bacteria through exposure to contaminated water or mist. The source of the mist can be air conditioning units, showers or hot tubs. It is not contagious between humans. It is treated with antibiotics. Disney is now waiting on health officials to see when the two towers can be put back online. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Two cooling towers were shut down2. Twelve people developed the disease after being to Anaheim or Disneyland3. The disease is spread through contaminated water or mist4. Contaminated water or mist can be spread by A/C units, showers or hot tubsVOICEOVER (in English): "Disneyland has shut down two of its 18 cooling towers after an outbreak of Legionnaires' disease." "Twelve cases of the bacteria-caused illness were discovered about three weeks ago among people who went to Anaheim or Disneyland.""Legionnaires disease is a severe lung infection caused by Legionella bacteria through exposure to contaminated water or mist." "The source of the mist can be air conditioning units, showers or hot tubs. It is not contagious between humans. It is treated with antibiotics." SOURCES: CNN, LA Timeshttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/12/health/disneyland-legionnaires-anaheim/index.htmlhttp://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-disneyland-legionnaires-20171110-story.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/13/3482516/3482516_5B765ED08EE24A84BA5E25025E5BC8A3_171113_3482516_Disneyland_shuts_down_cooling_towers_after_Legio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A6/415/1A64158AADB948DF8CCAEFBD59300972_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Legionnaires' disease, Legionnaires outbreak, Disneyland Legionnaires' outbreak, Disneyland cooling towers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3483477</guid>
      <title>Half of Americans now hypertensive under new guidelines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEU.S. health experts tightened the guidelines for high blood pressure for the first time in 14 years, classifying 30 million more Americans as hypertensive.The Washington Post reports that high blood pressure was once defined as a systolic reading of 140 and a diastolic reading of 90, but has recently been lowered to 130 over 80 by the American Heart Association, the American College of Cardiology, and nine other health organizations.Blood pressure refers to the force of blood flowing through the blood vessels. When too high, it can damage arterial tissues and increase the risk for heart disease, stroke, and kidney problems.Under the old guidelines, 32% of U.S. adults had high blood pressure. With the new lowered threshold, 46% or 103 million Americans are now considered hypertensive.Normal levels are pegged at less than 120 over 80. Those with readings between 120 to 129 over less than 80 are considered to have elevated blood pressure, and recommended lifestyle changes. Medication is given to patients with Stage 1 hypertension who are at risk, while those at Stage 2 are given 2 different classes of medicine.Since hypertension is a silent killer, experts want to help people get the condition under control earlier, and place a strong emphasis on making healthier life choices.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Threshold for high blood pressure lowered from 140/90 to 130/802. Risks presented by hypertension3. 46% of US adults now considered hypertensive under new guideline4. Categories under the new guidelineVOICEOVER (in English): "High blood pressure was once defined as a reading of 140 over 90, but has recently been lowered to 130 over 80.""Blood pressure refers to the force of blood flowing through the blood vessels. When too high, it can damage arterial tissues and increase the risk for heart disease, stroke, and kidney problems.""Under the old guidelines, 32% of U.S. adults had high blood pressure. With the new lowered threshold, 46% or 103 million Americans are now considered hypertensive.""Normal levels are pegged at less than 120 over 80, and lifestyle changes recommended for those with elevated bp. Medication is given to patients with Stage 1 hypertension who are at risk, while those at Stage 2 are given 2 different classes of medicine."SOURCES: American Heart Association, Washington Posthttp://hyper.ahajournals.org/content/early/2017/11/10/HYP.0000000000000065https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2017/11/13/blood-pressure-of-130-is-the-new-high-according-to-first-update-of-guidelines-in-14-years/?utm_term=.23c5e689b1f2***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 12:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/14/3483477/3483477_EE052B0969EC4F10B7308AC29704C4A8_171114_3483477_Half_of_Americans_now_hypertensive_under_new_gui_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FD0/920/FD0920DEABFD460CA42770CDBC060C65_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, high blood pressure, hypertension, hypertensive, high blood, blood pressure, blood pressure monitor, heart disease, stroke, kidney disease, high blood pressure guidelines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3483302</guid>
      <title>Building the world's largest yacht</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENorwegian businessman Kjell Inge Rokke is giving away a sizeable part of his fortune to build what could be the world's largest yacht.Designed by Espen Oeino, the Research Expedition Vessel is currently being constructed in Vard, Norway  According to Yacht Harbor, it will be the world's largest vessel when completed in 2020.The yacht is expected to be 182 meters long. It can carry 60 scientists and 40 crew for research voyages, and 36 guests and 54 crew for private excursions.According to its website, the boat will be fitted with advanced sonar technology, as well as a trawl that can go to 3000m in depth and a moonpool for underwater vehicles.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of yacht being constructed2. Depiction of yacht's size3. Depiction of sonar4. Depiction of yacht's underwater capabilitiesVOICEOVER (in English): "Designed by Espen Oeino, the Research Expedition Vessel is currently being constructed in Norway's Vard shipyard" "According to Yacht Harbor, it will be the world's largest vessel when completed in 2020.""The vessel is 182 meters long." "It can carry 60 scientists and 40 crew for research voyages, and 36 guests and 54 crew for private excursions.""The boat will reportedly be fitted with advanced sonar technology, as well as a trawl that can go to 3000m in depth and a moonpool for underwater vehicles that can go to 6000m."SOURCES: Rosellinisfour-10.no, Yacht Harbourhttp://www.rosellinisfour-10.nohttps://yachtharbour.com/news/norwegian-billionaire-to-build-181-6-metre-espen-oeino-designed-vessel-1669?src=news_page_bar_pos_1***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 09:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/14/3483302/3483302_E29AAD2B8C8E4E4ABE0774DCBB66557C_171114_3483302_Building_the_world_s_largest_yacht_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B65/08F/B6508F85EE8C420DACD5B82E3714CEF7_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, yacht, research yacht, world's largest vessel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3484165</guid>
      <title>Gunman kills 4, wounds 10 in California mass shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFour are dead and many more injured after a man went on a shooting rampage through a rural Northern California town.The Los Angeles Times reports that just before 8 a.m. on Tuesday, a gunman shot and killed a male and a female neighbor near his home in Rancho Tehama, before fleeing in a stolen truck.The suspect went on a shooting spree through the community, opening fire at several locations, including an elementary school.He carjacked another vehicle and went around firing shots at random, even shooting at a mother who was driving her son to school. The shooter killed 4 people and injured at least 10.Local police eventually caught up to the suspect and shot him dead during an exchange of gunfire. He was found with a semiautomatic rifle and two handguns.The gunman was later identified to be 43-year-old Kevin Neal, a local resident. No motive has been declared for the violent spree, but authorities believe the man may have been set off by a dispute with his neighbors.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Gunman killed a man and female neighbor  2. Gunman opening fire outside an elementary school, injuring some children3. Gunman shooting at random people on the road4. Gunman killed after facing off with policeVOICEOVER (in English): "Just before 8 a.m. on Tuesday, a 43-year-old man shot and killed a man and a female neighbor near his home in Rancho Tehama, before fleeing in a stolen truck.""The suspect went on a shooting spree through the community, opening fire at several locations, including an elementary school.""He carjacked another vehicle and went around firing randomly, shooting at a mother who was driving her son to school. The shooter killed 4 people and injured at least 10.""Local police eventually caught up to the suspect and shot him dead during an exchange of gunfire. He was found with a semiautomatic rifle and two handguns."SOURCES: KCRTV, Los Angeles Times, CBShttp://www.krcrtv.com/news/local/tehama/officials-responding-to-reported-shooting-near-elementary-school-in-rancho-tehama/656286015http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-norcal-elementary-school-shooting-20171114-story.htmlhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/california-shooting-rancho-tehama-elementary-school-students-hospitalized-following-deadly/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 10:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/15/3484165/3484165_DC5C380517FB49529F6DECB8696F5B70_171115_3484165_Gunman_kills_4__wounds_10_in_California_mass_sho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/392/ACB/392ACB09D4C14B8392B95EC6CD770B8B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, california shooting, elementary school shooting, rancho tehama, rancho tehama shooting, rancho tehama reserve, school shooting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3483944</guid>
      <title>Bill Gates firm planning smart city in Arizona</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA real estate investment firm owned by Bill Gates has invested in a project to build a smart city in the Arizona desert.Gates' Cascade Investment LLC paid around $80 million for a large stake in a 24,800 acre development called Belmont, according to the Arizona Republic.The area is around 50 miles west of Phoenix in an area called West Valley. "Belmont will create a forward-thinking community with a communication and infrastructure spine that embraces cutting-edge technology, designed around high-speed digital networks, data centers, new manufacturing technologies and distribution models, autonomous vehicles and autonomous logistics hubs," Belmont Partners, the Arizona real estate investment firm involved in the project, said in a news release.   The city will have 3,800 acres for office, commercial and retail space as well as 470 acres for public schools. Belmont will also have 80,000 residential homes.One of the reasons Belmont was chosen is its location next to the proposed Interstate 11 freeway, which has yet to receive funding. If completed, Interstate 11 would run from Reno, Nevada to Mexico, the Arizona Republic reported. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Smart city being built in the desert2. Smart city with digital networks, data centers, manufacturing and logistics3. Office space in proposed development4. The development will have land for public schools and 80,000 residential unitsVOICEOVER (in English): "A real estate investment firm owned by Bill Gates has invested $80 million in a project to build a smart city called Belmont in the Arizona desert 50 miles west of Phoenix.""Belmont will be constructed on a flexible infrastructure model that can accommodate high-speed digital networks, data centers, advanced manufacturing and distribution models.""The smart city will have 3,800 acres for office, commercial and retail space."  "Four-hundred and seventy acres will be allotted for public schools. Belmont will also have 80,000 residential units."SOURCES: The Arizona Republic, Popular Mechanics, UPIhttp://www.azcentral.com/story/money/real-estate/catherine-reagor/2017/11/08/bill-gates-cascade-invests-belmont-real-estate-development-near-phoenix/842280001/http://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/a29005/bill-gates-smart-city/https://www.upi.com/Top_News/US/2017/11/12/Bill-Gates-buys-Arizona-land-to-build-future-smart-city/6391510528677/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 07:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/15/3483944/3483944_3300ABBFBF1242E8A16199E2248C0F60_171115_3483944_Bill_Gates_firm_planning_smart_city_in_Arizona_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5C8/0F2/5C80F26759D744D7953B6786745825C3_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Bill Gates smart city, smart city, Belmont Arizona, Belmont smart city, Bill gates real estate firm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3483751</guid>
      <title>Autonomous space plane passes 3,810m drop test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe autonomous Dream Chaser space plane completed a free-flight drop test from a height of 3,810m over California on Saturday.The plane can carry 7 passengers, reports Space.com, and looks like a smaller version of current NASA shuttles. When complete, it will use Atlas rockets to fly six delivery missions to the International Space Station by 2024.The test on Saturday examined the plane during the final approach and landing phase of flight.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Dream Chaser and NASA shuttle2. Depiction of Dream Chaser on top of rocket3. Depiction of Dream Chaser near the International Space Station4. Depiction of Dream Chaser landingVOICEOVER (in English): "The privately-built autonomous Dream Chaser space plane completed a free-flight drop test in California on Saturday November 11.""It can carry 7 passengers and looks like a smaller version of current NASA shuttles.""When complete, Dream Chaser will use Atlas rockets to fly half-a-dozen delivery missions to the International Space Station by 2024.""The test on Saturday examined the plane during the final approach and landing phase of flight."SOURCES: Sierra Nevada Corporation, Space.comhttps://www.sncorp.com/https://www.space.com/38756-dream-chaser-space-plane-free-flight-test.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 01:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/15/3483751/3483751_C0EDD0EF4FD44F9083D0034212D81690_171115_3483751_Autonomous_space_plane_passes_3_810m_drop_test_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/26F/521/26F5210A20034C848B9CD43430F9EBB7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, drop test, space plane, autonomous space plane, dreamchaser, nasa, iss, space station delivery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3484732</guid>
      <title>New Boom supersonic airliner to take-off by 2023</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new airliner that boasts supersonic speeds is set to revolutionize air travel once it takes flight in 2023.BBC reports that Boom Technology's planned supersonic aircraft will have a cruise speed of 1,451 miles per hour, 2.6 times faster than any other airliner.While a flight from New York to London would typically take 7 hours on a commercial flight, the trip would take a little over three hours on a supersonic airliner.The Mach 2.2 aircraft will have 55 seats, each priced at about $5,000 for a roundtrip ticket.A one-third-scale prototype called the XB-1 will begin test flights in 2018 to demonstrate and refine the key technologies required for supersonic travel.Unlike the now retired Concorde and its notoriously loud sonic boom, the Boom aircraft will have turbofans for noise reduction, and won't be much louder than a normal plane. The company does have some hurdles to face before their project comes to fruition. Supersonic flights are still banned in the U.S., but with federal laws currently up for renegotiation, that could soon change.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Boom supersonic can fly at mach 2.2 speed, 2.6 times faster than regular airliners2. Supersonic airliner can make a New York to London flight in 3 hours and 15 minutes3. Supersonic airliner will have 55 seats, ticket priced at $5,0004. Plane to avoid supersonic boom by using turbofans VOICEOVER (in English): "Boom Technology's planned supersonic aircraft will have a cruise speed of 1,451 miles per hour, 2.6 times faster than any other airliner.""While a flight from New York to London would typically take 7 hours on a commercial flight, the trip would take a little over three hours on a supersonic airliner.""The Mach 2.2 aircraft will have 55 seats, each priced at about $5,000 for a roundtrip ticket.""Unlike the now retired Concorde and its notoriously loud sonic boom, the Boom aircraft will have turbofans for noise reduction, and won't be much louder than a normal plane."SOURCES: Boom Technology, BBChttps://boomsupersonic.com/http://www.bbc.com/news/business-41972529***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 07:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/16/3484732/3484732_C7883EAA2A5E410E87A499F98861991F_171116_3484732_New_Boom_supersonic_airliner_to_take_off_by_2023_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3C5/A4F/3C5A4F1EF91E4C86A94419AD774B3AD3_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, boom supersonic, supersonic plane, supersonic airliner, supersonic flight, boom technology, concorde, supersonic, business class]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3484676</guid>
      <title>Denver getting high-speed traffic system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONETraffic in Colorado's capital city could get much faster in the next half-decade.Headed by tech firm Arrivo, the Denver high-speed traffic tube project will first build a test track following the city's E-470 toll road, reported The Verge.The system will see a variety of vehicles, both passenger and cargo, using the system. According to the company website, the technology uses a combination of magnetic levitation and electrics to propel cars at speeds of up to 200 miles per hourIf successful, Arrivo could potentially expand it to connect with Denver's current transportation infrastructure.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Map of route 2. Depiction of proposed Arrivo models3. Depiction of Arrivo models traveling4. Depiction of route through cityVOICEOVER (in English): "The system will see a variety of vehicles, both passenger and cargo, using it." "The technology uses a combination of magnetic levitation and electrics to propel cars at speeds of up to 200 miles per hour.""If successful, Arrivo could potentially expand to connect with Denver's current transportation infrastructure."SOURCES: Arrivo, The Verge, Ars Technicahttp://www.arrivo-loop.comhttps://www.theverge.com/2016/11/18/13681412/hyperloop-one-settles-lawsuit-bambrogan-pishevarhttps://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2017/11/colorado-dot-is-partnering-with-hyperloop-offshoot-to-build-denver-test-track/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 06:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/16/3484676/3484676_BED7C0F963FA4323B96F66FCDD3795BA_171116_3484676_Denver_getting_high_speed_traffic_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BC0/F92/BC0F92A494CC41CE902F9EA999C0E1D3_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, denver hyperloop, denver, arrivo, super urban network, traffic tube, colorado, brogan bambrogan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3485708</guid>
      <title>Keystone Pipeline spills 210,000 gallons of oil in South Dakota</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Keystone Pipeline leaked 210,000 gallons, or 5,000 barrels, of oil Thursday in Marshall County, South Dakota near Amherst.Officials are currently investigating the cause of the leak, CNN reported. TransCanada, the company that owns the pipeline, said it detected a drop in pressure around 6 a.m. on Thursday morning and shut down the pipeline. The pipeline runs from Hardesty, Alberta to Cushing, Oklahoma and Wood River/Pakota, Illinois. The company said in a statement, "the section of pipe along a right-of-way approximately 35 miles (56 km) south of the Ludden pump station in Marshall County, South Dakota was completely isolated within 15 minutes and emergency procedures were activated." TransCanada said it received permission from the landowner to investigate the spill and plan cleanup, the Washington Post reported. This would be the largest Keystone oil spill to date in South Dakota, said state spokesman for the Department of Environment and Natural Resources Brian Walsh, CNN reported.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Keystone Pipeline2. The Keystone Pipeline leaking oil3. TransCanada shut down the pipeline after detecting a drop in pressure4. TransCanada cleaning up the leaked oilVOICEOVER (in English): "The Keystone Pipeline runs from Hardesty, Alberta to Cushing, Oklahoma and Wood River/Pakota, Illinois." "On Thursday morning it leaked 210,000 gallons, or 5000 barrels, of oil in Marshall County, South Dakota near Amherst.""TransCanada, the company that owns the pipeline, said it detected a drop in pressure around 6 a.m. and shut down the pipeline.""TransCanada said it received permission from the landowner to investigate the spill and plan cleanup."SOURCES: Washington Post, CNN, NPRhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/energy-environment/wp/2017/11/16/keystone-pipeline-spills-210000-gallons-of-oil-on-eve-of-key-permitting-decision/?utm_term=.fd0ae923068fhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/16/us/keystone-pipeline-leak/index.htmlhttps://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2017/11/16/564705368/keystone-pipeline-oil-spill-reported-in-south-dakota***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 09:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/17/3485708/3485708_44C7CC693E864375896ACF033F6F5523_171117_3485708_Keystone_Pipeline_spills_210_000_gallons_of_oil__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/86B/BD8/86BBD8FE94804807BD90D94DD2814BC7_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Keystone Pipeline, Keystone Pipeline leak, Keystone Pipeline spill, oil spill, TransCanada oil spill]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3485455</guid>
      <title>Swedish firm specializes in 3D body part printing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONESwedish startup firm Cellink specializes in low-cost and accessible 3D bioprinting. The company was founded in 2016 by Erik Gatenholm and Hector Martinez. It has already developed several 3D bioprinters as well as bioprinting materials (bioinks), according to 3ders.org. Cellink is currently focused on growing cartilage and skin cells for drug and cosmetics testing, BBC reported. The company also makes bioink, the liquid that human cells are mixed with, then 3D printed. Cellink makes its ink from cellulose from Swedish forests and alginate formed from Norwegian Sea seaweed, according to BBC. Cellink bioinks run between $9 to $299, while the printers cost between $10,000 and $39,000. Health experts believe that in 10 to 20 years, bioprinting could be used to make fully functioning organs for transplant. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Cellink 3D bioprinter printing out an ear2. Cellink researchers working in the lab3. Cellink makes bioink with cellulose and alginate4. Bioprinting could be used to make functioning organs in the futureVOICEOVER (in English): "Swedish startup firm Cellink specializes in low-cost and accessible 3D bioprinting by offering bioink as well as 3D bioprinters." "Cellink is currently focused on growing cartilage and skin cells for drug and cosmetics testing.""The company makes its bioink  the liquid that human cells are mixed with  with cellulose from Swedish forests and alginate formed from Norwegian Sea seaweed.""Health experts believe that in 10 to 20 years, bioprinting could be used to make fully functioning organs for transplant." SOURCES: BBChttp://www.bbc.com/news/business-41859942https://www.3ders.org/articles/20170522-3d-bioprinting-startup-cellink-opens-new-office-in-cambridge-ma.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 06:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/17/3485455/3485455_4B466F6BE11B43088D12504F9D67FB88_171117_3485455_Swedish_firm_specializes_in_3D_body_part_printin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7B4/55A/7B455A7BFEEE477B8892A072776232C6_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, 3D printing, 3D body part printing, 3D bioprinting, Cellink]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3485417</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered exoplanet could sustain life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists using the European Southern Observatory's planet-hunting HARPS instrument have discovered a new exoplanet just 11 light-years from our solar system.Ross 128 b is roughly the same size as Earth and is believed to share a similar surface temperature, according to a press release from ESO.The exoplanet's host star is Ross 128, a red dwarf that is smaller and cooler than our Sun. It's 20 times closer to its star than Earth is to the sun, and completes an orbit in just 9.9 days.Red dwarf stars such as the Proxima Centauri are unstable and often subject their planets to flares and deadly UV radiation. But Ross 128 is a much quieter star, which means its exoplanets may be a more comfortable place to host life.Scientists are unsure if Ross 128 b is in fact habitable, but agree that it is a good candidate for study. ESO's Extremely Large Telescope is set to look for biomarkers such as oxygen in the exoplanet's atmosphere by 2025.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Ross 128 b same size and surface temperature as Earth2. Exoplanet completes an orbit around its red dwarf star Ross 128 in 9.9 days3. Planets near red dwarf stars often subject to deadly flares, UV radiation4. Ross 128 b doesn't experience flares, may be habitableVOICEOVER (in English): "Ross 128 b is roughly the same size as Earth and is believed to share a similar surface temperature.""The exoplanet's host star is Ross 128, a red dwarf that is smaller and cooler than our Sun. It's 20 times closer to its star than Earth is to the Sun, and completes an orbit in just 9.9 days.""Red dwarf stars such as the Proxima Centauri are unstable and often subject their planets to flares and deadly UV radiation.""But Ross 128 is a much quieter star, which means its exoplanets may be a more comfortable place to host life."SOURCES: European Southern Observatoryhttps://www.eso.org/public/news/eso1736/?lang***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/17/3485417/3485417_92256E97E5A04D778F636C105CD1D584_171117_3485417_Newly_discovered_exoplanet_could_sustain_life_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C49/229/C49229AEA88949CD8F6335FD753E652B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, ross 128, ross 128 b, exoplanet, new planet, earth like planet, temperate planet, proxima centauri, proxima b, life outside earth, ESO, ELT, extremely large telescope]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3487569</guid>
      <title>Search for missing Argentina sub hampered by bad weather</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe search for an Argentine naval submarine that went missing with 44 crew members is being hampered by bad weather, officials said. The ARA San Juan submarine was returning on a routine mission from the Tierra del Fuego archipelago to its home base in Mar del Plata, CNN reported. The San Juan was originally scheduled to arrive at port on Sunday. It was last spotted Wednesday in the San Jorge Gulf.   Seven failed satellite calls were detected on Saturday morning, however, the Argentine defense ministry said it could not confirm the attempts came from the ARA San Juan, the Guardian reported.The San Juan is a 65-meter-long TR-1700 submarine, powered by four diesel and one electric engine, the Argentine military said, according to CNN. The Argentine navy says the missing sub has enough oxygen, food and water to last for at least two weeks, the BBC reported. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The ARA San Juan2. The submarine was last seen at Golfo San Jorge3. Seven failed satellite calls may have been from the missing ARA San Juan4. The San Juan has enough oxygen, food and water for 2 weeksVOICEOVER (in English): "The search for an Argentine naval submarine that went missing with 44 crew members is being hampered by bad weather.""The ARA San Juan was returning on a routine mission from the Tierra del Fuego archipelago to its home base in Mar del Plata. It was last spotted on Wednesday in the San Jorge Gulf.""Seven failed satellite calls were detected on Saturday morning, however, the Argentine defense ministry said it could not confirm the attempts came from the ARA San Juan.""The Argentine navy says the missing sub has enough oxygen, food and water to last for at least two weeks."SOURCES: BBC, CNN, Guardianhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-42045380http://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/19/americas/argentina-missing-submarine/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/nov/19/search-for-missing-argentinian-submarine-fails-to-find-any-clues***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 09:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/20/3487569/3487569_BE8611AE5B3C4D379B5BD799778F3B49_171120_3487569_Search_for_missing_Argentina_sub_hampered_by_bad_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/04A/94D/04A94D2AEDE741D8A18C185CFC6D9FBF_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Argentine submarine, Argentine submarine missing, ARA San Juan, ARA San Juan missing, missing submarine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3487554</guid>
      <title>North Korean defector's stomach is full of parasites</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEMedical staff treating a wounded North Korean defector found numerous parasites inside his body, revealing a picture of poor health that may be commonplace in the north. The North Korean border guard was shot several times while fleeing across the demilitarized zone to South Korea last week.According to Reuters, surgeons treating the defector found several parasites inside his body. Several of these were removed from his digestive tract, including one 27 cm long roundworm.That is likely due to farming practices in the north where human excrement as fertilizer due to a lack of chemical fertilizer. Known as night soil, this practise is notorious for spreading parasites and disease.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korean soldier fleeing2. North Korean soldier in hospital3. Roundworms in small intestine4. North Korean farmVOICEOVER (in English): "The North Korean border guard was shot several times while fleeing across the demilitarized zone to South Korea last week.""Medical staff treating the defector say they found numerous parasites inside his body.""Several of these were removed from his digestive tract, including one 27 cm long roundworm.""They were likely caused by farming practices in the north where human excrement is used for fertilizer due to a lack of chemical fertilizer.""Known as night soil, this practise is notorious for spreading parasites and disease." SOURCES: Reuters, CNBC, Washington Posthttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-southkorea-defection-soldi/injured-defectors-parasites-and-diet-hint-at-hard-life-in-north-korea-idUSKBN1DH0RL?il=0https://www.cnbc.com/2017/11/16/body-of-north-korean-defector-full-of-parasites.htmlhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2017/11/19/what-the-parasites-in-a-defectors-stomach-tell-us-about-north-korea/?utm_term=.bf5543c26dbe***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 09:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/20/3487554/3487554_603B5E19A2A0450F989C77C2A32DE89C_171120_3487554_North_Korean_defector_s_stomach_is_full_of_paras_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FB0/A83/FB0A83D6A9524C4BBBE4800A7CFEEEF1_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, health, north korea, south korea, defector, kim jong un, north korean health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3488324</guid>
      <title>U.S. researchers warn number of major earthquakes may increase next year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe number of intense earthquakes may increase in 2018, according to new research.The prediction warns that as the Earth's rotation slows, the amount of earthquakes increase.Researchers say the planet is currently in the fourth year of these five-year periodical slowdowns. They warn this could see a threefold increase in earthquakes next year, from 6 in 2017 to 20 in 2018. "Next year we should see a significant increase in numbers of severe earthquakes," said University of Colorado researcher Dr. Roger Bilham. "So far we have only had about six severe earthquakes. We could easily have 20 a year starting in 2018."Bilham, along with Rebecca Bendick from the University of Montana, studied earthquakes of magnitude 7 and higher since 1900 and found five instances of seismic increases. Most of the greater earthquakes occurred near the equator.Scientists suspect this maybe because of small changes in the Earth's core, but exactly why earthquakes would respond to a slowing Earth is unknown.New Zealand seismology experts at the University of Otago said they don't support the findings, and that the research shouldn't inspire panic. They called it "another example of a fortuitous correlation between earthquake occurrence and an unrelated phenomenon."RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of Earth slowing down2. Depiction of earthquake3. Earth equator4. Core of planet EarthVOICEOVER (in English): "The prediction warns that as the Earth's rotation slows, the amount of earthquakes will increase.""Researchers say the planet is currently in the fourth year of these five year periodical slowdowns.""University of Colorado researcher Dr Roger Bilham warns this could see a threefold increase in Earthquakes next year, from 6 in 2017 to 20 in 2018.""The researchers studied earthquakes of magnitude 7 and higher since 1900 and found five instances of seismic increases.""Most of the greater earthquakes occurred near the equator.""Scientists suspect this maybe because of small changes in the Earth's core, but exactly why earthquakes would respond to a slowing Earth is unknown."SOURCES: The Guardian, Newshubhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/nov/18/2018-set-to-be-year-of-big-earthquakeshttp://www.newshub.co.nz/home/new-zealand/2017/11/kiwi-scientists-question-prediction-earthquakes-could-triple-next-year.htmlhttp://www.newshub.co.nz/home/world/2017/11/scientists-predict-devastating-earthquakes-will-triple-in-2018.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 08:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/21/3488324/3488324_D80312EABE7B4890A882FA49F421EE21_171121_3488324_U_S__researchers_warn_number_of_major_earthquake_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B91/FC5/B91FC59B484B4EE2B70046B176033B4A_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, major earthquakes, earthquake frequency increase, seismology, equator earthquakes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3489272</guid>
      <title>Uber paid hackers to hide massive data breach affecting 57 million accounts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEPersonal information of millions of Uber customers and drivers were stolen by hackers in 2016, in a breach that the company has kept secret for more than a year.Bloomberg reports that In October 2016, two hackers gained access to a third-party cloud-based service used by Uber, and obtained information on 57 million of its users.Compromised data from the attack included names, email addresses, phone numbers, as well as license numbers of around 600,000 U.S. drivers.The company claims users' bank and credit card information, social security numbers, trip location history and dates of birth were not accessed.The hackers reportedly emailed Uber asking for money, and were paid $100,000 to delete the stolen files and keep quiet about the breach.News of the hack was not disclosed to either its users or any government agencies, despite a number of state and federal laws requiring the company to do so.Uber's chief security officer and a senior lawyer have been sacked for their shady handling of the hack. The New York State Attorney General has also opened an investigation into the incident, according to USA Today.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Hackers accessed data of 57 million Uber users in October 20162. Compromised data included names, email address, phone numbers; driver's license of 600,000 U.S. drivers3. Uber paid hackers $100,000 to delete stolen informationVOICEOVER (in English): "In October 2016, two hackers gained access to a third-party cloud-based service used by Uber, and obtained information on 57 million of its users.""Compromised data from the attack included names, email addresses, phone numbers, as well as license numbers of around 600,000 U.S. drivers.""The hackers reportedly emailed Uber asking for money, and were paid $100,000 to delete the stolen files and keep quiet about the breach."SOURCES: Uber, Bloomberg, USA Todayhttps://www.uber.com/newsroom/2016-data-incident/?utm_term=zaFzSGXkJQlfSAQzAVWOK1q6UkmRLrXA9VYbVM0&adg_id=218769&cid=10078&utm_campaign=affiliate-ir-Skimbit%20Ltd._1_-99_national_D_all_ACQ_cpa_en&utm_content=&utm_source=affiliate-irhttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-11-21/uber-concealed-cyberattack-that-exposed-57-million-people-s-datahttps://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2017/11/21/uber-kept-mum-year-hack-info-57-million-riders-and-drivers/887002001/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 12:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/22/3489272/3489272_85CB6424527945DDBE1BA1AE8758D3F6_171122_3489272_Uber_paid_hackers_to_hide_massive_data_breach_af_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/660/1BC/6601BC684A6D438EB018E2947211A14E_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, uber hack, data breach, uber hacked, data hack, hack, hackers, 2016 uber hack, ransom, personal data, personal information, stolen data, uber scandal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3489929</guid>
      <title>Water flowing through Mars may just be sand, says study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew research from the U.S. Geological Survey has found that the mysterious streaks once thought to be proof of water on Mars are probably just sand flows. According to NASA, recurring slope lineae or RSL are long, dark streaks that expand on the slopes of Mars during warmer seasons, and retract when the temperature gets colder.RSL served as compelling evidence of water on Mars. It looked similar to features on Earth formed by water flows, and contained molecules that help water stay liquid. But a closer look reveals behavior that's unlike flowing water.Streaks existed only on the tops of steep slopes, and all settled at the angle of repose  the maximum slope at which loose solid material can be piled without slumping.Based on the findings, researchers concluded that the markings weren't created by water, but by dry grains like sand and dust that accumulate and flow down the slopes.The RSL may still contain water, but probably not enough to sustain tiny microbial critters, more so human life.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Long, dark streaks on Mars called RSL expand during warm Martian summers2. RSL similar to features on Earth formed by flowing water, contained salts associated with liquid water3. Streaks only on the top of the steepest hills, all settle at angle of repose4.RSL believed to be markings left by sand flowing downhillVOICEOVER (in English): "Recurring slope lineae or RSL are long, dark streaks that expand on the slopes of Mars during warmer seasons, and retract when the temperature gets colder.""RSL served as compelling evidence of water on Mars. It looked similar to features on Earth formed by water flows, and contained molecules that help water stay liquid. But a closer look reveals behavior that's unlike flowing water.""Streaks existed only on the tops of steep slopes, and all settled at the angle of repose - the maximum slope at which loose solid material can be piled without slumping.""Based on the findings, researchers concluded that the markings weren't created by water, but by dry grains like sand and dust that accumulate and flow down the slopes."SOURCES: USGS, NASA, CNNhttps://www.usgs.gov/news/previous-evidence-water-mars-now-identified-grainflowshttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?release=2017-299http://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/21/world/mars-water-sand-rsl-study/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 09:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/23/3489929/3489929_C65B42BB420E4C83931E779D321B9C1D_171123_3489929_Water_flowing_through_Mars_may_just_be_sand__say_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/662/B4C/662B4C0923A948D6BED79531F218D763_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mars, water on mars, life on mars, RSL, sand flow, mars sand flow, slope lineae, recurring slope lineae, Mars slopes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3489858</guid>
      <title>NASA starstruck by first interstellar asteroid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA says a recently discovered asteroid is our solar system's first interstellar visitor. The asteroid was discovered by the Panoramic Survey Telescope and Rapid Response System in Hawaii on October 19, 2017.NASA-funded research published in the journal Nature says it is the first interstellar object to enter our solar system and will travel inside it for over a year.Scientists speculate the asteroid is 400 meters long, and around 40 m wide. A lot about it is unknown, but the asteroid could be made up materials like metals or rocks, and is likely to be billions of years old. NASA says the asteroid will exit the solar system in January 2019 after passing through Saturn's orbit. It will next head for the Pegasus constellation.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Telescope observing asteroid 2. Asteroid's path through solar system3. Asteroid in space4. Asteroid over Saturn and Pegasus ConstellationVOICEOVER (in English): "The asteroid was discovered by the Panoramic Survey Telescope and Rapid Response System in Hawaii on October 19, 2017.""Research published in the journal Nature says it is the first interstellar object to enter our solar system and will travel inside it for over a year.""Scientists speculate the asteroid is 400 meters long, and around 40 m wide.""A lot about it is unknown, but the asteroid could be made up materials like metals or rocks, and is likely to be billions of years old""NASA says the asteroid will exit the solar system in January 2019 after passing through Saturn's orbit. It will next head for the Pegasus constellation."SOURCES: NASA, Nature, Inhabitathttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=7006https://www.nature.com/articles/nature25020https://inhabitat.com/nasa-confirms-asteroid-came-from-another-solar-system-and-its-incredibly-bizarre/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 08:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/23/3489858/3489858_98C71C90FEEB47BD91EE40A15383FAD5_171123_3489858_NASA_starstruck_by_first_interstellar_asteroid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C77/97D/C7797DAFD45A46D48E2918E05ADC37CB_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, new asteroid 2017, asteroid 2017, interstellar asteroid, hawaii telescope, nasa finds asteroid, beyond the solar system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3489792</guid>
      <title>What could happen under Net Neutrality repeal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe Federal Communications Commission has released regulations that would roll back net neutrality regulations passed by the agency two years ago. Net Neutrality is the principle of an open internet where Internet Service Providers (ISPs) give consumers access to all content without favoring some sources or blocking others, according to USA Today.  It also prohibits ISPs from throttling certain content over others.  In 2015, the FCC decided to regulate broadband service like a utility, similar to electricity and water, according to the New York Times. The major broadband and telecom companies like AT&T and Comcast argue against net neutrality saying government regulation reduces the incentives to improve service. Without net neutrality, the internet could become divided into two tiers: one with fast service and one without.Larger internet and media companies as well as the affluent will be able to pay for the high-speed lane, while everyone else will have to use the slow lane. The new rules would require ISPs to disclose any blocking, throttling and prioritization of content.States are also prohibited from enacting their own net neutrality laws that conflict with the new FCC rules, USA Today reported.  The FCC will vote on December 14 to repeal current net neutrality rules.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Woman using the internet2. Without net neutrality the internet could be divided into two tiers3. People surfing the internet 4. ISPs would need to disclose blocking, throttling and prioritization VOICEOVER (in English): "The Federal Communications Commission has released regulations that would roll back net neutrality regulations.""Without net neutrality, the internet could become divided into two tiers: one with fast service and one without.""Larger internet and media companies as well as the affluent will be able to pay for the high-speed lane, while everyone else will have to use the slow lane." "The new rules would require ISPs to disclose any blocking, throttling and prioritization of content."SOURCES: USA Today, New York Timeshttps://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/news/2017/04/26/what-net-neutrality-and-what-would-its-reversal-mean/100930220/https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/news/2017/11/22/whats-stake-fccs-net-neutrality-vote/888870001/https://mobile.nytimes.com/2017/11/21/technology/net-neutrality-repeal-questions.html?referer=http://m.facebook.com/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 07:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/23/3489792/3489792_D233B4D9148A4685879E9EBC7BCAD225_171123_3489792_What_could_happen_under_Net_Neutrality_repeal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/02D/116/02D1162087774314B00A08658DE5F135_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Net Neutrality, Net Neutrality repeal, Net Neutrality regulations, ISPs, throttling, paid prioritization, blocking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3489759</guid>
      <title>Google collects Android user location data even if location services are off</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEGoogle has been collecting location data on Android phones, even when the location services are disabled, according to Quartz. This means Google can access users' locations and their movements well beyond consumer privacy norms. After being contacted by Quartz, Google said cell tower addresses have been included in information sent to a system that manages push notifications and messages on Android phones for the past 11 months. According to a Google spokesperson, the data was not used or stored, and that the company was taking steps to stop the practice by the end of November. With user location data, cell towers could be used to triangulate location to around a quarter-mile radius, and even closer in urban areas where cell towers are closer together. Even though the information is encrypted when it is sent back to Google, a third party could still compromise the system. Since January, all Android devices, even with location services disabled, were sending cell-tower addresses to Google. Devices with cellular data or WiFi connection appeared to send data each time they were in range of a new cell tower. Android devices without a SIM card, but connected to a WiFi network, would still send tower addresses to Google.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Google collecting Android users' location data through cell towers2. Devices sending data in range of a new cell tower3. Devices with no SIM card, but connected to a WiFi network, sending tower addresses to Google4. Data could be used to triangulate users' locationsVOICEOVER (in English): "Since January, all Android devices, even with location services disabled, have been sending cell-tower addresses to Google." "Devices with cellular data or WiFi connection appeared to send data each time they were in range of a new cell tower." "Android devices without a SIM card, but connected to a WiFi network, would still send tower addresses to Google.""With user location data, cell towers could be used to triangulate location to around a quarter-mile radius, and even closer in urban areas where cell towers are closer together."SOURCES: Quartzhttps://qz.com/1131515/google-collects-android-users-locations-even-when-location-services-are-disabled/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 07:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/23/3489759/3489759_2C5DDC27B9324AEEAC07932D39A7F1CC_171123_3489759_Google_collects_Android_user_location_data_even__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7AD/454/7AD45476D6354B2DAECD62C680C7D845_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Google, Google Android user location, Android user location data, Google collecting location data]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3491020</guid>
      <title>Mitsubishi admits to falsifying product data</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEShares of Japanese firm Mitsubishi are dropping after the company admitted to tampering with product data.Mitsubishi Materials admitted on Thursday that two of its subsidiaries had falsified product data to match specifications set by clients, according to the Japan Times.Mitsubishi Cable Industries altered data on its O-ring sealing products, affecting 270 million units sold over a two and a half year period to firms that include aircraft and car makers.Specs on metal products for car and electronic components were also misrepresented by Mitsubishi Shindoh, with least 29 companies believed to have bought the parts between October 2016 and 2017.So far, none of the products have been caused safety problems. Reports claim one other unit had supplied products with falsified information, though these have already been confirmed safe to use.The Mitsubishi scandal is the latest blow to Japan's once-prestigious manufacturing industry, which has been rocked by multiple controversies this year from companies like Kobe Steel, Nissan, Subaru, Toshiba, and Takata.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mitsubishi Materials subsidiaries falsified product specification data2. Data on O-rings altered, product sold to companies for more than 2 years 3. Data on brass, copper components altered, product sold to 29 companies over a yearVOICEOVER (in English): "Mitsubishi Materials admitted on Thursday that two of its subsidiaries had falsified product data to match specifications set by clients.""Mitsubishi Cable Industries altered data on its O-ring sealing products, affecting 270 million units sold over a two and a half year period to firms that include aircraft and car makers.""Specs on metal products for car and electronic components were also misrepresented by Mitsubishi Shindoh, with least 29 companies believed to have bought the parts between October 2016 and 2017."SOURCES: Japan Times, Reuters, CNN Moneyhttps://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2017/11/23/business/corporate-business/mitsubishi-subsidiaries-found-falsified-data-products-supplied-aerospace-automotive-power-customers/#.WheLa4iGOUkhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-mitsubishi-ma-scandal/mitsubishi-materials-says-units-falsified-product-data-idUSKBN1DN09D?il=0http://money.cnn.com/2017/11/23/news/companies/mitsubishi-materials-false-data-kobe-steel/index.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/24/3491020/3491020_91664E2484F84DDCA50232C9B894063B_171124_3491020_Mitsubishi_admits_to_falsifying_product_data_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/ABB/4BF/ABB4BFD44A3F4BA0922E5D7AC5414026_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, mitsubishi, mitsubishi scandal, mitsubishi controversy, fake documents, falsified documents, japan, manufacturing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3490763</guid>
      <title>China tests next-generation ICBM</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEChina is adding a new intercontinental ballistic missile  the Dongfeng-41  to its nuclear arsenal.The missile recently underwent its eighth test launch since it was first announced in 2012. The ICBM is a three-stage solid-fuel missile, 15 meters long and weighing around 30 metric tons.   The Dongfeng-41 has a 12,000-km range, meaning it could strike almost any location in the world, China's state media reported, according to Newsweek. It has a top speed of over Mach 10.The Dongfeng-41 can carry up to 10 MIRV warheads. The missile could be ready for deployment as early as 2018.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The Dongfeng-41 in a mobile missile launcher2. The Dongfeng-41 is a solid fuel missile, 15 meters long and weighing around 30 metric tons3. The Dongfeng-41 has a 12,000 km range4. The Dongfeng-41 can carry up to 10 MIRV warheadsVOICEOVER (in English): "China is adding a new intercontinental ballistic missile  the Dongfeng-41  to its nuclear arsenal. It recently underwent its eighth test launch since it was first announced in 2012." "The ICBM is a three-stage solid-fuel missile, 15 meters long and weighing around 30 metric tonnes."   "The Dongfeng-41 has a 12,000 km range, meaning it could strike almost any location in the world. It has a top speed of over Mach 10.""The Dongfeng-41 can carry up to 10 MIRV warheads. The missile could be ready for deployment as early as 2018."  SOURCES: Newsweek, Wikipediahttp://www.newsweek.com/china-tests-10-warhead-missile-could-strike-anywhere-world-possible-2018-721128https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DF-41***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 09:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/24/3490763/3490763_9C1015E25A0142278C656D616422EC50_171124_3490763_China_tests_next_generation_ICBM_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/31B/DB8/31BDB80F5FDA4E4088DB3287ED811B81_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, China Dongfeng 41, Dongfeng 41, DF-41, China ICBM, China ICBM test, China arms race]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3490610</guid>
      <title>Hand sanitizer could affect breathalyzer results, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA new study finds that alcohol-based hand sanitizers can emit vapors that can disperse through the air and enter the mouth, causing breathalyzers to error out or even give a positive reading.  The findings were published last week in the Journal of Forensic Sciences. Previous studies have found that hand sanitizers can affect readings on handheld devices, Gizmodo reported. This study looked at evidential breath alcohol instruments in police stations. Researchers first administered breathalyzers to 65 subjects in a controlled, ventilated room. Then one of two operators used a golf ball-sized dollop of foam sanitizer or two pumps of liquid sanitizer and rubbed the solution into their skin until dry.The operators then administered one more round of tests. Of the 130 tests, 13 gave a positive reading, even though the subject did not consume any alcohol. Another 41 tests caused the machine to error out. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Police officer administering breathalyzer in station2. The study focused on evidential breath alcohol instruments in police stations3. Officer using hand sanitizer before administering breathalyzer 4. Of the 130 tests, 13 gave false positive readings, while 41 tests errored outVOICEOVER (in English): "A new study finds that alcohol-based hand sanitizers can emit vapors that can disperse through the air and enter the mouth, causing breathalyzers to error out or even give a positive reading."  "The study looked at evidential breath alcohol instruments in police stations. Researchers first administered breathalyzers to 65 subjects in a controlled, ventilated room." "Then one of two operators used a golf ball-sized dollop of foam sanitizer or two pumps of liquid sanitizer and rubbed the solution into their skin until dry." "The operators then administered one more round of tests. Of the 130 tests, 13 gave a positive reading, even though the subject did not consume any alcohol. Another 41 tests caused the machine to error out." SOURCES: Gizmodohttps://gizmodo.com/hand-sanitizer-alters-the-results-of-breathalyzer-tests-1820642866***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 06:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/24/3490610/3490610_2AE437D9117D45479825978AFA899258_171124_3490610_Hand_sanitizer_could_affect_breathalyzer_results_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C06/52D/C0652DE7A5964CACAC7CFB839C56ADA0_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, breathalyzer, hand sanitizer, alcohol based hand sanitizer, hand sanitizer breathalyzer results, hand sanitizer affects breathalyzer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3490567</guid>
      <title>World's first cloned dog has been cloned again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEA team of scientists has re-cloned the world's first dog clone, in a bid to find out if the process has an impact on a clone's health or lifespan.BBC reports that dog clone Snuppy was created in 2005 using a stem cell from an Afghan hound, and born via a surrogate labrador mother.The original dog, named Tai, died from cancer when he was 12 years old. Snuppy would later live to age 10 before also succumbing to cancer, though not the same kind.When Snuppy was five years old, researchers collected his stem cells while also taking eggs from female dogs and taking out their nuclei.Using a process called somatic cell nuclear transfer, nuclei from the stem cells were transferred into the empty eggs, then stimulated into dividing  creating over 94 embryos.The embryos were implanted into surrogates, resulting in the birth of four live re-clones. Though one died from diarrhea days after the birth, the remaining three are now nine months old and still healthy.Researchers published their report in the journal Scientific Reports. They say they will closely monitor the puppies and measure virtually all aspects of their lives, including growth, metabolism, immune system, and disease development. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Snuppy cloned using stem cell from Afghan hound, born via surrogate mother2. Scientists collect stem cells from Snuppy, egg cells from female dogs3. Snuppy's stem cell nuclei transferred into empty eggs using somatic cell nuclear transfer 4. Embryos resulted in 4 live births, one of which died from diarrheaVOICEOVER (in English): SOURCES: Scientific Reports, American Council on Science and Health, BBChttps://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-15328-2https://www.acsh.org/news/2017/11/19/worlds-first-cloned-dog-has-been-cloned-again-12167http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/science/nature/4742453.stm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 06:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/24/3490567/3490567_E8860BA4A7D044608AD078EDDD500C77_171124_3490567_World_s_first_cloned_dog_has_been_cloned_again_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AE2/158/AE215861CD954A4F9978694119D79AE0_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, cloned dog, cloning, snuppy, dog clone, animal clone, reclone, afghan hound, animal cloning, cloning, recloning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3490526</guid>
      <title>Belgian, Hawaiian authorities investigating if videogame loot boxes are gambling</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAuthorities in Belgium and the U.S. state of Hawaii are investigating whether a common video game feature called loot boxes are gambling.Loot boxes are virtual containers earned or purchased while playing a videogame. They typically contain a randomized assortment of virtual items aimed at enhancing the player's experience and in-game abilities. Because of the elements of chance and money involved, Belgian and Hawaiian authorities are concerned the practise may expose minors to gambling.According to the Telegraph, Hawaii state representative Chris Lee wants to put legislation in place to protect minors from the practice. The U.S. island state is currently investigating gaming publisher Electronic Arts for "predatory practices" against minors due to its use of loot boxes in their game Star Wars Battlefront 2.According to the Brisbane Times, an regulatory analyst for the state of Victoria in Australia said loot boxes do constitute gambling, but are difficult to regulate.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of loot box selection2. What a loot box contains3. Overview of loot box investigation 4. Depiction of child playing a video game with loot box systemVOICEOVER (in English): "Loot boxes are virtual containers earned or purchased while playing a videogame.""They typically contain a randomized assortment of virtual items aimed at enhancing the player's experience and in-game abilities.""Because of the elements of chance and money involved, Belgian and Hawaiian authorities are investigating whether the practise exposes minors to gambling.""According to the Brisbane Times, an regulatory analyst for the state of Victoria in Australia said loot boxes do constitute gambling, but are difficult to regulate."SOURCES: Telegraph, PC Gamer, Brisbane Timeshttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/hawaii-crack-predatory-loot-boxes-video-games/http://www.pcgamer.com/belgium-says-loot-boxes-are-gambling-wants-them-banned-in-europe/https://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/technology/loot-boxes-in-video-games-constitute-gambling-regulator-says-20171123-gzr3ek.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 05:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/24/3490526/3490526_5DB521AEE9E34CC0958D345E665A6FA2_171124_3490526_Belgian__Hawaiian_authorities_investigating_if_v_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2A9/8EF/2A98EF58A41D4696A69DA59C9A83A150_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, loot box gambling laws, video game loot box, star wars battlefront 2 loot box, electronic arts, loot box, loot box gaming, loot box investigation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3490520</guid>
      <title>London city buses to be powered by coffee</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEWaste coffee grounds will be powering London's buses, as the city finds newer and cleaner ways to run its public transport system.BBC reports that clean technology company Bio-bean has created a new biofuel by blending oil extracted from used coffee grounds with B20 biodiesel.The firm estimates that it would take just 2.55 million cups of coffee to create enough of the biofuel to power a London bus for an entire year.Bio-bean is working with Shell and Transport for London for its pilot project, which will see about 6,000 liters of coffee oil being used by some buses starting Monday.Many of the city's buses are already running on biofuel made from wastes such as cooking oil or beef to reduce emissions, but this is the first time a coffee-derived fuel is being introduced.Londoners reportedly produce about 200,000 tonnes of coffee waste a year, and most end up in landfills where they emit harmful methane gas. The new initiative is not only beneficial to the environment, but also convenient for buses, which don't need to be modified to use the fuel.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Oil extracted from used coffee grounds combined with biodiesel 2. 2.55 million cups of coffee blended with diesel can power a London bus for one year 3. Biofuel made from other waste products used in many London buses to cut emissionsVOICEOVER (in English): "Clean technology company Bio-bean has created a new biofuel by blending oil extracted from used coffee grounds with B20 biodiesel.""The firm estimates that it would take just 2.55 million cups of coffee to create enough of the biofuel to power a London bus for an entire year.""Many of the city's buses are already running on biofuel made from wastes such as cooking oil or beef to reduce emissions, but this is the first time a coffee-derived fuel is being introduced."SOURCES: Bio-bean, BBC, Reutershttp://www.bio-bean.com/bio-diesel/http://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-london-42044852https://www.reuters.com/article/us-biofuels-buses/full-of-beans-coffee-grounds-to-help-power-londons-buses-idUSKBN1DK0B9***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 05:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/24/3490520/3490520_A3FCA49FAB574E779A17658A37B53558_171124_3490520_London_city_buses_to_be_powered_by_coffee_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/050/2E4/0502E443A7A242FDAEB094F094E9A3D5_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, coffee bus, coffee oil, coffee biofuel, coffee diesel, biofuel, London coffee bus, waste coffee, coffee grounds, biodiesel, clean fuel, clean energy, powered by coffee]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3492585</guid>
      <title>40 injured in Tenerife nightclub floor collapse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEDozens were injured early Sunday when the floor of a Spanish nightclub abruptly collapsed under their feet.The Guardian reports that the Butterfly Disco pub in Tenerife, in Spain's Canary Islands, was full of revellers around 2:30 a.m. Sunday morning.A 4 meter-by-4 meter area of floor suddenly gave way, sending people crashing into an empty area below. At least 40 clubbers were wounded after falling one storey into the basement. Among the victims were tourists from France, Romania, Belgium, and the UK.The injured were taken to the hospital and treated for fractured thigh bones, broken and sprained ankles, as well as cuts and bruises.According to the mayor of Tenerife, the popular gay nightclub had a legitimate license and did not appear to be overcrowded when the incident occurred. Firefighters are currently sifting through the debris to look for clues on how and why the dance floor collapsed.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. People inside Tenerife nightclub2. Nightclub floor collapses into empty basement area3. People fall one storey to the basement, 40 wounded4. Injuries include femur fractures, broken and sprained ankles, cuts, bruisesVOICEOVER (in English): "The Butterfly Disco pub in Tenerife, on Spain's Canary Islands, was full of revellers around 2:30 a.m. Sunday morning.""A 4 meter-by-4 meter area of floor suddenly gave way, sending people crashing into an empty area below.""At least 40 clubbers were wounded after falling one storey into the basement.""The injured were taken to the hospital and treated for fractured thigh bones, broken and sprained ankles, as well as cuts and bruises."SOURCES: BBC, The Guardianhttp://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-42128323https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/nov/26/dozens-of-revellers-hurt-after-nightclub-floor-gives-way-in-tenerife***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 08:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/27/3492585/3492585_D90304F0905147D2B1EAD74BD39AAF52_171127_3492585_40_injured_in_Tenerife_nightclub_floor_collapse_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3CA/694/3CA6949B21D74B7799AB140A43F445C1_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, nightclub collapse, floor collapse, dance floor collapse, tenerife nightclub, canary islands, tenerife, broken bones, fracture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3492578</guid>
      <title>Robot algae eliminates cancer cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEScientists have transformed an algae commonly used as a dietary supplement into a cancer-eliminating robot.Details of the research were published this month in the journal, Science Robotics.Researchers coated spirulina microalgae in iron nanoparticles before inserting it inside a rat's stomach. The iron coating combined with the natural shape of spirulina, allowed scientists to control the and direct microalgae with magnets.Spirulina emits a compound toxic only to cancer cells. Researchers found it eliminated 90% of cancerous cells inside lab dish after two days.The biodegradability of robot depends on the thickness of iron nanoparticle coating. The thicker this is, the longer the robot can operate inside a subject.Lead researcher Dr So Li Zhang told Science it's not ready for doctors to use, reckons it might be ready for use in about ten years.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of spirulina being coated in iron, then transferring to rat2. Depiction of spirulina inside stomach and magnets moving it3. Depiction of spirulina eliminating cancer cells4. Depiction of spirulina losing iron coating and fading into stomachVOICEOVER (in English): "Researchers coated spirulina microalgae in iron nanoparticles before inserting it inside a rat's stomach.""The iron coating combined with spirulina's natural shape, allowed scientists to control the and direct microalgae with magnets.""Spirulina emits a compound toxic only to cancer cells. Researchers found it eliminated 90% of cancerous cells inside lab dish after two days.""The biodegradability of robot depends on how thick the iron nanoparticle coating is.""The thicker this is, the longer the robot can operate inside a subject."SOURCES: Sciencehttp://robotics.sciencemag.org/content/2/12/eaaq1155http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2017/11/robot-made-algae-can-swim-through-your-body-thanks-magnets***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 08:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/27/3492578/3492578_F31846FF7E6F4521B2BF214B56FD90BD_171127_3492578_Robot_algae_eliminates_cancer_cells_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A32/3FF/A323FFBCC6A94843895851DCE1D7C435_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, robot cancer treatment, cancer treatment, diet food cancer robot,  spirulina, spirulina diet food,  spirulina diet supplement]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3492577</guid>
      <title>Robotic heart aid to help weaker hearts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew research published this month in Science Robotics details a robot heart device that can help pump blood to hearts with weakened ventricles.  The plastic device is powered by compressed air pressure and is place around damaged ventricle. It then squeezes the heart to help it pump blood throughout the body.The mechanics of the device are said to be adaptive to the beating rhythm, reported Seeker, citing the research. It has only been tested on animals so far, but could one day hold potential for human treatment.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Overview of device2. Device on heart3. Device adapting to heart's rhythmVOICEOVER (in English): "The plastic device is placed around a damaged ventricle and is powered via air pressure.""It then squeezes the heart to help it circulate blood throughout the body.""The mechanics of the device are said to be adaptive to the organ's normal beating rhythm.""It so far has only been tested on animal hearts." SOURCES: Robotics, Seekerhttp://robotics.sciencemag.org/content/2/12/eaan6736https://www.seeker.com/health/medicine/this-soft-robot-hugs-the-heart-and-helps-it-beat***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 08:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/27/3492577/3492577_48B67530AFFB4AACBFC80EE968266C84_171127_3492577_Robotic_heart_aid_to_help_weaker_hearts_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0CA/604/0CA604AA90C54111941E4FCD166D6ADB_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News,  robot heart, boston childrens hospital, heart device, automated heart, mechanical heart, articial heart, heart aid, heart]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3492505</guid>
      <title>Bali volcano monitored after second eruption, shuts down flights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEVolcanic eruptions from Bali's Mount Agung has caused officials to cancel flights and evacuate around 24,000 residents. Mount Agung erupted on Saturday night and three times on Sunday, sending a thick ash cloud thousands of meters up into the atmosphere, the Guardian reported. Bali's international airport was forced to close. Massive plumes of ash have been blowing toward the east, which also caused Lombok International Airport on Pulau Lombok to temporarily close, according to CNN.An exclusion zone up to 10 km from the crater has been put in place, with officials warning anyone still in the area to leave. Agung is classified as a stratovolcano, also known as a composite volcano. They are conical volcanoes that are built up by many layers of hardened, lava, tephra, pumice and volcanic ash. Mount Agung erupted for the first time in 50 years in September, prompting an evacuation of more than 185,000 people. In 1963, a large eruption killed around 1,100 people, according to the Guardian.   RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Mount Agung eruptions have canceled flights and caused evacuations2. The eruptions sent volcanic ash thousands of meters up into the atmosphere3. Officials have put in place a 10 km exclusion zone4. Mount Agung is a composite volcanoVOICEOVER (in English): "Volcanic eruptions from Bali's Mount Agung has caused officials to cancel flights and evacuate around 24,000 residents." "Mount Agung erupted on Saturday night and three times on Sunday, sending a thick ash cloud thousands of meters up into the atmosphere.""An exclusion zone up to 10 km from the crater has been put in place, with officials warning anyone still in the area to leave." "Agung is classified as a stratovolcano, also known as a composite volcano. They are conical volcanoes built up by many layers of hardened lava, tephra, pumice and volcanic ash." SOURCES: CNN, Guardian, Telegraphhttp://edition.cnn.com/2017/11/26/asia/mount-agung-eruption-bali-indonesia/index.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/nov/26/balis-mount-agung-jetstar-flights-resume-after-volcanos-second-eruptionhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/11/26/thousands-tourists-stranded-bali-airport-mount-agung-erupts/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 07:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/27/3492505/3492505_ED9DB6E559014BBE89F802176C13640B_171127_3492505_Bali_volcano_monitored_after_second_eruption__sh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8CE/D59/8CED59E207EA44CE9E7C64C34B56512E_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Bali volcano, Bali Mt. Agung, Mount Agung eruption, Mount Agung evacuations, composite volcano, stratovolcano]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3493272</guid>
      <title>America debuts new military base in South Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEThe U.S. has been working on one of its largest military overseas construction projects at Camp Humphreys in South Korea, located about 50 miles south of Seoul.Once the $11 billion expansion is finished, the installation will house a majority of the approximately 30,000 U.S. troops in South Korea, the Daily Beast reported. The 3,454-acre base is the size of a small city. A veterinary clinic, a dental clinic and a food court opened up in October. The massive complex has new headquarter buildings, an airstrip, firing ranges, barracks, motor pools, communications facilities, schools, day care centers, stores, churches and even a golf course, according to the Daily Beast. U.S. forces are spread across 174 bases in South Korea. Camp Humphreys will allow the U.S. to concentrate their forces there. The U.S. military plans to cut the number of bases in South Korea to just 96 by 2020.   In the event of open war with North Korea, Camp Humphreys would give the U.S. forces the ability for rapid deployment to the front lines.  RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Camp Humphreys location2. Camp Humphreys will house a majority of U.S. troops3. Buildings located on the base4. Camp Humphreys barracks5. Fighter jets taking off from Camp Humphreys runwayVOICEOVER (in English): "The U.S. has been working on one of its largest military overseas construction projects at Camp Humphreys in South Korea, located about 50 miles south of Seoul.""Once the $11 billion expansion is finished, the installation will house a majority of the approximately 30,000 U.S. troops in the country.""The 3,454-acre base is the size of a small city. A veterinary clinic, a dental clinic and a food court opened up in October." "The massive complex has new headquarter buildings, an airstrip, firing ranges, barracks, motor pools and communications facilities.""In the event of open war with North Korea, Camp Humphreys would give the U.S. forces the ability for rapid deployment to the front lines."  SOURCES: Daily Beast, Washington Posthttps://www.thedailybeast.com/america-debuts-new-military-mega-base-in-south-koreahttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/as-north-korea-intensifies-its-missile-program-the-us-opens-an-11-billion-base-in-south-korea/2017/07/28/a155e34c-70b1-11e7-8c17-533c52b2f014_story.html?utm_term=.16c8b83d64f9***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 08:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/28/3493272/3493272_03426800BF2E436AAB8F79F5831B2D1C_171128_3493272_America_debuts_new_military_base_in_South_Korea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/91A/2E8/91A2E8B4289D463889C9C20ACBC5FAF3_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, Camp Humphreys, Camp Humphreys South Korea, US forces South Korea, US bases South Korea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3493201</guid>
      <title>Flies carry more diseases than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENew research has found that flies hold more harmful bacteria than scientists previously believed.Details of the findings were published in the journal Scientific Reports. The research team involved an international team of scientists from Singapore and the U.S.Scientists found over 600 bacteria inside an analysis of 116 flies. House flies were laden 351 different kinds of bacteria while the blowfly was found to contain 316 types.Scientists believe that flies bred with no germs could be used as a means to observe and measure public health. These would be released into the environment, before being captured at a later date for analysis.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Depiction of a house fly landing on a steak2.House fly and blow fly bacteria numbers3. Fly being analysed for diseaseVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists found over 600 bacteria inside an analysis of 116 flies.""The insects can transmit harmful bacteria to food via their feet, legs or wings." "House flies were laden 351 different kinds of bacteria while the blowfly was found to contain 316 types.""Scientists believe that flies bred with no germs could be used as a means to observe and measure public health.""These would be released into the environment, before being captured at a later date for analysis."SOURCES: Scientific Reports (Nature), BBC, Science Daily https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-16353-xhttp://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-42113217https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2017/11/171124084757.htm***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 07:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/28/3493201/3493201_6A1827DF086B4D3D9774632E3D0C9A44_171128_3493201_Flies_carry_more_diseases_than_previously_though_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/51E/0BA/51E0BA6C9A794523B546AA92AD5E4797_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, flies spread disease, fly disease, fly bacteria, flies and disease, flies and health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3493963</guid>
      <title>North Korea launches ballistic missile into</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEAfter 74-day hiatus, North Korea has test-launched another ballistic missile, which some believe is possibly its more powerful one yet.Reuters reports that an intercontinental ballistic missile was launched from Pyongsong early Wednesday, reportedly flying on a lofted trajectory and reaching a maximum height of 4,500 kilometers.The missile flew nearly 1,000 kilometers for approximately 53 minutes before landing off the coast of Aomori, within Japan's exclusive economic zone.Two previous ICBMs test-launched this year traveled a shorter distance, flying for 37 minutes on July 4, and 47 minutes on July 28.Had the missile flown on a standard trajectory, experts say it would have a range of more than 13,000 kilometers  enough to reach Washington D.C. and the rest of the continental U.S., and even Europe or Australia, according to the Guardian.South Korea responded to the launch by conducting its own missile test off the country's east coast.Japan detected radio signals on Tuesday suggesting the North might be preparing for a ballistic missile test. The government has since condemned the launch.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. North Korea-launched missile reached maximum height of 4,500 km on a lofted trajectory2. Missile landed inside Japan's exclusive economic zone3. Missile range up to 13,000 km if flown on a standard trajectory, could reach U.S.4. Missile would also reach Europe, AustraliaVOICEOVER (in English): "An intercontinental ballistic missile was launched from Pyongsong early Wednesday, reportedly flying on a lofted trajectory and reaching a maximum height of 4,500 kilometers.""The missile flew nearly 1,000 kilometers for approximately 53 minutes before landing off the coast of Aomori, within Japan's exclusive economic zone.""Had the missile flown on a standard trajectory, experts say it would have a range of more than 13,000 kilometers  enough to reach Washington D.C. and the rest of the continental U.S., and even Europe or Australia"SOURCES: Reuters, Washington Post, New York Times, The Guardianhttps://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles/north-korea-tests-suspected-icbm-splashes-down-near-japan-idUSKBN1DS2MBhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/north-korea-fires-missile-for-the-first-time-in-more-than-two-months/2017/11/28/0c136952-d46c-11e7-9461-ba77d604373d_story.html?sw_bypass=true&utm_term=.ffc4450f8a4dhttps://www.nytimes.com/2017/11/28/world/asia/north-korea-missile-test.htmlhttps://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/nov/28/north-korea-has-fired-ballistic-missile-say-reports-in-south-korea***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/29/3493963/3493963_17B895AC54714F098A3FB6F8BFE9F7B0_171129_3493963_North_Korea_launches_ballistic_missile_into_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/36A/535/36A535003CEF43DCB1F0A955B05AA5D2_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, north korea missile, missile launch, ICBM, ballistic missile, north korea missile program, north korean missile, japan EEZ]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3493969</guid>
      <title>The Ogallala aquifer is drying up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Ogallala aquifer, the worlds largest source of groundwater, is shrinking due to overuse by farmers in eight U.S. states.The aquifer underlies parts of Colorado, Kansas, Nebraska, Texas, New Mexico, Texas, Oklahoma, Wyoming and South Dakota. There is no shared agreement between the states on how to use it.The Denver Post examined federal data on the aquifer and found that it had shrank at double the rate over the last 6 years, compared with the last sixty. The water loss has impacted those living in rural areas. One resident told the Denver Post that he doesnt know if hell get water when he turns on a faucet.Many streams and rivers linked to the aquifer have dried up and more are expected to do so if nothing changes. Various species of fish, including the minnow and the catfish, are also disappearing.The Denver Post reports that even if farmers in 8 the states drastically reduced their pumping, itd take centuries for the planet to renew the aquifer.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. The aquifer on the map2. Aquifer use over years3. Man turning on tap and getting nothing4. Depiction of water loss and drought river.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/29/3493969/3493969_6C820A4D787B416A8640F08F0805D0FC_171129_3493969_The_Ogallala_aquifer_is_drying_up_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7B7/7C1/7B77C1169CB64BEFB4E02E00DC8248B9_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,News,groundwater depletion,ogallala aquifer,aquifer depletion,great american desert,ogallala states]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3493869</guid>
      <title>Seattle Space Needle to undergo $100 million renovation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEFifty-five years after opening, Seattle's iconic Space Needle is undergoing a massive multi-million dollar renovation.Seattle Times reports that workers recently raised a donut-shaped platform to begin work on the Space Needle's $100 million renovation project.Updates will focus mostly on the observation deck and restaurant, and are set to be completed by May 2018.To give visitors more sweeping views of the city, the observation deck's pony walls and cages will be replaced with floor-to-ceiling glass panels.SkyCity, the Needle's restaurant, will be fitted with glass floors and a new motor, and will become the world's first glass-floor rotating restaurant once it reopens.The current renovation project is expected to keep the iconic landmark relevant for the next 50 years or so. Other changes include a new coat of paint on the exterior, and more elevators.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Space needle begins construction on $100 million renovation2. Renovations to be completed in May 20183. Observation deck to get floor to ceiling glass paneling4. SkyCity restaurant to get rotating glass floorVOICEOVER (in English): "Workers have raised a donut-shaped platform to begin work on the Space Needle's $100 million renovation project.""Updates will focus mostly on the observation deck and restaurant, and are set to be completed by May 2018.""To give visitors more sweeping views of the city, the observation deck's pony walls and cages will be replaced with floor-to-ceiling glass panels.""The Needle's restaurant will be fitted with glass floors and a new motor, and will become the world's first glass-floor rotating restaurant once it reopens."SOURCES: Space Needle, KING, Seattle Timeshttp://seewhatsup.space/http://www.king5.com/news/local/seattle/seattles-iconic-skyline-landmark-to-undergo-massive-upgrade/448118158https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/work-crews-revamping-space-needle-like-building-a-ship-inside-a-glass-bottle/***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 06:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/29/3493869/3493869_289A01E9963E4475B50882B55084E35D_171129_3493869_Seattle_Space_Needle_to_undergo__100_million_ren_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6AA/BD6/6AABD60B49AC4BA398F8136AD7BCC9A8_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, space needle, seattle, space lift, century project, space needle renovation, observation deck, glass observation deck, revolving restaurant, skycity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3494830</guid>
      <title>How the Bitcoin bubble could burst</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONECryptocurrency Bitcoin swelled to $11,000 per coin on Wednesday, prompting intense speculation about the latest bubble and how and why it could soon burst.According to Bloomberg, developers divided on how to upgrade the Bitcoin network have led to fragmentation of the original currency into different versions, too much of which could be a problem. Bitcoin's history of being used to buy illicit materials from the dark web means regulators are watching and could crackdown any time, especially if it grows big enough to impact a nation's monetary policy.As an intangible asset, Bitcoins have previously been targeted by hackers, and may again fall victim to digital theft.Though the value bitcoin is volatile, at the moment, it's at an all-time high. But because the supply is limitless, there is a risk of collapse in value if demand should ever go down.Experts have likened the bitcoin craze to the dotcom bubble, Tulip Mania, and other economic bubbles  all of which burst eventually.If they're to be believed, Bitcoin's downward spiral is only a matter of time.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Division on Bitcoin network updates could lead to excessive fragmentation2. Regulators may crack down on Bitcoin 3. Bitcoin is an intangible asset that can easily be hacked4. Bitcoin value too volatileVOICEOVER (in English): "Developers divided on how to upgrade the Bitcoin network have led to fragmentation of the original currency into different versions, too much of which could be a problem. "Bitcoin's history of being used to buy illicit materials from the dark web means regulators are watching and could crackdown any time, especially if it grows big enough to impact a nation's monetary policy.""As an intangible asset, Bitcoins have previously been targeted by hackers, and may again fall victim to digital theft.""Though the value bitcoin is volatile, at the moment, it's at an all-time high. But because the supply is limitless, there is a risk of collapse in value if demand should ever go down."SOURCES: Bloomberg, CNBChttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-11-29/for-bitcoin-skeptics-the-question-is-what-will-pop-this-bubblehttps://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-11-14/the-forks-and-fights-behind-bitcoin-s-turbulence-quicktake-q-ahttps://www.cnbc.com/2017/11/29/bitcoin-passes-10000-cryptocurrency-crash-considered-by-experts.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 09:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/30/3494830/3494830_F6B913AB48134234A2398AE2180861AA_171130_3494830_How_the_Bitcoin_bubble_could_burst_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2D6/A78/2D6A785806CF41F7B5BDE6F7EA20D6A0_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, bitcoin, bitcoin bubble, cryptocurrency, currency, digital currency, economic bubble, bitcoin cash, bitcoin gold]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3494650</guid>
      <title>Asteroid 3200 Phaethon to pass close to Earth in December</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONENASA has announced that a giant space rock will be passing close to Earth next month, but that it is not cause for concern.CBS reports that 3200 Phaethon is an asteroid with a diameter of 3 miles that has been labelled 'potentially dangerous' because its orbit crosses paths with the Earth.Phaeton will be the closest to Earth on December 16, when it is projected to be within 6.4 million miles or 27 lunar distances of our planet. It hasn't gotten this close since 1974, and isn't expected to swing by again until 2093.Phaethon may be named after a Greek demigod who nearly destroyed Earth, but since the giant rock is in a relatively stable orbit, there is no threat of a catastrophic collision.Astronomers believe the asteroid to be the parent body for the annual Geminid meteor shower, which happens when Earth passes through Phaethon's debris field.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. 3200 Phaethon measurement, orbit2. Asteroid to pass within 6.4 million miles of Earth on December 163. Phaethon believed to be parent body for annual Geminid meteor showerVOICEOVER (in English): "3200 Phaethon is an asteroid with a diameter of 3 miles that has been labelled 'potentially dangerous' because its orbit crosses paths with the Earth.""Phaeton will be the closest to Earth on December 16, when it is projected to be within 6.4 million miles or 27 lunar distances of our planet.""Astronomers believe the asteroid to be the parent body for the annual Geminid meteor shower, which happens when the Earth passes through Phaethon's debris field."SOURCES: CBS, NASAhttps://www.cbsnews.com/news/asteroid-expected-closest-pass-earth-40-years/https://ssd.jpl.nasa.gov/sbdb.cgi?sstr=3200%20phaethon;old=0;orb=1;cov=0;log=0;cad=0#orb***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 06:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/30/3494650/3494650_FE1F817D968B4669991904C9AE2BC9A0_171130_3494650_Asteroid_3200_Phaethon_to_pass_close_to_Earth_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AD6/17E/AD617E52388D4E4887188D32806E275D_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, asteroid, 3200 phaethon, asteroid passes earth, asteroid orbit, asteroid collision, giant asteroid, space rock, geminid, meteor shower, geminid meteor shower, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3494606</guid>
      <title>Origami inspired artificial muscle can lift 1,000 times its own weight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEResearchers from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Harvard University have developed origami-inspired artificial muscles that can lift up to one thousand times their own weight. The devices could be used on next-generation soft robots, to be deployed within the body or outer space, the LA Times reported. The scientists wanted to make robots that were soft and compliant yet had strength similar to hard-bodied systems. The group used origami techniques to create muscle-like devices that could allow for limb flexibility without the need for hard parts. They made devices that could shorten, curl, twist or bend when compressed and sealed them in a polymer bag and filled them with air or other fluids. Vacuuming the air out then allowed for movement to grip, lift and twist objects. The team discovered the origami muscles could squeeze down to a then of their original size or lift up to a thousand times their own weight. Soft robotic limbs could be used in the future on small scales within the body or at large scales for outer space construction. RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Soft robotic hand2. Soft robotic snake arm picking up a bottle3. The devices can squeeze down to a tenth of their original size or lift up to 1000 times their own weight4.  Robotic limb lifting a flower and a heavy weightVOICEOVER (in English): "Scientists from MIT and Harvard wanted to make robots that were soft and compliant yet had strength similar to hard-bodied systems, so they turned to origami for inspiration." "They made devices that could grip, lift and twist objects and sealed them in a polymer bag and filled them with air or other fluids. Vacuuming the air out allowed for movement." "The team discovered the origami muscles could squeeze down to a tenth of their original size or lift up to a thousand times their own weight." "Soft robotic limbs could be used in the future on small scales within the body or on large scales for outer space construction." SOURCES: LA Timeshttp://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-artificial-muscles-origami-20171127-htmlstory.html***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 05:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/30/3494606/3494606_7290420F90004B50B98E1BB6D92F1947_171130_3494606_Origami_inspired_artificial_muscle_can_lift_1_00_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/522/E67/522E678568D94438A8EDD25D0A08D29D_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, artificial muscle, soft robots, soft robotic limb, origami inspired robots, soft robotics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3494595</guid>
      <title>Supermoon coming December 3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit http://archive.nextanimationstudio.com or contact inquiries@nextanimation.com.tw to license this or any News Direct videoFor story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twRESTRICTIONS: NONEBudding astronomers will be able to take in a super moon this on December 3. During a supermoon event, the lunar body can become bigger and up to 30% brighter.This is because the moon orbits closer to the Earth than it does in a regular orbit.NASA advises that a supermoon is best viewed outside a city due as powerful urban lights can diminish how bright it actually is.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Supermoon size 2. Supermoon orbit3. People watching the supermoon in the countrysideVOICEOVER (in English): "During a supermoon event, the lunar body can become bigger and up to 30% brighter.""This is because the moon orbits closer to the Earth than it does in a regular orbit.""NASA advises that a supermoon is best viewed outside a city as powerful urban lights can diminish how bright it actually is."SOURCES: NASA, National Geographic, Newsweekhttps://www.jpl.nasa.gov/edu/news/2017/11/15/whats-a-supermoon-and-just-how-super-is-it/https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/11/how-to-see-brightest-supermoon-2017-december-space-science/http://www.newsweek.com/supermoon-december-full-cold-moon-723324***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 05:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/11/30/3494595/3494595_7048BA56BB554AFBA8AB117ED1297911_171130_3494595_Supermoon_coming_December_3_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/262/E22/262E22555042472A830FBFC075729EFC_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[News, supermoon, supermoon lunar eclipse, supermoon, moon, moon in the sky, supermoon nasa, moon, nasa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
