<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Reuters Connect Content</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 19:37:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3412943</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[New Ebola suit made by Johns Hopkins team offers more protection and comfort in hot, humid climates]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team at John Hopkins University has developed a protective suit for Ebola workers that is more comfortable and offers more protection than existing “moon suits.”The new anti-Ebola suit has a large integrated plastic shield that stretches around the face, providing a wide viewing area.It uses a belt-worn battery pack, which can be recharged with a cellphone charger, that blows dry and filtered air into the hood.The designers of the new suit put a person wearing the new Ebola suit and another person wearing the standard Ebola suit in a room with a temperatures of 98 degrees Fahrenheit and 85 percent humidity. The new suit allowed the wearer to breathe normally, while person in the old suit felt unwell within minutes.A breakaway zipper allows the wearer to open the suit from the back. The wearer then needs to stick the wrist tabs on the floor or stand on it to get out of the entire suit by standing up straight. This ensures the wearer would not make any contact with the outer layer of the suit.The new suit was one of three solutions for Ebola workers that will share a $1.7 million prize in a competition held by the U.S. Agency for International Development. The other two were an antiseptic gel that protects the skin and an antimicrobial anti-contamination spray.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>50</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/12/18/3412943/3412943_75095320F6D440C6B0997E41332B78AD_170808_3412943_New_Ebola_suit_made_by_Johns_Hopkins_team_offers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5CB/1CE/5CB1CE0849DB4C5E9BF816EBED610E60_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,ebola,ebola suit,john hopkins,USA-TECHNOLOGY/EBOLA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412941</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[NASA Dawn spacecraft captures first picture of dwarf planet Ceres]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[NASA’s Dawn spacecraft is currently on its way to the asteroid belt where it will eventually meet with Ceres, its largest celestial body. The dwarf planet has an average diameter of about 950 km (590 miles).Dawn captured the first image of Ceres on December 1. At just 9 pixels in width, the tiny photo was taken at a distance of about 1.2 million kilometers (740,000 miles), roughly three times the distance between Earth and the moon.The spacecraft is expected to deliver much high-resolution images in early 2015, when it’s significantly closer to Ceres.The $466 million Dawn mission launched by NASA in September 2007 aims to study not only the dwarf planet, but also protoplanet Vesta.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 11:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/12/15/3412941/3412941_FD3FE6D3598C4CF4B7976BABB8AF099E_170808_3412941_NASA_Dawn_spacecraft_captures_first_picture_of_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DF8/904/DF8904DF7C5A43B391B295F79617CDED_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Ceres,Space,NASA,Dawn spacecraft,asteroid,celestial body,dwarf planet,SPACE-CERES/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412939</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[NASA’s New Horizons spacecraft to begin Pluto mission]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Nine years and 3 billion miles after it was launched into space, NASA’s New Horizons spacecraft has awoken from hibernation and is preparing to travel to Pluto and the Kuiper Belt.The New Horizons spacecraft, which weighs about half a ton, is about the size and shape of a baby grand piano.According to NASA’s New Horizons website, the spacecraft has gone into hibernation 18 times, Ars Technica reported, for a total of 1,873 days, since its launch in January 2006 in order to minimize wear on its components and reduce the risk of system failures.It is expected to make its closest approach to Pluto on July 14, 2015. It will then explore the Kuiper Belt from 2016 to 2020.The mission’s objectives include mapping the surface composition and temperatures of Pluto and Kuiper Belt objects, as well as their geology and morphology.New Horizons is expected to be 100 astronomical units away from the Sun by 2038 and will be able to send data about the outer heliosphere if it is still operational by then, CNET reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 11:57:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/12/12/3412939/3412939_88B0C91F61914965B772A4D512F47991_170808_3412939_NASA___s_New_Horizons_spacecraft_to_begin_Pluto__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/500/D9F/500D9FEF3C2C41059821E65F28DDE622_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,ew Horizons spacecraft,Pluto,NASA,Kuiper Belt,space,Pluto mission,Charon,NASA-NEWHORIZONS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412937</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Japan launches Hayabusa 2 spacecraft to collect samples from asteroid]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Hayabusa 2, a spacecraft designed to bring back samples from an asteroid to earth, was launched today from the Yoshinobu Launch Complex at JAXA’S Tanegashima Space Centre. Hayabusa means “Falcon” in English, according to RT News.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 11:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/12/03/3412937/3412937_307FC459D46244EDB3C02C7169FA2DF8_170808_3412937_Japan_launches_Hayabusa_2_spacecraft_to_collect__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7DC/72F/7DC72F3E1B4B456D882328A4C4243B0A_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Hayabusa 2,spacecraft,launch,Japan,asteroid,sampling,space,JAXA,JAPAN-SPACE/HAYABUSA2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412931</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Solar-powered trees provide shade, power and Wi-Fi for the community]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Unveiled in Zikhron Ya’akov, Israel, the eTree harnesses solar power to charge mobile devices, cool water, and provide free WIFI for communities.The tree’s form is inspired by the Acacia tree, with seven solar panels branching out from the structure’s brown metal trunk. The panels can generate as much as 1.4 kilowatts of power, or enough to run 35 laptops.The structure is also built with a rechargeable battery that stores power for cloudy days and lights up LEDs at night. Its developer, Sologic, intends to equip future eTrees with technology that condenses water from from air, and built-in cameras that connect eTree communities around the world.The $100,000 trees would not replace solar panels but may catch on as a fun park fixture worldwide.“We're in the middle of the desert and we're able to create everything we need just from the solar system,” Sologic CEO Michael Lasry said in an NPR report.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 11:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/11/28/3412931/3412931_5C6D18C3F3AB41F3A28099FE9AF60F63_170808_3412931_Solar_powered_trees_provide_shade__power_and_Wi__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1B1/1BD/1B11BD71522940AE8411FA0B64E3058E_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,eTree,Solargic,solar panels,Isreal,TECHNOLOGY-ETREE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412930</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Ambulance drone: A flying defibrillator that can save hundreds of people having heart attack]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Dubbing it ‘ambulance drone’, a student at a Dutch university has developed a flying defibrillator that can respond within minutes after a heart attack sets in.“Around 800,000 people suffer a cardiac arrest in the European Union every year and only 8 per cent survive,” said Belgian-national Alec Momont, the developer of the device. “The main reason for this is the relatively long response time of emergency services of about 10 minutes, while brain death and fatalities occur within four to six minutes.”The ambulance drone is equipped with a camera and a GPS navigation system. Powered by six propellers, the the drone can reach a maximum speed of 100 kilometres per hour.When someone suffers a heart attack, bystanders can call an emergency hotline and an ambulance drone is next dispatched.Using a camera mounted on the drone, a staffer can then instruct bystanders to attach the defibrillator to the patient.The drone can transport the device to someone in need inside a 12 km2  zone within one minute, significantly increasing the survival rate of patients.Apart from the defibrillator, the developer hopes that the drone will be able to carry other medical supplies such as oxygen masks and insulin injections.Momont aims to create an ambulance drone network in the Netherlands within the next five years. Each drone costs around €15,000, but Momont does not believe price will be an issue. “I have calculated these at approximately €15,000 per drone, which is clearly a reasonable amount if you consider the number of lives that could be saved,” Momont said.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 11:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/11/03/3412930/3412930_C5B8836DD37B4DE6B858707DCDABA579_170808_3412930_Ambulance_drone__A_flying_defibrillator_that_can_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A4B/C0A/A4BC0A65A7EB44C1BE3655F154465F7D_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,ambulance drone,heart attack,cardiac arrest,Alec Momont,TU Delft University,Netherlands,TECHNOLOGY-AMBULANCE/DRONE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412929</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[New material developed by Danish scientists that can absorb, store and release oxygen]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[It might sound like something out a sci-fi film, but the day could soon arrive when oxygen can be obtained by just a few grains of a newly developed material.Scientists in Denmark announced they have developed a substance that absorbs, stores and releases huge amounts of oxygen.The substance is so effective that just a few grains are capable of storing enough oxygen for a single human breath while a bucket full of the new material could capture an entire room of O2.With the new material there are hopes those requiring medical oxygen might soon be freed from carrying bulky tanks, while SCUBA divers might also be able to use the material to absorb oxygen from water, allowing them to stay submerged for significantly longer.The substance was developed by tinkering with the molecular structure of cobalt, a chemical element that when found in meteoric iron, resembles a silver-gray metal.  Scientists are hailing the breakthrough, but it could be many years before viable commercial uses of the new substance become available.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 11:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>45</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/10/05/3412929/3412929_AE17FABC49F14B4A9E232A5945DAA712_170808_3412929_New_material_developed_by_Danish_scientists_that_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/36E/3A7/36E3A78C9AF34A258BE92E76CFDCD2AE_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,University of Denmark,cobalt,oxygen breakthrough,storing oxygen,SCUBA divers,no more oxygen tanks,scientific breakthrough,new discoveries,DENMARK-TECHNOLOGY/OXYGEN]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412928</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Carbon capture technology improves oil extraction]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A joint venture between NRG Energy and JX Nippon Oil & Gas aims to use carbon dioxide extracted from power plants for improved crude oil recovery.The carbon capture technology taps into flue gases released from NRG’s WA Parish coal plant near Houston. Flue gas, which consists of carbon dioxide and a mix of other gases, is pumped into a capture system, where CO2 is pulled out with a solvent that forms a temporary bond with CO2. The gas is then released from the solvent with a slight reheating.The purified CO2 is pumped deep into an oil field near Victoria, Texas where it binds with crude oil and increases the viscosity of the oil, making it easier to pump the oil out of the ground. The mixture is next pumped up to the surface and separated. CO2 is sent back into the extraction loop to pump out more oil.“Any solution that doesn't take carbon from the air is, in principle, not sustainable,” physicist Peter Eisenberger of the Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory at Columbia University, who is developing a method to extract CO2 from the sky, said in a Yale Environment 360 Report.Over the next several decades, oil recovery from aging fields is expected to consume around 33 billion metric tons of CO2 in total, according to an estimate conducted by John Thompson, director of the Fossil Fuel Transition Project for the non-profit Clean Air Task Force.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 11:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/09/30/3412928/3412928_05752E55E98D4B2EBD27304D2733FECA_170808_3412928_Carbon_capture_technology_improves_oil_extractio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/333/98B/33398B7D18AA4783B5D9D049B85C25DB_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,NRG energy,Houston,Victoria,Texas,JX Nippon oil,carbon extraction,carbon capture,crude oil,carbon dioxide,enhanced oil recovery,SCIENCE-CARBONCAPTURE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412927</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists discover nuclear waste-eating bacteria]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers from the University of Manchester have discovered a special “extremophile” bacteria that can survive in radioactive waste disposal sites and can feed on radioactive waste.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 11:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>47</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/09/12/3412927/3412927_CC1A7AB24E7447EFAC30B1D396D2D12E_170808_3412927_Scientists_discover_nuclear_waste_eating_bacteri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C28/AE2/C28AE28EAD994A9F891D35C071585BD0_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,nuclear waste-eating bacteria,radioactive waste disposal,isosaccharinic acid,ISA,extremophile ba,SCIENCE-BACTERIA/RADIOACTIVE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412925</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Japanese test detects Ebola in 30 minutes]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A collaboration between Japan’s Nagasaki University and Eiken Chemical has developed a test that can detect an Ebola infection in 30 minutes. After blood is taken from a patient, RNA is extracted from the sample and synthesised into DNA, which is mixed with Ebola-binding primers and other reagents in a technique developed by Eiken known as reverse transcription-loop-mediated isothermal amplification, or RT-LAMP. The mixture is heated to 60 to 65 degrees Celsius. Any genetic material from the Ebola virus in the sample is amplified during the reaction, causing the reagent to become cloudy, providing a visual confirmation of an Ebola reaction.Currently, polymerase chain reaction, or PCR, is the established method for detecting an Ebola infection. This method requires more specialized lab equipment and requires one to two hours for the testing to be completed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 11:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/09/03/3412925/3412925_1E588BED67A7446B989C99E86B9E13E4_170808_3412925_Japanese_test_detects_Ebola_in_30_minutes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0B0/FBD/0B0FBD7B5F754DDF8E93A57D0D80826B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Japan,Ebola virus,Eiken Chemical,diagnostic,blood test,Nagasaki University,SCIENCE-JAPAN/EBOLA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412924</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Massive red tide threatens ocean life and tourism in Florida]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The largest red tide Florida has seen in a decade is moving towards the western coast and could impact marine life and tourism, officials say.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>59</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/08/15/3412924/3412924_7E7152FBFE934093A986F4E8FF206BB7_170808_3412924_Massive_red_tide_threatens_ocean_life_and_touris_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9F1/F02/9F1F024FD8794107A0B36673A6A0A890_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,red tide,algae bloom,algae,Karenia brevis,Florida,Gulf of Mexico,Tampa Bay,Florida Fish and W,USA-FLORIDA/REDTIDE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412923</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[MIT develops device that reads to blind in real time]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology have developed a device that is able to scan text and turn it into audio in real time for visually impaired users.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 11:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/07/09/3412923/3412923_3BCCA3E0A7B24E54AB44EEDF2CE5D216_170808_3412923_MIT_develops_device_that_reads_to_blind_in_real__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7AD/350/7AD3502BDB224738A340A32F823C20BF_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,MIT lab,Massachusetts Institute of Technology,FingerReader,vision impairment,reading device,TECHNOLOGY-FINGERREADER/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412922</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[How deep sea mining works in 3D]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Hydrocarbons such as oil and gas have been harvested from under the sea for decades. But more and more companies are now trying to obtain licenses to mine minerals like copper, cobalt, manganese and gold from the seabed. A project to mine undersea iron ore sand deposits off the New Zealand coast was recently rejected by the country’s Environmental Protection Authority (EPA) because of uncertainty on the impact of the project on the environment, Reuters reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 11:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>116</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/07/01/3412922/3412922_FE398C453F0048A68CB699DCEE612D1C_170808_3412922_How_deep_sea_mining_works_in_3D_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6D1/E16/6D1E1604F72F452C83ABA6E6C68CBE04_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Sea bed,ocean floor,mining,seabed mining,iron-ore operation,SCIENCE-DEEPSEAMINING/3DEXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412921</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Sensors on ferry to monitor water quality in Puget Sound]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team at the University of Washington is using ferries equipped with a current sensor known as Acoustic Doppler Current Profilers, or ADCPS, in its hull to monitor the water quality in Puget Sound estuary, where fresh water mixes with the ocean.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 11:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>41</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/06/17/3412921/3412921_0AA9591F043D41B087968DBEA9622B33_170808_3412921_Sensors_on_ferry_to_monitor_water_quality_in_Pug_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/474/891/474891A34FAA4E02A419C44DDC41970B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Puget Sound,Washington,estuary,Acoustic Doppler Current Profilers,ADCP,algae bloom,University,SCIENCE-ADCPS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412256</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Mega-Earth 17 times the weight of Earth discovered]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Kepler space telescope has discovered an Earth-like planet that is so large astronomers are calling it a ‘mega-Earth.’ Kepler-10c, found in the constellation Draco, is situated 560 light-years from Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 13:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/06/06/3412256/3412256_C6C5B0AA7E674D079041A294BC04A439_170807_3412256_Mega_Earth_17_times_the_weight_of_Earth_discover_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6A8/87F/6A887F28AC344DA9BD9D07E4C9A54E80_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,mega-Earth,mega Earth,Kepler-10c,Kepler space telescope,NASA,space,SPACE-MEGAEARTH/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412255</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Bolivia opens world’s highest cable railway]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Bolivia inaugurated the first segment of the world’s highest cable railway line on Friday, which allows passengers to travel between the city of La Paz to neighboring city El Alto in about 10 minutes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 13:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/05/31/3412255/3412255_3ED9573AA3F04941A20C435C5118F562_170807_3412255_Bolivia_opens_world___s_highest_cable_railway_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FBB/9DB/FBB9DB7D67C24667B77483905374B269_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,bolivia,la paz,el alto,cable car,world highest cable railway,BOLIVIA-CABLERAILWAY/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412253</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[NASA unveils the latest design of Z-2 space suit]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[NASA has finalized the design of the latest space suit Z-2, a second-generation prototype of a series which it hopes will one day be worn by astronauts on Mars.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 13:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>64</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/05/28/3412253/3412253_550B3578B5F04B25A1F64BB3102CA2F9_170807_3412253_NASA_unveils_the_latest_design_of_Z_2_space_suit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2DC/B86/2DCB861290744A0FBB96C0B5FF3D058E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Z-2,NASA,space suit,space,Mars,NASA-SPACESUIT/Z2]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412252</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[West Antarctic ice sheet collapse likely inevitable]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A number of studies published in the past year show that the melting of the West Antarctic ice sheet is likely unstoppable. The glacier will probably disappear in a matter of centuries, adding 13 feet (4 metres) of water to sea levels, according to NASA.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 13:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/05/13/3412252/3412252_5338FFF43E134028B1A83802D9486956_170807_3412252_West_Antarctic_ice_sheet_collapse_likely_inevita_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E2C/2CF/E2C2CFB617B24CE5A87D8FCB524F723A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,West Antarctic,ice sheet,glacier,global warming,volcano,CLIMATECHANGE-WESTANTARTIC/ICESHEET]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412251</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Mind-controlled exoskeleton to allow paralysed person to walk at World Cup]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A robotic exoskeleton could allow a paraplegic to deliver the first kick of the World Cup in Brazil next month, as part of a project to showcase technology aimed at overcoming paralysis.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 13:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>50</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/05/12/3412251/3412251_CBEA5888D3224CB39C2AAE218154F95C_170807_3412251_Mind_controlled_exoskeleton_to_allow_paralysed_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B76/E3F/B76E3FA02DB347CFA573E9355558A957_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Brazil,World Cup,exoskeleton,Walk Again project,football,technology,SCIENCE-EXOSKELETON/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412250</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists new interpretation of Egyptian painting sheds new light on how pyramids were built]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A new interpretation of a painting inside an Egyptian tomb has shed new light on how ancient Egyptians moved heavy stones to build the pyramids.Stones used to create the Egyptian pyramids weighed on average about 2.5 tonnes each. Research by scientists at the University of Amsterdam shows workers moved the stones on wooden sleds with upturned edges at the front. However, the friction of the wood against dry sand in the desert would have caused significant drag, creating a sand berm in front of the sled as it moved forward. Workers would then need to clear the built up sand before the sled could be moved again.A new interpretation of an ancient Egyptian painting shows workers may have instead poured water onto the sand in front of sleds. Sand with just the right amount of dampness causes microdroplets of water to bind to the grains of sand, creating a form across the grains and making the sand stiffer, significantly reducing friction and drag as the sled was moved forward. This meant less manpower was needed to move the sleds forward.Artwork within the tomb of Djehutihotep, which was discovered in the Victorian Era, depicts a scene of slaves hauling a colossal statue of the Middle Kingdom ruler. In the painting, a man standing at the front of the sled is portrayed pouring liquid into the sand. Scientists say this discovery could even have implications for how modern society can efficiently transport everything, including sand, cement and flour.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 13:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/05/06/3412250/3412250_85AFD7DF120A40F6B44010CB910C58C4_170807_3412250_Scientists_new_interpretation_of_Egyptian_painti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/216/E84/216E840FA0094910B69905AD9520B2DA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,pyramids,moving pyramids,moving stones,Egyptians]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412249</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Europe launches Sentinel-1A satellite to monitor climate change]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The first in EU’s series of earth-monitoring satellites launched aboard a Soyuz rocket from French Guiana on Thursday evening, the European Space Agency said. Sentinel-1A is launched to a height of 700 km above earth where it orbit around earth via the two poles. “There is no Earth observation project as big as this,” Prof Anne Glover, the European Union's chief scientific adviser said in a BBC report.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 13:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/04/07/3412249/3412249_EA45C6D16B41444085D9110C641AD600_170807_3412249_Europe_launches_Sentinel_1A_satellite_to_monitor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/369/D68/369D6850C0DD4511A4249E43B30C0D4C_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,European Space Agency,Sentinel-1A,weather monitoring,weather satellite,Soyuz,French Guiana,dis,EUROPE-SPACE/SENTINEL1A]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412248</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[8.2-magnitude earthquake strikes near Chile, triggers tsunami]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An 8.2 magnitude earthquake shook Chile on Tuesday evening, sending tsunami waves to the coast where people have been asked to evacuate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 13:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>49</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/04/02/3412248/3412248_709F04AE517146FB9BC772261044C998_170807_3412248_8_2_magnitude_earthquake_strikes_near_Chile__tri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B55/3EC/B553EC2576774A89B5DCE7A59B334C54_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Chile,earthquake,tsunami,Iquique,fault line,South America,CHILE-EARTHQUAKE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412247</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Doomsday seed bank welcomes new addition]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Some 20,000 new seed samples were added to the collection held by the Svalbard Global Seed Vault in Norway late last month. The new additions included Japanese barley, Brazilian beans, wild potatoes and wild sweet potatoes from Peru, and red okra seeds from the United States.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 13:48:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/03/03/3412247/3412247_7ED37DD7A90B4ADEA57EFD71AFDCAAE0_170807_3412247_Doomsday_seed_bank_welcomes_new_addition_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/926/D6D/926D6D56B2E54818A3790E6886D5C5CA_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Svalbard Global Seed Vault,biodiversity,food security,climate change,science,Norway,NORWAY-SEEDVAULT/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412246</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Adaptive mechanisms help humans survive extreme cold]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Parts of the United States have experienced record-breaking cold weather this week caused by a polar vortex that saw temperatures fall to as low as -70 degrees Fahrenheit. Although certain human populations such as the Inuit in Canada and the Nenets in Russia have adapted certain traits to help them better survive in polar climates, humans as a species are not designed to survive such in subzero temperatures. However, humans do posses a number of mechanisms for adapting to extreme cold.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 13:48:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/14/01/08/3412246/3412246_393E2E417FF14EB382C12D6D1A08D64A_170807_3412246_Adaptive_mechanisms_help_humans_survive_extreme__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B5C/88C/B5C88C2757494F3CB1731F4790963551_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Cold,metabolism,vasoconstriction,cold adaptation,arctic,SCIENCE-VASOCONSTRICTION/COLDADAPTATION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412245</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Plastic microbeads from exfoliating products pollute the Great Lakes]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A joint study conducted by 5 Gyres Institute and the State University of New York at Fredonia has found large amounts of microplastic beads contaminating the waters of the Great Lakes. Surface samples were taken from 21 locations and analysed for microplastics of various shapes, sizes and colors found in commercial personal products.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 13:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/12/17/3412245/3412245_CE44447F941E4DC2B287982CCDA589EF_170807_3412245_Plastic_microbeads_from_exfoliating_products_pol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/598/1A6/5981A6B4D58149CA973048F5E594980B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Microbeads,microplastic,exfoliator,toothpaste,scrub,plastic,5 Gyres Institute,SUNY Fredonia,SCIENCE-MICROBEADS/GREATLAKES]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412244</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Vast freshwater reserves found in seabed]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers in the University of Flinders in Australia have found vast reserves of low-salt water beneath the seabed. Rivers and rain water over the past hundreds of thousands of years infiltrated the ground to form aquifers. Even as sea level rose when ice caps started melting 20,000 years ago, sediment and clay partially kept salt water from seeping into the groundwater.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 13:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/12/09/3412244/3412244_48E18972BB854BAEB799FF14F8D07DD7_170807_3412244_Vast_freshwater_reserves_found_in_seabed_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/680/3A9/6803A98F1E1D4D488883E85BFE5FFF3C_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Australia,University of Flinders,groundwater,freshwater,seawater,SCIENCE-SEABED-FRESHWATER/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412242</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Sydney researchers develop robotic herder]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team at the University of Sydney developed a robotic herder to move cows from the pasture to the dairy.In a recent trial, researchers found that the cows readily accepted the presence of the herding robot.  Named Rover by its creators, the robot matches the herd's pace which keeps the cows calm and prevents them from sustaining injuries. The robot is equipped with a Velodyne 3D LiDAR, which sends out lasers to detect and track the movement of cows. A GPS system onboard Rover also tracks the motion of the vehicle over rough terrain. Data collected from these sensors produce a 3D reconstruction of the herd and the robot's movement on the pasture. The tested prototype requires human control, but the final version of the robot is expected to be fully automated. Researchers are also looking to equip Rover to collect soil quality data and check for damaged fences."When we have discussed this concept with farmers they have been extremely excited and we have had a flurry of calls and emails asking how they can get hold of one," Dr Kendra Kerrisk, dairy researcher and associate professor at the University of Sydney, said in a BBC report.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 13:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/11/20/3412242/3412242_1645CB95D681467194399E81CCB49E35_170807_3412242_Sydney_researchers_develop_robotic_herder_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8FA/832/8FA832F60851463C87C685F28A7D57D5_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Sydney,Australia,Rover,cow herding,3d lidar mapping,AUSTRALIA-SCIENCE/ROBOTICHERDER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412241</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[What causes knuckles to making popping sounds?]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[This animation describes what happens when a person cracks their knuckle joints. All of the joints in the body are surrounded by connective tissues, ligaments and synovial fluid. Synovial fluid is a clear, thick liquid that contains dissolved gasses. When joints, such as the ones between finger bones are pulled apart as a person cracks his or her knuckles, the volume increases between the joints, lowering the pressure inside the synovial fluid and causing the gases within it to burst.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 13:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/10/25/3412241/3412241_7B5856AE2421438E970D6E9D33219C88_170807_3412241_What_causes_knuckles_to_making_popping_sounds__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8D5/F80/8D5F80DB95B7412EA93F29E46EE7A9B5_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,knuckle cracking,joints,health,arthritis,SCIENCE-KNUCKLEPOPPING/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412239</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists develop ‘electronic vacuum cleaner’ to suck up Beijing’s toxic smog]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Dutch designer Daan Roosegaarde has developed an ‘electronic vacuum cleaner’ that can be used to clean up the toxic smog in Beijing. It was reported that Roosegaarde is working with the mayor of Beijing to apply this technology in a new park in the city. The system uses copper coils to create a weak electromagnetic field, which reportedly can attract smog components in the air and pull them down to the ground where they can be cleaned.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 13:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/10/23/3412239/3412239_403C57E795D843D6A4850895E4DCA527_170807_3412239_Scientists_develop____electronic_vacuum_cleaner__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E0B/EC0/E0BEC05424064CBE891E646E6DAD5F08_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Beijing,China,toxic smog,electronic vacuum cleaner,Daan Roosegaarde,electromagnetic field,TECHNOLOGY-SMOG-VACUUM/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412238</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[$75,000 balloon ride to lift passengers 30 km into space]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[For $75,000, space tourism company World View will be launching passengers 30 km into space by air balloon for a two-hour view of the earth’s curve. Although the balloon will attain more than twice the altitude reached by conventional airplanes, passengers will not experience weightlessness in the stratosphere. “Outer space” is 100 km above the earth’s surface, just beyond the reach of gravity.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 13:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/10/23/3412238/3412238_658AA5217BFA4967B11AFE8D1398260D_170807_3412238__75_000_balloon_ride_to_lift_passengers_30_km_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E85/1EF/E851EF886B0D4FAABB9A92EA1A3531E2_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,space balloon,space tourism,outer space,TECHNOLOGY-WORLDVIEW/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412236</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Venice tests flood barrier system]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Venice performed a test run of a flood barrier system designed to keep the Adriatic tides from overwhelming the city. The project, known as MOSE, has been underway since 2003 and is expected to be complete by 2014.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 13:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>57</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/10/14/3412236/3412236_636467B138284D42AC30EDD99CF91EC2_170807_3412236_Venice_tests_flood_barrier_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7F9/DB5/7F9DB5F8B32A4253B23E3A239C352095_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Venice,Italy,Venetian lagoon,flood,barrier,MOSE,ITALY-VENICE/MOSE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412234</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[3D-printed toothbrush cleans teeth in six seconds]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The American Dental Association recommends that people brush their teeth at least three to four minutes a day, but now a company called Blizzident is marketing a device of the same name it says can achieve the same results in only six seconds.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 13:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/10/11/3412234/3412234_6A8A876D5A874651AFA7FFF3EA4242D0_170807_3412234_3D_printed_toothbrush_cleans_teeth_in_six_second_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/09D/DA3/09DDA3D3BD2E443FBFE7E3994FEE2BD3_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,3D printer,Blizzident,dentist,toothbrush,medical,health,TECHNOLOGY-BLIZZIDENT/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412233</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[MIT scientists invent blocks able to create giant lightweight structures]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at MIT have developed a lightweight structure of tiny blocks that can be snapped together, similar to the way child’s construction toys can be put together, and revolutionize the assembly of large objects, such as airplanes, spacecraft, and even dikes and levees.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 13:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/10/04/3412233/3412233_3F13EA4EE57B41F581124CB5E661B512_170807_3412233_MIT_scientists_invent_blocks_able_to_create_gian_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5DA/813/5DA8133847C841A9B4A60FA4040EC06F_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,ultralight materials,construction,assembly,MIT,SCIENCE-MIT/ULTRALIGHTMATERIAL]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3412232</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scotland to build Europe’s largest tidal energy project in Pentland Firth]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scotland plans to build Europe’s largest tidal energy project in the Pentland Firth, between Orkney and the Scottish mainland.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 13:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/09/20/3412232/3412232_6C3A58298E294E46A1BB354BF55DEF10_170807_3412232_Scotland_to_build_Europe___s_largest_tidal_energ_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/933/A01/933A01487E2C410FABFEF88C8966CA9F_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Scotland,tidal energy project,Meygen,Pentland Firth,tidal current energy,underwater turbine,SCOTLAND-ENERGY/TIDAL]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410135</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Cargo ship’s hull acts as giant sail]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Norwegian engineer has come up with a revolutionary design for a ship that could save up to 60 percent in fuel costs when compared to a normal cargo vessel.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 11:57:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/09/17/3410135/3410135_F2D3A7C2A92C45A296EA9367B3D0DB5C_170804_3410135_Cargo_ship___s_hull_acts_as_giant_sail_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0F3/3E1/0F33E132FF9346A4AD55E707ED4EA1CC_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Norway,Terje Lade,Vindskip,cargo ship,sail,NORWAY-VINDSKIP/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410134</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Tiny ‘earless’ Gardiner’s frog listens with its mouth, surprises scientists]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[cientists have discovered that the tiny Gardiner’s frog - long assumed to be deaf - is actually able to hear using its mouth. Gardiner’s frogs are found in the rainforests of the Seychelles, a series of 115 small islands in the Indian Ocean. They grow to a maximum of just 11 millimeters and are among the tiniest in the world. This species of frog does not possess a middle ear with an eardrum and was thus thought to be deaf.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 11:57:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/09/06/3410134/3410134_E47E71E625B44FE1961FFBA5320AC675_170804_3410134_Tiny____earless____Gardiner___s_frog_listens_wit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8CA/CEC/8CACEC74AE814E769951A12145D6696E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Gardiner’s frogs,Seychelles,rainforest,earless frogs,CNRS,deafness,hearing with mouth,SCIENCE-FROG/GARDINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410133</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Solar-powered bin to reduce trash collections]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A council in London is trying out a novel way to reduce the expense of emptying streetside litter bins.Merton in south west London is trialling the Big Belly bin, which works using solar power generated by solar panels fitted to the top.The panels generate enough energy to run a trash compactor that crush the refuse when the bin becomes full.The big belly needs just eight hours of sunlight per month and can collect the same amount of trash as up to eight conventional bins.The manufacturer of the bins says they can reduce the number of waste collections needed by up to 86 percent. The bins can also reduce the number of vehicle trips required and fuel used by trash collectors.Each compactor comes equipped with an electronic monitoring system.When it is almost full the bin sends a message to a smartphone indicating that it is ready to be emptied.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 11:56:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/08/09/3410133/3410133_A56033E60B3D4498B747063E54936D74_170804_3410133_Solar_powered_bin_to_reduce_trash_collections_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DB2/4DD/DB24DD25EE1F4697A31908CAB322D91D_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Merton,Big Belly,solar binm compactor,UK,London,TECHNOLOGY-SOLARBINS/BIGBELLYBIN]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410132</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[New icebreaker ship will cut through ice sideways]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Finland's Arctech Helsinki Shipyard is taking a different approach with its new icebreaker, ice-breaking rescue vessel NB 508. Also known as the Baltika, the vessel is being built for Russia's Ministry of Transport for use in the Gulf of Finland, near St. Petersburg. At 76 metres long and 20 metres wide, it features an asymmetric hull, which it will use to cut through ice obliquely, potentially doubling the size of the channels it clears compared with traditional icebreakers, which travel through ice in a straight path. Three engine pods mounted on the hull can rotate to deliver propulsion at any angle.The Baltika is expected to be in the water by November and will be cutting ice by the spring thaw. It will also be used in search and rescue and oil spill cleanup operations, which it can perform even in heavy seas. The asymmetric hull will make the vessel difficult to steer at sea, causing it to pitch and roll in an irregular fashion, so its pilots will require special training.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 11:56:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/08/05/3410132/3410132_06954A6D919146ADA025226714E6BB49_170804_3410132_New_icebreaker_ship_will_cut_through_ice_sideway_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E5A/7DE/E5A7DED18EF14474BC6941B9839E3CAB_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,ice breaker,icebreaking,rescue vessekm NB 508,Balitika,Arctech Helsinki Shipyard,shipping,technology,FINLAND-ICEBREAKER/BALTIKA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410131</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Greenhouse gas released during earthquakes contributes to global warming]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A new study suggests earthquakes may contribute to global warming by releasing greenhouse gas from the ocean floor.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 11:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/30/3410131/3410131_8627E0D994A04D648B153290F1D89AE2_170804_3410131_Greenhouse_gas_released_during_earthquakes_contr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FF1/F45/FF1F45C1335546879D6E4C6AC1F2C348_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Greenhouse gas,Earthquake,global warming,methane,pollution,CLIMATECHANGE-GREENHOUSEGAS-EARTHQUAKE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410130</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists discover what triggers allergic reactions to cats]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists in the UK have discovered how allergic reactions to cats are triggered. A research team from the University of Cambridge discovered that the Fel d 1 protein found in cat dander is the most common cause of severe allergic reactions to cats.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 11:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>50</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/25/3410130/3410130_F35B1100AA004D54822E7679C60E56CB_170804_3410130_Scientists_discover_what_triggers_allergic_react_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/587/004/587004337BD74526A2E03E9EBB0C2934_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,cat allergy,research,University of Cambridge,cat dander,TLR4,LPS,innate immune system,SCIENCE-ALLERGY/CATS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410129</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Earth's gold formed by stellar collisions, scientists say]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[American astronomers have revealed that gold is likely the byproduct of the cataclysmic merger of neutron stars, according to the USA today.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 11:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/19/3410129/3410129_A1D6E0CA23BC4945AB683FACF82ECD90_170804_3410129_Earth_s_gold_formed_by_stellar_collisions__scien_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1AE/E24/1AEE24D1315A4FBA921B93F8C97A6610_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,gold,supernova,star,neutron star,SCIENCE-GOLD/STELLARCOLLISION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410128</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Seismic scream precedes volcanic eruptions]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists at the University of Washington have discovered what they have dubbed a ‘seismic scream’ that precedes explosive volcanic eruptions. Readings taken from Alaska's Redoubt volcano prior to a 2009 eruption recorded a series of tremors around 2km below the crater.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 11:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/18/3410128/3410128_EFF515616F4447CFAA043E384EC3A3BB_170804_3410128_Seismic_scream_precedes_volcanic_eruptions_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/821/D27/821D27E39DC84ADDB7EEE4ECDC591631_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Volcanoes,Alaska,Redoubt,eruption,seismic scream,SCIENCE-SEISMICSCREAM/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410127</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[New big-nose, horned-face dinosaur discovered in Utah]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A new dinosaur has been unearthed in the fossil-rich deserts of Utah. According to Reuters, “the novel species, Nasutoceratops or "big-nose horned face," is the only known member of a group of dinosaurs thought to have lived 76 million years ago on a land mass in Western North America isolated by an ancient seaway, said Scott Sampson, one of the paleontologists who discovered the extinct reptile.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 11:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/18/3410127/3410127_2AE53428948F461DB7CFF66E88F010ED_170804_3410127_New_big_nose__horned_face_dinosaur_discovered_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/45C/5B7/45C5B73237244940AEF1F007BD15CF01_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Nasutoceratops,Utah,dinosaur,new,USA-DINOSAUR/NASUTOCERATOPS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410126</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[“Smart” scalpel can detect cancerous tissue from healthy tissue]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A ‘smart’ scalpel that instantly sniffs out cancerous tissue has been created by scientists, according to media reports today. By accurately distinguishing between healthy tissue and tumours, the ‘magic wand’ could revolutionise cancer surgery, reports The Daily Mail.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 11:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/18/3410126/3410126_421D14CBEE254C5D96BF28C2E9E5AA60_170804_3410126____Smart____scalpel_can_detect_cancerous_tissue__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/268/5E1/2685E1AACC7E4D2D8353DEADB7332457_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,smart scalpel,iKnife,cancer knife,TECHNOLOGY-SMARTSCALPEL/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410125</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[US astronomer discovers new Neptune moon]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A US astronomer has discovered a previously unobserved moon orbiting Neptune using images from the Hubble Space Telescope.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 11:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/16/3410125/3410125_E72A16377B294CA78A0D22385D14AE4F_170804_3410125_US_astronomer_discovers_new_Neptune_moon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AF0/8F4/AF08F46C59374D4F85927895A72FEFE4_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Hubble space telescope,astronomy,new moon,Neptune,Neptunian system,Mark Showalter,NASA,SPACE-NEPTUNE/MOON]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410122</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[British 'penetrator' space probe passes crucial ice test]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[British researchers have tested a projectile technology designed to search for extraterrestrial life around the Solar System, according to a report by the BBC. The 20-kilogram steel projectile, as part of Thursday's test, was fired at a 10-tonne cube of ice intended to replicate the surface of Jupiter's icy moon Europa. The probe hit the block at just under the speed of sound and decelerated instantly, experiencing a peak deceleration of 24,000g.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 11:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/16/3410122/3410122_CEB22CBDD864493B8C5F51B9E380A758_170804_3410122_British__penetrator__space_probe_passes_crucial__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D5D/0A1/D5D0A1B0D9234CF992CA04FA2EA3CDB9_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Jupiter,Europa,space penetrator,space,Moonlite,ice,SPACE-BRITAIN/PENETRATOR]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410121</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Astronomers discovers blue planet where it rains glass]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A research team in the UK have determined the true colour of a planet orbiting another star for the first time using NASA’s Hubble Space Telescope.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 11:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>71</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/12/3410121/3410121_801A7D64D0D0497C80088AF8997BA764_170804_3410121_Astronomers_discovers_blue_planet_where_it_rains_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FCC/90D/FCC90D84980F42C89B73F1EACD03B9C3_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,astronomy,blue planet,NASA,Hubble Space Telescope,glass,HD 189733b,SPACE-BLUEPLANET/189733B]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410119</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Earthquake-proof desk designed to save lives]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Two Israeli inventors have come up with a design for an earthquake proof table they hope could save thousands of lives in quake-prone developing countries. Arthur Brutter and Ido Bruno aim to provide affordable protection to schoolchildren living in such country.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 11:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/09/3410119/3410119_14DE39335F2E45B2ADE8BD40FB2F62D5_170804_3410119_Earthquake_proof_desk_designed_to_save_lives_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E63/73D/E6373DCC93224594BA63C8802C461CD4_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Earthquake-proof desk,Israel,Arthur Brutter,Ido Bruno,ISRAEL-EARTHQUAKEDESK/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410118</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists created telescopic contact lenses]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists created the first telescopic contact lens that allows users to zoom in their vision almost three times. The telescopic contact lens has two regions. The centre allows light to pass straight through, which provides normal vision. The edge acts as a telescope and magnifies the light using a patterned aluminum mirror. The image is magnified 2.8 times to the edge of the retina at the back of the eyeballs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 11:48:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/03/3410118/3410118_3513D40B3B4D47B1BC6BE021611AB6E2_170804_3410118_Scientists_created_telescopic_contact_lenses_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8DD/84C/8DD84C9A8C0346F4ABC1B9D2168EAF85_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,telescopic,contact lens,age-related macular degeneration,AMD,University of California,San Diego,SCIENCE-TELESCOPICLENS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410117</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[‘Peanut Patch’ could cure peanut allergies in children]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A French company developed a skin patch that could help children who have peanut allergy.The skin patch contains a small dose of peanut protein which will be absorbed into the human body once applied to the skin. This would solicit the immune system's reaction, known as Epicutaneous Immunotherapy. Over time, as more and more peanut protein is introduced into the body, desensitization will make the immune system used to the allergen.It was reported that approximately 20 percent of patients between the ages of 5 to 17 were able to consume ten times the amount of peanut protein after wearing the patch for about 12 months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 11:48:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>41</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/07/03/3410117/3410117_D97C7DB519484EE2822B138B2B7F4154_170804_3410117____Peanut_Patch____could_cure_peanut_allergies_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B7A/F7F/B7AF7F6E141E46A8A50DFC4788369DF7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,peanut patch,peanut allergy,children,Viaskin,TECHNOLOGY-PEANUTPATCH/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410116</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Ikea and UNHCR invent more durable refugee shelter]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Ikea has teamed up with the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees to create more durable shelters for refugees.The structures consist of four walls and are roughly twice the size of current temporary dwellings. Measuring about 17.5 square metres they are able to comfortably fit five people. Built around a simple framework of poles and connectors and covered in insulated plastic, the shelter takes roughly four hours to build, but is able to last almost three years, even in adverse weather.The siding covering the shelters is a material called Rhulite that lets in light during the day, but keeps it from casting shadows outside during the night, giving those inside more privacy. The material also reflects sunlight during the day while retaining heat in the evening.Ikea and the UNHCR are also hoping to improve the design with netting that will serve as a solar panel to charge a battery that can provide power for lighting.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 11:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/06/27/3410116/3410116_9CA488B22E174342B47D5766B6F590AF_170804_3410116_Ikea_and_UNHCR_invent_more_durable_refugee_shelt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/294/979/294979FC6EC246A6B7BB0BF6E2319C3C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,refugee shelter,Ikea,UNHCR,TECHNOLOGY-IKEA/REFUGEESHELTER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410115</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Graphene transistors]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Electronic components that use a single molecular layer of carbon, a material substance known as graphene, are one step closer to reality. Researchers at the Department of Chemistry Nano-Science Center at the University of Copenhagen and Chinese Academy of Sciences, Beijing, have successfully tested a graphene-based transistor in an integrated circuit, or computer chip.This animation illustrates how a graphene-based transistor operates and explains how it improves on current transistor technology.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 11:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/06/25/3410115/3410115_EF92F6E98C764B09856D650F766D2A08_170804_3410115_Graphene_transistors_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/270/E95/270E95A9353C4FE081EE7C5330780714_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,graphene,transistor,semiconductor,microchip,integrated circuit,technology,application,SCIENCE-GRAPHENETRANSISTORS/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3410114</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Auditory brainstem implant gives three-year-old Grayson the gift of hearing]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Three-year-old Grayson Clamp has been given the gift of hearing with a revolutionary auditory brainstem implant.The implant is an electronic device that stimulates nerves in the brain, allowing the child to process sound.Grayson was born without the cochlear nerves that convey auditory information to the brain. Without these nerves a more common cochlear ear implant was not an option.The auditory brainstem implant is surgically inserted into the brain near the ear. A microphone device near the ear receives sound and this signal is passed through the implant to a microchip at the brainstem which conveys the information directly to the brain, bypassing the cochlear nerves altogether.This video shows how the auditory brainstem works.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 11:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/06/24/3410114/3410114_5C6FD39D0124405C99E38B6A2644DF03_170804_3410114_Auditory_brainstem_implant_gives_three_year_old__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/882/066/882066B3688E46DBB402D617B2A26AD3_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,three-year-old hears for first time,three-year-old hears father’s voice for first time,brain implant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409228</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Bioengineered vein successfully implanted in U.S. first]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[In a first-of-its-kind operation in the United States, doctors at Duke University hospital implanted a bioengineered vein into the arm of a patient on June 5.The operation is the first U.S. trial of human-cell based vein implant. The bioengineered vein is based on a biodegradable mesh scaffolding. Donor cells are added to and the mesh dissolves away. The vein is then cultured in nutrients for two months.Its is then washed of the living cells, leaving a collagen structure. These non-living veins can can be stored, then and transplanted freely as they do not generate an immune response.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 10:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/06/10/3409228/3409228_60C2CDEE8F134364B36E54189B983D5E_170803_3409228_Bioengineered_vein_successfully_implanted_in_U_S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6A6/334/6A6334702F7048A88390CA1832329661_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,biomedicine,bio engineered,artificial vein,Humacyte,USA-BIOENGINEERING/ARTIFICIALVEIN]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409227</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Lunar rocks expose moisture on the moon similar to earth's]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An analysis of lunar rocks brought to the earth by US astronauts shows that there are traces of water on the moon. Samples brought back from the moon back in the 1970s reveal ancient droplets of volcanic glass that contain moisture. While this is already known, a recent study shows that those moisture samples are remarkable similar to those found on ancient Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 10:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>84</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/06/06/3409227/3409227_DD35734C447F414C96C3E87BD0EE5988_170803_3409227_Lunar_rocks_expose_moisture_on_the_moon_similar__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9A4/25F/9A425F4AB4B1485EB0F616C8582F1D01_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,NASA,Interplanetary GPS,pulsar,spacecraft,space navigation,SPACE-LUNARROCKS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409224</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Arctic ocean acidification threatens fish lifecycle and livelihood of arctic environment.]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Arctic ecosystem, already under pressure from record ice melts, faces another potential threat in the form of rapid acidification of the ocean, according to an international study published on Monday. Acidification, blamed on the transformation of rising levels of the greenhouse gas carbon dioxide from the air into carbonic acid in the sea, makes it harder for shellfish and crabs to grow their shells, and might also impair fish reproduction, it said.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 10:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/05/24/3409224/3409224_D18E5C7DD8154CC78E6DF89618DCF12E_170803_3409224_Arctic_ocean_acidification_threatens_fish_lifecy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A58/506/A58506396B36449F88096032136AEA97_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,arctic ocean,arctic ocean acidification,climate change,global warming,CLIMATECHANGE-ACIDIFICATION/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409223</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Honeybees could help in clearing of 1990s Balkans war minefields]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers in Croatia have found a way that the humble honeybee can help to clear up a deadly legacy of the 1990s Balkan wars. The researchers are training the bees to help find landmines. The bees are trained by adding particles of TNT to sugar solution which leads the bees to identify the smell of explosives with the scent of food.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 10:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/05/20/3409223/3409223_177423DD174E4A18B5E678C265057025_170803_3409223_Honeybees_could_help_in_clearing_of_1990s_Balkan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D27/D2B/D27D2B074F5E4578914DB8FA09CDD370_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Croatia,landmines,honeybees,TNT,scent,detect,CROATIA-LANDMINES/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409222</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Soccket: a green way to turn play into energy]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Harvard university graduates have invented a fun solution to tackling the lack of electricity in the developing world. Soccket is a soccer ball that harnesses energy every time it is kicked.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 10:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/05/17/3409222/3409222_1F60801034A145B78EC3CFF751A4EDF2_170803_3409222_Soccket__a_green_way_to_turn_play_into_energy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/228/737/228737927D75449BAEF64AB5EECA2C98_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,soccket,soccer ball,green energy,electricity,eco friendly,eco products,USA-SOCCKET/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409221</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Concrete spheres offer possibility of storing offshore wind turbine energy]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIT has patented an energy storage system it posits makes offshore wind energy more sustainable.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 10:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/05/06/3409221/3409221_D2B3394ACD764B38BE01D0F13E3A21AC_170803_3409221_Concrete_spheres_offer_possibility_of_storing_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5E9/247/5E9247F8F6A741A4A81ABFE612E7F9B8_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,wind turbine,green power,MIT energy research,concrete spheres,offshore energy,USA-ENERGY/CONCRETESPHERE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409219</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Shark net wall to protect beachgoers in South Africa]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Cape Town is developing a shark net curtain that would protect the public from an increase in shark attacks along the beach at Fish Hoek.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 10:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/05/03/3409219/3409219_B0EBE35836C142BB967797FDB889DD66_170803_3409219_Shark_net_wall_to_protect_beachgoers_in_South_Af_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/826/078/8260784AB1D648D2941C5BD49E234BF6_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,South Africa,sharks,shark attack,Fish Hoek,Cape Town,shark net,SOUTHAFRICA-SHARKNET/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409216</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[How the first floating liquefied natural gas project will work]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The first floating liquefied natural gas project is set to go into operation in 2015.The natural gas extraction unit, known as PETRONAS Floating LNG1, or PFLNG1,  will be located in Malaysia, roughly 180 kilometers off the coast of Sarawak.The unit is 60 meters wide and 300 meters long, and has a capacity of producing 1.2 million tonnes of liquefied natural gas per year.The unit will be anchored above a natural gas site appropriate site, and can process, purify and liquefy natural gas without bringing it to a plant on shore. Carrier vessels will regularly visit the unit to pick up liquefied natural gas, then directly transport the resource to locations on land.The process eliminates the need for complicated and expensive pipelines to transport gas to land-based plants for liquefaction before delivery to areas that need it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 10:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>45</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/04/29/3409216/3409216_06F481E018034AD18CD3E4148F37C122_170803_3409216_How_the_first_floating_liquefied_natural_gas_pro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/10B/627/10B627F7B40449B29B0F136F4B717FC2_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,first floating liquefied natural gas project,Malaysia,PETRONAS Floating LNG1,PFLNG1,SCIENCE-PFLNG1/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409215</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Lab-grown kidney used in animals]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A regenerated kidney, which was grown in a laboratory has been transplanted into a living animal and has successfully produced urine, scientists at Massachusetts General Hospital in Boston announced on Sunday. The scientists started with the kidneys of recently deceased rats and used detergent to wash away the old cells leaving behind an underlying scaffold of connective tissues. They then regenerated the organ by seeding the scaffold with human umbilical-vein cells to line the blood vessels, and kidney cells from newborn rats to produce other tissues that make up the organ. The seeded scaffold was then put into an organ bioreactor to grow until it is ready for transplantation. However once transplanted into rats, the regenerated kidney was only able to produce one third as much as urine as normal kidneys, and cleared creatinine 36 times slower than normal.This method was developed by organ-regeneration specialist Harald Ott in 2008. Ott has used the technique to grow hearts and lungs since then. The team is now testing the same technique using pig and human kidneys.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 10:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/04/15/3409215/3409215_27DED6D39A774ACE923FD9D5F0587C35_170803_3409215_Lab_grown_kidney_used_in_animals_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/25E/A09/25EA096F9F3B40D881C433C66831D153_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Laboratory,kidney,rat,bioengineer,SCIENCE-BIOENGINEER/KIDNEY]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409213</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Fusion rocket engines speed trip to Mars]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Fusion rocket engines could take a manned crew to Mars in 30 to 90 days, NASA-funded scientists at the University of Washington say.The scientists are building a fusion-driven rocket system that pulses at a rate of one blast per minute, causing exhaust to exit the divergent magnetic nozzle at 30 km per second. Solar energy will provide electricity needed to charge capacitors that power the fusion rocket's magnets. For each pulse of the rocket engine, powerful magnets crush a series of lithium metal rings around a ball of tritium-deuterium plasma. An exothermic reaction occurs, providing thrust.The fusion rocket engine will only be active for 10 percent of the voyage, to speed the spaceship away from Earth, and to slow the spaceship down upon arrival near Mars. Unlike a conventional chemical rocket, the fusion rocket's lithium fuel takes up only 50 percent of its mass, compared to 98 percent for a liquid fuel Saturn V rocket.The fusion rocket should also be more cost effective than a chemical rocket, whose primary cost is transporting fuel to space.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 10:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>64</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/04/15/3409213/3409213_9D9ED72807F54D0E94C2CB7477FEA1B2_170803_3409213_Fusion_rocket_engines_speed_trip_to_Mars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/67E/573/67E573E3C8BC499FBF61C617B3E78E95_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Fusion rocket,Mars,interplanetary travel,science,SCIENCE-TECHNOLOGY/FUSIONROCKET]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409212</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Drones aid wildlife conservation and fight poaching]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Pilotless drone aircraft will be used to track wildlife and fight poachers in wildlife reserves around the world. Park rangers in Kenya plan to introduce drones to help monitor endangered animals over vast expanses of park land.The drones will be day and night capable and will help rangers combat poaching. Conservationists will also be able to tag animals with RFID chips, which communicate by radio with drones orbiting overhead.By constantly monitoring the animals' whereabouts, scientists hope the drones will increase their understanding of animal behavior.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 10:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/03/27/3409212/3409212_8A50AE5A19A5474FA7A4945BDC172225_170803_3409212_Drones_aid_wildlife_conservation_and_fight_poach_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C27/1BF/C271BF56AF8A4FFB806CD193D5B39F1D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,drones,technology,wildlife,conservation,poaching,Kenya,surveillance,KENYA-TECHNOLOGY/DRONES]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409210</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[19-year-old student creates design to clean up the ocean]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A 19-year-old Dutch student has developed a model for a self-sustaining Ocean Array Platform designed to rid the world of the more than 7.25 million tons of plastic trash that currently float on or near the surface of its oceans.The platform, which contains two large booms on either end, will use ocean currents to collect trash. The trash will then be filtered into a large trash receptor on the back of the platform.With solar paneling and water-generated turbines below the ocean surface, the platform will run completely on natural energy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 10:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/03/27/3409210/3409210_0B70CD21C35A42B482BB942D0688603A_170803_3409210_19_year_old_student_creates_design_to_clean_up_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/453/1C4/4531C492D3C64804978FE5AA71BB4D42_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Trash,Cleanup,Environment,Science,Technology,Ocean,Plastic,TECHNOLOGY-OCEANARRAYPLATFORM/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409209</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Deep sea mining: an explainer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The British government has voiced its support for the deep sea mining industry following the awarding of exploration rights to a British subsidiary of Lockheed Martin, UK Seabed Resources. Prime Minister David Cameron has said the sector could be worth 40 billion pounds to the British economy over the next 30 years.The exploration license covers a 58,000 sq km patch of seabed between Hawaii and Mexico.To mine the seabed, a support vessel arrives at the site and launches a mining vehicle.The subsea mining tool - or crawler - roves the seabed, slicing clumps of mineral-rich rock called 'polymetallic nodules' from the crust.For smooth passage in the high-pressure environment, the hose is floated above the crawler and weighted beneath the ship.The crawler crushes the rocks, and a mixture of gravel and seawater is pumped to the surface vessel via an umbilical hose.Working at depths of up to 4 km, the crawler is specially designed to withstand corrosion and extreme pressure.The nodules are packed with many rare earth elements and valuable metals, including cobalt, manganese, nickel, copper and aluminium.Although costly and technically complex, such projects could be extremely profitable.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 10:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>56</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/03/15/3409209/3409209_1A70D376FD1F4FD792993C1306148780_170803_3409209_Deep_sea_mining__an_explainer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9F2/492/9F249251934F4C529F937813FE6AD966_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Deep sea mining,polymetallic nodules,rare earth metals,undersea mining,Lockheed Martin,SCIENCE-DEEPSEAMINING/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409208</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Engineer invents self-healing asphalt]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Professor Erik Schlangen of Delft University of Technology has invented a type of asphalt that can repair itself. The key component to such asphalt is steel wool fibers. Schlangen added steel wool fibers to porous asphalt and applied an induction plate to the material to heat the wool. The result was the steel wool fibers heating up within the asphalt to melt the bitumen around it, which helped fill and close any small cracks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 10:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/03/14/3409208/3409208_E948DC695E4E48E08CA0032B9A88FE9C_170803_3409208_Engineer_invents_self_healing_asphalt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FD2/955/FD2955893A82437AA93CF9495BC0F765_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,self-healing roads,self-healing asphalt,Erik Schlangen,Delft University of,TECHNOLOGY-ASPHALT/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409207</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[CERN scientists close in on confirming Higgs boson]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists at the CERN research center have said it is now almost certain they found the Higgs boson, or “God Particle,” so named because it gives other subatomic particles their mass. Extensive analysis of findings from July last year means the scientists are extremely close to confirming the existence of Higgs boson. A physicist from the center said the only other thing the particle could also be is a graviton, another subatomic particle associated with gravitational fields.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 10:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>59</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/03/08/3409207/3409207_98BBCDCC445C49AE876F69B4E4B7DA64_170803_3409207_CERN_scientists_close_in_on_confirming_Higgs_bos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EFD/A69/EFDA692C65D5407181D945DB92FA6D78_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,CERN,LHC,Higgs boson,Graviton,particle physics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409206</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Brain to brain technology on rats]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists in the US have succeeded in connecting the brains of lab rats, enabling one rat to communicate directly to another via a cable. The Brain-to-brain interface (BTBI) technology allows two brains to share behavioral and sensorimotor information in real-time. The two rats had electrodes implanted into the tactile-motor region of their brains, which were then linked together using wires.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 10:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>62</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/03/01/3409206/3409206_7A6A76DD7E0D47E3BCA94D364C7A1885_170803_3409206_Brain_to_brain_technology_on_rats_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B07/55E/B0755E4E9C6746B19C1B0BD71917E1A6_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Duke University,Miguel Nicolelis,brain-to-brain interface technology,University of Natal,Brazil,USA-TECHNOLOGY/BRAINTOBRAIN]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409205</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Australian businessman unveils plans for Titanic 2]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Australian businessman Clive Palmer has unveiled designs for Titanic 2, a modern-day replica of the doomed cruise ship that sank on its maiden voyage in 1912. Introducing the ship at a press conference in New York, Palmer said the Titanic 2 would faithfully recreate the experience of sailing on the original liner, including having three passenger classes that would not be allowed to mingle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 10:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>65</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/02/27/3409205/3409205_EDB7379415CA45B5978654F8796E12D0_170803_3409205_Australian_businessman_unveils_plans_for_Titanic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B5E/708/B5E708BC642147DAB19D79B88E93E405_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Titanic,Titanic 2,AUSTRALIA-TITANIC2/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409204</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Spray-painting asteroids could prevent Earth collision]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Asteroids on a collision course with Earth could be rerouted by spray painting them with a thin layer of paint, a Texas A&M University professor says. Dave Hyland, an aerospace and physics professor at Texas A&M, says an asteroid collision could be prevented by spraying a thin layer of paint on an approaching asteroid. SOURCES: Texas A&M]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 10:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/02/26/3409204/3409204_52601284EBAF4100880900E4F6B8F576_170803_3409204_Spray_painting_asteroids_could_prevent_Earth_col_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/540/6BB/5406BB7587A149539C206D9515789874_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,NASA,asteroid,collision,space,satellite,SPACE-ASTEROID/SPRAYPAINTING]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409203</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Canadian satellite will hunt asteroids and space debris]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Canadian satellite designed to search for near-Earth asteroids is scheduled to launch from India this week.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 10:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/02/26/3409203/3409203_D9BA83FF2F2B4558A62B0D6291D6CAA7_170803_3409203_Canadian_satellite_will_hunt_asteroids_and_space_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8AF/3FE/8AF3FEE25C924A848C7081EAC23811EE_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,asteroid,tracking,NEOSSat,satellite,space debris,Canadian Space Agency,SPACE-CANADA/NEOSSAT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3409201</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Dense cluster of ancient pyramids found in Sudan]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Archaeologists have discovered at least 35 ancient pyramids and graves thought to be about 2,000 years old at a site called Sedeinga in Sudan. The dense concentration is surprising to researchers, who in 2011 found 13 pyramids clustered closely together in a 5,381 square feet area, slightly larger than an NBA basketball court. They date back around 2,000 years to a time when the kingdom of Kush flourished in Sudan. Kush shared a border with Egypt and was influenced by Egyptian funerary architecture. The structure of the pyramids are designed with a circle built inside them and cross-braces connecting the circle to the corners of the pyramid. There is only one pyramid outside of Sedeinga known to have been built in the same style. The largest pyramid found is seven meters wide at its base, while the smallest is only 750 millimeters long. SOURCE: Scientific American, Live Science]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 10:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/03/03/3409201/3409201_170ECB532B454A43A53B14FEBD7DC693_170803_3409201_Dense_cluster_of_ancient_pyramids_found_in_Sudan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/210/394/210394FB82F8428D8CA47A2348861EC3_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,pyramids,Sudan,archaeology,Sedeinga,Kush,SUDAN-PYRAMIDS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408378</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scottish scientists make 3D stem cell printer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team of scientists at Heriot-Way University in Edinburgh have developed a method that can can print clusters of human stem cells in various sizes, making them the first scientists to successfully 3D-print human embryonic stem cells, or hESCs. The breakthrough, which was achieved in cooperation with in collaboration with Roslin Cellab, a stem cell technology company, was published in the Feb. 5 edition of Biofabrication. SOURCE: Science Daily, The Verge, Gizmodo]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 11:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/02/06/3408378/3408378_F166FE00D890466084FBAC5EF8DF0454_170802_3408378_Scottish_scientists_make_3D_stem_cell_printer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F45/5BA/F455BA12F4AD497B97EF81277EA94FE5_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,3D printing,stem cells,Scotland,UK,medical,science,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408377</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[New Halley research station opens in Antarctica by UK]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The British Antarctic Survey (BAS) has opened a new Antarctic research station built to work in the most extreme conditions. The Halley VI research station, designed by Hugh Broughton Architects, was constructed on the floating Brunt Ice Shelf, which moves around 700 meters west towards the Weddell Sea each year. Architect Hugh Broughton pioneered the use of glass reinforced plastic (GRP) on the steel-framed panels that support the 1,860 square meter structure. SOURCE: British Antarctic Survey,]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 11:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>52</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/02/06/3408377/3408377_FCB5D5E55D7648ECBCC61A5A9C1664F5_170802_3408377_New_Halley_research_station_opens_in_Antarctica__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/48A/34B/48A34BFBDE95438A961581C06EDFE99B_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Halley VI,British Antarctic Survey,Antarctica,research,UK,science,SCIENCE-ANTARTIC/NEWHALLEY]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408376</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[New App sends text message when plants need water]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at Oso Technologies will begin production on a device that helps people keep their indoor and outdoor plants alive by sending text messages to users on their smartphone alerting them when their plants need watering. Plant Link uses a combination of soil sensors and software that constantly monitors plant water levels.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 11:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/02/06/3408376/3408376_0A449412B4A94F5EACDB49228B386248_170802_3408376_New_App_sends_text_message_when_plants_need_wate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/185/0CC/1850CC0B9F4E4D5795AFE94995719C21_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Plant Link,App,Oso Technologies,text message,watering plants,TECHNOLOGY-PLANTLINK/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408375</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Signs of life from Antarctic lake buried under more than 2,000 feet of ice]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Signs of life have been detected in waters from a subglacial Lake Whillans half a mile beneath the surface of Antarctic. On Jan. 28, scientists retrieved a baseball bat-sized gray plastic vessel filled with water from Lake Whillans. The vessel was sent into a cargo container laboratory on skis, where some of the water was poured into bottles that contain a growth medium to culture bacteria in the water. When the lake water was viewed under a microscope, it was observed that tiny cells in the water glowed green in response to DNA-sensitive dye. Scientists said that despite being sealed beneath 2,600 feet of ice, it is likely microbes in the lake obtained energy by consuming oxygen released from water melting off the ice sheet in the lake to metabolize iron and sulfur.  US scientists reported on Jan. 27 that they had drilled through 2,600 feet of ice to reach Lake Whillans, a subglacial lake buried beneath the Antarctic ice sheet. Scientists with the Whillans Ice Stream Subglacial Access Research Drilling (WISSARD) project, which is funded by the US National Science Foundation's Office of Polar Programs, began drilling Jan. 21.One of the primary purposes of the WISSARD project is to look for signs of life in the lake, which, if present, would most likely be in the form of microorganisms adapted to live in the extreme cold, dark environment of a subglacial lake.The American project marks the third attempt to drill into a subglacial lake in Antarctica within the past year. Russia successfully drilled into Lake Vostok last year. A British attempt to drill into Lake Ellsworth failed last month. SOURCE: MSNBC, Discovery Magazine, Popular Mechanics, Discover Magazine, Wired, University of California, Santa Cruz]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 11:09:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>105</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/02/05/3408375/3408375_226DEDB7FAA0488A87433EE15A6EC6E7_170802_3408375_Signs_of_life_from_Antarctic_lake_buried_under_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7FA/5CD/7FA5CD74A2BB4EABAEC9BAD984F6F095_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Antarctica,Lake Whillans,Whillans Ice Stream Subglacial Access Research Drilling,WISSARD,US Nati,ANTARTICA-LAKEWHILLANS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408374</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Sinkhole swallows building in Chinese city]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An investigation has begun after a sinkhole opened up, swallowing a building in central Guangzhou, capital of China's Guangdong Province. The sinkhole opened up next to construction site where workers were building an underground railway tunnel.Workers from the construction site noticed the ground subsiding shortly before the collapse occurred and raised the alarm.According to Reuters, "Around 300 residents from the surrounding area were evacuated and nearby roads closed off before the surrounding three buildings in the complex collapsed later that evening, China Central Television (CCTV) added. CCTV said that so far no one has been reported injured or killed in either collapse."This animation explains how natural sinkholes form and how construction can contribute to the collapse of a sinkhole.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 11:09:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/30/3408374/3408374_7072526EFA3B43C793F5E0D7450CBE77_170802_3408374_Sinkhole_swallows_building_in_Chinese_city_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6B2/FB3/6B2FB31C06264C3AA2A0312AB21A9207_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,China,Guangdong,Guangzhou,sinkhole,construction work,CHINA-SINKHOLE/GUAHGZHOU]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408373</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Microneedle patch a painless way to deliver vaccines]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at MIT are developing a method of delivering vaccines with patches of tiny needles that would embed a substance containing the vaccine onto the skin, much like a tattoo. The technique would eliminate the need of a syringe.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 11:08:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/30/3408373/3408373_8C6BA4390B6F4E87ADA9EFFF92214CAF_170802_3408373_Microneedle_patch_a_painless_way_to_deliver_vacc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/71D/16A/71D16AC594A447089152D5188C0E85FE_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,microneedle,patch,tattoo,vaccine,medical,SCIENCE-VACCINE/MICRONEEDLEPATCH/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408371</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Swallowable camera pill provides imaging of esophageal lining]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at Ninepoint Medical and Massachusetts General Hospital have developed a new tethered, pill sized endoscope that can provide cross-sectional and three-dimensional images of the upper gastrointestinal tract. Researchers placed imaging equipment into a clear capsule that patients can swallow. A 1mm-wide cable is attached to one end of the capsule and tethered to a display machine next to the patient.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 11:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>47</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/25/3408371/3408371_DE7CA75A017546898235B6CEA360E07A_170802_3408371_Swallowable_camera_pill_provides_imaging_of_esop_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/712/F8E/712F8E54759249918791F733220000C3_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Massachusetts General Hospital,Ninepoint Medical,swallowable pill camera,endoscope,SCIENCE-ENDOSCOPY/SWALLOWABLEPILL]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408369</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists develop robot ‘hedgehogs’ to explore Martian moon]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Stanford researchers in collaboration with NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, have developed a nearly completely autonomous system to explore the Martian Moon Prohos. The system consists of a mothership Prohos Surveyor and a rover called Hedgehog.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 11:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/23/3408369/3408369_A1100CF8898B435C81E652D48C136BC1_170802_3408369_Scientists_develop_robot____hedgehogs____to_expl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2B8/C7C/2B8C7CC07BC7483B8E430A1D4071704F_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,unar probe,Mars,Prohos,Hedgehog,Standford,NASA,MIT,SPACE-MARS/HEDGEHOG]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408368</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Four-stranded DNA discovered, linked to cancer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditionally DNA has been represented in the double helix form, but a newly-discovered, four-stranded DNA may provide some insight into the fight against cancer. A group of scientists on the Cambridge University research team told Nature Chemistry that the “quadruple DNA” appears when a cell is in an unstable or dysfunctional state, which ultimately links it to cancer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 11:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/23/3408368/3408368_39BB03A117D54EC08F0C26777CD42FD8_170802_3408368_Four_stranded_DNA_discovered__linked_to_cancer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D77/DB7/D77DB7BDA45441728DA370A02E1EB73B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Health,science,medicine,4-stranded DNA,discovery,cancer,SCIENCE-QUADRUPLEDNA/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408367</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Silica extracted from rice husks used in new tires]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Italian tire maker Pirelli is making fuel-saving tires that are more environmentally-friendly by obtaining one of their ingredients from rice husks. One way tires can save fuel is to reduce rolling resistance that is caused in part by the car’s weight repeatedly pressing down on its tires.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 11:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>56</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/21/3408367/3408367_F6CAC9B947944374815A4FBF96785199_170802_3408367_Silica_extracted_from_rice_husks_used_in_new_tir_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6D1/90C/6D190C65F2C745318BA43A50CF4BEC91_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Silica,tires,rice,hysteresis loss,Pirelli,ITALY-PIRELLI/RICEHUSKTIRES]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408365</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Mantle drilling project aims to understand Earth’s past]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team of international scientists are planning to drill into the Earth's mantle to bring back samples that will help them to answer questions about the origins and evolution of life. The team will be working aboard the Japanese deep-sea drilling vessel Chikyu. Scientists have identified three possible locations in the Pacific Ocean where the crust has been formed by spreading oceanic ridges and is at its thinnest.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 11:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/15/3408365/3408365_84F7019116A2431CA8A6DDEA08254C61_170802_3408365_Mantle_drilling_project_aims_to_understand_Earth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B21/54F/B2154F5F904B40439A4487C8C1844339_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Drill,Earth,mantle,Chikyu,University of Southampton,SCIENCE-MANTLEDRILLING/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408364</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[China air pollution: Air Quality Index explained]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Air quality in Beijing has risen above hazardous levels in the last few days, reaching 755 on an index that measures particulate matter in the air with a diameter of 2.5 micrometers (PM2.5). A measurement above 100 is considered unhealthy, while measurement above 300 is considered dangerous meaning children and the elderly are advised to remain indoors. The unofficial index is hosted by the US Embassy. This animation explains what PM2.5 pollutants are and their potential effects on the body.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 11:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/13/01/14/3408364/3408364_915320C2BE84464490433149A58D06CB_170802_3408364_China_air_pollution__Air_Quality_Index_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0D0/0AF/0D00AFD506AA4A789113600ED620A160_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Beijing,environment,pollution,air quality,SCIENCE-AIRQUALITYINDEX/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408363</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Chinese man build giant tsunami pods]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A farmer from Qiantun village in Henan, south of Beijing, has built seven survival pods to save people from natural disasters such as tsunamis and earthquakes. Liu Qiyuan’s tsunami survival pods are built using a steel frame, a waterproof fiberglass outer layer, and can seat up to 14 people. The pod has extra space for oxygen tanks, food and water, which Li claims hold enough supplies to support 14 people for up to five months. The pod is designed to remain upright in water and is made to withs]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 11:04:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>60</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/12/18/3408363/3408363_7675C7BEB2DF45F6B8DE04B0C1D85A75_170802_3408363_Chinese_man_build_giant_tsunami_pods_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/655/11F/65511F08ABCE4AE5BAE01BD14C63B0CD_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,China,tsunami,survival pods,Mayan apocalypse,life-saving,shelter,Liu Qiyuan,Noah's Ark,life,TECHNOLOGY-CHINA/TSUNAMIPOD]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408361</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[German pioneers solar cooking reflectors in Mexico]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A German entrepreneur is manufacturing and installing solar deflector stoves for cooking in El Sauz, Mexico.Gregor Schappers adopted the design of Austrian inventor Wolfgang Scheffler for the stoves. An average reflector measures eight meters square and can produce heat up to 1,020 degrees Celsius. The frame is constructed for conditions at equinox, when the sun is perpendicular to the equator.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 11:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>61</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/12/06/3408361/3408361_276929888D874CE6B0EECB4B05F20F98_170802_3408361_German_pioneers_solar_cooking_reflectors_in_Mexi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/668/5AC/6685AC6AB5F14A93AABEFDD20758C622_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Wolfgang Scheffler,Gregor Schappers,Scheffler Community Kitchen,solar power,solar reflector,TECHNOLOGY-MEXICO/SOLARCOOKING]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408360</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Bread could last 60 days without molding]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An American company says it has developed a technique that can keep bread mold-free for 60 days. The bread is treated using a sophisticated microwave array that kills the spores that cause mold. The company, Microzap, claims their technique could significantly reduce the amount of wasted bread. The technology can also be used with other foods like fresh turkey and several kinds of fruit and vegetable. Mold is one of the biggest threats to bread. When bread is wrapped in plastic, any water that]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 11:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/12/05/3408360/3408360_653A0EFA5BD742DCA6442F8B39AFA25A_170802_3408360_Bread_could_last_60_days_without_molding_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/76D/DFF/76DDFFF69C4940C0A08F091E028AFE94_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Microzap,mold,spores,Salmonella,Lubbock,Don Stull,Satyalococcus,USA-MICROZAP/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408359</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Climate change imperils French truffle production: scientists]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Climate change-induced drier summers in France and Spain are damaging truffle harvests, according to a new study. Truffles are fungi that grow symbiotically with various tree species including beech, oak, hazel, and pine. Truffles thrive in damp summer conditions; they mature, releasing spores, which germinate, beginning the life cycle again the following spring. In recent years, French truffle production had fallen from 1,000 tonnes annually from a century ago, to 25 tonnes today.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 11:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>71</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/11/29/3408359/3408359_88A41354498D4CE082355B1C731BB63D_170802_3408359_Climate_change_imperils_French_truffle_productio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D91/8EE/D918EE5FDFB94A21AA094F48D1D2F2B2_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,truffles,symbiosis,climate change,global warming,mycelia,CLIMATECHANGE-TRUFFLE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408358</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Noroviruses explained]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Noroviruses are a group of viruses better known as winter vomiting disease. Infection with these viruses affects the stomach, causing gastroenteritis. Noroviruses are found in the stool or vomit of infected people and transmitted person-to-person via the fecal-oral route. Symptoms of norovirus illness include nausea, vomiting, diarrhea, and occasionally a high temperature. Those infected normally recover within one or two days, while remaining infectious for another 48 hours.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 11:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>53</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/11/28/3408358/3408358_65FAFAF6BFAE47E3A9AC6009F1FFBECD_170802_3408358_Noroviruses_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B82/305/B82305D60C73409DBBBE98FD12CDA659_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Norovirus,gastroenteritis,winter vomiting bug,stomach flu,outbreak,infection,transmission,SCIENCE-NOROVIRUS/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408357</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Kites used to generate electricity]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A group of German scientists are studying ways to harness wind energy from high-flying stunt kites. The higher the altitude, the stronger and more reliable wind energy becomes. In a test run conducted this month, scientists attached large stunt kites to trains that were fitted with energy convertors. The kites captured wind energy from up to 500 meters above ground, then converted the kinetic energy into electricity.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 11:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>56</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/11/27/3408357/3408357_0D8A259997D94380AC2AE5FE29A82F0A_170802_3408357_Kites_used_to_generate_electricity_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/07A/D9C/07AD9CD72DF449C6B8D102A91A7B7C37_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,kite,stunt kite,green energy,wind energy,wind turbine,clean energy,Germany,GERMANY-ENERGY/KITES]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408356</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Futuristic highways in the Netherlands glow in the dark]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A futuristic highway that can save energy and improve road safety is set to be installed in the Netherlands by mid-2013. Two companies, Studio Roosegaarde and Heijmans Infrastructure, came up with the highway, which includes: glow-in-the-dark road markings painted with photo-luminescent paint which are charged during the day and light up during the night; temperature-responsive paint which indicates slippery roads when temperatures fall below zero; and interactive lights along the highway.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 10:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>58</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/11/26/3408356/3408356_D6247CE11F244462BD9D214F82C0356C_170802_3408356_Futuristic_highways_in_the_Netherlands_glow_in_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/703/034/7030349772E146EBB045A4BC0C36EE55_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,roosegaarde and heijmans,The Smart Highway,Dutch Design Awards 2012,Best Future Concept,TECHNOLOGY-NETHERLANDS/SMARTHIGHWAY]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3408352</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Australian scientists to train wildlife to avoid poisonous toads]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists in Australia have developed a special bait to prevent native wildlife from dying after eating cane toads. Cane toads are poisonous amphibians introduced to Australia to control beetles in the 1930s. However, native Australian animals including dingos, blue-tongue lizards, goannas and northern quolls prey on them, getting sick or dying from the poison.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 10:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/11/26/3408352/3408352_F6A9E7EFA18E48A4B103D4F180BA3C15_170802_3408352_Australian_scientists_to_train_wildlife_to_avoid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/15D/82C/15D82CCD3D0E48ED98D56E543EBA2D3A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Australia,cane toad,poison,dingo,blue-tongue lizards,goanna,quoll,David Pearson,AUSTRALIA-CANETOAD/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407546</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Australia’s BHP to introduce robot mining trucks]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Australian mining company BHP Billiton has announced it will introduce automated trucks at its new Jimblebar Mine. The fleet of 12-15 trucks will go into service late next year and will be controlled from the company’s remote mining operations center in Perth. The robot trucks use GPS, radars and proximity detectors to navigate between the loading and dumping sites. Compared with manually operated trucks, which need five drivers per truck, robot trucks require just two to three drivers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 11:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/11/01/3407546/3407546_F8438478BC0B4C318626F5D5DA3B2283_170801_3407546_Australia___s_BHP_to_introduce_robot_mining_truc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/690/5CE/6905CE9CBF5F4DD59EA25ABF2BA7296B_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Australia,Perth,Pilbara,Jimblebar,BHP,automated trucks,mine,robot,AUSTRALIA-BHP/ROBOTTRUCKS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407545</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[French company extracts precious metals from waste water]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A French company has come up with a new technique for extracting precious metals such as gold from waste water. The process involves pumping the waste water through tiny plastic resin pellets. Precious metals inside the water, like gold, platinum, palladium, and rhodium then stick to the pellet and are removed from the waste water. A liter of the resin can treat up to 10 cubic meters of waste water, recovering up to 100 grams of precious metal in the process.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 11:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/31/3407545/3407545_B364CD0111934091896A6E71C0B42BA2_170801_3407545_French_company_extracts_precious_metals_from_was_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EB0/9C6/EB09C665212348FF9D0BF935A76A48B2_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Magpie Polymers,Precious metals recycle,Wastewater treatment,FRANCE-WASTEWATER/MAGPIEPOLYMERS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407543</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Afghan devises simple, cheap landmine clearance tool]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An Afghan national industrial designer at Holland’s Design Academy in Eindhoven has created a device which he says will help clear landmines. Called the Mine Kafron, the device - a giant ball shaped like a dandelion and designed to roll around in the wind - is made of bamboo, plastic and iron. It is equipped with GPS tracking so areas that have been cleared of mines will be visible via a Website.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 11:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/30/3407543/3407543_FC52BB2287A44A838C1009079AD398CA_170801_3407543_Afghan_devises_simple__cheap_landmine_clearance__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A82/302/A8230278AC4A4D359216F98ED5486C7F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,minesweeper,Afghanistan,technology,Holland,Design Academy Eindhoven,AFGHANISTAN-MINESWEEPER/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407542</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Swing states explained]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[In US presidential elections the 50 states are divided into solid states, states that lean toward a certain party and swing states. Often the election result hinges on the electoral college votes available in the swing states. Certain of a number of electoral college votes, candidates will often concentrate most of their campaign efforts on winning just one or two swing states. This animation explains how winning certain swing states can win the presidential election.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 11:14:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>75</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/26/3407542/3407542_43D28946DC70461B8778582E796015B4_170801_3407542_Swing_states_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F43/2A8/F432A8CD4BDC41E486DF172F22A39443_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,US,2012,presidential election,swing states,purple states,politics,voting,elections,Obama,USA-SWINGSTATES/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407541</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Trigger for major volcanic eruptions found]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists say they have found the “trigger” that causes some of Earth’s most powerful volcanic eruptions, such as the 2010 eruption of Eyjafjallajokull in Iceland that disrupted flights and stranded millions of passengers worldwide, according to a report published in the journal Scientific Reports. SOURCE: Scientific Reports]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 11:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>18</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/16/3407541/3407541_A374C5A428F54A75A87EC12A372EF068_170801_3407541_Trigger_for_major_volcanic_eruptions_found_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/43C/BF7/43CBF7429E5C46FB914C2FAD27395E24_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,volcano,Eyjafjallajokull,Iceland,University of Southampton,geology,science,Las Canadas,Canary,SCIENCE-VOLCANO/TRIGGER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407540</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Felix Baumgartner’s space suit]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Austrian skydiver Felix Baumgartner became set a world record for highest skydive and became the first human to break the sound barrier without the aid of a machine when he dove from 24 miles above the Earth on Sunday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 11:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/15/3407540/3407540_822A51AFD7FE4264B34F2A581403635F_170801_3407540_Felix_Baumgartner___s_space_suit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/224/47C/22447C7CC5B84E829CC2B33EFFCE8776_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Austrian,skydiver,Felix Baumgartner,world record,skydive,space suit,NASA,AUSTRIA-FELIXBAUMGARTNER/SPACESUIT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407538</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Carbon nanotube pencil used to draw sensor circuitsCarbon nanotube pencil used to draw sensor circuits]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists from MIT have used carbon nanotubes to make a pencil lead, which they then used to draw sensors on paper printed with gold electrodes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 11:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/12/3407538/3407538_1E618F9E2F334276BD2A704FCEF167AA_170801_3407538_Carbon_nanotube_pencil_used_to_draw_sensor_circu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/08B/DB1/08BDB13804814CE88AF497E0353B60E2_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,MIT,chemists,Carbon nanotubes,pencil lead,sensors,gas,SCIENCE-CARBONNANOTUBES/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407535</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[‘Super Earth’ planet likely made of diamond]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A rocky planet that orbits a star located in the constellation Cancer is likely made largely of diamond, according to astronomers. 55 Cancri e is roughly twice as big as Earth and eight times heavier. The ‘super Earth’ is so close to its star that an orbit takes just 18 days while the surface temperature is 3,900 degrees Fahrenheit.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 11:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/12/3407535/3407535_C3FC30C520D94A89B5F07D071CCEC9DB_170801_3407535____Super_Earth____planet_likely_made_of_diamond_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E5E/3B3/E5E3B3215ADD446B87847CF7FF17F469_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Diamond planet,55 Cancri e,55 Cancri,diamond,18 hours,orbit,SPACE-SUPEREARTH/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407534</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Quartz glass holds data for hundred million years]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Hitachi unveils a method of storing digital information on quartz glass that holds data for more than 300 million years. The prototype is created by Professor Kiyotaka Miura of the Kyoto University, consisting of four layer of quartz glass, irradiated by a pulsed femtosecond laser to from dots and store 0s and 1a for binary data. The glass is waterproof, resistant to magnets, and can withstand heat of up to 1,000 degrees Celsius for two hours without suffering damage. It holds data at a density]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 11:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/11/3407534/3407534_4B99550AD4D745AA9D8FE3FDDC524838_170801_3407534_Quartz_glass_holds_data_for_hundred_million_year_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>53</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/234/AB2/234AB29D8F6E4C41AFB50339CD60BEE7_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Hitachi,quartz glass,femtosecond laser pulses,Kiyotaka Miura,Kyoto University,storage capacity,TECHNOLOGY-QUARTZ/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407530</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Asteroid dust could help combat climate change]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists in Scotland have come up with a novel geoengineering solution to combat global warming - using dust from an asteroid to reflect the sun's rays. The plan by boffins at the University of Strathclyde would involve using an electromagnet "mass driver" to alter the orbit of the asteroid 1036 Ganymed and positioning it at Lagrange point L1, where the gravitational pull of the Earth and Sun cancel out. Creating a dust cloud made from the asteroid anchored by the rock would then block approximately 6.58 percent of solar radiation from reaching the Earth, according to the plan.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 11:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/10/01/3407530/3407530_DC8336C03FB946868D7B37024F8C79A8_170801_3407530_Asteroid_dust_could_help_combat_climate_change_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B4B/E39/B4BE397632F24D009671EFD6A80F79FC_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,1036 Ganymed,asteroid,geoengineering,University of Strathclyde,mass driver,global warming,solar radiation,AUSTRALIA-TSUNAMIPOD/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407528</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Australian boat builder unveils tsunami survival pod]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An Australian houseboat builder has designed and built a tsunami survival pod. The reinforced pod is made from welded steel, has crumple zones to withstand impacts and can hold up to four people in safety seats. It has bulletproof glass and holds enough oxygen for up to two and a half hours. The design was inspired by the 2011 tsunami that hit Japan.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 11:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/09/24/3407528/3407528_7318644A6727466A9C2D4131C084DB7E_170801_3407528_Australian_boat_builder_unveils_tsunami_survival_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/04E/5B4/04E5B43BAF2941889C848482757F31B9_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Australia news,Tsunami,Tsunami survival pod]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407527</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Light from tablet computers disrupts sleep, says study]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Using tablet computers before bedtime can disrupt normal sleep patterns, a new study found. Under normal conditions the pineal gland in the brain secretes melatonin, a chemical that is partially responsible for regulating the sleep-wake cycle. Researchers at New York’s Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute found that when exposed to blue light from tablet computers the pineal gland is mislead into thinking it’s still daytime, and stops secreting the sleep-inducing chemical.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 11:09:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/09/12/3407527/3407527_E849F102122E4D9CBEF22157195B8320_170801_3407527_Light_from_tablet_computers_disrupts_sleep__says_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5FD/66A/5FD66A9BFABB4DF08A8F4B948ED30B79_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,iPad,Samsung,Galaxy,S3,iPhone,iPhone 5,Apple,melatonin,pineal gland,hypothalamus,brain,SCIENCE-BLUELIGHT/SLEEP]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407525</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Arctic ice cap melt could release vast amounts of methane]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[As seawater temperatures rise, the Arctic ice cap has been shrinking. From 2003 to 2010, records show Arctic ice melting rapidly. This year it shrank by 27,000 square miles from its record 2007 low to 1.5 million square miles, the lowest measurement since 1975. Apart from the risk of rising sea levels, the melting ice increases the possibility of releasing 4 billion metric tons of methane hydrate trapped underneath the Arctic ice sheet into the atmosphere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 11:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/09/05/3407525/3407525_B0527D5C53264A68B9D11EEEDA61C61C_170801_3407525_Arctic_ice_cap_melt_could_release_vast_amounts_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>62</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/19F/3F8/19F3F8759C194E768BE48AC059AE7614_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,methane,arctic ice melt,global warming,climate change,methane hydrate,CLIMATECHANGE-ARCTIC/ICECAP]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407524</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Blood clots and minimum-invasive retrieval methods]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Head injury is the most common cause of blood clots in the brain, and is thought to cause strokes. Three minimal invasive catheter methods to retrieve clots have been developed. Coiling uses a coilable microwire to wrap around the clot and a balloon to open up the artery so that the clot can be removed. Vacuuming uses a separator attached to a suction device to penetrate the clot and suck it out. The titanium net is attached to a microwire and allows blood cells to pass while retrieving the clot]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 11:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/30/3407524/3407524_4F12D4B349E5425ABDC9FD9F1F631EF6_170801_3407524_Blood_clots_and_minimum_invasive_retrieval_metho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/462/C8D/462C8DFDAED0411697498310F6317B1C_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Merci Retrieval System,Penumbra System,SHELTER catheter,blood clot,stroke,brain injury,retriev,SCIENCE-BLOODCLOTS/RETRIEVAL]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407521</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists unveil secret to strength in locust wings]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Insect wings are 10 times thinner than a human hair, yet they can withstand millions of cycles of rapid flapping in unfavorable conditions. Scientist Jan-Henning Dirks studied the S. gregaria, a long-distance flying desert locust, to discover the secret to insect wing strength. Dirks found that the membrane of the locusts’ wings is not as durable as was expected. Cross veins make the wings 50 percent more durable.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 11:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/28/3407521/3407521_A01930CBDABA4F8CB62900C7A05E5F30_170801_3407521_Scientists_unveil_secret_to_strength_in_locust_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>60</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/92D/2C5/92D2C53E91A0464598688ED284BBBF70_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,locust,wing,cuticle,hind wing,S. gregaria,Schistocerca gregaria,desert locust,insects,fly,SCIENCE-LOCUSTWINGS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407520</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Harvesting uranium from seawater]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers have come up with a potential new method of harvesting uranium - the fuel source for nuclear power - from seawater. Scientists at the 224th meeting of the American Chemical Society reported that when Chitin - a long-chain molecule found in shrimp shells - was woven into fiber mats, it captured uranyl ions from seawater more effectively than existing methods.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 11:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/27/3407520/3407520_83D56C8B60694B81856F03ABCE73E3F3_170801_3407520_Harvesting_uranium_from_seawater_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>69</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A09/CC0/A09CC0512DE74B638613724E258299E1_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,uranium,science,nuclear power,nuclear energy,poly-acrylamidoxime,University of Alabama,America,SCIENCE-URANIUM/HARVEST]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407519</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Wind farm]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The world’s largest rooftop wind farm has been installed on top of the Oklahoma Medical Research Foundation in Oklahoma City. Eighteen V2 vertical axis omni-directional wind turbines were positioned on the North and South sides of the complex. The project is the largest building integrated wind energy system in the U.S.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 11:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/27/3407519/3407519_EA60E347C7DF4D01A98E73C20F82005E_170801_3407519_Wind_farm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D65/6B9/D656B930A7E94D018A439D2706BA5F0D_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Oklahoma medical research foundation,OMRF,venger wind,v2 wind turbines,swg energy,world's large,USA-ENERGY/WINDFARM]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407518</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Aphid converts light into energy, like a plant]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists have discovered a type of aphid that is capable of converting light into energy in a photosynthesis-like process. The pea aphid makes carotenoids, a pigment and essential antioxidant that nearly all other animals must obtain by eating certain foods. Like plants, pea aphids use carotenoids to absorb light and convert it into adenosine triphosphate, or ATP, a molecule that all living things use to transfer energy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 11:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/17/08/24/3407518/3407518_D3FB2B7BD43248D39A2EC45FF48188D0_170801_3407518_Aphid_converts_light_into_energy__like_a_plant_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/442/2B0/4422B025ED114B2B97AF53097C0DE3C4_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,pea aphid,photosynthesis,adenosine triphosphate,ATP,carotenoid,antioxidant,carrots,science,SCIENCE-APHID/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3407517</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[DNA fingerprinting for trees may reduce illegal logging]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Furniture manufacturers and stores concerned about illegal timber can now perform DNA tests on their wood. DNA testing can identify the species and origin of a piece of timber. This allows companies to track timber from forest to shop floor in order to ensure that shipments are legal.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/17/08/21/3407517/3407517_A0257E60AFF84F0D9F1A248EE76D089B_170801_3407517_DNA_fingerprinting_for_trees_may_reduce_illegal__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/742/13C/74213CFEC7084059BF603B8596BD62C7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Singapore,DNA,lumber,timber,tracking,illegal logging,SINGAPORE-TREEDNA/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406643</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[What causes smartphone glass to break]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Whether a smartphone screen will shatter or escape destruction depends on a few factors. Two of these factors include; hardness and strength of the glass. Glass breaks when the force of impact becomes stronger than surface compression. A new company has come up with glass that can withstand more pressure per square inch. The new screen technology would increase phone screen durability by making it more resistant to cracks and shattering.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 11:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/21/3406643/3406643_8DF423B5EE2648D08417247E13892ECB_170731_3406643_What_causes_smartphone_glass_to_break_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/697/5C5/6975C523D6FA45D295E5E7A63F664145_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Technology,apple,smartphone,smartphone screen,Corning Gorilla Glass 2,SCIENCE-SMARTPHONE/GLASS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406642</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Curiosity rover zaps martian rock to test equipment]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Mars Curiosity rover has tested its laser and spectroscopy equipment on a 7cm rock dubbed ‘Coronation’. The rover’s ChemCam (Chemistry and Camera instrument) unit hit the rock with 30 pulses of infrared light over a 10-second period, observing the spark created through a special telescope. The unit will employ laser-induced breakdown spectroscopy to determine the kind of elements present in the Martian surface in further tests on the geology of the red planet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 11:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/20/3406642/3406642_3677793FFE164F0787B482660730EA72_170731_3406642_Curiosity_rover_zaps_martian_rock_to_test_equipm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E75/7C2/E757C2FE0F5249BE873677192D671B8B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Mars,Curiosity,Laser,Coronation,ChemCam,spectroscopy,Chemistry and Camera instruments,SPACE-MARS/CORONATION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406641</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[West Nile Virus - an explainer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[This year the US is facing its worst West Nile Virus outbreak in years. To date, there have been ten deaths reported in Texas and six in Louisiana. This animation shows the transmission cycle of the virus, how it attacks the human central nervous system, and ways to prevent infection.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 11:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/15/3406641/3406641_E02E177F403C471EB84AF57ABF4119DB_170731_3406641_West_Nile_Virus___an_explainer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>95</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CEE/B51/CEEB511C76B0418A97D5B7D77DFDBE3F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,West Nile virus,mosquito,Japanese encephalitis,Dengue fever,outbreak,health,SCIENCE-WESTNILEVIRUS/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406640</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Diseased trees turned into methane producers, study shows]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A paper published in Geophysical Research Letters shows that aging and diseased trees produce flammable concentration of methane, believed to be a new source of the potent greenhouse gas. Applied on a global scale the methane releases could count for up to ten percent of worldwide emissions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 11:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/13/3406640/3406640_BE4858887EB1406EBEFB71E1D45E7D41_170731_3406640_Diseased_trees_turned_into_methane_producers__st_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B80/641/B80641A7CD894880A0E6C29ACF58D337_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Connecticut,trees,methane,carbon,forest,geophysical,global warming,Geophysical Research Lette,CLIMATECHANGE-METHANE/DISEASEDTREES]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406638</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Baseball: What makes a curveball curve]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A curveball is a type of breaking ball that has a sideways or downward motion. When the pitcher releases the ball, the stitching on the leather causes pressure on one side of the ball to be greater than on the other side. This imbalance of force, called the Magnus force, makes the ball move faster on one side than the the other, resulting in a curved trajectory. This animation explains what makes a curveball curve.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 11:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/13/3406638/3406638_9B8EAAE1EDAD46F59EED568D7D628EB4_170731_3406638_Baseball__What_makes_a_curveball_curve_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>95</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/418/75C/41875C7068704327A031B0D298925367_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,baseball,physics,pitching,pitcher,how-do,tutorial,curveball,breaking ball,SCIENCE-CURVEBALL/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406637</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Acute water intoxication explained]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[This animation explains water intoxication, which is more common in the summer when people are more physically active. When a person drinks more than 2,000 milliliters of fluid a day, he or she risk being over-hydrated. Severe over-hydration can lead to acute water intoxication. Acute water intoxication happens when a large amount of water enters the body, making the concentration of electrolytes outside cells lower than inside cells. This triggers osmosis, in which water flows into cells, causi]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 11:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/13/3406637/3406637_9A8542FE53FD4742B720AC4890DFDC8E_170731_3406637_Acute_water_intoxication_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>53</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/03C/AF6/03CAF6F6B78E435A979DF5C8B0105466_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,acute water intoxication,water intoxication,over-hydration,hyponatremia,thirst,health,SCIENCE-ACUTEWATERINTOXICATION/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406636</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Cancer stem cell theory supported by study]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists want to know why cancer cells sometimes return after chemotherapy has eradicated the tumor. One debated theory is that cancer has its own “stem cells”. Three studies published in Nature and Science are in support of this theory. Researcher Luis Parada treated the mice with chemotherapy drugs after first making their brain cancer cells glow bright green. He found certain types of cancer cells can survive chemotherapy, and give rise to a new tumors afterwards.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 11:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/09/3406636/3406636_CB68F0837A2D484B983841FD26DE1D2F_170731_3406636_Cancer_stem_cell_theory_supported_by_study_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>74</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2AD/CEF/2ADCEF17F3AB46BDB1239F7168BA4086_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,cancer,tumor,cancer stem cell,stem cell,Nature,Science,Luis Parada,chemotherapy,mice,brain,SCIENCE-CANCER/STEM CELL THEORY]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406635</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Newly discovered bat virus offers insight to deadly Nipah, Hendra]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Australia’s newly discovered Cedar virus may provide a clue for curing the deadly Hendra and Nipah viruses, which are Henipaviruses carried in the bodily fluids of the Pteropid fruit bat. They have a respective 50 and 75 percent mortality rate. Cedar shares 90 percent of the genes found in the Hendra and Nipah viruses, but it does not cause any diseases in infected people. Scientists are trying to identify the differences between the viruses, in hopes of finding a cure for the Hendra and Nipah.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 11:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/08/3406635/3406635_40D871A7A9BB494FA59EA138A0A74F0F_170731_3406635_Newly_discovered_bat_virus_offers_insight_to_dea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>156</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C81/0A6/C810A65F1CFA48C89F3D45EF652DD3E5_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Nipah,Hendra,Cedar,fruit bat,bat virus,Henipavirus,Pteropid,Malaysia,Australia,AUSTRALIA-CEDARVIRUS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406629</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Achilles tear explained]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese hurdler Liu Xiang suffered an Achilles tear when he was running the 110-meter hurdles in the London Olympics on Aug. 7. The achilles tendon is attached to the calf muscle and heel bone. Tears or ruptures can be caused by sudden increases in stress or intensity, tight calf muscles, or bone spurs on the heel bone that cut into the Achilles tendon. Achilles tear is commonly treated by invasive surgery during which the Achilles tendon is stitched back together.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 11:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/08/3406629/3406629_9456309D5B4B40A2BFD7BAD1C841EC22_170731_3406629_Achilles_tear_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>45</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/515/C4D/515C4D74716F4B208762963886551BDB_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,achilles,tendon,rupture,tear,Liu Xiang,hurdles,Olympics,track and field,medical,SCIENCE-ACHILLESTEAR/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406627</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Windstalk concept clean energy project]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The windstalk is a concept design by New York design firm Atelier DNA as a possible clean energy generation project for Abu Dhabi’s Masdar City. The proposed windstalk farm would consists of more than one thousand 180-foot-tall carbon fiber reinforced resin poles anchored by sloping concrete bases. At the top of each windstalk is a wind-powered LED light. As the windstalk sways in the wind, pressure is applied to piezoelectric discs, generating electricity, which powers the light.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 11:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/08/01/3406627/3406627_0A088FCC92624AA682A948BDE5470FC9_170731_3406627_Windstalk_concept_clean_energy_project_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CE0/E6A/CE0E6AF6598647CA9EFA2859A1DDD181_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,windstalk,Atelier DNA,energy,environment,Dubai,New York,design,piezoelectric,SCIENCE-WINDSTALK/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406626</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Landslides on Saturn’s moon, Iapetus, raise interest]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists are interested in Iapetus, Saturn’s third largest moon, because of its massive landslides, long-runout landslides that can travel horizontally as much as 30 times their vertical falling distance. On Earth, landslides typically travel less than twice their vertical falling distance.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 11:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/31/3406626/3406626_4A92B506988C437E96350836C5A848E2_170731_3406626_Landslides_on_Saturn___s_moon__Iapetus__raise_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2E6/3C4/2E63C4036A9F44C798A1861DF91AE0E1_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Saturn,moon,Iapetus,landslide,SPACE-SATURN/LANDSLIDE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406625</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Creating plant-based vaccines]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Vaccine firm Medicago has successfully used a plant-based production method to create more than 10 million doses of an H1N1 VLP influenza vaccine candidate in one month, the US Department of Defense’s DARPA lab announced on July 25.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 11:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/31/3406625/3406625_E6C437E5125942B0BF08800D51160E2C_170731_3406625_Creating_plant_based_vaccines_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BCF/FAF/BCFFAF23FF12462783C7428C7BBECCB4_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,flu,vaccine,virus,bacteria,medical,SCIENCE-VACCINES/PLANT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406624</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Chemical AAQ helps blind mice to see]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team of scientists from University of California, Berkeley, in collaboration with researchers at the University of Munich and University of Washington in Seattle, have discovered a chemical that temporarily restores vision to blind mice called AAQ (acrylamide-azobenzene-quaternary ammonium). AAQ is a photoswitch that binds the protein ion channels in the surface of the retina. When there is light, the compound is activated and allows the ions to flow through the channels.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 11:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/30/3406624/3406624_6FDFFBD628084A869F2D41D082DC88D0_170731_3406624_Chemical_AAQ_helps_blind_mice_to_see_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>58</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D83/EAD/D83EADF9C9C44FD6BD2A74472F81C780_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,AAQ,acrylamide-azobenzene-quaternary ammonium,Berkeley University,retinitis pigmentosa,SCIENCE-AAQ/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406623</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Libor scandal explained]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Barclays Bank has been accused of attempting to manipulate the London Interbank Offered Rate (Libor). This animation explains what the Libor is, why it’s important and how Barclays attempted to manipulate the rate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 11:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/12/3406623/3406623_6B9EC0BD98D748099353B887141373B5_170731_3406623_Libor_scandal_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4A4/819/4A4819860A254629BDFCA0B34A80BD6E_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Libor,scandal,finance,banking,BRITAIN-LIBORSCANDAL/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406622</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Acidification of Oceans major threat to world’s reefs]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Acidification of the world’s oceans has become the largest threat to the health of the globe’s coral reefs, according to a top US scientist. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration chief Jane Lubchenco said that acidity levels are rising as oceans absorb more and more carbon dioxide, posing a threat to coral, fish stocks and hence the livelihood and food supply of millions of people around the world. This animation explains acidification process and its effects.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 11:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/10/3406622/3406622_6CFE20E4AFFB48B49F35F48450F4E3C6_170731_3406622_Acidification_of_Oceans_major_threat_to_world____2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DA7/C6C/DA7C6C1CB37D4D19866ECA3659184C88_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,NOAA,National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration,Coral,reefs,acidification,bleaching,CLIMATECHANGE-ACIDIFICATION/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406621</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Emergency residential power generator illustration]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[For residents who experience regular power outages, it's a good idea to set up backup standby generators that turn on automatically during an outage. Portable generators can also be used in place standby generators to power a house. This animation illustrates the various household appliances that can be powered by generators.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 11:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/04/3406621/3406621_7FFEE34BFB3F48449B09D7473F2CFFF8_170731_3406621_Emergency_residential_power_generator_illustrati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5F6/B20/5F6B20959C1D420DA94190E9D9668267_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,power,emergency,generator,TECHNOLOGY-PORTABLEGENERATORS/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406620</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[CERN Large Hadron Collider: How it works]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on tests conducted at the Large Hadron Collider on the French-Swiss border, scientists at the CERN research center believe they have found the so-called "God Particle," the Higgs boson, so named because it gives other subatomic particle their mass. The Higgs boson has been theorized for decades but never directly observed. Confirmation of its existence would place it alongside other subatomic particles to have been observed within the Standard Model of particle physics. This animation explains how the Large Hadron Collider works. The existence of the Higgs boson was confirmed after analyzing data from the Large Hadron Collider, which is part of the European Organization for Nuclear Research (CERN).]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 11:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/04/3406620/3406620_2FF32B7C1DFA45DFBFE7F2485660638B_170731_3406620_CERN_Large_Hadron_Collider__How_it_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>63</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9DC/24B/9DC24BAEEB564840809FB50CEA596411_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,CERN,Large Hadron Collider,Higgs boson,science,SCIENCE-CERN/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406617</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Scientists find evidence for Higgs boson]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists at the CERN research center believe they have found the so-called "God Particle," the Higgs boson, so named because it gives other subatomic particle their mass.The Higgs boson has been theorized for decades but never directly observed. Confirmation of its existence would place it alongside other subatomic particles to have been observed within the Standard Model of particle physics. This animation explains why the Higgs boson is believed to exist.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 11:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/04/3406617/3406617_58A00419983545D6B7FB0F96F021AB05_170731_3406617_Scientists_find_evidence_for_Higgs_boson_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>66</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4E6/61A/4E661A2437AD4AE3AFB399C22A958608_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,CERN,Large hadron collider,god particle,Higgs boson,science,SCIENCE-HIGGSBOSON/EVIDENCE]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406616</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Artificial pancreas: how it works]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[British researchers are developing an artificial pancreas that would automatically control levels of glucose in the bloodstream, obviating the need for diabetics to constantly monitor and regulate their blood sugar levels during the day and reducing the risk of dangerous blood sugar levels developing while diabetics are sleeping. The artificial pancreas is being developed by principal research associate Roman Hovorka and a team at the University of Cambridge. It would not replace the pancreas but would consist of an externally worn sensor that would monitor glucose levels and an external pump that would use a computer algorithm to calculate doses of insulin and glucose and dispense them based on changes in glucose levels.   SOURCES: HealthDay News, University of Cambridge Metabolic Research Laboratories]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 11:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/07/02/3406616/3406616_03A0AB2C49DF4F42B84105E602AE359C_170731_3406616_Artificial_pancreas__how_it_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>41</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/15C/E31/15CE31D3059046C6A1CD7F75F6D9302B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,artificial pancreas,Cambridge,medical,UK,health,science,diabetes,insulin,glucose,glucagon,SCIENCE-ARTIFICIALPANCREAS/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3406614</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Cow bred to produce low-lactose milk]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese scientists say they have developed the world’s first genetically modified calf that will produce low-lactose milk. Scientists at Inner Mongolia University injected genes from bacteria-like organisms known as archaea into cells from cow embryos using the technique used to clone Dolly the Sheep. Fourteen embryos were transplanted into 14 cows. Five calves were born, of which three carried the low-lactose gene. Two died soon after birth. SOURCES: Daily Telegraph]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 11:27:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/06/19/3406614/3406614_F762E912E8DC445690877578370EC813_170731_3406614_Cow_bred_to_produce_low_lactose_milk_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E17/4C7/E174C74524E54F918F5704E48DB17E91_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,cow,lactose intolerance,genetically modified,clone,China,SCIENCE-MONGOLIA/LOWLACTOSEMILK]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404462</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Backpack makes transporting water easier in developing countries]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Greif and Impact Economics together have launched the BackthePack movement and developed the WaterWear backpack to help women and children in developing countries transport clean water more safely and with less effort. The pack holds up to 20 liters of water, reducing spills with roll-down closure, and weights 7 times lighter than a 20L jerry can. SOURCES: wH2O Journal, Treehugger]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 11:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/06/19/3404462/3404462_1E7F56EA2E0F4905A23A95F16952F017_170728_3404462_Backpack_makes_transporting_water_easier_in_deve_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/000/34D/00034DA67AB644EEA779E05D3F7913E8_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Greif,Back the Pack,WaterWear backpack,USA,Impact Economics,developing country,Haiti,TECHNOLOGY-BACKTHEPACK/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404461</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Bones grown in lab could be used to repair badly damaged limbs]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Stem cell therapy may be used to fix broken bones in the future. Researchers at private company Bonus BioGroup and Israel’s Technion Institute of Research have successfully implanted bones grown from fat tissue stem cells into rats. Human experiments are scheduled for later this year. SOURCES: The Telegraph]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 11:14:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/06/11/3404461/3404461_62AF515EE49C4B7190034C5E38697ABE_170728_3404461_Bones_grown_in_lab_could_be_used_to_repair_badly_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6ED/A80/6EDA80B69AA44F19BCD8750FF2DBFAC2_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,stem cell,bone,injury,accident,bone fracture,cast,crash,fat,fat issue,liposuction,Avinoam,SCIENCE-BIOENGINEER/LIMBS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404459</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Root canal procedure]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A root canal is a dental procedure performed by a dentist or endodontist to treat a badly infected or damaged tooth rather than remove it. A root canal procedure is performed when bacteria infects tissue in the tooth’s pulp, which contains nerves and blood vessels, and spreads throughout the root canal, the cavity in the tooth that contains the pulp. A root canal typically takes between one to three visits. This animation explains how a root canal works. Source: Mayo Clinic, Bupa]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 11:14:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/06/07/3404459/3404459_AE301800CDFB4D92B5C33A1328B3E8F0_170728_3404459_Root_canal_procedure_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CA3/C04/CA3C04E50B1E4F79B982D71DA38E8110_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,root canal,tooth,dental,health,dentist,SCIENCE-ROOTCANAL/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404458</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Human settlement on Mars by 2023]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Dutch group called Mars One plans to have humans live on Mars by 2023. Starting next year, selected candidates will be put through a 10-year training program preparing for living on Mars. The supply mission will use Space X Heavy to launch the communication satellite and supplement to Mars by 2016. The first 4 astronauts will be sent to Mars by 2022 and land on Mars by 2023. SOURCES: THE WEEK, Yahoo news]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 11:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/06/07/3404458/3404458_BC2C45BD5505463787FB6C2D34ABFFF4_170728_3404458_Human_settlement_on_Mars_by_2023_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>56</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/305/AD0/305AD013C6574A289B7BE8FD1648F763_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Mars One,Dutch,Space X,satellite,Mars,Red Planet,space,astronauts,Hohmann transfer orbit,SPACE-MARS/HUMANSETTLEMENT/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404456</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Solar cogeneration: a more efficient form of solar power]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Solar cogeneration combines a photovoltaic and thermal module to provide electricity and hot water. Traditional PV systems convert about 15 percent of solar energy into electricity, with the remaining energy wasted. Solar cogeneration captures up to 75 percent, converting the waste heat into hot water. It can yield five times the energy of traditional PV systems. SOURCES: Solar Novus Today, GIGAOM]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 11:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/06/05/3404456/3404456_ABBE38D6E78F4E29B9512FC34F8BF4D8_170728_3404456_Solar_cogeneration__a_more_efficient_form_of_sol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>53</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D25/BD7/D25BD78A2FF44212AC4B8070C75B7DE8_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,CongeraSolar,California,solar cogeneration,energy,solar photovoltaic,PV system,electrocity,SCIENCE-ENERGY/SOLARCOGENERATION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404454</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[How small insects survive in the rain]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team of scientists from the Georgia Institute of Technology have discovered how small insects cope with rain. The study found that when a mosquito is hit by a raindrop, its body puts up little resistance. The mosquito simply combines wit the droplet and begins to fall. Water repellent hairs then enable the mosquito to free itself from the droplet before it hits the ground. SOURCES: BBC]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 11:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/06/05/3404454/3404454_69626E7BE4AC424A92AEB909FFF805AC_170728_3404454_How_small_insects_survive_in_the_rain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E12/A43/E12A43B0141B4F6FB857C93B633A7E90_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Georgia Institute of Technology,Mosquito,rain,water repellent hairs,raindrop,SCIENCE-SMALLINSECTS/RAIN]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404451</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Mystery surrounding Earth’s core deepened by new study]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A new study has increased the mystery surrounding the inner workings of the planet. The study by boffins at the University of London and published in Nature, found that the solid ball of iron that forms the Earth’s core is losing heat 2-3 times faster than previously thought via a process called conduction. This suggests that the core could be solidifying much faster than earlier estimates. Source: NY Times]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 11:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/05/31/3404451/3404451_3FE4ABF323504BE3BC1FB0608164C634_170728_3404451_Mystery_surrounding_Earth___s_core_deepened_by_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E42/62D/E4262D58AF8B49EBB7A2AA5B8293D00A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Earth,core,Mars,University of London,Nature,conduction,SCIENCE-EARTHCORE/CONDUCTION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404450</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Developing more effective migraine treatments]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[For a century, scientists thought migraines were a vascular disease. But now it is thought that migraines are related to a wave of overactive neurons that spreads across the brain, which in turn affects blood vessels. Researchers hope to use this understanding to develop more effective treatments with fewer side effects for migraines that can stop the wave of overexcited neurons. Sources: Scientific American, Science News, Mayo Clinic, University of Maryland Medical Center.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 11:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/05/29/3404450/3404450_A3549C702EF748CDB6AEE504E959E1E6_170728_3404450_Developing_more_effective_migraine_treatments_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/792/437/79243784D9EF4252B130BD8A2DF300D1_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,migraine,neuron,neurotransmitter,ion,pain,medical,brain,SCIENCE-MIGRAINE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404448</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Permafrost melt releasing stored methane]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers from the University of Alaska at Fairbanks (UAF) have identified tens of thousands of methane seeps in areas along the coast of Alaska and Greenland. Some experts believe the escape of large quantities of previously frozen methane could lead to a swift acceleration in global warming. SOURCES:BBC]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 11:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/05/21/3404448/3404448_F4D6D8840C0248A894021C424AF0996B_170728_3404448_Permafrost_melt_releasing_stored_methane_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/240/520/240520207D324788ADA0ED695DCABF43_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Arctic,permafrost,melting,Siberia,Alaska,Greenland,methane,global warming,CLIMATECHANGE-PERMAFROST/MELT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404447</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Study identifies how pigeons navigate using magnetic fields]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists have moved one step further to decoding the secret behind the superior navigation skills of pigeons. A new study by scientists at Baylor College of Medicine published in Nature found neurons in the pigeon’s brains react to changes in the intensity and direction of magnetic fields. They believe the neurons interpret signals sent from receptors located in the eyes, nose and ear, helping the pigeon to navigate. Sources: Discovery, Popular Science]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 11:09:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/27/3404447/3404447_3F3D2813636D4D1581EA7C4175F5040A_170728_3404447_Study_identifies_how_pigeons_navigate_using_magn_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1B0/638/1B06383841254D60BB0DBF0F6CFA7713_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,pigeons,navigation,GPS,magnetic field,brain stem,Baylor College of Medicine,Houston,SCIENCE-PIGEONS/NAVIGATION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404446</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Egg laying ‘led to dinosaurs extinction’]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The fact that dinosaurs laid eggs was a major factor in their extinction, a scientist has claimed. Marcus Clauss of the University of Zurich said the physical limitations of egg size meant that dinosaur young were comparatively small and had to compete with adults of other animal groups. The end came when a large meteorite smashed into Earth 65 million years ago killing all large dinosaurs. Source: The Telegraph, AFP]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 11:08:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/19/3404446/3404446_34C427847C6A4822808D6780C36D8EFB_170728_3404446_Egg_laying____led_to_dinosaurs_extinction____2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/301/3B4/3013B4A60AD743349C3C98FA3A52FD5E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,dinosaurs,extinct,eggs,University of Zurich,cretaceous-tertiary,mammals,meteorite,65 million,SWITZERLAND-DINOSAURS/EXTINCTION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404445</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Evacuated Tube Transport could take you around the world in just 6 hours]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Evacuated Tube Transport is an airless, frictionless, maglev-like form of transportation which is safer, cheaper and quieter than trains or airplanes. Six-person capsules travel in the tubes and can reach a maximum speed of 6,500 km/h, and provide 50 times more transportation per kwh. A tube can travel from New York to Beijing in two hours, and make a round-the-world trip in just six hours. Sources: ET3.com, Discovery News]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 11:08:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/17/3404445/3404445_34C4CFEA73254CFD95D6C528775E42FE_170728_3404445_Evacuated_Tube_Transport_could_take_you_around_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EED/B75/EEDB75AA2DC04B1C959753E361D0DC9D_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Evacuated Tube Transport,ET3,ETT,transportation,travel,maglev,electric,capsule,technology,TECHNOLOGY-TRANSPORT/EVACUATEDTUBETRANSPORT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404444</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[ErgoSensor monitor detects improper ergonomic posture]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Electronics giant Philips has unveiled a monitor keeps computer users in a healthier position. The sensor is built-in to where the webcam is located. It is able to detect a user's position and distance from the monitor, and gives advices on body posture. It also comes with a timed-break function that reminds users if they have been sat at the display for too long. When the user is away from the screen, the display will automatically switch itself off to save power. Sources: CNET, Philips]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 11:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/11/3404444/3404444_953E8B6655C54142809F1A2BF7E2D270_170728_3404444_ErgoSensor_monitor_detects_improper_ergonomic_po_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D8B/126/D8B12672A11442E1A4A01196E2AF24E6_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Philips,ErgoSensor,ergonomics,LCD monitor,health,tech,energy savings,display,sensor,TECHNOLOGY-ERGOSENSOR/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404441</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Geothermal energy: How it works]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Geothermal energy taps reservoirs of steam or hot water beneath the earth’s surface heated by magma, friction or radioactive heat sources. Cold water is pumped into the reservoir, where it is heated. Pressure pushes heated water up to the surface. This hot water heats a secondary fluid via a heat exchanger. Steam from the secondary fluid spins a turbine to generate electricity. Sources: Economist]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 11:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/06/3404441/3404441_04E10977965D43FF873C5D7FD51E5F09_170728_3404441_Geothermal_energy__How_it_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/99A/B64/99AB644641954302848F330FA683CB46_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,geothermal,energy,environment,water,power,electricity,SCIENCE-GEOTHERMAL/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3404440</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Inside the world's quietest room]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An anechoic chamber in Minneapolis’s Orfield Laboratory holds the Guinness world record for the world's quietest place at -9.4 decibels. As humans can only detect sounds above 0 decibels, the chamber is virtually soundless. The room consists of a mesh floor, walls lined with meter-long sound-proofing wedges, and a meshed ceiling. Source: Minnesota Public Radio]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 11:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/05/3404440/3404440_FC610D4AADCA4AFFA6ED3CB72C4EA3E5_170728_3404440_Inside_the_world_s_quietest_room_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/354/5EA/3545EA44104044138F6BFE269E12567E_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Orfield Laboratory,quiet,quietest,Guinness world record,Steven Orfield,noise,sound,sound proof,SCIENCE-SOUNDPROOFROOM/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403591</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Wildfires more common during Cretaceous]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Findings published in the journal Cretaceous Research reveal that during the Cretaceous, 145 to 65 million years ago, wildfires were much more common than previously thought. During the Cretaceous, temperatures were higher and there was more oxygen in the atmosphere, increasing the number of places where and how often wildfires would occur. These conditions also helped flowering plants, which evolved during the Cretaceous. Sources: University of London via Science Daily, BBC]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 11:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/03/3403591/3403591_B8879B0C53F84738BA45E2CCC1C31852_170727_3403591_Wildfires_more_common_during_Cretaceous_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/652/681/652681E4E3114EC4AA40E388FFD8C722_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,fire,wildfire,dinosaurs,Cretaceous,nature,science,University of London,Field Museum,Chicago,SCIENCE-WILDFIRE/CRETACEOUS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403589</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Titanic: animated reconstruction of the sinking of the Titanic]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[On April 15, 1912, the Titanic was on its maiden voyage from the UK to New York when it struck an iceberg and sank to the bottom of the Atlantic. A detailed map of the wreckage created by combining by 130,000 images captured by unmanned submarines during an expedition in 2010 suggests that while the bow glided nose-first to the bottom of the ocean, the stern picked up speed as it corkscrewed to the bottom of the ocean. Sources: National Geographic, AP, BBC]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 11:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/04/03/3403589/3403589_0BDBE58A3346434C9C5F121F5D105968_170727_3403589_Titanic__animated_reconstruction_of_the_sinking__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>77</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A6A/FF9/A6AFF968F23D461AB65D9D2DFEB50712_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Titanic,animated,reconstruction,sinking,sink,reconstruction,wreck,iceberg,BRITAIN-TITANIC/RECONSTRUCTION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403588</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Carbon capture and sequestration methods]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Carbon capture and storage is a way to limit damage to the environment by carbon dioxide emissions. Carbon dioxode can be injected deep underground into saline aquifers, depleted oil or gas reservoirs, and unmineable coal beds. The gas can also be piped into the ocean. At a depth of 1,000 meters, it dissolves into the water. On the seafloor at 3,000 meters, where carbon dioxide becomes dense enough not to rise, it forms a “carbon dioxide lake.” Sources: Science Daily, National Geographic]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 11:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/03/21/3403588/3403588_A212432CBF3E49D085284963E483BA43_170727_3403588_Carbon_capture_and_sequestration_methods_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/90E/898/90E898B95CBA46F4AF89A2A893EB430F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Carbon capture and storage,carbon dioxide,environment,science,pollution,energy,SCIENCE-CARBONCAPTURE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403585</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[‘Unique’ neutron star system’s activity captured by NASA]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[In October 2010, a neutron star near the center of the Milky Way emitted hundreds of X-ray bursts triggered by thermonuclear explosions on the star's surface. NASA’s Rossi X-ray Timing Explorer, or RXTE, observed some 400 such events between October 13 and November 19 on T5X2, a pulsar in the Terzan 5 star cluster. A study of the data will be published in the March 20 issue of The Astrophysical Journal. Source: NASA via Science Daily]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/03/14/3403585/3403585_224C8F24AFFA413C8D08EEF8C876A904_170727_3403585____Unique____neutron_star_system___s_activity_ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C19/BE7/C19BE74858444C99B2628128ABB3444C_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,RXTE,neutron,star,pulsar,NASA,T5X2,satellite,space,science,X-rays,thermonuclear,SPACE-NEURONSTAR/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403584</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Tyrannosaurus rex bite stronger than previously thought]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[In a new study published in UK journal Biology Letters, researchers at Liverpool University predict that a Tyrannosaurus rex’s bite is much stronger than previously thought. Researchers used laser scanners to digitize T. rex jaws and used computer models to reconstruct the jaw muscles of the T. rex and estimate its bite force. The study predicts T. rex had a bite force of 20,000 to 57,000 Newtons. Source: Liverpool University via National Geographic]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 11:27:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/03/05/3403584/3403584_877EC4A83308480FA01C1597B530F965_170727_3403584_Tyrannosaurus_rex_bite_stronger_than_previously__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4DA/05F/4DA05F28972B4A24B342D307452E708A_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Tyrannosaurus rex,T.rex,Liverpool University,biology,dinosaurs,bite,elephant,BRITAIN-TYRANOSSAURUSREX/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403582</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Asteroid could strike Earth in 2040]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a 1 in 625 chance that a 460-foot asteroid named 2011 AG5 will strike the Earth in the year 2040, scientists have warned. The impact probability is based on an observation of only one-half of the asteroid’s orbit, and could change upon further study. In 2029, the asteroid must pass through a 62-mile wide window in space, or “keyhole,” in order to maintain its collision course with the planet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 11:26:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/02/28/3403582/3403582_1B748D3DBC4D4E728C81D73E124940D4_170727_3403582_Asteroid_could_strike_Earth_in_2040_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/02E/C77/02EC77EC4D6A4C5AA292EB2A99FE479B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,2040,2011 ag5,asteroid,asteroid impact,space,collision,Earth,SCIENCE-ASTEROIDSTRIKE/2040]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403581</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Ice Age flower brought back to life by Russian scientists]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Russian scientists have successfully germinated a seed that had been stuck in the Siberian permafrost for around 30,000 years. The perfectly preserved Silene stenophylla seeds were found in ancient squirrel tunnels located around 125 feet under the earth’s surface. The ancient plants are subtly different than their modern counterparts with wider petals and more buds.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/02/22/3403581/3403581_81A58807AED54773ACEC843F628FE725_170727_3403581_Ice_Age_flower_brought_back_to_life_by_Russian_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9E4/0D1/9E40D1A1CAC94FF7B6A63D04E4B7C78F_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Flower,Ice Age,Russian scientists,back to life,30,000 years,Silene stenophylla,SCIENCE-ICEAGE/FLOWER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403580</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[CleanSpace One satellite designed to clean up space junk]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Ecole Polytechnique Federale de Lausanne, or EPFL, has unveiled a satellite program dedicated to cleaning up space junk. The CleanSpace One program consists of satellites with a grappling arm designed to take out space junk piece by piece, making space safer for the ever growing number of satellites. NASA tracks about 16,000 objects that are considered space junk.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 11:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/02/16/3403580/3403580_BD64E3BC96024C24B55B625D70C61A99_170727_3403580_CleanSpace_One_satellite_designed_to_clean_up_sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EA2/7B5/EA27B5B4F1EE41CA9DB6F0120528A6A0_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,EPFL,NASA,Outer space,Satellite,SPACE-CLEANSPACEONE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403579</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Artificial jawbone created with 3D printing technology]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[An 83-year-old woman's infected jawbone has been successfully replaced with an artificial 3D-printed titanium jawbone in a world first. The 3D-printing technology developed by LayerWise NV of Belgium used additive laser melting in which a 3D printer builds up a medical implant layer by layer. The artificial jaw was fabricated from titanium powder and weighs about 107g. The patient is now able to speak and function normally again.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 11:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/02/14/3403579/3403579_CA1D6AF98AE5453BB705A53973588D7D_170727_3403579_Artificial_jawbone_created_with_3D_printing_tech_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/330/DE4/330DE4FEFF49497ABE24992391CAA7D5_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,3D,technology,LayerWise,artificial,jaw,3D printing,BELGIUM-3DPRINTING/ARTIFICIALJAW]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403578</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Ocean wave electricity]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Renewable energy startup Columbia Power Technologies recently developed a technology that generates electricity from ocean waves. The Searay works by using magnets and an electric coil to generate electricity from the rise and fall of the waves. CPT hopes the Searay, one of a number of devices in development that use wave power to generate electricity, will become the next 'wave' in renewable energy. Sources:Forbes, Columbia Power Technologies]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 11:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/02/10/3403578/3403578_EB24550AF62D45598585AE92F06793AA_170727_3403578_Ocean_wave_electricity_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8A1/E25/8A1E254CD29C431AAB8AE62A54862644_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,lucia.chang@nextanimation.com.tw Pre-2015 content upload for Newsdirect Archive Site Pre-2015 content upload for Newsdirect Archive Site   Comments Share FileEditViewInsertFormatDataToolsAdd-onsHelpAll changes saved in Drive      $%  123  Arial   10                                        Wave electric,Ecofriendly,Renewabale engery,Columbia power,Save Energy,Columbia Power Technologi To enable screen reader support,press Ctrl+Alt+Z To learn about keyboard shortcuts,press Ctrl+slash      	  	Youtube Top 100 pre 2015  Top Discovery Videos  		   Explore  Wave electric,Ecofriendly,Renewabale engery,Columbia power,Save Energy,Columbia Power Technologi,SCIENCE-OCEANWAVE/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403576</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Clams feed off Earth’s mantle near deep, low-temperature vents]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Japanese and US scientists working from the Japanese R/V Yokosuka have found a species of clam near low-temperature vents in the Mariana Trench. The clams live at a depth of 5,620 meters in a subduction zone near vents where low-temperature water emerges from exposed mantle. The mantle reacts with the water in a process called serpentinization, producing hydrogen and methane. The methane produces hydrogen sulfide, which clams feed on. Sources: Mainichi Daily News, University of Hawaii]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 11:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/02/10/3403576/3403576_C767480BAF444ACD8AC272C3AFDDCAE9_170727_3403576_Clams_feed_off_Earth___s_mantle_near_deep__low_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3CC/8BF/3CC8BFEF3A94467CA623F237DD2F5DEC_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,clam,Yokosuka,Mariana Trench,serpentinization,mantle,rock,hydrogen sulfide,science,nature,SCIENCE-CLAMS/SERPENTINIZATION]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403574</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[EU to use drones to catch cheating farmers]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Authorities across Europe are turning to drones in a bid to catch farmers who may be ignoring EU farming regulations or claiming illegal subsidies. The drones can be used to catch offenders who have ignored regulations and felled trees or illegally dumped farm chemicals. Drones can also be used in places where a lack of clear skies makes using satellites unsuitable.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 11:22:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/12/02/09/3403574/3403574_5A906070ED294DA6A00626D596DA240E_170727_3403574_EU_to_use_drones_to_catch_cheating_farmers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0F7/C72/0F7C72EBCB5A47C09456470E55DD2FF3_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,EU,Scotland,drones,farming subsidies,illegal activity,farmers,EUROPE-TECHNOLOGY/DRONES]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403571</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Kepler 22b: earth-like planet discovered]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[NASA’s Kepler space telescope has discovered a planet in a habitable zone around a star with similar conditions to our own Sun. Kepler 22b’s year is 290 days long and scientsts estimate the surface temperature is around 72 degrees, although they are not sure if the planet is made up of water, gas or rock. Kepler 22-b lies about 600 light-years away from earth and is about 2.4 times the size of Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 11:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/11/12/06/3403571/3403571_E920C2755D064A549E33FEC774D709F5_170727_3403571_Kepler_22b__earth_like_planet_discovered_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/371/C11/371C11BC90CB458FB9570C6EB3C43A1B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Kepler 22b,new Earth,Kepler space telescope,NASA,habitable zone,goldilocks zone,SPACE-KEPLER22B/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403570</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Arctic ozone loss hits new record]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Arctic Ozone loss this year formed an "ozone hole" similar to the one in the Antarctic for the first time, scientists report. The destruction of ozone was more pronounced due to an unusually long period of cold weather which speeds up the reaction between chlorofluorocarbons and atmospheric ozone. Source: BBC]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 11:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/11/10/03/3403570/3403570_0BC2C55D4A514180AF28B716E62EA757_170727_3403570_Arctic_ozone_loss_hits_new_record_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5E8/AE7/5E8AE7F19351432D8103DE14862C0032_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Arctic,ozone layer,chlorofluorocarbons,UV-,UV-A,atmospheric ozone,CLIMATECHANGE-ARCTICOZONE/]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403569</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[How rotator cuff injuries occur]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The world’s top tennis player, Novak Djokovic, heads to Flushing Meadows for the US Open this week. Despite his recent dominance, he has complained of a shoulder injury over the past weeks. Shoulder injuries are common in tennis because the sport involves consistent rotation of the arm. This makes the bursa and rotator cuff rub against the shoulder bone, causing inflammation and pain. Source: WebMD, Orthoinfo, Orthogate]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 11:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/11/08/31/3403569/3403569_FAE31D69F24446058F2F719576F9B075_170727_3403569_How_rotator_cuff_injuries_occur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BBF/879/BBF879BC6E474AEDA9253114CD26C9E4_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,rotator cuff,US Open,Novak Djokovic,shoulder,Flushing Meadows,New York,medical,SCIENCE-ROTATORCUFF/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403568</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[How hurricanes form]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Hurricanes form when warm humid air rises from the ocean. Convergent winds force the warm air into the atmosphere, where it releases latent heat as it condenses into clouds and rain. The exchange of the heat from the surface creates a pattern of wind that spirals up around the eye of the storm, and the hurricane grows, powered by the ocean’s heat and evaporating water. Source: NASA]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 11:19:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/11/08/26/3403568/3403568_C807554F4DF44755A3F77DDC256F0856_170727_3403568_How_hurricanes_form_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B11/A65/B11A65CA54864B0EB273CF22904C3071_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,hurricane,weather,Irene,SCIENCE-HURRICANES/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403566</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[How lightning strikes happen and how to avoid them]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Nine people were recovering after being struck by lightning in Florida on Tuesday, including 22-year-old Brian Owens, who was in an SUV, and eight people at the Discovery Cove theme park. This animation shows how lightning strikes occur and what to do to avoid being struck by lightning.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 11:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/11/08/17/3403566/3403566_932186600E334C8DB7FEB1855923E259_170727_3403566_How_lightning_strikes_happen_and_how_to_avoid_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>59</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/326/D51/326D51A0072845CFABD5BF746232777E_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,lightning,Brian Owens,Discovery Cove,Florida,SCIENCE-LIGHTNING/EXPLAINER]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403563</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[Earth may have had two moons]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[In a paper published on Wednesday in Nature, scientists proposed that two moons were formed billions of years ago when a Mars-sized planet slammed into the Earth  our Moon and a tiny Trojan moon that inhabited what’s known as a Lagrange point 60 degrees in front of or behind the Moon. Eventually the Sun’s gravity caused both moons to collide, with the tiny moon fragmenting across the far side of our Moon. Source: Nature]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 11:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/11/08/04/3403563/3403563_9476D7AE5D79400F8FB948D4560D3D9C_170727_3403563_Earth_may_have_had_two_moons_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/200/00C/20000CD9F86547A583606B50A4953313_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Next Animation Studio,Taiwanese Animators,News,Politics,Education,Educational,News & Politics,Earth,Moon,science,astronomy,Nature,SPACE-EARTH/TWOMOONS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3403562</guid>
      <title><![CDATA[How a nuclear plant works]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A nuclear power plant creates energy that turns water into steam. The steam turns a turbine that is connected to a generator that produces electricity. Meanwhile, the steam is converted back to water and returned to the reactor core. Inside the reactor core are fuel rod contains pellets of uranium dioxide. Nuclear fission occurs inside the fuel rods, releasing thermal energy that turns the water into steam. To prevent overheating, control rods are inserted into the reactor core.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:14:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/648/11/06/01/3403562/3403562_8461CA3436C64563886F4B31C24ED256_170727_3403562_How_a_nuclear_plant_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/04E/D18/04ED1897E86B430E866A30DD52AF2925_