<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Wochit</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 15:06:09 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3231310</guid>
      <title>Race to Mars: Mars One to colonize Mars by building permanent habitats on red planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARS  The race to Mars has begun. SpaceX Chief Executive Elon Musk has announced that the company will send people to the red planet by 2024 and that he would reveal plans for colonization in September, the Los Angeles Times reported.Meanwhile, a nonprofit group also aims to establish permanent Mars colonies, sending the first group of astronauts by 2026.After Earth, Mars is the most habitable planet in our solar system. It has similar natural resources, a temperate climate and an adaptable gravitational pull on its surface. Mars One  a non profit foundation founded in 2011 with a team of ambassadors and advisors including an astronaut, Nobel Prize laureate and the former NASA Chief Technologist  has developed a mission plan to colonize Mars. Mars One has already selected six teams of four individuals. The first team will begin training next year, according to the Mars One website.In 2020, Mars One will launch a communications satellite to the red planet. Between 2022 and 2025, a series of rovers will land and assemble the habitats. The colony will have livable habitats, a life support unit and a communications system.The Living Unit will house an inflatable living section and an airlock used by astronauts when leaving the sealed, habitable settlement. The unit will include materials for the construction of rooms, floors and electrical outlets, and comes equipped with shower and kitchen areas. Additional units will arrive and be constructed as new teams join the colony.The Environmental Control and Life Support System (ECLSS) is rigged with extra technologies which capitalize on the natural resources available on Mars. Thin film solar photovoltaic panels will be included to generate electricity. The ECLSS will be equipped with heating units to boil and extract water from ice in the planet’s soil, according to the Mars One website.The ECLSS will be connected to the Living Unit through a tube which will feed nitrogen and argon gas, extracted from Mars’ atmosphere, into the habitable space as inert gases. Once the astronauts have landed, it will also be in charge of the water purification and removal of waste gas such as carbon dioxide from the Living Unit atmosphere.The Mars colony’s communication system will involve two orbiting satellites: one around Mars and one around the sun. The satellite orbiting Mars will only be interrupted when Mars is positioned between it and Earth. To counter the lapse, the second satellite orbiting the sun will intercept and relay the transmission, allowing almost 24/7 communication with Earth. The colony will lose transmission only when the sun is between Mars and Earth and Mars is between its satellite and Earth simultaneously. Mars One will launch a team of four every two years starting in 2026. It will take a year after departing Earth for a team to land on the surface of Mars. The organization hopes to train and send new teams, even after the initial six have colonized the planet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 18:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/06/03/3231310/3231310_DFA31B2DC1AE4E37A22E87E64CB71664_161214_3231310_Race_to_Mars__Mars_One_to_colonize_Mars_by_build_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AE3/EA5/AE3EA58FA7244459A1A7D7551480F33D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mars,space,martian,mars one,nasa,solar system,planet,mars habitat,mars colonization,mars colony,life on mars,alien,mars base camp,lockheed martin,space x,life on other planets,mars one project,mars one mission,race to mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231303</guid>
      <title>SwagBot: Australia develops cattle-herding robots that may replace farmers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  Australian researchers have developed a special robot that can herd cattle in large, rugged terrain that may eventually replace farmers and herding dogs.The robot is known as the SwagBot. It is a battery-operated, omnidirectional ground vehicle developed by Australian Centre for Field Robotics.The SwagBot can move as fast as 20 kilometers per hour on smooth terrain. During its first field test, the robot demonstrated that it can also navigate through rugged terrain.“The trial has been very successful so far, so it’s given us the confidence to move to the next phase,” Salah Sukkarieh of the University of Sydney, the leader of the trial told New Scientist.The team is working on algorithms that will allow the SwagBot to detect changes in the body temperature and posture of the cattle in order to monitor their health. It will also be equipped with color and shape sensors to identify good pasture for the cattle.According to the New Scientist, the Swagbot will be the first robot in the world to be able to monitor the health of livestock if the algorithms are tested successfully.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 18:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/07/14/3231303/3231303_45EBD7AC10444D28B382DB0E4DE2591B_161214_3231303_SwagBot__Australia_develops_cattle_herding_robot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/91F/6C4/91F6C4908E594CECBCAEFB0E33DA2447_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Swagbot,cattle-herding robots,farming robots,australian centre for field robotics,robots,university of sydney,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231297</guid>
      <title>China glass bridge: Zhangjiajie Canyon glass bridge is the world&#x2019;s longest and highest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHANGJIAJIE, CHINA  China has recently completed the world’s highest and longest glass bridge, giving the country another thrilling and scary tourist attraction.The glass bridge stretches across a canyon in Zhangjiajie, a national park in China’s Hunan province. It was designed by Israeli architect Haim Dotan.The length of the bridge is 430 meters, slightly shorter than the height of Malaysia’s Petronas Towers. Authorities say it can hold up to 800 visitors.Its glass floor is made of 5-cm-thick laminated glass, a type of safety glass that remains held together by a vinyl interlayer if it shatters. A total of 99 laminated glass panels are installed on the bridge, which can support up to 800 visitors.There is no official opening date for the glass bridge, but the South China Morning Post reported that it is likely to be open to the public in July.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 18:09:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/06/14/3231297/3231297_48E77A9B18FB4CDD90A0BE1398F65FFC_161214_3231297_China_glass_bridge__Zhangjiajie_Canyon_glass_bri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0B4/97A/0B497A7C904644BEAB68445A5B1708CC_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China glass bridge,zhangjiajie canyon glass bridge,world’s longest and highest glass bridge,zhangjiajie canyon,hunan province,china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231283</guid>
      <title>Amazon Prime delivery drones might be docking on lamp posts, power poles, cell towers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  Amazon has submitted a patent for using tall structures like lamp posts and church steeples as docking and recharging stations for its delivery drones.The patent is for a series of multi-use unmanned aerial vehicle docking stations. The system outlined in the patent would enable Amazon to recharge and house its drones remotely in between deliveries at the stations. The company would also be able to provide maintenance and navigational guidance to lost drones. THe stations could also double as delivery hubs, where drones can drop off packages to be picked up by its receiving Amazon Prime user or another drone for further delivery.Amazon wants to allow drones to perch atop existing tall structures, such as lamp posts, cell towers, power poles and buildings. The patent is still pending. The company looks to develop a system of UAV drones that would deliver packages within 30 minutes or less.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 18:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/07/21/3231283/3231283_C31F018C05044BDCA6F72AC7198B4DB8_161214_3231283_Amazon_Prime_delivery_drones_might_be_docking_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FEB/E67/FEBE67D2174E45CC8D38BD13FD0D8BFC_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Amazon,amazon prime,amazon prime drone,amazon prime drone delivery,drone delivery,us patent,uav,uav docking station,multi-use uav docking station,amazon prime air delivery,amazon drone delivery,amazon prime delivery,unmanned aerial vehicle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231274</guid>
      <title>Autism: Danish company designs Orbisbox based on Dr. Temple Grandin&#x2019;s hug machine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SLAGELSE, DENMARK  A Denmark-based company has developed a hugging machine called OrbisBox to help calm people with autism.The device is 163 centimeters tall, 85 cm wide and 223 cm in length. It can be transported to different locations and contains side plates covered with polyurethane foam.The device is said to be a commercial model based on Dr. Temple Grandin’s invention of the “hug machine.” Dr. Grandin is a world renowned spokesperson for autism, who created the device when she in college.Once the user is inside the OrbisBox, the side plates will start to move in and press against them, mimicking the sense of a hug. The weight of the pressure can be adjusted from 10 kg to 30 kg.The box has built-in speakers to play soothing music. Lighting can also be changed to make the user feel more relaxed.Autism is a complex brain development disorder which scientists say likely affects boys five times more than it does girls. Signs of autism may include difficulties in social interaction, strange attachment to objects and unawareness to danger.Due to their hypersensitivity, people with autism are often uncomfortable or unable to seek comfort from other people.Autism is a growing developmental disorder in the U.S. that it currently affects roughly 2 percent of teenage boys, or 1 in 42 boys, according to Autism Speaks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 18:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/06/26/3231274/3231274_8716CB3A4C794D4DB48D9D9044A3676E_161214_3231274_Autism__Danish_company_designs_Orbisbox_based_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/83C/540/83C540ED1C9C4220A9C1BADEB86718FA_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Orbisbox,gloria mundi care,denmark orbisbox,autism,hug machine for autism kids,autism boys,dr temple grandin,autism speaks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231268</guid>
      <title>Drone ships: Rolls-Royce developing futuristic fleet of semi-autonomous ships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Rolls-Royce has unveiled plans for a fleet of unmanned, remote controlled ship to hit the seas in 2020.The Advanced Autonomous Waterborne Applications (AAWA) Initiative, led by Rolls-Royce, is a €6.6 million project funded by Tekes (Finnish Funding Agency for Technology and Innovation) that will provide preliminary specifications and designs for next generation advance ships.To begin, the ships will carry freight and be controlled from a central control center by a small crew of seven to 14 people. The crew will use interactive smart screens, voice recognition systems, holograms and surveillance drones to monitor what is happening both on board and around the ships. The ships can operate in two main modes: remote control and autonomous mode. When in remote control, ships can be controlled using a device similar to a joystick. In this mode, the operator controls speed and direction and is privy to the boat’s relative position to objects nearby.When in autonomous mode, ships will execute planned missions, like navigating to the next waypoint, on their own. In this mode, the operator is limited to receiving data such as location, speed, headway and ETA to end point. In this mode, operators are able to monitor more ships at one time. Additionally, more information will be provided should a ship stray from its original plan due to unforeseen circumstances. Different levels of operator interaction will be requested depending on various scenarios. In a white paper published in June, researchers concluded that drone ships should operate on a hybrid of both remote control and autonomous mode. The technology required to create such ships are already in existence. Currently, researchers are working on a concept demonstration to be completed by 2017 and a full scale development for commercial use to be completed by 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 17:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/07/25/3231268/3231268_FEA35F1CD7544FF3BAB9017952C3F170_161214_3231268_Drone_ships__Rolls_Royce_developing_futuristic_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A12/787/A12787D020E5468DA9F86A4178E4DFFB_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Rolls royce,rolls-royce,drones,drone,drone ship,robot,robots,robot ship,rolls royce drone ship,rolls-royce drone ship,unmanned ship,Advanced Autonomous Waterborne Applications Initiative,aawa,autonomous ships,drone boats,robot boats,autonomous boats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231254</guid>
      <title>Shark deterrent: How shark attacks might be repelled by electromagnetic wristbands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW JERSEY  Sharks are widely feared as the ocean’s deadliest predator, but advancements in shark repellent technology are making the water a safer place for divers and surfers.Scientists in New Jersey have developed Sharkbanz, wrist and ankle bands that utilize the magnetism of the Earth to ward off inquisitive sharks. Sharks have receptors, located in their facial region, that allow them to detect electromagnetic energy. They have the most sensitive electromagnetic sense of all known animals. Sharks use this unique advantage to judge distance, shape, as well as heart rate in other animals. Sharkbanz do not require batteries, as they draw power from the magnetic field of the Earth. As a shark swims within one to two meters away, magnetic waves coming from the band disrupt its electro-receptors. When submerged in water, it is advised that divers place the band over their wrists, so they can direct the magnetism when sharks swim towards them. The technology has been proven to repel small creatures such as the nurse shark and southern stingray, as well as the more aggressive, predatory-type animals such as tiger sharks and bull sharks, who are known for their attacks on people.Sharkbanz aren’t likely to protect band-wearers from the advances of great whites, as those sharks tend to be ambush predators who attack their prey from long distances at high speeds. However, if one happens to be casually investigating, it may very well deter them from further inquiry.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 17:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/07/25/3231254/3231254_094EBF1CC84940969F4E49CA93069441_161214_3231254_Shark_deterrent__How_shark_attacks_might_be_repe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/526/C51/526C5199EF2D49ED90184464DC932D87_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sharkbanz,shark attacks,shark,repellent,shark technology,surfer attacked by shark,shark wristband]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231249</guid>
      <title>ATM skimming: How to spot an ATM skimmer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  This animation explains the practice of automatic teller machine (ATM) skimming, a common form of fraud that involves a compromised ATM that allows criminals to access bank accounts. According a survey published in April 2016, such incidents increased 546% from 2014 to 2015 in the United States. The data came from financial analytics company FICO and FICO Card Alert Service software, which also states that 60% of the incidents took place at non-bank ATMs.ATM skimming usually employs two separate components. First, a fake card reader is fitted onto the ATM’s card slot. It scans and stores the information on the card’s magnetic strip as it slides through.Then, a pinhole camera hidden on or near the ATM records the PIN entered on the keypad. Alternatively, a fake keypad is placed on top of the real one to record the digits entered.To avoid becoming victim to skimming fraud, one must check for any objects mounted on the ATM or near it.  Comparing the ATM being used to another nearby can help spot suspicious differences. Examine any mounted parts by pulling them to see whether they are securely attached. Feel the keypad for its sensitivity and check whether it was placed on top of a real one.The research also reports that 60% of incidents took place at non-bank ATMs. You might want to avoid using ATMs in malls, for instance, and stick with those located outside or inside your bank.According to PCMag, one should examine any mounted parts by pulling them to see if they are securely attached. Also, try to feel the keypad for its sensitivity and check if it was placed on top of a real one.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 17:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/07/28/3231249/3231249_42976B36644443E992D98007A1DD0EC6_161214_3231249_ATM_skimming__How_to_spot_an_ATM_skimmer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C0E/D85/C0ED85113CED4171AE0E9F2374F4F1C4_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Atm skimming,atm skimmer,how to spot atm skimmer,atm fraud,debit card fraud,compromised atm,crime,fraud]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231244</guid>
      <title>World&#x2019;s largest aircraft Stratolaunch to launch rockets into space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  Washington-based company Vulcan Aerospace announced that its Stratolaunch Systems, an air-launch platform for rockets, is close to completion.According to Vulcan Aerospace’s website, the Stratolaunch has a wingspan of 385 ft and measures 238 ft in length. This six-engine aircraft is currently the world’s largest aircraft.The aircraft is designed to carry rockets weighing up to 275 tons. It would take off with the rocket attached to its belly from a runway and release the rocket when it reaches 35,000 feet in the air. The rocket then fires its own engine and travel towards its orbit.According to Financial Review, the company hopes to make air-rocket launch in the low-Earth orbit a routine commute through the use of the Stratolaunch System.The Stratolaunch Systems is expected to be completed by the end of this year and is estimated to start commercial services before 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 17:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/07/21/3231244/3231244_5E3D513747E944CBA192BC9F763CCA77_161214_3231244_World___s_largest_aircraft_Stratolaunch_to_launc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/867/041/867041D6C85846B7985D5816085A230B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Stratolaunch systems,stratolaunch,vulcan aerospace,stratolaunch low earth commute,vulcan aerospace space venture,space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231239</guid>
      <title>SwagBot: Australia develops cattle-herding robots that may replace farmers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  Australian researchers have developed a special robot that can herd cattle in large, rugged terrain that may eventually replace farmers and herding dogs.The robot is known as the SwagBot. It is a battery-operated, omnidirectional ground vehicle developed by Australian Centre for Field Robotics.The SwagBot can move as fast as 20 kilometers per hour on smooth terrain. During its first field test, the robot demonstrated that it can also navigate through rugged terrain.“The trial has been very successful so far, so it’s given us the confidence to move to the next phase,” Salah Sukkarieh of the University of Sydney, the leader of the trial told New Scientist.The team is working on algorithms that will allow the SwagBot to detect changes in the body temperature and posture of the cattle in order to monitor their health. It will also be equipped with color and shape sensors to identify good pasture for the cattle.According to the New Scientist, the Swagbot will be the first robot in the world to be able to monitor the health of livestock if the algorithms are tested successfully.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 17:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/07/14/3231239/3231239_CCE0618086124AA3B903F0F2B57BE833_161214_3231239_SwagBot__Australia_develops_cattle_herding_robot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DFB/92D/DFB92D3082414651831B8F4F40049C74_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Swagbot,cattle-herding robots,farming robots,australian centre for field robotics,robots,university of sydney,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231207</guid>
      <title>China&#x2019;s elevated bus actually a huge scam, government says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QINHUANGDAO, CHINA  China’s much-hyped elevated bus which last week completed a test run in the northern city of Qinhuangdao, Hebei province, may not just be impractical and unfeasible, as critics say. Several Chinese state media outlets now say the whole thing was an illegally funded project aimed at scamming investors.China’s Global Times tabloid also attacked the thing’s designer for having only an elementary school education. Nevertheless, this animation depicts the thing and explains some of its attributes.The Transit Elevated Bus, or TEB, is 22 meters long, 7.8 meters wide and can carry up to 300 passengers.It runs on rails laid on ordinary roads and occupies two traffic lanes. Passengers board the bus through an elevated bus stop.It is powered by both solar power and electricity. Through a technology called relay charging, the bus receives electricity as it enters a bus station.The TEB straddles the road 2 meters above the ground, which allows smaller vehicles to pass below.It is equipped with sensors on its front, rear and sides to warn vehicles to not get too close and large vehicles to not pass below.The TEB Development Company says one bus could replace 40 conventional buses and could save 2,640 tons of carbon emissions.Four buses could be linked together and operate in a train-like manner. The bus can reach a top speed of 60 kilometers per hour.However, the bus can only run on a mostly straight track and is unable to perform sharp turns. Although last week’s test received wide media coverage, the thing only traveled 300 meters at a slow speed, and without traffic beneath it. What’s more, the city didn’t even know about the test, let alone approve it.So this elevated bus, which is actually a train, may never get off the ground.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 17:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231207/3231207_444E41769370457793FBCF129B22F038_161214_3231207_China___s_elevated_bus_actually_a_huge_scam__gov_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E72/C96/E72C9615A4134BA299CFF201BA43AF42_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China straddling bus,china futuristic bus,china transit elevated bus,china straddling bus test run,china traffic congestion,teb,qinhuangdao straddling bus,china technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231201</guid>
      <title>Moon landing: Florida-based private company granted permission for moon mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The United States government has granted a Mountain View, California-based company permission to launch a mission to the moon, the first time the government has allowed a company to conduct a commercial space mission beyond Earth’s orbit.“We choose to go to the moon not because it’s easy, but because it’s a good business,” the founder and chairman of Moon Express, Naveen Jain, said on the company’s Facebook page.Moon Express’ The MX-1 is about the size of a coffee table. It will be launched sometime in 2017 on an Electron rocket, a rocket currently being built by startup Rocket Lab.The MX-1 will carry a scientific and commercial payload that includes cremated human remains. It will also transmit pictures and videos of the moon back to Earth.The spacecraft is solar-powered and uses hydrogen peroxide as rocket fuel.Its missions include mining for resources such as water and Helium-3. It can also serve as a refueling station for other satellites.At the moment, commercial satellites have only gone as far as the geosynchronous orbit, about 22,000 miles above Earth.Only three nation states -- the United States, the former Soviet Union and China -- have landed on the moon.However, the permission granted to Moon Express does not guarantee access for other private companies to the moon. The company said its permission was a onetime deal and that all future requests will be reviewed case by case until new laws are passed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 17:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/10/3231201/3231201_34F3897E70624363A3B77B1BCE17895B_161214_3231201_Moon_landing__Florida_based_private_company_gran_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/679/EF6/679EF633C4264D2396AF4231E5BABAFB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Moon express,moon express mx-1,florida-based moon express,moon mission,private moon mission,private lunar mission,space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231198</guid>
      <title>Asteroid mining: Deep Space Industries to harvest asteroids by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SILICON VALLEY, CALIFORNIA  A California startup plans to mine asteroids for profit.The company from Silicon Valley, Deep Space Industries, recently announced that it plans on launching a precursor mission in 2017 and will commence its first mission by 2020. The company wants to mine asteroids for water, carbon and other elements, precious metals, and even in-space building materials. It will begin with extracting water.Deep Space Industries plans on sending a small spacecraft named Prospector-1 to low-Earth orbit on an experimental mission. The Prospector-1 weighs 50 kilograms when fueled and was designed to be cost effective. Once the initial campaign is complete, Prospector-1 will hitch a ride on low-Earth orbit then point towards an asteroid and jet propel itself to its target. Once near, Prospector-1 will map the surface and subsurface of the asteroid locating resources. Prospector-1 will also attempt to land on the asteroid. On the asteroid, Prospector-1 will mine water, which it will use as fuel. The craft expels superheated water vapor to generate thrust. Asteroids will be selected by a group of experts. If successful, the first mission will pave way for future spacecrafts to use asteroid water as refueling stations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 17:19:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/12/3231198/3231198_8A675E30FBCE4D729FF6ECB69CD95675_161214_3231198_Asteroid_mining__Deep_Space_Industries_to_harves_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/51C/843/51C843FBBD5B4BB5A02592A31930E227_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Space,asteroids,prospector 1,commercial space travel,prospector x,deep space,deep space industries]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231186</guid>
      <title>Mosquito-repelling TV: Indian families can now buy an LG TV that bothers insects</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI, INDIA  South Korean company LG Electronics has launched in India, a television equipped with mosquito-repelling technology.According to Reuters, the latest product is targeted at lower-income consumers whose living conditions would make them vulnerable to mosquitoes.The technology consists of an ultrasonic device, which emits sound waves above 30 kHz. The sound waves are inaudible to human but can be used to drive mosquitoes away.The device would continue to function when the TV switched off as long as the TV remains plugged to a power source.In addition to the mosquito-repelling TV, LG has also applied the technology in its air conditioners and washing machines sold in India.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 17:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/12/3231186/3231186_7D54FC1103494EFBA2B7168ADFDE38AD_161214_3231186_Mosquito_repelling_TV__Indian_families_can_now_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B51/E3F/B51E3F0FECE64D10B5B246AD8D6CA2A1_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[LG mosquito away tv,LG electronics,LG mosquito-repelling tv in India,India mosquito problems,LG mosquito-repelling technology,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231177</guid>
      <title>DuoSkin: MIT students design &#x2018;smart&#x2019; tattoo that can control your gadgets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  A group of PhD students from MIT Media Lab, in collaboration with Microsoft Research, have developed a ‘smart’ tattoo that can remotely control your gadgets while looking pretty.The technology is called DuoSkin. According to the official website, there are three types of tattoos available. One version of the smart tattoo has an input function using capacitive touch sensing. The gold leaf functions as electrodes, and is attached to a touch controller that filters all raw data. Once the tattoo is applied onto the skin, the user can swipe or click on the tattoo as a trackpad.Another type of smart tattoo uses skin as a display. A layer of thermochromic ink is added into the tattoo, which changes colour when exposed to high temperatures. The third type of tattoo contains an NFC chip that connects to a coil made of gold leaf, which allows users to exchange data through near field communication.The technology will be presented at International Symposium on Wearable Computers 2016 in Heidelberg, Germany in September.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 16:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/16/3231177/3231177_B658E15C140E42B99C584B9E6007A109_161214_3231177_DuoSkin__MIT_students_design____smart____tattoo__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/828/56C/82856C9158684AFC80992665A0EAAF74_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[MIT,duoskin,MIT duoskin,MIT media lab,MIT smart tattoo,smart tattoo controls gadgets,wearable tech,science,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231158</guid>
      <title>Uber to launch self-driving car service in Pittsburgh</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PITTSBURGH  Uber is launching a self-driving car service later this month in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. According to a report by Bloomberg, the Pittsburgh service will use 100 Volvo XC90 SUVs equipped with Uber’s autonomous driving system. An engineer seated at the wheel and a co-pilot in the passenger seat will keep track of the vehicle’s activity and safety. Customers will be chosen at random for trips in the autonomous cars. Those trips will be free. Uber told Bloomberg it will work with other carmakers as well, as the company does not plan to develop its own self-driving vehicles as Google and Tesla are doing. Earlier this year, Uber started testing self-driving Ford Fusions in Pittsburgh in a trial with the Detroit automaker.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 16:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/19/3231158/3231158_B00007D0DFD8420599F4C3C7CF19A06D_161214_3231158_Uber_to_launch_self_driving_car_service_in_Pitts_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/907/7BB/9077BBE6DD8F4201B60C077B2B97490A_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Uber,Volvo,autonomous driving,driverless cars,Pittsburgh,Pennsylvania,Carnegie Mellon University,autonomous vehicles,self-driving]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231153</guid>
      <title>Driverless taxi: Singapore gets world&#x2019;s first self-driving taxi cab service</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE  A Singaporean company has launched the world’s first self-driving taxi in the island nation, beating out Uber and other giants.The public run comes days after Uber announced plans for a new driverless service in Pittsburgh. The ride-sharing giant had been set to launch the service using Volvo SUVs fitted with an autonomous driving system by the end of August.The Straits Times reports that on Thursday, startup nuTonomy started a trial run using two electric vehicles: a Mitsubishi i-Miev, and a Renault Zoe. Both are equipped with Lidar technology that uses lasers to map out its environment. Inside the vehicle are two mounted cameras that are meant to detect obstacles on the road and traffic lights.The service currently runs within a 6-kilometer route in Singapore’s One-North Business Park. Users need be invited to be part of the trial program, and then register to a phone app which they will then use to request rides. Though only open to about a dozen people so far, the trial program is expected to expand to accommodate thousands within a few months.Rides are free during the trial run, and a driver will be in the vehicle with the passenger to serve as backup in case of any emergencies.The company, founded by two Massachusetts Institute of Technology researchers, is hoping to expand the fleet to about a hundred by 2018, and believes the driverless taxis could reduce cars on the road from 900,000 to 300,000.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 16:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/26/3231153/3231153_ADA789F8079A48089D76D543C9889BAE_161214_3231153_Driverless_taxi__Singapore_gets_world___s_first__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/96B/211/96B211AD3D6D4DCCA4C8B11E6AA32797_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Driverless taxi,driverless car,self driving taxi,self driving car,nutonomy,singapore,world’s first driverless taxi,world’s first,autonomous vehicle,autonomous taxi]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231149</guid>
      <title>Chip My Life: Australians implanting microchips in their hands to unlock doors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GLEBE, AUSTRALIA  A new trend has been developing in Australia, with hundreds of them implanting microchips in their hands that allow them to remotely unlock doors.“You could set up your life so you never have to worry about any password or PINs,” Shanti Korporaal told news.com.au.Korporaal, from Sydney, set up a business called Chip My Life with her husband. She has two implants in her hands.The microchip is roughly the size of a grain of rice. There are two types of microchips available for sale: RFID and NFC.The chips can be used to replace identification badges to unlock secure doors or transfer medical data.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 16:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/29/3231149/3231149_5B3C593122D946628C5FC976138EBD63_161214_3231149_Chip_My_Life__Australians_implanting_microchips__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6EF/6C3/6EF6C381AE0441379502E60E362D5FB7_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chip my life,australian microchips implant,shanti korporaal,cyborgs,wearable tech,science,technology,australia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231078</guid>
      <title>How one Japanese city recycles almost all its garbage into cement</title>
      <description><![CDATA[This animation shows how one city in southern Japanese city recycles almost all of its household waste.The city of Hidaka in Saitama turns 98.8 percent of household waste into cement through a process of aerobic fermentation, according to the Taiheiyo Cement Corporation.The process begins when garbage bags are placed inside a waste recycling kiln. The kiln is heated to 1,450 degrees Celsius and rotates slowly for three days.Inside the kiln, the garbage is broken apart and mixed. The garbage breaks down through aerobic fermentation.The fermented material is then crushed, sieved and sorted. The ash generated during the process goes into another kiln, where it is mixed with other raw materials to make cement. The cement then goes to market.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 15:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/24/3231078/3231078_E0F44CF8023343CD97E872E1BE4579B3_161214_3231078_How_one_Japanese_city_recycles_almost_all_its_ga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A21/DA0/A21DA083C29948B4AFA87450C5CD5560_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Japan recycling,hidaka,cement recycling,cement,Taiheiyo Cement,recycling,hidaka recycling]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231074</guid>
      <title>The SkyLine: Chicago may install aerial gondola ride to boost tourism</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Chicago is reviewing an ambitious plan to install aerial cable cars, dubbed “The SkyLine,” as the city’s newest tourist attraction.The idea was first presented at a luncheon of the City Club of Chicago in May. The aerial gondola ride would stretch from Wacker Drive to Navy Pier along the Chicago River.The gondolas would be lifted 17 stories above the ground and are able to transport about 3,000 people per hour.The ride would operate day and night all year round. It is said to be able to attract 1.4 million visitors a year to Chicago.The estimated cost for the project is about $250 million. The founder of the project is confident that it can be privately financed without any state or city funding.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 15:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/28/3231074/3231074_1ECF73B819A345FEA804AEBDB91A79AA_161214_3231074_The_SkyLine__Chicago_may_install_aerial_gondola__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8DB/110/8DB110B4D45E4B00B657A945881B2E07_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chicago,chicago skyline,the skyline chicago,chicago aerial cable cars,chicago glass cable cars,chicago aerial gondola,chicago tourism]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3231070</guid>
      <title>Secret surveillance: Baltimore  police spy on residents using Persistent Surveillance Systems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE  Baltimore police acknowledged that the city residents had been unknowingly under aerial surveillance since January.According to the Guardian, the programme was privated funded between Persistent Surveillance Systems and the Baltimore city police. The practise was first revealed by Bloomberg.According to Bloomberg, the Persistent Surveillance Systems include about six cameras positioned at different angles attached to the bottom of a plane.The plane would fly above the city in a circular orbit that allows the cameras to take pictures of 32 square miles of the city. The pictures taken by the six cameras are then stitched together to form 192-megapixel images and are continuously transmitted to a ground station.As the images are constantly updated, the analysts on the ground could track vehicles or suspect to see their movements prior or after the crime.Baltimore police spokesman TJ Smith told the Guardian that it was “was not a secret surveillance program” and “there was no conspiracy not to disclose it”, despite the fact that not even the mayor nor the city council were informed about the program.It was disclosed that the systems was used for 100 hours between January and February and 200 hours over the summer. The police department will evaluate whether to use the systems permanently.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 15:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/30/3231070/3231070_D1F2F7945A6F47289E135B283942E733_161214_3231070_Secret_surveillance__Baltimore__police_spy_on_re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8D6/6B9/8D66B91C1EC34D359115CB42A4D455DB_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Baltimore surveillance,baltimore aerial surveillance,persistent surveillance systems,baltimore secret surveillance,baltimore police,baltimore under secret surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227333</guid>
      <title>Driverless buses hit the road in Finland as Helsinki aims to go car-free by 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HELSINKI  Finland is testing driverless electric buses as part of an ambitious 10-year plan to make car ownership unnecessary in the country’s capital.Two driverless EZ10 minibuses with obstacle-detection technology are being tested on public roads in Helsinki’s southern Hernesaari district, alongside other vehicles and pedestrians.The minibuses can hold up to 12 passengers each and can reach a top speed of 40 kilometers per hour. However they will travel at an average speed of 10 kilometers per hour, the Guardian reported.Officials said the buses could be used in future to connect existing public transport systems, according to Finnish news site Yle.Finland is a world leader in trials of automated transport, partly because Finnish law doesn’t require vehicles on the road to have a driver.Helsinki is testing the buses as part of a plan to make car ownership unnecessary by 2025 by providing a point-to-point “mobility on demand” system, according to the Guardian.The trial began on Aug. 16 and runs for a month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 14:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/08/31/3227333/3227333_2223791DF9F3459B9D8D85596A347307_161209_3227333_Driverless_buses_hit_the_road_in_Finland_as_Hels_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E25/A42/E25A42969C7A4D0F861FEFF8F0910B7D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Driverless bus,electric vehicles,driverless bus,driverless bus in finland,ez10,autonomous bus,robot bus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227180</guid>
      <title>New Jersey train crash: Hoboken Terminal crash kills one woman and wounds 108</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOBOKEN, NEW JERSEY  A train traveling at a “high rate of speed” crashed into a platform at Hoboken Terminal in New Jersey on during rush hour on Thursday morning, killing one woman and injuring 108.According to New Jersey news site NJ.com, the train crashed into the platform at 8:45 a.m. New Jersey Governor Chris Christie said a woman was killed while standing at the platform and killed by debris from the crash. That woman was identified by the state medical examiner as Fabiola Bittar de Kroon, 34, NBC News reported.At least 108 other people were injured, reported NBC News citing officials. Three of the wounded were in critical condition and 11 were listed as serious, reported NJ.com citing Dr. Ken Garay, Chief Medical Officer at Jersey Medical Center.The cause of the crash is currently unknown, however authorities do not currently suspect that terrorism or foul play was involved.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 13:08:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/30/3227180/3227180_1A75F695649043E38C165ACADD291A62_161208_3227180_New_Jersey_train_crash__Hoboken_Terminal_crash_k_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0E0/0BC/0E00BC1C945A47E59553B0A902C1F8F3_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[New Jersey train crash,hoboken terminal,train crashes in new jersey,hoboken train station accident,train crash,train wreck,train accidents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227179</guid>
      <title>Chinese killing spree: 19 dead after man allegedly goes berzerk on being denied loans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUNMING, CHINA  A man has been arrested following a mass killing in a remote village in China’s Yunnan province that claimed the lives of 19 people.The attack took place in Yema Village in Huize County on Wednesday night. According to Chinese outlet, Sina, the suspect, identified as 27-year-old Yang Qingpei, allegedly visited his relatives to borrow money to repay his gambling debt and killed them when they refused to lend him money.Police came to one of the houses on Thursday morning and found two bodies. They then checked five houses nearby and found 17 more bodies. All victims were related to the suspect. The oldest was seventy-two and the youngest was just three years old.The suspect was arrested on Thursday afternoon in Kunming, the capital city of Yunnan province, about 200 km away from Yema village.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 13:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/30/3227179/3227179_00381E9236F1413687648515E730D5DD_161208_3227179_Chinese_killing_spree__19_dead_after_man_alleged_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/738/07F/73807F1CC7E645CF979CBF622737E9A9_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Yunnan murders,yunnan mass killing,yang qingpei,man kills 19 relatives in china,yema village murder,yema village yunnan,crime in china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227127</guid>
      <title>&#x2018;Doomsday vault&#x2019; Norway: How the Svalbard Global Seed Vault works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SVALBARD, NORWAY  Deep inside a mountain on a remote Norwegian island are more than 860,000 varieties of seeds, kept, literally, on ice for preservation should a global catastrophe occur.Carved into rock and ice, the Global Seed Vault is safely buried into the Plataberget Mountain in Svalbard, Norway, not far from the North Pole. Also known as the “doomsday vault,” the facility was created by scientist, conservationist and biodiversity advocate Cary Fowler to safeguard one of the planet’s most vulnerable and valuable resources: plants. The vault is, in essence, a fail-safe backup system for the world’s seed banks, a last resort for the preservation of plant genealogy. Currently, 864,309 samples are housed in the vault. The plan is to house 4.5 million varieties of crops, with an average of 500 samples of each variety. The vault can hold a maximum total of around 2.5 billion seeds.The vault opened in 2008 and is nearly 394 feet inside the mountain in Svalbard, the furthest north a person can fly on a scheduled flight, making it both remote and accessible. The facility was designed to last 1,000 years and to withstand a range of catastrophes including climate change.The area is geologically stable, with low humidity levels, and is well above sea level, keeping the seeds dry even if the ice caps melt. Permafrost and thick rock ensure that the seed samples will remain frozen at minus 18 degrees Celsius even without power.  The seeds are stored and sealed in custom-made three-ply foil packages, which are sealed inside boxes and stored inside the vault. Seeds are deposited into the vault following strict guidelines. Seeds can only be deposited if they originate from the country of the depositor (genetically modified crops are not allowed) and are shared under the Multilateral System or under Article 15 of the International Treaty on Plant Genetic Resources for Food and Agriculture, which seeks to guarantee future food security. And, like a bank, deposited seeds can only be withdrawn by the depositor. Security at the vault is state of the art and fully automated. There are no full-time staff, and no single person with all the keys necessary for entrance. New seeds are also only accepted a few days a year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 12:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/30/3227127/3227127_6B76605A8C674300896A402F431B2A69_161208_3227127____Doomsday_vault____Norway__How_the_Svalbard_Gl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B8C/11B/B8C11BF13DDB4589BC81A464DE70E347_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Svalbard,norway,seed vault,doomsday vault,life vault,seeds,seed storehouse,norway seed vault,seed vault norway,global seed vault,svalbard global seed vault,global crop diversity trust,food supply,seeds on ice,cary fowler,crop trust,seed bank]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227122</guid>
      <title>School shooting: Teen kills father, goes on shooting rampage at South Carolina school</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOWNVILLE, SOUTH CAROLINA  A teenage boy killed his own father before opening fire at a rural South Carolina school on Wednesday.The 14-year-old suspect shot his 47-year-old father in the chest with a handgun at their home in Anderson County, Reuters reported.The boy then hopped in a pickup truck, which he drove for about two miles, before crashing into a fence at Townville Elementary School. The unnamed teenager entered the school playground and began firing.Two 6-year-old boys were wounded in the leg and foot, one of them critically. A female teacher was also shot in the shoulder.An unarmed volunteer firefighter subdued the teenager before he could do any more damage and held him until the cops showed up.The suspect was home schooled and therefore wasn’t a student at Townville Elementary. It’s unknown whether the shooter knew any of the school victims.His motive remains unclear, but police have ruled out terrorism.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 11:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/29/3227122/3227122_79F2DA6778B04C88A7942DF5C8437623_161208_3227122_School_shooting__Teen_kills_father__goes_on_shoo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/158/171/1581712144EB48DCB01B7F18F4202788_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[School shooting,townville elementary school,townville shooting,school shooting animation,school shooting usa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227113</guid>
      <title>Roller coasters can help pass kidney stones, especially Big Thunder Mountain at Disney</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EAST LANSING, MICHIGAN  A Michigan State University urologist has discovered that riding on a specific type of roller coaster could help people pass kidney stones.“Basically, I had patients telling me that after riding a particular roller coaster at Walt Disney World, they were able to pass their kidney stone.I even had one patient say he passed three different stones after riding multiple times,” David Wartinger, a professor emeritus in the Department of Osteopathic Surgical Specialties told the Science Daily.Wartinger conducted with experiment with kidney stones smaller than the size of 4 mm filled in a 3D model of a hollow kidney. After riding at the Big Thunder Mountain roller coaster at the theme park for 20 times, the stones were successfully passed.He told the Science Daily that a roller coaster which is rough and quick with some twists and turns could successfully help patients to pass their kidney stones, whereas roller coasters that are too fast with upside down or inverted movements would not have the same effect.Furthermore, sitting in the front of the roller coaster only has about 16% success rate of passing the kidney stones while sitting in the last car of the ride increases the rate to 64%.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 11:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/29/3227113/3227113_47ED4F21D0614D1BBEBFD521DDD244AD_161208_3227113_Roller_coasters_can_help_pass_kidney_stones__esp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F9B/247/F9B24701A31F46D48004B394A3BEC46D_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Roller coasters pass kidney stones,big thunder mountain passes kidney stones,new kidney stone treatment,roller coaster and kidney stones,health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227109</guid>
      <title>Urban Rigger: Shipping containers become floating dorms for Danish students</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK  A Copenhagen start-up created an innovative student dormitory that floats on water.The floating student dormitory is called the Urban Rigger. The structure is made of 9 containers stacked in two levels on a concrete pontoon which can create 12 rooms. Each room is a studio setting with bedroom and living room areas.The structure has an open-air courtyard in the middle and storage zones and a laundry room in the basement. It uses sustainable technologies such as solar panels and hydro source heating to provide energies. The rent for one room will be roughly about $600 per month, which is a bargain in Copenhagen. Urban Rigger has already received over 3,000 applications from students who are interested in living on water.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 11:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/28/3227109/3227109_0A53475083364616B493E5FB52190DE2_161208_3227109_Urban_Rigger__Shipping_containers_become_floatin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2F2/735/2F2735A2F4D349ECB52F1B08FB4AB3E6_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Urban rigger,shipping containers become floating dorms,floating dorms in copenhagen,copenhagen urban rigger,containers turn into dorms,innovation,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227102</guid>
      <title>Mercury shrinking: NASA says planet Mercury experiences tremors and is getting smaller</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE  New research from NASA suggests that Mercury is shrinking and experiences seismic activity, joining Earth as the solar system’s other tectonically active planet.Prior to crashing on Mercury, NASA’s MErcury Surface, Space ENvironment, GEochemistry, and Ranging (MESSENGER) spacecraft photographed the planet’s surface for the 18 months, reported Space.com, and found long cliffs. These cliffs, or scarps, suggests Mercury may experience seismic activity.The researchers expect that seismic activity on Mercury is similar to the moon’s. The moon is a natural satellite, not a planet.According to Space.com, the planet is still hot enough to keep contracting and have a molten outer core. That same core has helped sustain Mercury’s magnetic field for billions of years.The findings, published in the October issue of Nature Geoscience, was managed by the John Hopkins University Physics Laboratory and funded by NASA.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 11:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/28/3227102/3227102_9F1DF5D19E7A4C06B5E5E70D1F39430A_161208_3227102_Mercury_shrinking__NASA_says_planet_Mercury_expe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/07F/020/07F020B25340472692E1FFD1E2C977C9_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA mercury,Mercury is shrinking,mercuryquakes,earthquakes on mercury,mercury getting smaller,planet mercury,nasa mercury,messenger nasa mercury,Earth mercury,mercury,moonquakes,mercury and the moon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227094</guid>
      <title>Three-person baby: Baby born with DNA from three people is world&#x2019;s first</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO  A team from the New Hope Fertility Center in New York has created the world’s first three-person baby.New Scientist reports that a 5-month old baby boy was conceived via a new method that uses his birth parents’ DNA, along with that of a second woman.The technique was used to avoid passing on his Jordanian mother’s mitochondrial genes, which carried the DNA associated with Leigh Syndrome. The fatal genetic disorder, which affects the brain, muscles, and nerves of developing infants, had already led to the deaths of the couple’s two previous children.New Hope doctors, led by Dr. John Zhang, used a procedure called the spindle nuclear transfer, which involved taking out the nucleus of the donor egg and replacing it with the mother’s, according to the research published in Fertility and Sterility.The resulting egg, a hybrid containing the mother’s nuclear DNA and the donor’s mitochondrial DNA is then fertilized by the father’s sperm.Five embryos were created using the procedure, but only one developed normally. It was implanted in the mother’s uterus, and the baby was born nine months later.Dr. Zhang later tested the boy’s genes, and found that less than 1 percent carry his mother’s mutation  too low to cause any problems.The controversial method has not been approved in the U.S., so the team had to travel to Mexico to perform it there. A similar procedure is legally approved in the UK, though it involves fertilizing both eggs before swapping the nucleus.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 10:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/28/3227094/3227094_8751187794F64D7E845E6B8B4E1ADA32_161208_3227094_Three_person_baby__Baby_born_with_DNA_from_three_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/58D/255/58D255F9D0CA43BCB707E6A11C5CD104_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Three person baby,three parent baby,spindle nuclear transfer,artificial conception,in vitro fertilization,leigh syndrome,genetic disorder,genetic mutation,fertility technique]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3227053</guid>
      <title>Animal language? Researchers in Norway teach horses to communicate through symbols</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OSLO, NORWAY  Researchers in Norway have made a breakthrough in an animal cognition study, using symbols to help horses communicate their level of comfort to humans. In the study published in the journal Applied Animal Behaviour Science, 23 horses were put through a range of hot, cold, and warm temperatures, and given three options to select from based on what they were experiencing. If the horses nudged the board with the horizontal line, they were communicating they felt cold and were asking for their blanket to be applied. If the horses nudged the board with the vertical line, they were communicating they felt hot and were asking for their blanket to be removed. If the horses nudged a board with no symbol on it, they were communicating they felt fine as is. Horses were given a carrot for making the correct choices.It was clear whether the horses were choosing the symbols that corresponded with their comfort, as they were either covered in thick blankets, which made them obviously hot, or taken outside in freezing weather which would call for them to demand a blanket. The horses learned to provide their preferences after only 14 days of 10-15 minutes of training each day. This new research groups horses in with dolphins, apes, and pigeons as animals proven to be able to communicate with humans through symbols.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 10:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/28/3227053/3227053_F5E66BD80DF743E681807D59F7339D73_161208_3227053_Animal_language__Researchers_in_Norway_teach_hor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/687/954/68795413B5BA451F8EBD6365F89706B6_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Horse communication,horses norway,Norwegian Veterinary Institute,animal cognition,horse speaks,horse talks,horse blanket,horse study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226667</guid>
      <title>Three-person baby: Baby born with DNA from three people is world&#x2019;s first</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO  A team from the New Hope Fertility Center in New York has created the world’s first three-person baby.New Scientist reports that a 5-month old baby boy was conceived via a new method that uses his birth parents’ DNA, along with that of a second woman.The technique was used to avoid passing on his Jordanian mother’s mitochondrial genes, which carried the DNA associated with Leigh Syndrome. The fatal genetic disorder, which affects the brain, muscles, and nerves of developing infants, had already led to the deaths of the couple’s two previous children.New Hope doctors, led by Dr. John Zhang, used a procedure called the spindle nuclear transfer, which involved taking out the nucleus of the donor egg and replacing it with the mother’s, according to the research published in Fertility and Sterility.The resulting egg, a hybrid containing the mother’s nuclear DNA and the donor’s mitochondrial DNA is then fertilized by the father’s sperm.Five embryos were created using the procedure, but only one developed normally. It was implanted in the mother’s uterus, and the baby was born nine months later.Dr. Zhang later tested the boy’s genes, and found that less than 1 percent carry his mother’s mutation  too low to cause any problems.The controversial method has not been approved in the U.S., so the team had to travel to Mexico to perform it there. A similar procedure is legally approved in the UK, though it involves fertilizing both eggs before swapping the nucleus.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 18:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/28/3226667/3226667_4681E3D05F294425BB010FA4BF18D229_161208_3226667_Three_person_baby__Baby_born_with_DNA_from_three_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F7A/8E2/F7A8E2E1ABA84FFF850ABF5E1D34D35A_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Three person baby,three parent baby,spindle nuclear transfer,artificial conception,in vitro fertilization,leigh syndrome,genetic disorder,genetic mutation,fertility technique]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226663</guid>
      <title>Animal language? Researchers in Norway teach horses to communicate through symbols</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OSLO, NORWAY  Researchers in Norway have made a breakthrough in an animal cognition study, using symbols to help horses communicate their level of comfort to humans. In the study published in the journal Applied Animal Behaviour Science, 23 horses were put through a range of hot, cold, and warm temperatures, and given three options to select from based on what they were experiencing. If the horses nudged the board with the horizontal line, they were communicating they felt cold and were asking for their blanket to be applied. If the horses nudged the board with the vertical line, they were communicating they felt hot and were asking for their blanket to be removed. If the horses nudged a board with no symbol on it, they were communicating they felt fine as is. Horses were given a carrot for making the correct choices.It was clear whether the horses were choosing the symbols that corresponded with their comfort, as they were either covered in thick blankets, which made them obviously hot, or taken outside in freezing weather which would call for them to demand a blanket. The horses learned to provide their preferences after only 14 days of 10-15 minutes of training each day. This new research groups horses in with dolphins, apes, and pigeons as animals proven to be able to communicate with humans through symbols.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 18:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/28/3226663/3226663_54D7C18D88A34C67BC16254E81A0AD86_161208_3226663_Animal_language__Researchers_in_Norway_teach_hor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/540/32F/54032FF87B014CBEB1178E40ED17358E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Horse communication,horses norway,Norwegian Veterinary Institute,animal cognition,horse speaks,horse talks,horse blanket,horse study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226661</guid>
      <title>Tesla: new update protects your kids and pets from overheating to death inside cars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA  Electric car company Tesla released its version 8.0 update on Thursday morning.According to Tesla’s newsletter, this is biggest UI revamp since the launch of the Model S. The update comes with various improvements to the media player, maps system, Autopilot system, and also comes with a new function called “Cabin Overheat Protection.”The “Cabin Overheat Protection” function is designed to prevent overheating deaths of children and pets inside vehicles. The new feature automatically turns on the vehicle’s ventilation and air conditioning system when the temperature inside the car rises to 105 degrees Fahrenheit. However, the function currently only remains operational within the 12 hours after a driver leaves the vehicle.According to Elon Musk’s Twitter updates, a future update will allow users to set maximum and minimum temperature settings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 18:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/28/3226661/3226661_72B6D1443D8843A7AD6DD5C5FA7D3B48_161208_3226661_Tesla__new_update_protects_your_kids_and_pets_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D71/737/D71737065F4B4797B90AFD59E0A90A4B_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tesla,cabin overheat protection,electric car,tesla update,Elon Musk,Palo Alto,California]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226626</guid>
      <title>Houston mass shooting: Disgruntled lawyer in Nazi military garb goes on shooting spree</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON, TEXAS  Residents of a Southwest Houston neighborhood in Texas awoke Monday to gunshots when a disgruntled lawyer carried out a mass shooting.KTRK reports that around 6:30 a.m., a lawyer dressed in a Nazi military uniform began open firing at passing cars on Law Street in West University Place.The suspect randomly shot at the drivers, shattering windows and windshields and injuring nine people. When Houston police arrived, they engaged the suspect in a standoff, eventually killing him. Multiple weapons were found on him, including a .45 semi-automatic Thompson carbine rifle, a .45 semi-automatic handgun, and a knife still in its sheath. Both firearms were obtained legally, according to the New York Times.Local reports have identified the gunman as Nathan DeSai, though police have not officially named him as the shooter. A black Porsche Boxster registered to DeSai searched by officers was found to contain 2,600 rounds of live ammunition and various Nazi paraphernalia.Authorities believe DeSai was a lone gunman and not connected to any terror group. Although a solid motive has yet to be pinned down, they do think the suspect’s recent money and business troubles play a big factor in his actions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/27/3226626/3226626_6C963E44EE044D9A9ED81D3333F7DBA8_161208_3226626_Houston_mass_shooting__Disgruntled_lawyer_in_Naz_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DF5/BE3/DF5BE3FEE4714D578EBEE8C49432E758_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Houston shooting,houston gunman,houston shooting suspect,nathan desai,disgruntled lawyer,nazi military uniform,nazi uniform,houston mass shooting,houston shooter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226624</guid>
      <title>UPS tests drone delivery of medicine in Massachusetts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHILDREN’S ISLAND, MASSACHUSETTS  Package delivery company UPS partnered with drone-maker CyPhy Works to conduct a test delivery using a drone last Thursday.The drone used in the test delivery was CyPhy Works’ Persistent Aerial Reconnaissance and Communications system (PARC). It flew three miles over the Atlantic Ocean from Beverly, Massachusetts to Children’s Island, where it successfully delivered an asthma inhaler to a child at the camp. The PARC drone is battery-powered and equipped with night vision. It also features secure communications system, preventing information from being intercepted or disrupted.“Drone technology used in this way can save lives and deliver products and services to places that are difficult to reach by traditional transit infrastructures, ” Helen Greiner, the founder and chief technology officer of CyPhy Works said in a press release.Greiner told NBC49.com that the drones are not going to replace delivery trucks.The United States Federal Aviation Administration’s rules for commercial use of drones officially took effect last month, which include a number of restrictions on commercial drone operations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:19:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/27/3226624/3226624_B6C02172B691485AB299DF27E0FA55EC_161208_3226624_UPS_tests_drone_delivery_of_medicine_in_Massachu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D82/774/D827749FEB7C4B2A8503BCD09E813730_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ups tests drone delivery,Cyphy Works drones,UPS drone delivery of medicine,UPS drone delivery,drone delivery,technology,drone delivery to Children’s island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226623</guid>
      <title>Self-driving car crash: Google Lexus collides with car in California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  Google’s self-driving Lexus SUV has been involved in a serious car crash last Friday with its front right door completely smashed.The crash took place at the intersection of Phyllis Avenue and El Camino Real in Mountain View, California.The traffic light was green for at least 6 seconds before its self-driving car entered the intersection, Google said in a statement, stressing that its vehicle was not at-fault. Soon after, another car travelling westbound on El Camino Real ran a red light and crashed into the right side of the self-driving car. No one was hurt in the accident. Apart from Mountain view, Google is testing its fleet of 58 self-driving cars in three other locations including Kirkland, Phoenix and Austin.Google had boasted its zero at-fault accident history until one of its self-driving Lexus SUV stuck a bus in February this year, breaking its perfect record.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:18:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/27/3226623/3226623_546AEFCCD404418998E9566FFFE61FBD_161208_3226623_Self_driving_car_crash__Google_Lexus_collides_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AC2/637/AC263718EF9C46B08771339C214AB356_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Google self-driving car accident,google self-driving suv accident,self-driving car accident,google car accident,mountain view,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226619</guid>
      <title>Snapchat Spectacles: New Snapchat sunglasses record 10-second circular videos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Messaging app Snapchat plans to release sunglasses that record video later this fall.Called Snapchat Spectacles, the shades have a camera with a 115-degree-angle lens, which is a wider angle than on a regular smartphone and closer to the eyes’ natural field of view, the Verge reported.The glasses film circular videos that are 10 seconds long, and recording starts with the tap of a button. A light lets others know that the camera is rolling.If you want to film for longer then you have to tap the button again, but the recording limit is 30 seconds per video. Video can be played back in landscape or portrait mode and crops automatically.The clips transfer by default to Snapchat Memories via Bluetooth on iOS devices. Android users can use Wi-Fi to upload video to their phones.The company, which was recently renamed Snap Inc., said it will make a limited number of Snapchat Spectacles. They’ll come in black, teal and coral, and retail for about $130.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/27/3226619/3226619_59B12F7C718942F0A776CC9056B56777_161208_3226619_Snapchat_Spectacles__New_Snapchat_sunglasses_rec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2C5/7DF/2C57DFD7FD9C4261B341290A5D45DDAC_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Snapchat,snapchat spectacles,snapchat sunglasses,video sunglasses,snap inc,video camera sunglasses]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226614</guid>
      <title>Jose Fernandez: Miami Marlins star pitcher dies in tragic boating accident near Miami Beach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  Major League Baseball lost one of its most beloved players after a boat crash took the life of the Miami Marlins’ star pitcher Jose Fernandez.WPLG reports that in the early hours of Sept. 25, Fernandez was on a boat with two friends. The three were cruising on full speed just off Miami Beach when their boat collided with a rocky jetty along the Government Cut harbor entrance. The impact caused the boat to flip over, and Fernandez and his friends did not survive the crash.A U.S. Coast Guard vessel patrolling the area later spotted the boat’s blinking lights above the rocks. Upon investigation, they found the crashed vessel around 3:30 a.m. and notified other authorities.Rescuers recovered two bodies under the boat, and another in the water. All three did not have their life vests on.Authorities believe Fernandez died from the crash impact, not from drowning. The two other men with him were identified to be Eduardo Rivero and Emilio Macias, according to the Miami Herald.Based on the severity of the damage sustained by the vessel, authorities believe the boat’s speed was definitely a big factor in the accident, though it doesn’t appear as if illegal drugs or alcohol were involved.Fernandez was born in Cuba, and defected to the U.S. as a teen. He was expecting his first child with girlfriend Carla Mendoza, and posted about it on his official Instagram account days before his death.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 18:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/26/3226614/3226614_CFE0742EA57E4993A5E803FCE590090B_161208_3226614_Jose_Fernandez__Miami_Marlins_star_pitcher_dies__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C9B/DB3/C9BDB34D0EF64AB4AE414BB414051C20_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Jose fernandez,jose fernandez killed,jose fernandez death,boat crash,boating accident,miami boat crash,miami marlins,baseball,pitcher,star pitcher,major league baseball mlb]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226612</guid>
      <title>Beer pipeline in Belgian city of Bruges starts pumping, can fill 12,000 bottles an hour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUGES, BELGIUM  Belgium’s beer pipeline has officially started operating beneath the ancient city of Bruges on September 16.The two-mile beer pipeline originates from De Halve Maan beer brewery in the city centre of Bruges to a bottling plant out of town.“We wanted to avoid running big expensive tanker trucks back and forth transporting our beer,” the New York Times quoted Xavier Vanneste, the director of De Halve Maan as saying. “So we constructed a direct pipeline from the brewery to the bottle room.”The pipeline is able to transport enough beer to fill 12,000 bottles an hour, the Guardian reported.The earliest brewing at De Halve Maan was recorded in 1564. Vanneste was advised to shut down the historical site and move the operation to an industrial setting. However, he refused the proposal in order to keep the Bruges-made beer authentic, Reuters reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 18:08:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/26/3226612/3226612_CEF77DF8C1DC4340B2D3CC2B90F8A920_161208_3226612_Beer_pipeline_in_Belgian_city_of_Bruges_starts_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/95C/98E/95C98E2E536744E1A4E63A22C75ABBFF_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bruges beer pipeline,belgium beer pipeline,de halve maan brewery beer pipeline,de halve maan beer,belgium beer,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226608</guid>
      <title>Yahoo hack: Hackers swipe 500 million Yahoo passwords in biggest ever data breach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SUNNYVALE, CALIFORNIA  Internet giant Yahoo is today coming to terms with a cyber-calamity after admitting it is the victim of the biggest data breach in history.In 2014, hackers gained access to at least 500 million Yahoo accounts, but for some reason we’re only hearing about this now.The hackers swiped account names, email addresses, phone numbers, birth dates, passwords, and even security questions and answers, tech site Cnet reported.Yahoo blamed an unknown foreign government for the hack, so fingers immediately pointed to the usual suspects of China, Russia and North Korea.The biggest fear is that hackers will use the stolen data to access accounts on other websites.So if you haven’t done so already, go and change your Yahoo password.Cybersecurity experts also recommend not using the same password across different sites. Err, because hacking.”We shouldn’t need to tell you this, but “123456”, “password” and “let me in” are just too obvious and around half a billion Yahoo users are now at risk of finding that out the hard way.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/23/3226608/3226608_8CA85D8F59264B26AD289808E69405D8_161208_3226608_Yahoo_hack__Hackers_swipe_500_million_Yahoo_pass_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BAC/9B9/BAC9B9B851AD4731A3B43C2273BBEABE_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Yahoo,yahoo hack,yahoo hack password 2016,yahoo hack 2016,yahoo hack password,hacking,yahoo hacker]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226594</guid>
      <title>Climate change PM 2.5: California fights cow farts and diesel truck with new laws</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO  The state of California has signed off on legislation to clamp down on greenhouse-gas emissions including black carbon from diesel trucks, and methane gas from cow flatulence. On September 19, California Governor Jerry Brown announced new bills to restrict environmental pollutants damaging to the air we breathe. Under the new laws, carbon emissions stemming from diesel trucks will be reduced by 50 percent. Dairy farmers have been instructed to reduce methane emissions from the state’s 5.15 million cows by 40 percent by the year 2030.Farmers will receive funding from the state to invest in methane digesters, to convert the pollutants from manure into energy to be sold to electrical utilities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/23/3226594/3226594_B673DEE26DA540EEB8B3C17B6CD70054_161208_3226594_Climate_change_PM_2_5__California_fights_cow_far_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/198/0D3/1980D3201FD84F8798C70D1B8E88F540_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[California energy,cow farts,methane digester,black carbon,carbon emissions,jerry brown,methane gas,dairy,california governor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226589</guid>
      <title>South China Sea: Is Taiwan building anti-aircraft gun towers on Taiping Island?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPING ISLAND, SOUTH CHINA SEA  Taiwan’s Ministry of Defense would like to keep its military facilities in the South China Sea secret, and is asking Google to blur satellite images of the area on its Earth and Map services.China Post reports that new military construction was recently revealed on Taiwanese-controlled Taiping, the largest naturally occurring feature in the much-disputed Spratly Islands.Eagle-eyed observers spotted four three-pronged concrete structures arranged in a semicircle near the northwest shoreline. Defense officials aren’t disclosing what they are, but experts speculate that they could be anti-aircraft towers.Taiping, also known as Itu Aba, already has a 1,195-meter airstrip that’s long enough to accommodate F-16 fighter jets, C-130 Hercules cargo planes, and P-3C patrol crafts, according to the Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative. With these aircraft, surveillance patrols have an operational radius of up to 2,500 kilometers.A pier completed earlier this year on Taiping has a 210-meter berth, capable of docking 10,000-tonne frigates, reports the Taipei Times.Taiping has other existing installations, including a command post, radar, and lighthouse. It is classified as a rock and not an island under the UN Convention on the Law of the Sea, a ruling which Taiwan strongly rejects.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/23/3226589/3226589_A27014D2B9F7439CA31A768A344F129A_161208_3226589_South_China_Sea__Is_Taiwan_building_anti_aircraf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EC7/5B8/EC75B82790F7426FAD88C71651D60634_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taiping island,itu aba,south china sea,spratlys,spratlys islands,south china sea dispute,militarization,anti aircraft tower,anti aircraft gun,taipei,taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226584</guid>
      <title>Trump contradicted by Ford on US jobs: Firm says no job losses as plant opens in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DEARBORN, MICHIGAN  American automaker Ford Motors has announced that it will move part of its business overseas, in the process drawing criticism from Republican candidate Donald Trump.The Detroit Free Press reports that Ford is investing $1.6 billion into building a plant in Mexico in preparation for shifting small-car production out of the country over the next two to three years. Small vehicles like the Focus and C-Max are currently being built in the company’s plant in Wayne, Michigan, which employs 3,747 workers. By 2018, production of the two cars will move from Michigan to San Luis Potosi, where lower wages will reduce costs.Critics, including Trump, are blasting the company for local jobs that may be lost as a result of the move. But Ford has denied the claims, saying that the Wayne, Michigan facility will still assemble vehicles. According to Reuters, analysts expect that the plant instead produce larger vehicles like the Bronco SUV and the Ranger pickup.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/23/3226584/3226584_0708CDFDF0E2491BA54B6421D401939B_161208_3226584_Trump_contradicted_by_Ford_on_US_jobs__Firm_says_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/304/047/3040472CB6B24A1888A188CF3E799814_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ford moves to Mexico,small car production,Ford small car production,Ford car production,US auto industry,Ford motors,Ford cars,Ford car production,Ford]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226581</guid>
      <title>Poison ivy: Harvard researchers discover why it makes us itch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON  Researchers at Harvard Medical School have finally figured out what it is about poison ivy, poison oak, and poison sumac that causes our skin to itch.Poison ivy has oils on its leaves called urushiol. When the compound comes into contact with human skin, it sets off a chain reaction that results in a skin irritation. The chain reaction involves the body’s immune system releasing two proteins to defend the body  interleukin 17 and interleukin 22. These proteins are what cause the inflammation triggered by poison ivy. The research team had been using lab mice for the study, until they realized the mice lacked a molecule called CD1a, which plays a key role in the inflammation process of human skin. Researchers then genetically engineered mice to produce CD1a. From applying urushiol to these altered mice, they discovered a new antibody that interrupts the inflammatory reaction. The research team believes these findings could also be used to benefit sufferers of psoriasis.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/23/3226581/3226581_B31B37F04934410185E941CEA070948B_161208_3226581_Poison_ivy__Harvard_researchers_discover_why_it__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A87/D81/A87D8118492F4F8B9AABDD9275463922_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Poison ivy,poison ivy treatment,poison ivy cure,harvard,nature immunology,urushiol,interleukin,kyoto university,boston children’s hospital]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226577</guid>
      <title>Fighting superbugs: Researchers develop new ways to combat drug-resistant bacteria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA  Researchers have discovered two new ways to fight superbugs.Currently, the only treatment for bacterial infections is through the use of antibiotics. Antibiotics release antimicrobial polymers into the body that kill bacteria. Different antibiotics are designed to kill different bacteria in different ways, but all antibiotics must first be absorbed into the bacteria. Once the antimicrobial polymer passes through the bacterial cellular wall, the polymer can go to work to kill the bacteria.  However, bacteria over time can mutate to protect themselves against antibiotics. The most common mutation is the development of an efflux pump, which expel antimicrobial polymers that make it past the bacterial cellular wall before they’re able to cause damage. These immune bacteria have become known as superbugs.Researchers at UT Southwestern Medical Center in Texas have discovered a synthetic compound that blocks efflux pumps, making superbugs once again vulnerable. And researchers at the University of Melbourne in Australia have created a new form of antibiotic. They have developed a star-shaped peptide polymer that fights bacteria in more than one way, one of which is by ripping apart the bacterial cellular wall. This makes it difficult for superbugs to become resistant.The polymer is also nontoxic. A person would have to take 100 times the dosage rate of the star-shaped polymer for it to become toxic.Both methods still need to be refined and both research teams are still working towards human trials.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226577/3226577_3DD48B26F97D41A495E04A3022031D57_161208_3226577_Fighting_superbugs__Researchers_develop_new_ways_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E97/044/E970447E43084B27B0CDE2AB1162778C_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Antibiotics,bacteria,health,illness,polymer,science,superbug,superbugs,University Of Melbourne,ut southwestern medical center,killing superbugs,peptide polymers,antimicrobials,polymers,UT southwestern medical center,university of melbourne. University of texas,university of texas southwestern medical center,drug-resistant bacteria,antibiotic resistant,synthetic compounds,synthetic drug]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226573</guid>
      <title>Self-driving boats called Roboats could sail Amsterdam canals by 2017</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMSTERDAM  In a collaboration with researchers at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), the Amsterdam Institute for Advanced Metropolitan Solutions (AMS Institute) is currently developing autonomous boats.Roboat is the first large-scale research project that will put self-driving boats on water as early as 2017. The first prototype, a flatbed, six-by-six-foot design was created for basic transportation of people and goods through Amsterdam’s many canals. The flatbed boats can also be utilized as on-demand bridges or water stages, easily assembled within hours to relieve traffic congestion.Researchers are also looking at other designs that could assist in underwater research, detecting waterborne diseases at an early stage. The Roboats also have potential to help clean canal waters by picking up floating debris or waste.The project is currently being backed with $27 million and researchers are hoping the autonomous boats can be utilized in cities across the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226573/3226573_A7EAFDE7FFD749219701F414FDE6DCD5_161208_3226573_Self_driving_boats_called_Roboats_could_sail_Ams_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BDD/8AA/BDD8AA6CB22E4F19AF08E8414C8DE744_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Roboats,robot boats,self driving,self driving boats,self driving vehicles,ams institute,amsterdam,autonomous,autonomous boats,canals,waterways,research,science,technology,boats,transportation,MIT,Massachusetts Institute of Technology,the Amsterdam Institute for Advanced Metropolitan Solutions,AMS Institute]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226572</guid>
      <title>The next Zika: Mayaro virus discovered in Haiti for the first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORT-AU-PRINCE, HAITI  A mosquito-born virus named Mayaro that experts fear may have as big a global health impact as Zika, has been discovered in Haiti.On January 8, 2015, an 8-year-old boy went to the school clinic for fever and abdominal pain and was diagnosed typhoid. After checking his blood sample, it was found that he had been infected with Mayaro virus.Mayaro virus is a single-stranded positive RNA virus, mainly transmitted by Haemagogus mosquitoes, but Aedes aegypti mosquitoes, known carrier of Zika virus, may also be vectors. Symptoms of mayaro includes abdominal pain and joint pain, which can last for as long as a year.The virus was first discovered in Trinidad in 1954. It was then spread to French Guiana, Suriname, Venezuela, Peru, Bolivia and Brazil.Little is known about the Mayaro virus at the moment. Doctors in Florida warn that the virus may pose future threats.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226572/3226572_0135518112F1489D8247B68DC89A07D6_161208_3226572_The_next_Zika__Mayaro_virus_discovered_in_Haiti__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C48/152/C4815219935B4601A4BB9AD7BD33571D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mayaro virus,mayaro virus in haiti,zika virus,zika outbreak,mosquito-borne virus,health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226570</guid>
      <title>Kellogg&#x2019;s food poisoning scare: 10,000 cereal boxes pulled over listeria bacteria risk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BATTLE CREEK, MICHIGAN  American cereal foods maker Kellogg announced a recall of approximately 10,000 cases of Eggo Nutri-Grain Whole Wheat Waffles in 25 states across the United States on Monday due to potential risks of listeria contamination.Listeria monocytogenes bacteria is commonly found in soil and water. Vegetables can become contaminated from the soil; animals can carry the bacteria without appearing ill and can infect meat and dairy products.The bacteria inside the food can spread to the processing facility and can survive there for years, where they can multiply and contaminate other foods that come through the same facility. It can even survive being frozen and can spread to the freezer where the contaminated food is stored.People consume food with listeria monocytogenes would be infected with the bacteria, which would spread beyond the gastrointestinal tract and cause infections such as fever and muscle aches.Listeria outbreak isn’t uncommon in the US. In May, CRF Frozen Foods announced a nationwide recall of  almost 360 frozen fruits and vegetables over listeria contamination. Famous ice cream brand Blue Bell recalled its products everywhere after a large listeria outbreak in 2015.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226570/3226570_E14D6D830E694537B05931BFF50B13A1_161208_3226570_Kellogg___s_food_poisoning_scare__10_000_cereal__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B2D/3B9/B2D3B907D7054F9C88697E43C6A98A82_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Listeria outbreak,listeria contamination,kellogg recall,kellogg recalls eggo waffle,eggo waffle recall,food safety,us food contamination]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226568</guid>
      <title>Fertilization research: UK lab birth 30 baby mice from embryos created in non-egg cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BATH, UK  Scientists at the University of Bath in the U.K. have made a discovery that they say challenges almost two centuries of knowledge on fertilization. It is widely thought that mammals could only be born from an egg fertilized with sperm, but this discovery, published in the journal Nature Communication, bypasses that entirely.According to a University of Bath article on the study, researchers used chemicals to “trick” mouse eggs into developing as if they’d been fertilized. This produced parthenogenotes, an embryo that dies after a few days.At this point the embryos had a half set of chromosomes and were in the stages of cell division, notes an NHS report. It’s here that researchers injected them with sperm. These embryos were then inserted into female mice and the process produced 30 mouse pups with a success rate of around one in four.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226568/3226568_0ED2AF0A1F3E4C9A89AE57AC492EFB5A_161208_3226568_Fertilization_research__UK_lab_birth_30_baby_mic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/47C/3DE/47C3DEF1DED143C8A04FBF49BA81E954_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Experiments on mice,fertilization experiments,fertilization no egg,fertilization research,university of bath,skipping fertilization,tricking embryos,chromosome]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226563</guid>
      <title>Illegal fishing: Global Fishing Watch monitors fishing boats to safeguard our oceans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  Tech-environmentalist group SkyTruth, non-profit organization Oceana, and Google have unveiled Global Fishing Watch, a free tool that allows people to track fishing activity worldwide, in a bid to curb the exploitation of marine life.A press release on the Google Maps blog explains that the system uses radio signals emitted by large vessels through the Automatic Identification System, or AIS. Satellites and other terrestrial antenna pick up the signals and store them in a database.An algorithm applied to the data uses vessel movements to determine what type of ship and fishing gear are being utilized. Ship positions are delayed by 72 hours, but can be tracked from as far back as January of 2012.Information is displayed on an interactive Google Earth map, and includes each country’s exclusive economic zones and protected areas, as well as the individual records and identities of more than 35,000 fishing boats.Users need only to have an internet connection to access the free data and remotely monitor any ships that could be fishing illegally.The system is far from perfect. Smaller vessels that don’t require the use of the Automatic Identification System or AIS can’t be tracked, according to Scientific American. The AIS itself can report false locations when tampered with by a crew trying to mask illegal activities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226563/3226563_83AF2D4259394E4C8E1F1F090C521731_161208_3226563_Illegal_fishing__Global_Fishing_Watch_monitors_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BF9/9DE/BF99DEDDE67A4C1FB2CBE3D951CFF318_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Global fishing watch,illegal fishing,data mining,crowd spying,watchdog,ocean advocacy,environment,skytruth,oceana,google,google earth,leonardo di caprio]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226559</guid>
      <title>China to build its Hualong One reactor in UK after Hinkley Point deal approved</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING   China’s investment in the approved Hinkley Point nuclear power station project may mean that it could build its own nuclear reactor in the UK.According to the Guardian, China will own 33% of the Hinkley Point C project in return to build its self-developed Hualong One reactor in Bradwell, Essex. Hualong One is a third generation pressurized water reactor that is designed to last at last at least 60 years. Its reactor core has 177 fuel assemblies, with a thermal power output of 3060 MWt. The reactor building is protected by two layers of walls; the inner wall contains a steel lining and the outer wall is designed to be strong enough to withstand the impact of a large commercial plane crash.China aims to export its nuclear reactors worldwide with its Hualong One reactor being sold in Pakistan, Argentina and Romania.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226559/3226559_6582AAA473BF4A8C8B30080E082182F9_161208_3226559_China_to_build_its_Hualong_One_reactor_in_UK_aft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7D8/A34/7D8A3431D3EC481294CC285CC0E039A4_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China nuclear export,china hualong one nuclear reactor,hualong one nuclear reactor,china nuclear industry,hinkley point project,bradwell essex nuclear project,nuclear]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226556</guid>
      <title>iPhone 7 hissing: Owners report iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus hiss when put under pressure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA  Disgruntled Apple iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus users are complaining that a low hissing sound emanates from the back of their phones when the devices are pushed to their processing limits.There is a consensus online that the noise could be “coil whine”, caused when the phone’s powerful A10 processor comes under a heavy workload, the Verge reports.Coil whine occurs when an electromagnetic coil physically vibrates due to the strength of the electric current passing through it. The noise can be dampened, for example with a drop of glue, but the dampener can deteriorate over time, according to tech website Ars Technica.Coil whine can occur in any electric circuit and is quite common in personal computers. It has not been much of an issue for smartphones until now however, probably because the processors in the devices previously weren’t big enough.Not all iPhone 7 users are experiencing the problem and so far Apple has declined to comment, the Verge reported.iPhone 7 owners with the hissing problem report that Apple has been willing to replace defective devices. However, a lack of stock means customers must wait around five to seven days for a replacement phone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226556/3226556_191FCF2854794EC1BBB28EDC3953C614_161208_3226556_iPhone_7_hissing__Owners_report_iPhone_7_and_iPh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CA0/17F/CA017F4C6BDE4CAD9F68C749DC25DEDD_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Apple,iphone,iphone 7,iphone 7 plus,iphone 7 noise,iphone 7 hiss,iphone 7 hissing,iphone 7 hissing problem,hissgate,buzzgate]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226550</guid>
      <title>The next Zika: Mayaro virus discovered in Haiti for the first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORT-AU-PRINCE, HAITI  A mosquito-born virus named Mayaro that experts fear may have as big a global health impact as Zika, has been discovered in Haiti.On January 8, 2015, an 8-year-old boy went to the school clinic for fever and abdominal pain and was diagnosed typhoid. After checking his blood sample, it was found that he had been infected with Mayaro virus.Mayaro virus is a single-stranded positive RNA virus, mainly transmitted by Haemagogus mosquitoes, but Aedes aegypti mosquitoes, known carrier of Zika virus, may also be vectors. Symptoms of mayaro includes abdominal pain and joint pain, which can last for as long as a year.The virus was first discovered in Trinidad in 1954. It was then spread to French Guiana, Suriname, Venezuela, Peru, Bolivia and Brazil.Little is known about the Mayaro virus at the moment. Doctors in Florida warn that the virus may pose future threats.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 17:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/22/3226550/3226550_F10F6C58C8B54CC587E8659AEA44B7F7_161208_3226550_The_next_Zika__Mayaro_virus_discovered_in_Haiti__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/962/D7F/962D7FA40184443EBB4E7A0C88493178_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mayaro virus,mayaro virus in haiti,zika virus,zika outbreak,mosquito-borne virus,health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226549</guid>
      <title>China says Tiangong-1 spacecraft will fall back to Earth in second half of next year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIUQUAN, CHINA  China says its first space lab Tiangong-1 will likely fall back to Earth in the second half of 2017, which seems to confirm speculation that it has already lost control of the spacecraft.Tiangong-1 spacecraft is currently orbiting Earth at an altitude of 370 km, which is about 30 km lower than the orbit of the International Space Station. It was launched in September 2011 and has stopped sending data back to Earth since March this year.“Based on our calculation and analysis, most parts of the space lab will burn up during falling,” Wu Ping, deputy director of the manned space engineering office said in a press conference.However, satellite tracker Thomas Dorman thinks such statement has confirmed his view that China has lost control of Tiangong-1 and the country will only inform the world at the very last minute, Space.com reported.According to Xinhua News, China will continue to monitor Tiangong-1 and send out warnings for possible collisions with objects and report internationally if necessary.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 17:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/21/3226549/3226549_71E312D909A94A7A907370A39E58EED9_161208_3226549_China_says_Tiangong_1_spacecraft_will_fall_back__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0A1/63C/0A163C2926AE45D79C833F3A60C66E33_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China tiangong-1,tiangong-1 fall back to earth,tiangong-1 space lab,tiangong-1 spacecraft,china space industry,china space lab,china space station,space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226545</guid>
      <title>Immigration fails: Homeland Security granted 859 deportees US citizenship by mistake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Due to flawed fingerprint records, the U.S. Department of Homeland Security had mistakenly granted American citizenship to 859 deportees, a U.S. government audit has found.According to NPR, the Office of Inspector General report says that FBI and the DHS don’t have the fingerprints of deportees because they didn’t have the records within their databases. The DHS didn’t start digitizing fingerprints records until 2007. There remains 148,000 paper records belonging to deportees, criminals or fugitives that need to be uploaded to the database, NPR reported, citing the report.According to the report, three of those mistakenly granted citizenship were working in security sensitives roles in airports and maritime facilities. Their credentials were revoked.The investigation was ordered after terror attacks in San Bernadino, California and Paris last year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 17:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/21/3226545/3226545_C108FC38F5D1498490D7AADE1384D2E9_161208_3226545_Immigration_fails__Homeland_Security_granted_859_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F36/06E/F3606E4A433B409BB2E49B9B4711A0D6_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Immigration fails,homeland security,us citizenship,illegal aliens,fbi,fingerprint records,foreign criminals,revoke citizenship,immigrant risks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226531</guid>
      <title>Pressure cooker bombs: how the explosives used in the New York City terror attacks work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  It has now been confirmed that the destructive devices used in the New York terror attacks were pressure cooker bombs. The pressure cooker bombs used in the attacks were filled with shrapnel and ball bearings, similar to those used in the 2013 Boston Marathon bombing. The explosives in Manhattan are said to have been detonated by a mobile flip phone and Christmas lights. With the materials sealed inside, the trigger ignites inside, with pressure slowly building until the explosion.The first bomb was placed in a waste disposal unit, which then exploded and injured 29 people. The second bomb was found undetonated, and a robot was sent in to safely remove it from the area.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 17:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/20/3226531/3226531_3A6970D0F2AD42BBB2DBC7307A71BD9C_161208_3226531_Pressure_cooker_bombs__how_the_explosives_used_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AFB/11E/AFB11E0DA795476B9E441662F49237DE_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[New york terror attack,pressure cooker bomb,how pressure cooker bombs work,new jersey terror attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226515</guid>
      <title>Killer smog PM 2.5: Indonesian forest fire haze may have killed 100,000 people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INDONESIA  Joint research from Columbia and Harvard universities suggests that haze from the 2015 Indonesian forest fires could have led to the deaths of over 100,000 people.The study, published in the journal Environmental Research Letter, estimates that smog may have been responsible for 91,600 people in Indonesia, 6,500 people in Malaysia and 2,200 people in Singapore. The study did not investigate the impact of the smog on children and infants.Smog from last year’s forest fires produced PM 2.5, a highly dangerous particulate matter. It can cause a variety of health problems including lung cancer and cardiovascular disease, the New York Times reported.Scientists say last year’s man-made forest fires in Indonesian Borneo and Sumatra  along with their resulting haze  were the worst recorded. Those fires were started to make way for agricultural production. A Greenpeace campaigner told the New York Times that despite being illegal, this practice is commonplace in various parts of Indonesia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 17:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/20/3226515/3226515_1717917E06E744229E89223D42E2D2AE_161208_3226515_Killer_smog_PM_2_5__Indonesian_forest_fire_haze__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/534/2D9/5342D923DB8846248CB92BDC4AEB5F56_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Pm 2.5,Killer smog,killer haze,deadly smog,indonesia forest fire,indoensian smog,indonesian haze,haze health,smog health problems]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226508</guid>
      <title>Amazon is building gigantic wind farm in Texas comprised of more than 100 wind turbines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SCURRY COUNTY, TEXAS  A new project announced by Amazon aims to result in renewable energy that will power thousands of homes across America. The Amazon Wind Farm Texas in Scurry County is comprised of at least 100 wind turbines, with the diameter of each measuring more than twice the wingspan of a Boeing 747 plane.The wind turbines will generate an estimated 100,000 megawatt hours of wind energy every year, enough to power close to 90,000 homes in the United States.This latest development by the company, along with four other clean energy projects, will result in 2.6 million megawatt hours each year, powering more than 240,000 homes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 16:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/20/3226508/3226508_D216A4F5F90F412A9D5D3178834A5550_161208_3226508_Amazon_is_building_gigantic_wind_farm_in_Texas_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9B4/66D/9B466DDD6CD64E70AC3CA34C261A91C4_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Amazon wind farm,amazon wind turbines,wind turbines,amazon renewable energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226507</guid>
      <title>New York terror attacks: What we know so far about suspected NY, NJ bomber Ahmad Rahami</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LINDEN, NEW JERSEY  Details are emerging about Ahmad Khan Rahami, the bombing suspect who was captured in Linden, New Jersey following a shootout on Monday morning.CNN reports that Rahami was born in Afghanistan and came to America in January of 1995 to seek asylum. He was became a naturalized U.S. citizen in 2011. That same year, he visited Kandahar, Afghanistan and Quetta, Pakistan, both considered Taliban strongholds. While there, he married a Pakistani woman.He again traveled to Quetta in April 2013, staying there nearly a year before returning to American soil in March of 2014. Both times, Rahami was questioned by immigration officials upon returning to the United States. He claimed to have been visiting relatives who were Afghan refugees, and managed to avoid suspicion	.In 2014, he was arrested after his sister accused him of trying to stab her. Rahami spent two months in jail before she recanted her allegations.According to ABC, his last known address was in Elizabeth, New Jersey. He lived with family in an apartment above their restaurant, First American Fried Chicken, where he frequently helped out.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 16:58:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/20/3226507/3226507_AFFDD2E26D3348EF84672E4C7424A7B4_161208_3226507_New_York_terror_attacks__What_we_know_so_far_abo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A12/42B/A1242BE69EF440548EDF7620128C6528_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ahmad khan rahami,afghanistan,new york explosion,new jersey explosion,chelsea bombing,us bombing,new york bombing,new jersey bombing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226503</guid>
      <title>Google tax evasion? Indonesia says Google owes millions in unpaid back taxes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAKARTA, INDONESIA  Indonesia is investigating Google over five years of unpaid taxes on advertising revenue that could lead to a bill of $400 million for last year alone.Indonesia thinks Google only paid 0.1 percent tax on its Indonesian ad revenue last year by diverting the cash to its Singapore office, Reuters reported.Australia has also raised questions in recent years about Google’s practice of booking Aussie ad revenues through Singapore, according to the Financial Times.Australia’s corporate tax rate is 30 percent. That figure drops to 25 percent in Indonesia and just 17 percent in Singapore.Web giants Yahoo, Twitter and Facebook are also being investigated by Indonesia, which has launched a separate probe into taxes paid by the Ford Motor Company.Indonesia claims Google allocated just 4 percent of the total revenue it generated in the country last year to its Indonesian branch.The Indonesian communications ministry estimates that the digital advertising industry in the country was worth $800 million last year, and none of it was taxed.Economic growth is slowing in Indonesia and the resource-rich country faces a revenue shortfall this year because of low commodity prices.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 16:56:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/20/3226503/3226503_675F3ACD9F6E4BE3B90307C4AD8ABF87_161208_3226503_Google_tax_evasion__Indonesia_says_Google_owes_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8F8/51D/8F851DC9FA024A02993EE115B2DB8826_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Google tax avoidance,google indonesia,google tax evasion,google tax,google tax explained,google,google tax indonesia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226502</guid>
      <title>New York bomb: Woman who found second device thought it was a kid&#x2019;s science project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A photographer who found a second explosive device in Manhattan didn’t call the cops at first because she thought it was a kid’s science experiment.Jane Schreibman discovered the pressure cooker bomb near her home in Chelsea on Saturday night.She told the New York Post that the pressure cooker had wires coming out of it that were attached to a cell phone or remote control.Schreibman discovered the second device about 90 minutes after a dumpster bomb went off just blocks away, injuring 29 people.The photographer found the device about 15 steps from the front door of her apartment. But it was only after she found roads blocked near her home that she thought she’d better call the cops.Detectives showed up about three minutes later and told Schreibman to run.The police bomb squad took the device away in the early hours of Sunday morning. So far the cops aren’t sure if it was functional. Unable to get back into her apartment, Schreibman went to a friend’s house and played Scrabble until 3 a.m, when a detective finally escorted her home, the New York Post reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 16:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/20/3226502/3226502_02B0CD6C39EB4CE983D207EFCA02D1D4_161208_3226502_New_York_bomb__Woman_who_found_second_device_tho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/81F/D6C/81FD6CAE3DEC4446A3B528610FFB4B0A_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[New york bomb,new york bombing,new york bombing 2016,new york bomb blast,new york explosion,new york bomb threat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226498</guid>
      <title>Space laser: Scientists propose using lasers to clean up space junk orbiting Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLOGNE, GERMANY  German scientists have proposed using laser pulses to clean up small, irregular shaped space debris.The study was published by SPIE, the international society for optics and photonics. The authors propose using high-energy laser pulses to change the orbit of the debris, leading it to re-enter and burn-up in the atmosphere."Laser damage is usually considered to be a negative phenomenon, but this paper considers a significant positive application of laser-induced damage. In this study, the damage produced by laser beams serves a highly useful and positive purpose by cleaning up the space around Earth," Vitaly Gruzdev of University of Missouri commented in a press release.According to NASA, there are nearly 3,000 tons of space debris in the low-Earth orbit. Most spacecraft can be protected from debris up to 1 cm in diameter, thanks to Whipple Shields. However, debris between 1 to 10 cm in size are particularly dangerous as they cannot be dodged or blocked. Space debris can travel at speeds up to 28,000 kph, which is fast enough for a small piece to damage satellite or a spacecraft.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 16:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/19/3226498/3226498_8DA949E387884C6EBABDC5B91E7E378F_161208_3226498_Space_laser__Scientists_propose_using_lasers_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EA2/F1F/EA2F1F7FB6D34A4FA39F26AA49377BC5_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Space debris,space junk,clean up space debris with laser,laser broom,space,nasa,german aerospace center,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226496</guid>
      <title>Minnesota mall attack: ISIS-backed Somali man shot to death after stabbing nine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. CLOUD, MINNESOTA  Hours after a Somali immigrant stabbed nine people in St. Cloud, Minnesota, the ISIS-linked Amaq news agency announced on Twitter that the attacker was a soldier of Islamic State.The St. Cloud Times reports that 22-year-old college student Dahir Adan went to Crossroads Mall Saturday night wielding a knife. He referenced Allah and asked at least one person if they were Muslim before savagely attacking people with his weapon.Shoppers lay bleeding in multiple locations as Adan rampaged through the mall, going from Sears in the southeast corner to a Macy’s on the north end.Off-duty police officer Jason Falconer confronted the suspect in the Macy’s store, shooting him down as the assailant charged with a knife. Adan died at the scene, leaving behind nine victims  seven men, one woman and a teenage girl. All were taken to the hospital and are expected to survive.Despite ISIS’s claim, the FBI is still only treating the incident as a potential act of terrorism.Two other attacks occurred on the same day, with both New York and New Jersey rocked by twin explosions. Authorities suspect both bombings may be linked, but have yet to determine if they are connected to ISIS or to the Minnesota stabbings, according to the New York Times.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 16:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/19/3226496/3226496_AA253EC0A11C4CD6AECF3D705454B8AD_161208_3226496_Minnesota_mall_attack__ISIS_backed_Somali_man_sh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BE2/BCE/BE2BCEC73FEE40CB848A362CBDBC005E_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Minnesota stabbing,minnesota mall attack,crossroads mall stabbing,crossroads mall attack,st cloud mall stabbing,st cloud mall attack,st cloud minnesota,amaq news agency,somali stabbing,somali suspect,somali man]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226340</guid>
      <title>Anti-drone privacy: SkyDroner system can force drone to land or fly back to its owner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE  A Singaporean company has designed an anti-drone surveillance system that protect one’s privacy and safety against invading drones.The SkyDroner is an anti-drone surveillance system that can detect drone activities within 1km radius. It has multiple sensors that allow it to identify the characteristics of an anonymous drone, such as its model.“The increase in recreational drone activities in the past two years has sparked concern of drone invasion in the airspace,” Robyn Tay, the founder of the SkyDroner, told CNBC.The SkyDroner can also distract and take over the command of the drone’s radio frequencies, such as sending it back to its operator or making it land at a designated location.According to CNBC, the system is intended to be used by places such as police departments, defense departments and airports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 15:04:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/10/19/3226340/3226340_7EC18DA4F6B740288C08262A5A65C4DA_161208_3226340_Anti_drone_privacy__SkyDroner_system_can_force_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/52F/78D/52F78DED016747B3804E3377A47A37B3_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Skydroner,anti-drone surveillance,drones,drone surveillance,skydroner500,skydroner1000,technology,surveillance,planet drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226338</guid>
      <title>Trump contradicted by Ford on US jobs: Firm says no job losses as plant opens in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DEARBORN, MICHIGAN  American automaker Ford Motors has announced that it will move part of its business overseas, in the process drawing criticism from Republican candidate Donald Trump.The Detroit Free Press reports that Ford is investing $1.6 billion into building a plant in Mexico in preparation for shifting small-car production out of the country over the next two to three years. Small vehicles like the Focus and C-Max are currently being built in the company’s plant in Wayne, Michigan, which employs 3,747 workers. By 2018, production of the two cars will move from Michigan to San Luis Potosi, where lower wages will reduce costs.Critics, including Trump, are blasting the company for local jobs that may be lost as a result of the move. But Ford has denied the claims, saying that the Wayne, Michigan facility will still assemble vehicles. According to Reuters, analysts expect that the plant instead produce larger vehicles like the Bronco SUV and the Ranger pickup.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 15:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/19/3226338/3226338_5BE346F3BB464DA28D483F104F5D37AA_161208_3226338_Trump_contradicted_by_Ford_on_US_jobs__Firm_says_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B4E/015/B4E015F8D73440458BC02F5944C8EFD1_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ford moves to Mexico,small car production,Ford small car production,Ford car production,US auto industry,Ford motors,Ford cars,Ford car production,Ford]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226336</guid>
      <title>New York City explosion: Blast rips through Chelsea district injuring dozens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  An explosion caused by what officials believe was a homemade bomb tore through the Chelsea neighborhood in New York City injuring at least 29 people on Saturday night. None of the injuries appeared to be life-threatening, the New York City Fire Department said. The force of the explosion blew out windows and could be heard several blocks away, according to BBC. Authorities believe the blast was caused by an explosive device in or near a dumpster, according to CNN.  The blast, which happened around 8:30 p.m., prompted the closure of a large section of Manhattan south of Midtown, the New York Times reported. On Sunday, 14th Street to 32nd Street was closed to traffic between Fifth and Eighth Avenues until further notice, according to the New York Times.A second device, believed to be a pressure cooker rigged with wires, was later found several blocks away on West 27th street. It was later safely removed by the NYPD Bomb Squad, according to the New York Police Department. “There is no specific and credible threat to New York City from any terror organization,” Mayor Bill de Blasio said in a news conference late Saturday night.However, the mayor did go on to say, “we believe at this point in time this was an intentional act.” Authorities said there appears to be no connection to a pipe bomb that exploded in a garbage can earlier on Saturday in Seaside Heights, New Jersey, USA Today reported. That blast occurred near a Marine charity run with no injuries reported, according to USA Today.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 15:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/18/3226336/3226336_B63C9F21A04E4EA1A6FCE0796229CA7B_161208_3226336_New_York_City_explosion__Blast_rips_through_Chel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/53E/F1C/53EF1C00F48F4558A1FC4E3B6C41666F_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[New York City explosion,Chelsea district explosion,Chelsea neighborhood explosion,Chelsea pressure cooker device,New Jersey pipe bomb]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226332</guid>
      <title>World&#x2019;s largest plane Antonov AN-225 to resume production</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China and Ukraine have signed an agreement on August 30 to restart the production of the world’s largest plane, the Antonov AN-225.The giant aircraft has six Progress D-18T engines. It is 59 feet tall, which is roughly as high as a six-story building. It has a wingspan of 290 feet and is 275 feet long. It easily dwarfs Boeing 747 and Airbus A380.Its cargo hold is 142 feet long and 19.6 feet wide and can carry a variety of cargo with a total weight up to 250 tonnes, such as 50 cars or 16 standard aeronautical containers of UAC-10 type. Other single piece of cargo weighing up to 200 tonnes can be mounted to its external store. The aircraft was originally built in the 1980s to transport the Soviet Union’s Space Shuttle, Buran. After the collapse of the Soviet Union, the financing for the project was terminated and the aircraft has been used as commercial cargo planes since 2001.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 14:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/18/3226332/3226332_13FE6227F94A4748A5C064793222C654_161208_3226332_World___s_largest_plane_Antonov_AN_225_to_resume_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/759/2B0/7592B01BB7A6452AA4F26EF44FA09FF7_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[World’s largest plane,world’s biggest plane,an-225,an-225 mriya,antonov an-225,china,ukraine,antonov]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226329</guid>
      <title>World&#x2019;s first large-scale tidal energy farm to be installed in Scotland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INVERNESS, SCOTLAND  The world’s first large-scale tidal energy farm will soon be installed off the Scottish coast.Four turbines, measuring up to 16 meters tall with 8-meter-long blades will be installed  off the northern coast of Scotland between Caithness and Orkney in the initial phase of the project.“I am incredibly proud of Scotland’s role in leading the way in tackling climate change and investment in marine renewables is a hugely important part of this,” the Guardian quoted Nicola Sturgeon, the First Minister of Scotland as saying.According to the Guardian, developer Atlantis Resources hopes to install a total of 269 turbines, a move that could provide energy for 175,000 homes. According to the Scottish Government, the country holds one quarter of the Europe’s offshore wind resources.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 14:57:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/16/3226329/3226329_A0695540967B4CDE88ECB71515C61F69_161207_3226329_World___s_first_large_scale_tidal_energy_farm_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AE7/07C/AE707CC0C750496FB7021865C85BD48D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Meygen project,meygen scotland tidal power,atlantis resources ar1500,ar1500 turbines,tidal energy,tidal power,scottish tidal power,tidal energy farm scotland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226328</guid>
      <title>Self-driving apartment rooms? Tridika maglev train-cum-apartments may soon be a thing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTREAL, CANADA  A Canadian company has released an innovative idea that expands the concept of self-driving cars into self-driving rooms.The self-driving room is known as Tridika. It is co-developed by Charles Bombardier and his company Imaginactive and Ashish Thulkar, a vehicle designer at the Indian Institute of Science.The Tridika can be configured into a car-setting or an office, depending on the user’s liking. It is completely driverless and works like a maglev train, with the magnets elevates and propels the box.It would become attached to the other wall of the building by a ramp, which lifts it up in front of the user’s apartment unit. The door of the apartment unit would open once detects the Tridika.There’s no known date or plan for whether this concept would become a reality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 14:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/16/3226328/3226328_2F001CE21A53441AA0CE916DC33F4907_161207_3226328_Self_driving_apartment_rooms__Tridika_maglev_tra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F9F/9C6/F9F9C6CCB2E248EDB7E0F9E95415365E_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tridika,self-driving rooms,self-driving living room,self-driving cars,technology,future technology,imaginactive,science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226317</guid>
      <title>Google drones: Chipotle &amp; Google to test burrito-delivering drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLACKSBURG, VIRGINIA  Virginia Tech looks set to become the dream school for every food-loving college student, as flying burrito deliveries could soon be a reality on campus.Bloomberg reports that the Project Wing division of Google’s parent company, Alphabet Inc., has teamed up with Chipotle to test drone deliveries at Virginia Tech.  The experimental service began this month and will be running for a few weeks, though it’s currently limited to a selected group of school employees, students, and other recruits. Burritos, the only item on the menu, are prepared by workers at a nearby food truck. They’re packaged and loaded onto a drone.  The drone then flies the order to a pickup area and slowly  lowers it to the ground.According to the Roanoke Times, the drones carried the meals for a short distance only about a tenth of a mile. Around 10 order were reportedly delivered in a span of 30 minutes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 14:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/15/3226317/3226317_22435F12A4504B09A4EC4094E3EC5F8C_161207_3226317_Google_drones__Chipotle___Google_to_test_burrito_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F23/784/F23784ED541D4834A7BD8031B5205BDB_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Drone delivery,burrito delivery,burrito drone delivery,burrito drone,chipotle delivery,chipotle burrito,project wing,google drone,unmanned aircraft,automated aircraft,drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226315</guid>
      <title>Self-driving shopping carts: Walmart patents completely unnecessary technology</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BENTONVILLE, ARKANSAS  Walmart has received a patent last week for its self-driving shopping carts system.According to the US Patent & Trademark Office, the shopping carts will be equipped with detachable motors with video cameras and sensors. Customers can request a cart using a user interface device, potentially a smartphone.Supermarket employees usually have to round up abandoned carts. With the new system, the carts will be able to return to the docking station automatically. The carts can also be used to restock products that are low in stock.It is not yet known when or where the new system will be applied in Walmart supermarkets.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 14:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/15/3226315/3226315_9343BB3E90AB4BDDA2FE1AAF473E5C9E_161207_3226315_Self_driving_shopping_carts__Walmart_patents_com_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/724/75E/72475EED26724821A5FDF226508767AF_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Walmart,walmart self-driving shopping carts,self-driving shopping carts,walmart robotic shopping carts,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226311</guid>
      <title>Marijuana breathalyzer test: THC breathalyzer &#x2018;The Hound&#x2019; tested on California drivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OAKLAND, CALIFORNIA  A breathalyzer to help law enforcement police marijuana smoking drivers is being tested in California.The marijuana breathalyzer, named The Hound, is put to use when a police officer pulls over a driver who is observed to be driving erratically. The driver blows into a tube in the device, twice and indicates that it has enough breath for testing purposes. A chemical analysis then locates and isolate the THC molecules in the sample. Once the process is complete, the test results THC levels measured in parts per trillion or picograms  are displayed on the screen.Drivers tested in California were not arrested or charged, but those who did test positive for THC were not allowed to continue driving, reported RT. Hound Labs, the company behind the device, is aiming to distribute the devices to law enforcement across the U.S. during the first half of 2017.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 14:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/15/3226311/3226311_6909D664E8614C8FB87EF3223685C89D_161207_3226311_Marijuana_breathalyzer_test__THC_breathalyzer____2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/295/F6C/295F6CF85A6C473DBD7F2C5A775614D9_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Marijuana breathalyzer,thc breathalyzer,cannabis,marijuana,weed breathalyzer,the hound,hound labs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226309</guid>
      <title>Fire-fighting drones: New York Fire Dep&#x2019;t will deploy drones to scope out fires</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  New York’s fire department will have a new set of eyes and ears atop the city in the weeks to come. The NYFD is currently testing out drones to help firefighters on the ground get a better look at how to fight fires before sending in humans. The $85,000 drones, painted fire-engine red, weigh roughly eight pounds. The drones can move in the up and down directions, and can toggle 360 degrees to adjust viewpoint. They will each have a 200-foot tether attached so to prevent it from getting stuck. From high up in the sky, they can capture both standard video and infrared images, which are then transmitted to a portable command center on the ground, so firefighters can see what they’re up against. It takes two firefighters to operate each dronea pilot to man the controls, and an observer to keep the area clear. The first drone will be deployed in the coming weeks, followed by two more before the end of the year.The idea to send out drones was hatched after the deadly 2014 gas explosion in East Harlem, when an amateur drone operator flew his drone in to help firefighters get pictures of the damaged site.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 14:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/14/3226309/3226309_21DEAE4EF112429F82063D64AF2746B8_161207_3226309_Fire_fighting_drones__New_York_Fire_Dep___t_will_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CB0/8F6/CB08F65A53A040A99E65B1F22D1212FF_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NYFD drone,firefighting drones,drone fire,New York drones,best drone footage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226306</guid>
      <title>ISIS in Germany: Sleeper cell suspects arrested in German refugee camps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERLIN  German authorities have arrested three Syrian refugees with suspected ties to Islamic State in a series of pre-dawn operations on September 13.The three men, Mahir al-H, 17, Mohamed A., 26 and Ibrahim M., 18, allegedly received fake passports, mobile phones with pre-installed communication programme and four-figure cash sums in US dollars from ISIS. The 17-year-old is said to have received trainings in Raqqa, ISIS stronghold in Syria.The men travelled to Germany through Turkey and Greece. They were arrested in refugee shelters in the northern state of Schleswig-Holstein.German authorities said the three might not have received concrete missions from ISIS so far and they could be a unit of ‘sleeper cell’ that remain dormant until further instructions.According to the BBC, the men entered Europe with the help of the same organization that trafficked the three suicide bombers outside the Stade de France national football stadium in Paris on November 13, last year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 14:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/14/3226306/3226306_66E1D974C193489A9DEFA47074975C5D_161207_3226306_ISIS_in_Germany__Sleeper_cell_suspects_arrested__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5F5/955/5F5955A1B1514C46AEA2B74C5AC9D0D3_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[ISIS crisis,Germany syrian refugees,syrian refugees in europe,syrian refugees isis,germany arrests isis,isis crisis in europe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226305</guid>
      <title>China to launch Tiangong-2 space station next week</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China will send its second space lab, Tiangong-2 into space next week, part of its strategy to create a manned space station that is expected to be in service around 2022.According to CCTV America, Tiangong-2 will orbit 393 kilometers above the earth. The Shenzhou 11 spacecraft, carrying two astronauts, will dock with Tiangong-2 in October. The cargo ship Tianzhou-1 will dock with Tiangong-2 next year to resupply the space station.Tiangong-2 is expected to monitor the earth while conducting conducting scientific experiments. It will also measure the topography of the oceans in order to study earth’s gravitational field, the TeCake reported.China’s first space laboratory, Tiangong-1, was launched in 2011 and has been in good working condition ever since.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 14:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/14/3226305/3226305_75B6B64BFF9D44A28296978849B57825_161207_3226305_China_to_launch_Tiangong_2_space_station_next_we_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6EB/905/6EB905FCBDC346F1974570390994A4BF_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[tiangong-2,tiangong-1,shenzhou-11,tianzhou-1,china,chinese space station,space,space station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226304</guid>
      <title>New York to grow 50,000 oysters on recycled toilets to clean up polluted Jamaica Bay</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  New York has teamed up with the Billion Oyster Project to embed 50,000 oysters in Jamaica Bay with the use of recycled toilets.The New York/New Jersey Harbor Estuary was once filled with oysters, but due to over harvesting, dredging and pollution, the bivalves died out in the area.Oysters are considered keystone species. A single oyster can filter as much as 50 gallons of water a day, removing chemicals and other pollutants. And oyster reefs stabilize shorelines, prevent erosion and act as a buffer against hurricanes and tropical storms.New York City and the Billion Oyster project will build one central donor oyster bed with 50,000 adult and spat-on-shell oysters, along with four receiver beds. Oysters normally embed themselves on old shells. With oysters extinct in the harbor for sometime, officials are utilizing a mixture of introduced oyster and clam shells along with old toilets, broken into small pieces, to help create a foundation on which new oysters will cling  at least for the four smaller beds.Once the oyster installation is complete, water quality will be monitored for future improvements. The beds will also be evaluated for the recruitment of new oysters. The project is being funded with a $1 million grant from the U.S. Department of Interior, administered by the National Fish and Wildlife Foundation. New York City’s Department of Environmental Protection is contributing $375,000. The Billion Oyster Project and students from the Urban Assembly New York Harbor School are assisting with the installation and monitoring of the oyster beds.The project is coordinated by the New York Harbor School and aims to restore one billion live oysters to New York harbor by 2030.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 14:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/14/3226304/3226304_E85B7C20E1594934A84C80EFC69F7FC9_161207_3226304_New_York_to_grow_50_000_oysters_on_recycled_toil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F89/037/F890377A3D8F47A8BE0D745E288A95A9_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[New york,jamaica bay,oyster,oysters,oyster farm,oyster habitat,oyster rehabilitation,billion oyster project,Bill de Blasio,Department of Environmental Protection,oyster beds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226294</guid>
      <title>Chinese billionaire hiding 6% of world&#x2019;s aluminium in Mexico desert to game NAFTA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN JOSE ITURBIDE, MEXICO  One of China’s richest men has been linked to a massive stockpile of aluminum in the Mexican desert that U.S. aluminum executives say is part of a scheme to game the global trade system, according to a report in the Wall Street Journal.The stockpile was discovered two years ago when aluminum executive Jeff Henderson hired a pilot to shoot aerial photos of a factory near the town of San Jose Iturbide, 500 miles south of the Mexican border with Texas, the Wall Street Journal reported.There, the pilot found a stockpile of nearly one million metric tons of aluminum, or roughly 6 percent of the world’s total inventory, according to the the Wall Street Journal’s report.Rerouting Chinese aluminum through Mexico into the U.S. allows Chinese companies to benefit from the North American Free Trade Agreement between Canada, Mexico and the U.S., which eliminates most of the tariffs on products traded among the three countries.According to the Wall Street Journal, Chinese billionaire Liu Zhongtian, the chairman of China Zhongwang Holdings, has denied the allegations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 14:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/13/3226294/3226294_A49A37142BB14FE98373D4361BE58595_161207_3226294_Chinese_billionaire_hiding_6__of_world___s_alumi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A03/395/A03395EEBF814152AFB092FA82B03D51_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Aluminium stockpile in mexico,san jose iturbide aluminium,china aluminium exports,china zhongwang holdings,liu zhongtian,nafta]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226292</guid>
      <title>Blue Origin: Crew escape system text could destroy rocket in next test launch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EL PASO, TEXAS  Private space company Blue Origin will be conducting its next round of testing on its New Shepard rocket in October.The reusable rocket is designed to take paying passengers to the edge of space. New Shepard consists of a crew capsule that can carry up to six passengers and a rocket booster. Once near its destination, the capsule separates from the booster. The capsule will then deploy its parachutes and sail down back to earth, while the booster will deploy its drag brakes and refire its engine making a vertical landing. Blue Origin has already successfully completed four test flights of its rocket booster. The fifth test to be held at the company’s testing facility in West Texas, near El Paso, will check its emergency escape system during flight.The New Shepard’s capsule is equipped with a rocket motor that will fire for two seconds should the booster fail after launch. The motor will quickly separate the capsule from the booster. Once away, the capsule will undergo its standard descent pattern. Blue Origin has already tested the system on the ground, but has yet to experiment during flight. At about 45 seconds after launch, when the New Shepard is at 16,000 feet up, the company will intentionally start the capsule’s escape sequence.Unfortunately, if the emergency testing succeeds, firing the rocket motor could possibly destroy the rocket booster.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 14:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/13/3226292/3226292_2722762190024F2194D2976DFCD4CE3A_161207_3226292_Blue_Origin__Crew_escape_system_text_could_destr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/941/C84/941C84D83B404670B0993E4608D81284_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Blue origin,space,rocket,space travel,blue origin space,blue origin landing,blue origin rocket,blue origin rocket landing,new shepard,blue origin new shepard,blue origin launch and landing,rocket test,escape system,rocket escape system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226289</guid>
      <title>Dolphins can speak and use words almost like humans, say researchers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FEODOSIA, CRIMEA  For decades, we’ve known dolphins were one of the more intelligent species on the planet, but new research may reveal they share a level of communication similar to our own. At the Karadag Nature Reserve in Russian-held Crimea, scientists used an underwater microphone to record the speech patterns between two Black Sea bottlenose dolphins. Expressing themselves with a series of whistles and clicks, the subjects, Yasha and Yana, were found to adjust the volume and frequency of each sound, forming individual words and sentences.In addition, the researchers also noticed the dolphins would take turns speaking, waiting for each other to finish their messaging without interruption, which may indicate they were listening.Yasha and Yana were found to create sentences of up to five words, though they have not deciphered the content of the conversations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 14:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/13/3226289/3226289_CE2163B859974E61A3393DDEEECA8AB8_161207_3226289_Dolphins_can_speak_and_use_words_almost_like_hum_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D58/F86/D58F868302E04BECA33B7A06CFA39AA0_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dolphin conversations,dolphins talking,dolphins communicating,Karadag Nature Reserve,black sea bottlenose dolphins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226284</guid>
      <title>Vision van: Mercedes-Benz unveils drone delivery cargo van that is operated by robots</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STUTTGART, GERMANY  German automaker Mercedes-Benz has unveiled an electric van equipped with package delivery drones.The Vision Van is an electric vehicle with a range of up to 270 km. Its rooftop serves as a launch and landing pad for Matternet M2 drones, which can carry a package of 4.4 pounds.All packages are scanned and sorted by robots before loading on to the van by a driverless handling vehicle. The onboard robotic shelving system then automatically locate and prepare the packages for the drone or the driver inside the cargo compartment.The van is installed with innovative algorithms that can calculate the best delivery route for the driver, who would steer the van using a joystick.The company said it will continue to explore the opportunities of innovative van-related business therefore it created a new organisational unit called Future Transportation Systems, which involve research teams in Stuttgart, Berlin and Silicon Valley.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/12/3226284/3226284_76B0E6BB633A45749ECBBAE9E065B4A4_161207_3226284_Vision_van__Mercedes_Benz_unveils_drone_delivery_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/45F/19E/45F19E81328944CF830786F6542B7701_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mercedes-benz vision van,vision van,innovative van mercedes-benz,mercedes-benz innovative cars,vision van with drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226280</guid>
      <title>Staying cool: Stanford scientists develop new clothing material to keep the body cool</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA  Scientists at Stanford University have developed a material that can help the skin stay cooler than conventional fabrics.According to the university, a material known as nanopolyethylene has pores that measure 50 to 1,000 nanometers across. It allows the heat emitted from the body by infrared radiation to pass through while it is also able to reflect 99% of visible light.Cotton clothing, though good at reflecting visible light, only allows 1.5 percent of infrared waves to penetrate, meaning most of the body heat is either absorbed by the fabric or reflected back onto skin. Polyethylene clothing allows infrared waves to penetrate but it also allows most visible light to penetrate as well.Experiments show nanopolyethylene is able to keep the skin much cooler than cotton or polyethylene.“If you can cool the person rather than the building where they work or live, that will save energy,” Yi Cui, associate professor of materials science and engineering at Stanford and of photon science at SLAC National Accelerator Laboratory was quoted in the university's press release.The scientists are working on adding more colors, textures and cloth-like characteristics to the material to make it ready for the textile industry.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 14:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/12/3226280/3226280_B23402B335FE4F578E75F7A3017276F0_161207_3226280_Staying_cool__Stanford_scientists_develop_new_cl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/564/DDD/564DDD5BAD584984A9C9807601C963C7_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Stanford university,cool clothing fabric,nanopolyethylene,climate change,clothing material to make body cool,extreme weather]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226277</guid>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Note 7 explodes due to manufacturing error</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA   The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration has advised passengers not to turn on or charge Samsung Galaxy Note 7 smartphones on aircraft, after faulty battery packs caused some of the phones to explode while charging.Due to the battery crisis, Samsung was forced to recall 2.5 million units of the Galaxy Note 7, its new flagship phablet.The faulty battery packs were made by Samsung SDI, a subsidiary of Samsung. Samsung has indicated it will no longer use Samsung SDI batteries in the Note 7.According to the Wall Street Journal, roughly 65 percent of Galaxy Note 7 batteries were made by Samsung SDI. Thirty-five percent were made by Chinese company Amperex Technology Limited, or ATL.The Samsung SDI batteries in the Note 7 were found to have faulty separators, which allow the two electrodes to touch. This redirects energy to chemicals called electrolytes, which help to conduct the current.When the battery is hot, the electrolytes react with other chemicals to release gas in a feedback loop called “thermal runaway,” which can lead to a fire.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/11/3226277/3226277_B39BEC8F090744B0A8D4BF38ED8AF603_161207_3226277_Samsung_Galaxy_Note_7_explodes_due_to_manufactur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1DF/184/1DF18400CC71441884C5269BF4C95309_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Samsung galaxy note 7 explodes,galaxy note 7 explosion,samsung smartphone explodes,samsung,samsung sdi batteries,galaxy note 7 batteries,smartphone explodes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226267</guid>
      <title>Google self-driving cars will be able to yield or pull over for police vehicles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  Google has submitted a new patent as part of its self-driving car project for technology that will allow cars to yield to emergency and police vehicles.In the patent that was submitted in 2014, but published earlier this month, Google outlined the need for its self-driving cars to be able to respond appropriately to emergency and police vehicles. Google plans on outfitting its cars with scanners that will be able to detect and identify light sources, colors and patterns. When a Google self-driving car is on the road, one or more computing devices will allow it to detect light and identify if that light is stationary, like that of a street light, or moving, like those on vehicles. It will then determine if the light is flashing. Should the light be both moving and flashing, the Google car will then identify the colors and pattern of flashing lights. Emergency and police vehicles have different light and patterns. Police vehicles also utilize unique patterns for various offenses. Based on the patterns of lights, the Google car can make the appropriate maneuver, such as yield to an ambulance or stop completely for a police vehicle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 14:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/10/3226267/3226267_58E9719E2FED477189CE81DC08A7EDBB_161207_3226267_Google_self_driving_cars_will_be_able_to_yield_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6F0/621/6F062112E3B34038ADCD93B06109BFFD_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Google,google self driving car,self driving car,patent,us patent,us patent and trademark office,police lights,ambulance lights,emergency vehicles,google self driving car project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226257</guid>
      <title>Plane lands in wrong country: AirAsia X flight to KL lands in Melbourne after nav error</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  An Australian aviation investigation report has revealed how an AirAsia X flight bound for Malaysia last year accidentally flew to Melbourne instead of its Asian hub after a navigational error.The AirAsia X Airbus A330 was scheduled to fly from Sydney to Kuala Lumpur.Australian authorities say the plane’s captain manually copied the gate coordinates displayed on a sign outside the cockpit window into the flight management guidance system. As he accidentally omitted a zero, the system located the plane near Cape Town, South Africa.Both the captain and the first officer heard several chimes as they prepared for takeoff. They chose to ignore the alerts because there were no other abnormal indications.Immediately after takeoff, an audible alert sounded, warning of terrain in the plane’s flightpath. Not seeing any obstacles, the pilots ignored the warning.The plane had already deviated from its supposed departure flight path and crossed the paths of other aircraft.An airport traffic control officer noticed the deviation and contacted the pilots. Only then did they realize the GPS error on their navigation display. The pilots requested permission to abort the flight and return to Sydney airport, but were unable to turn back due to deteriorating weather.The captain then accepted the alternative route to Melbourne and manually flew the plane to the new destination.AirAsia X told CNN that all of its aircraft have since been equipped with upgraded flight management systems to avoid repeating a similar mistake.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 13:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/09/3226257/3226257_020B98344DAD4AA3AD973F83DD6566C5_161207_3226257_Plane_lands_in_wrong_country__AirAsia_X_flight_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0CD/0AE/0CD0AE3094624C3EAFA77DF71B18EA69_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Airasia x flight melbourne,airasia x flight sydney,airasia x,flight navigational error,airasia x airbus a330,sydney airport,flight incidents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226232</guid>
      <title>USA vs Russia: Russian jet fighter comes within 10 feet of U.S. spy plane over Black Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  A Russian fighter jet got too close for comfort when it intercepted a U.S. Navy spy plane over the Black Sea yesterday.U.S. defense officials labeled the move “unsafe and unprofessional”, and warned the 19-minute long incident could escalate tensions between the two countries, ABC News reported.The U.S. and Russia are at loggerheads over Syria and the Ukraine and this latest flashpoint suggests they’re unlikely to be on good terms anytime soon.The U.S. Navy P-8A spy plane was buzzed by a Russian SU-27 “Flanker-B” fighter jet as it flew in international airspace over the Black Sea.At first the Russian jet maintained a distance of about 30 feet but it then passed within 10 feet of the U.S. plane, and that’s what got U.S. military chiefs so pissed.The U.S. pilot tried to contact the Russian jet but got no response, U.S. defense officials said.Russian defense officials admitted sending fighter jets to intercept the U.S. plane, Reuters reported.They claim the U.S. aircraft was close to the Russian border and had turned off its transponders, which are needed to ID the plane.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 13:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/08/3226232/3226232_21F0D9C72D75426BA4941EF81A613774_161207_3226232_USA_vs_Russia__Russian_jet_fighter_comes_within__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/615/CA4/615CA403717C48A8B9C61E5B1BDC03C7_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Russian jet intercepts US plane,usa vs russia,us v russia,cold war,new cold war,russia vs usa,russian air force,sukhoi su27]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226228</guid>
      <title>Plane lands in wrong country: AirAsia X flight to KL lands in Melbourne after nav error</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  An Australian aviation investigation report has revealed how an AirAsia X flight bound for Malaysia last year accidentally flew to Melbourne instead of its Asian hub after a navigational error.The AirAsia X Airbus A330 was scheduled to fly from Sydney to Kuala Lumpur.Australian authorities say the plane’s captain manually copied the gate coordinates displayed on a sign outside the cockpit window into the flight management guidance system. As he accidentally omitted a zero, the system located the plane near Cape Town, South Africa.Both the captain and the first officer heard several chimes as they prepared for takeoff. They chose to ignore the alerts because there were no other abnormal indications.Immediately after takeoff, an audible alert sounded, warning of terrain in the plane’s flightpath. Not seeing any obstacles, the pilots ignored the warning.The plane had already deviated from its supposed departure flight path and crossed the paths of other aircraft.An airport traffic control officer noticed the deviation and contacted the pilots. Only then did they realize the GPS error on their navigation display. The pilots requested permission to abort the flight and return to Sydney airport, but were unable to turn back due to deteriorating weather.The captain then accepted the alternative route to Melbourne and manually flew the plane to the new destination.AirAsia X told CNN that all of its aircraft have since been equipped with upgraded flight management systems to avoid repeating a similar mistake.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 13:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/08/3226228/3226228_0EB1263BEE6449BCB67B3BEEEEDABD5E_161207_3226228_Plane_lands_in_wrong_country__AirAsia_X_flight_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AA9/55A/AA955AE01DEA4DF59C595EE2CDD1B8FA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Airasia x flight melbourne,airasia x flight sydney,airasia x,flight navigational error,airasia x airbus a330,sydney airport,flight incidents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226219</guid>
      <title>Life on Earth could have started with a planetary smashup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON  Researchers at Rice University suggest that life on Earth as we know it could have been a result of a planetary smashup between our planet and an embryonic planet similar to Mercury some 4.5 billion years ago.Researchers at the lab, which specializes in recreating the high-pressure and high-temperature conditions that exist deep inside Earth and other rocky planets, recently published a study exploring how carbon came to this planet.Most scientists agree that about 4.5 billion years ago, Earth was covered with hot magma. As it cooled, most of the heavier metals near the surface sank deep into the planet. The theory is that the iron alloys bonded with carbon and sulfur, pulling both into the planet’s core. Any remaining carbon would have vaporized into space due to the extreme heat. Researchers at Rice University believe that the only way carbon and sulfur can remain near the surface is from an alternative, perhaps alien, source. To prove  or rather disprove, their theory, via the scientific method, they conducted experiments to gauge how sulfur or silicon might alter the affinity of iron for carbon.They looked to other celestial bodies like that of Mercury, which has a core that is thought to be relatively silicon-rich, or Mars, which has a core rich in sulfur.The experiments revealed that carbon could be excluded from the core  and relegated to the silicate mantle  if the iron alloys in the core were rich in either silicon or sulfur. They believe if a planetary smashup between another embryonic planet with either a silicon- or sulfur-rich core and Earth had occurred, the other planet’s core would have gone directly to the core of Earth, and the carbon-rich mantle would have mixed with our planet’s.The new carbon introduced to the Earth’s mantle would eventually float up to the surface, solidifying the crust. There, it bonded with other elements to form complex organic compounds: the building blocks of life.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 13:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/07/3226219/3226219_7EA18B45285A41ACB325591CB3C934E4_161207_3226219_Life_on_Earth_could_have_started_with_a_planetar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/467/897/4678971A3C034744839DD730DD557B08_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Science,earth,planetary smashup,colliding planets,life,life on earth,carbon,building blocks of life,how life started,mercury,mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226218</guid>
      <title>Climate change: Typhoons are getting stronger in East and Southeast Asia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHAPEL HILL, NORTH CAROLINA  New research shows typhoons in East and Southeast Asia are becoming stronger, and look set to continue to intensify.“Typhoons can cause very severe damage in human society. An important factor in determining the damage is intensity and also the size of the storm,” Wei Mei, lead author of the study and an assistant professor at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, told the Verge.The study notes that ocean waters off the coasts of East and Southeast Asia became significantly warmer and the typhoons in the region have also become much stronger.Typhoons intensify when passing through warm waters as they provide more heat energy.According to the study, the typhoons that hit East and Southeast Asia have intensified by up to 15 percent in the last 37 years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 13:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/07/3226218/3226218_4C68B1392F264BCC9DABBC021F9F8A0C_161207_3226218_Climate_change__Typhoons_are_getting_stronger_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D47/B2D/D47B2DFB211945EB9676258D76B1B730_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Typhoons,typhoon in asia,typhoon lionrock,typhoon in asia intensifies,typhoon study,climate change,rising ocean temperature]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226215</guid>
      <title>Could anti-inflammatory drugs be used to treat depression and Alzheimer&#x2019;s?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  A group of scientists in the United Kingdom is investigating whether targeting the immune system could treat mood disorders and neurodegenerative diseases.The researchers, a working group named Neuroimmunology of Mood Disorders and Alzheimer’s Disease, have discovered possible links between inflammation and mood disorders, suggesting that they could be treated with anti-inflammatory drugs.Inflammation is the body’s biological response to injury or infection. If not properly controlled, it can lead to diseases such as rheumatoid arthritis.The researchers have discovered a large number of people with rheumatoid arthritis also suffer from depression. It is possible that inflammatory chemicals interrupt the brain’s production of serotonin, a key neurotransmitter linked to mood.Scientists are investigating whether targeting the immune system could treat mood disorders, such as depression and neurodegenerative diseases including Alzheimer’s disease.  The precise type of inflammation that may cause mood disorders and the anti-inflammatory drugs best suited to treating it still under research.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 13:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/07/3226215/3226215_5EA5F21CF50F43C881FC88CCCD2182BB_161207_3226215_Could_anti_inflammatory_drugs_be_used_to_treat_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C15/ED3/C15ED3D9698442D7A371E648E6E17A16_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Anti-inflammatory,drugs,depression,Alzheimer’s,ageing,ibuprofen]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226213</guid>
      <title>Future of warfare: British navy tests unmanned robot spy speedboat drone in London</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  An experimental robot speedboat drone was unveiled by the British navy in tests on London’s River Thames on Monday.The prototype Maritime Autonomy Surface Testbed (MAST) drone can be sailed by a pilot, remote control or be programmed to operate on its own, the Telegraph reported.The vessel weighs 2 tons, is 34 feet long and 9 1/2 feet wide. It can reach top speeds of more than 50 knots.The speedboat drone has a collision avoidance system and sensors, which help it to avoid other vessels.Much of the technology on board the vessel remains top secret. However, sources told the Telegraph the tests could lead to a new generation of robotic vessels designed to track or spy on enemy boats.British military bosses fearful of legal challenges and public opinion are unsure about arming unmanned speedboats, defense experts told the Telegraph.The British navy will host a competition called Unmanned Warrior next month in which the MAST speedboats will battle it out with more than 40 other maritime drone systems.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 13:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/06/3226213/3226213_D26DD2FADB8A40B6B060CE51C8DA3805_161207_3226213_Future_of_warfare__British_navy_tests_unmanned_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/962/C36/962C3667577B4D3F90965EF18B4E61CA_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Speedboat drone,drone,drones,future of warfare,robot,navy robot,navy drone,drone boat,future tech,navy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226209</guid>
      <title>Zika virus: six ways to protect yourself against the dreaded virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  With Zika continuing to spread across the globe, here are some useful tips for protecting yourself from the dreaded virus.There are a number of ways to minimize the risk of contracting the Zika virus. If possible, avoid traveling to areas with reported cases of Zika. When possible, remain in air conditioned places, and make sure to shut screens on windows and doors. When heading to areas where you may be vulnerable to infection, spray insect repellant on any exposed skin. In addition, it is advisable to keep your body covered as best you can, with pants and long-sleeved shirts.Pregnant women should always use protection when engaging in sexual intercourse. Abstaining is the only way to eliminate the possibility of contracting the virus from sex.Lastly, when going to bed, use mosquito nets to protect against infected mosquitos attacking while you’re asleep.In the United States, the Centre for Disease Control and Prevention has reported 2,722 cases of the Zika virus as of August 31.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 13:27:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/04/3226209/3226209_F01894E0601B4512A2B573178ED43D59_161207_3226209_Zika_virus__six_ways_to_protect_yourself_against_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/46B/A6E/46BA6EF7AFB44A2AB0FD3E5D641C8471_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Zika virus,how to protect against zika,cdc,zika protection,brazil zika,zika in the us]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226206</guid>
      <title>Promessa and EcoLegacy turn human remains into plant food with alternative burial process</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GOTHENBURG, SWEDEN  A Swedish and an Irish company have been developing and providing new forms of burial.Promessa Organic from Sweden, led by biologist Susanne Wiigh-Mäsak, has developed what they’ve called Promession, a method by which the human body is converted into powder, dried and eventually turned into organic matter that converts into soil within a year.Similar to the process of freeze drying, promession involves a system called the Promator in which the body is first frozen to minus 18 degrees Celsius and submerged in liquid nitrogen. The body is refrozen as the liquid nitrogen evaporates into harmless gas.The brittle body then is vibrated and transformed into organic powder. The powder is taken to a vacuum-sealed chamber where water is evaporated. Afterwards, mercury, allegan, sodium and over 50 other foreign substances are removed. The remains are packed into an organic coffin and buried at the family’s request. After a year, the remains turn into soil, which can feed a tree.The company has also developed an improved “clean cremation” where the dry and metal free remains that exit the Promator system are burned. This clean cremation can guarantee Zero Mercury and avoid the production of dioxins. Irish company EcoLegacy offers a similar burial service. Their process, which they’ve called EcoLation, is similar to Promession, except the energy that is expelled in the process is turned into energy reused in future processes. Both processes differ and are more ecologically friendly than traditional burial and cremation. In traditional burial, coffins and chemicals (formaldehyde) are introduced into the environment. In cremation, heat energy is consumed and toxins are released to reduce the body into ashes, which are waste products that contain no organic material.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 13:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/02/3226206/3226206_9690FE68DD5340A5A80011CE982C7EAE_161207_3226206_Promessa_and_EcoLegacy_turn_human_remains_into_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7CA/86A/7CA86AF003F845A89EB385B0E4A0E5C1_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Promessa,promession,burial,promessa organic,promator,ecological burial,environmentally friendly,cremation,Susanne Wiigh-Masak,ecolegacy,organic,organic burial]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226203</guid>
      <title>New drug aducanumab may be key to preventing Alzheimer&#x2019;s disease</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  Early results from a clinical trial show a new Alzheimer’s disease treatment  a drug called aducanumab  may alleviate memory loss.Cambridge, Massachusetts-based company Biogen developed the drug and funded the study, which tested aducanumab’s safety in humans and was not designed to test for cerebral benefits. The test measured brain activity of 165 participants, some of whom received the drug once a month for up to 54 weeks, while others received a placebo. Of those that received the drug, 103 experienced a reduction in the amount of tangled amyloid-β, the toxic proteins thought to trigger Alzheimer’s, in their brains. When injected into early-stage Alzheimer’s patients, one or two in every thousand of the antibodies enter the brain where they latch on to wayward amyloid-β proteins. Researchers believe that other cells called microglia then arrive and clear the aberrant proteins from the brain.Scientists have debated for years whether the buildup of amyloid-β causes memory loss and other symptoms of Alzheimer’s. The trial’s results were in favour of the “amyloid hypothesis,” which suggests that elimination of the protein itself might alleviate the disease’s symptoms.Two larger phase III trials are now in progress, and planned to run until at least 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 13:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/02/3226203/3226203_4640B578A2CB4FD985EFA24B6528900D_161207_3226203_New_drug_aducanumab_may_be_key_to_preventing_Alz_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/290/59B/29059B74A0A54A7BA94F0689BE6FCEDC_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Alzheimer’s,alzheimer’s disease,biogen,amyloid,aducanumab,clinical trials,alzheimer’s clinical trials,amyloid-beta,amyloid hypothesis,memory,memory loss,medicine,medical,dementia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226196</guid>
      <title>SpaceX explosion: Falcon 9 rocket blows up in flames, destroys Facebook satellite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA  Facebook head honcho Mark Zuckerberg must be pissed with his SpaceX counterpart Elon Musk after a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket carrying a satellite that FB was planning to use exploded on the launch pad.The blast occurred as the rocket was being fueled on Thursday, but the cause of the explosion was not immediately known, Reuters reported.The SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket is designed to transport satellites and spacecraft into space. It has nine first-stage engines, which can sustain two engine shutdowns during flight without compromising the mission, according to SpaceX.The second stage delivers the payload into orbit. Its single engine can be reignited several times to send multiple payloads into space.The first stage of the rocket is designed to return to Earth so it can be reused. Rocket burns decelerate the Falcon 9 before four landing legs deploy.The Falcon 9 that exploded on Thursday was carrying an Amos-6 satellite, which Facebook planned to use to boost internet connectivity in Africa. The $62 million Falcon 9 rocket was due to launch on Saturday.Mark Zuckerberg wrote on Facebook that he was ‘deeply disappointed’ by the mission’s failure.And, Elon Musk aside, he definitely won’t be the only one.Facebook is a customer of Israeli company Spacecom, which owns the Amos-6 satellite.It remains to be seen if the blast will scupper Spacecom’s $285 million sale to a Chinese company, which was announced last week, according to Reuters.Conditions attached to the deal said the satellite had to be launched successfully and complete in-orbit tests. Whoops!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 13:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/02/3226196/3226196_FF84C678AE3F4F5297E69A7F886F2466_161207_3226196_SpaceX_explosion__Falcon_9_rocket_blows_up_in_fl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/65E/964/65E9645ED6F1489D89DB28646DD4DDAC_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[spaceX,spaceX explosion,falcon 9,spacex explodes,spacex rocket explosion,spacex blows up,spacex explosion 2016]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226194</guid>
      <title>North Korea abductions: Missing Mormon missionary taken to Pyongyang to teach Kim Jong Un</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA  A former Mormon missionary from Utah who disappeared in China 12 years ago was abducted by North Korea and forced to serve as Kim Jong Un’s personal English tutor, according to reports.David Sneddon now works as an English teacher in Pyongyang, is married to a North Korean woman and has two children, according to South Korea’s Abductees' Family Union.The startling claims were made by the union’s president, the Daily Telegraph reported, citing a report by Yahoo News Japan.Sneddon, then aged 24, was last seen hiking in the Tiger Leaping Gorge in China’s Yunnan province in 2004. He was in the country to study Mandarin. Sneddon was already fluent in Korean, which he learned during a Mormon mission to South Korea.According to Chinese authorities, Sneddon likely died in a hiking accident, but his family back in Utah aren’t buying that explanation. They believe the revelations that he was abducted and taken to North Korea.Yunnan province is along the path of a so-called underground railroad used by North Korean refugees to escape to third countries. North Korean agents are believed to operate in the area with China’s blessing, according to a website set up by the Sneddon family to help find their son.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 13:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/02/3226194/3226194_3ECCA40A1D034ED3B77F540CDEB6BF61_161207_3226194_North_Korea_abductions__Missing_Mormon_missionar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/628/5CD/6285CD379B3F4C7F92451CB52EFC2679_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[North korea abductions,david sneddon,kim jong-un,kim jong un,north korea kidnap,weird north korea,crazy north korea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226192</guid>
      <title>Zika in America: First local mosquitoes infected with the virus found in Miami Beach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI BEACH  Officials finally have conclusive proof that insects in the continental U.S. are carrying Zika, after infected mosquitoes were found in Florida.The Florida Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services announced in a press release on Thursday that three mosquito samples taken from a 1.5 square mile affected area in Miami Beach had tested positive for the Zika virus. Miami Beach is one of two Zika-affected areas in Miami-Dade County, the other being Wynwood, which first reported infections in July. According to the Florida Department of Health, 49 locally-transmitted Zika cases have been confirmed in the state thus far, while 576 others contracted infections while traveling outside the state. Another 80 cases involved pregnant women.Only one in five infected people show no symptoms, which include rashes, joint pain, fever, and red eyes. The virus has more often been linked with birth defects like microcephaly in babies.The new discovery has state authorities stepping up Zika prevention efforts, with Governor Rick Scott pushing for aerial spraying in the area.But with Hurricane Hermine blowing through Florida, not only will measures be delayed, the aftermath will most likely create more enhanced breeding grounds for the mosquitoes, reports Reuters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 12:58:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/02/3226192/3226192_BDB24B7C2D2947E49911617306A4DA48_161207_3226192_Zika_in_America__First_local_mosquitoes_infected_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/341/B69/341B696A7B30486B8A719AAD84F38495_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Zika in america,zika in florida,zika virus,zika outbreak,zika mosquitoes,zika infected mosquitoes,microcephaly,mosquitoes,miami beach,florida,wynwood,zika zone,zika hotspot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3225669</guid>
      <title>FAA rules for commercial drones go into effect</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The United States Federal Aviation Administration’s rules for the commercial use of drones officially took effect on August 29. Here are the key things to know.To fly commercial drones, one must be at least 16 years old, possess a remote pilot airman certificate, and must pass TSA vetting.Drones weighing between half a pound and 55 pounds may be registered online. Drones heavier than 55 pounds require special registration.Drones may not fly higher than 400 feet, and only during daylight hours.They also may not fly faster than 100 miles per hour, must be keep within the operator’s visual range at all times, are prohibited from flying over people, and may not be operated from a moving vehicle. Drones must also yield to manned aircraft.NASA expects commercially flown drones will account for around 40 percent of all small drones in operation by 2019, tech site ZDNet reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/01/3225669/3225669_FA9C21A9CFE24D00AF5438FC3F3040EA_161207_3225669_FAA_rules_for_commercial_drones_go_into_effect_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/12C/0AD/12C0AD1D4C6B4882B19429385B3DD291_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Drones,faa,faa rules for drones,faa drone rules,commercial drones in us,technology,aviation,faa rules for commercial drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3225666</guid>
      <title>Cuba is now easier to reach for U.S. citizens, airlines add 300 new flights per week</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HAVANA  Formerly frosty relations between the United States and Cuba continued to thaw this week as Havana began accepting scheduled flights from U.S. airliners for the first time in five decades.A JetBlue flight from Fort Lauderdale to Santa Clara on Wednesday was the first scheduled passenger flight between the U.S. and Cuba since the Cuban Revolution, the New York Times reported. U.S. airlines are now allowed to fly to Havana and nine other Cuban airports, adding 300 new flights per week to the formerly hardline communist island state.Traveling by sea to Cuba is also an option. Cruise company Carnival goes from Miami every other week, stopping in Havana, Cienfuegos and Santiago de Cuba.Uncle Sam still technically forbids U.S. citizens from traveling to Cuba solely for tourism. But in reality no one’s checking once you tick that box, travel experts on the island told the New York Times. American trips to Cuba must fall within one of 12 categories, which include visiting relatives, professional research, journalism or religious activities.Organized or independent “people to people” tours are also permitted, so long as they include a full-time schedule of activities and “meaningful interaction between the traveler and individuals in Cuba.”]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/01/3225666/3225666_91DC43291D88495DAA55293BFC15A891_161207_3225666_Cuba_is_now_easier_to_reach_for_U_S__citizens__a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/441/5E3/4415E3F1F34D45FF9F9C4F32EDDE04D4_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cuba,cuba flights,cuba 2016,cuba libre,us cuba relations,jetblue,jetblue cuba,cuba tourism,visiting cuba,visiting cuba 2016]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3225663</guid>
      <title>Coca-Cola workers find 370 kg of cocaine hidden in a shipment at a factory in France</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SIGNES, FRANCE  Workers at a Coca-Cola factory in France have discovered a huge stash of smuggled cocaine.French prosecutors said none of the workers are under suspicion, but they are investigating who sent the drugs, which were in bags hidden in a shipment of orange juice concentrate from Central America, Reuters reported.The haul of Andean marching powder weighed 370 kilos, and had a street value of 50 million euros, which is about $55 million US dollars. It was sent from Costa Rica and arrived at the factory in Signes, southern France on August 26.It’s widely rumored that the original 1886 recipe for Coca-Cola contained traces of cocaine. But Coca-Cola has always denied its products ever contained anything to give them an extra kick.The seizure at the factory is one of the biggest ever discoveries of cocaine in France. Investigators were trying to sniff out some leads to find out who sent it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/09/01/3225663/3225663_F2B742D8B8F44921B6A1B17620A71F85_161207_3225663_Coca_Cola_workers_find_370_kg_of_cocaine_hidden__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AEF/687/AEF6875D52014798B7384483DAC2CE3B_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cocaine,cocaine is a hell of a drug,cocaine coca cola,coke,coca cola,coke found,coke workers find coke]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
