<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Beachfront</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 11:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>This New Virus Could Spark the Next Global Pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Scientists from China have found a virus with "pandemic potential" that is related to the swine flu, according to a study in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences. The new virus is dubbed EA H1N1 G4.Science Magazine reports the G4 variant virus has genes from three types of H1N1: the Eurasian Avian flu; the strain that caused the 2009 pandemic; and a North American strain that has genes from pig viruses.Swab tests on 31,000 pigs found H1N1 spreading among farmed pigs in at least 10 provinces in China, and most of the 178 confirmed cases are of the new virus.According to a previous study, two people in China were infected by the new swine flu, although the virus did not transmit to others. The study notes that the virus appears to attack the human respiratory system.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 10:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/30/4014517/4014517_5AA1048BBB984BE88ABB1AC8345A21BE_200630_4014517_This_New_Virus_Could_Spark_the_Next_Global_Pande_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[EA H1N1 G4, G4, H1N1, new swine flu, swine flu, avian flu, influenza, pig, pigs, farmed pigs, pig farms, pandemic, pandemic potential, human-to-human transmission, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan Swimmers Wear 'Facekinis' to Prevent Coronavirus Spread</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  'Facekinis' have made a comeback as visitors to a recently re-opened waterpark in Wuhan donned facial tightknits to protect themselves not only from those hateful UV rays but apparently, also from the deadly virus. What's a 'facekini'? Well, typically sported by women of a certain age in China, the 'facekini' is a very unique face-covering swimwear that protects against harmful rays whilst offering glamour and flare, however, the post-COVID world has relaunched the face-knit as a must for all swimmers in a bid to prevent the spread of the coronavirus.According to the report, the water park has restricted its capacity to just 30%, visitors also need to have their temperatures checked and their health QR code scanned to enter; the facekini, however, is not required. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 06:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/30/4014371/4014371_213F627F210844319F0861E2F46DF7AA_200630_4014371_Wuhan_Swimmers_Wear__Facekinis__to_Prevent_Coron_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Astronomical Object May Be a 'Black Neutron Star'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA  Astronomers have long wondered what lies within the so-called mass gap between black holes and neutron stars. The largest known neutron star is 2.5 times the size of our Sun, while the smallest known balck hole is five solar masses. In a new study from the National Science Foundation's Laser Interferometer Gravitational-Wave Observatory, or LIGO, and the Virgo detector in Europe, scientists have announced the discovery of an object of 2.6 solar masses.This object, which some are calling a "black neutron star," existed about 800 million light-years away from Earth in a binary pairing with a large black hole of 23 solar masses.These two interstellar bodies collided in an event called GW190814, creating a huge splash of gravitational waves.LIGO and Virgo detected the black neutron star in August of 2019, as it merged with the black hole, leaving a newly formed black hole about 25 times the size of our Sun.A paper about the detection has been accepted for publication in The Astrophysical Journal Letters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 05:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/30/4014336/4014336_0141676ADFAC42DBBAB65400BE73E118_200630_4014336_Mystery_Astronomical_Object_May_Be_a__Black_Neut_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[black neutron star, neutron star, black hole, binary system, supernova, gravitational waves, astronomy, National Science Foundation's Laser Interferometer Gravitational-Wave Observatory, LIGO, Virgo detector, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penumbral Lunar Eclipse Will Happen on July Fourth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  A penumbral eclipse will occur over the Americas between July 4 and July 5, according to NASA. Penumbral eclipses occur when the Moon moves across the Earth's lesser shadow, or the penumbra.EarthSky.com reports a full moon visible in the evening of July 4, Eastern Daylight Time. The next night, a barely perceptible eclipse will take place at 11:44 p.m., with Saturn and Jupiter also visible in the evening sky.Most people in the Americas will be able to observe the eclipse, but only a small part of Northwest Africa will be able to see the event, because morning twilight will obscure the Moon.According to NASA, a full lunar eclipse occurs when the Moon enters Earth's greater shadow, or the Umbra. Sometimes, the Earth's atmosphere filters out blue light and bounces red light on the Moon. This results in the Blood Moon, the next of which will occur in 2021.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/30/4014274/4014274_8A995C6A8D57455FABCF3055B91448BF_200630_4014274_Penumbral_Lunar_Eclipse_Will_Happen_on_July_Four_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Lunar eclipse, penumbral eclipse, July fourth, July 4, penumbra, umbra, full eclipse, full lunar eclipse, blood moon, blue light, blue lights, blue spectrum light, red light, red spectrum light, atmosphere, NASA, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong: China Passes Draconian National Security Law</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Beijing has passed a new national security law on Tuesday. The controversial law grants the government sweeping powers that critics fear will be used to quash Hong Kong's freedoms and autonomy. The legislation passed the Standing Committee of the National People's Congress by a unanimous vote. The law sets down new crimes for subversion, splittism, and colluding with foreign governments and outside forces. The maximum penalty is life imprisonment.Hong Kong Chief Executive Carrie Lam will receive authority to appoint judges to hear national security cases, while Beijing gains the power to interpret laws as it sees fit. These developments have cast into doubt whether judicial independence will survive in the territory.Hong Kong Free Press reports that within minutes of the law's passage, Hong Kong activist Joshua Wong withdrew from Demosisto, the democracy group he had led. Later, Demosisto announced that the group is to disband in a Facebook post.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 08:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/01/4014837/4014837_61CC90055C9249659AE57245E7392882_200701_4014837_Hong_Kong__China_Passes_Draconian_National_Secur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, national security law, security law, controversial security law, democracy, freedoms, freedom, autonomy, crackdown, judiciary independence, National People's Congress, China, Hong Kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic Sandstorm Engulfs Chinese City in Minutes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOTAN, XINJIANG, CHINA  On June 28th, residents stood witness to a monstrous sandstorm. Footage posted to Weibo shows cars being brought to a halt as the instantaneous wind force reached level 9, carrying with it monstrous plumes of dust that blocked out the sun, making the roads too hazardous to drive. In other clips, we can see a heavy haze looming over buildings and a giant wall of sand moving towards it.Local residents said that this was the harshest sandstorm they have seen in quite some time.According to a report by BTV, Hotan Airport canceled a total of 5 flights, and delayed 9, affecting nearly 1,000 passengers. As an ancient oasis town, the area has always dealt with sandstorms because of its close proximity to the Taklimakan Desert, however, in recent years deforestation has made the area more sustainable to these extreme weather events. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/01/4014817/4014817_443556E10BE74F1CAEF9F299F4E3E653_200701_4014817_Apocalyptic_Sandstorm_Engulfs_Chinese_City_in_Mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Proposes Steam-Powered Bot for Exploring Icy Moons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA says it might use a steam-powered hopping robot to explore the icy terrain of Jupiter's moon Europa and Saturn's moon Enceladus.According to the agency's news release, the conceptual robot called SPARROW will feature avionics, instruments and thrusters inside a spherical protective shell, which is about the size of a soccer ball.SPARROW stands for Steam Propelled Autonomous Retrieval Robot for Ocean Worlds.The lander will transfer ice to the robot in situ, then the hopper will heat the substance into steam and use the gas to jump over great distances of the surface crust."The SPARROW concept will navigate Europa's meter-high blades of ice that would stop other robots cold. After taking samples, the robot will then return to the lander for collection."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 07:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/01/4014810/4014810_AAAECC2247794682A25F7F5DBE4AAAA5_200701_4014810_NASA_Proposes_Steam_Powered_Bot_for_Exploring_Ic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA, robot, steam-powered, steam powered, steam-propelled, steam propelled, Jupiter, Europa, Saturn, Enceladus, SPARROW, Steam Propelled Autonomous Retrieval Robot for Ocean Worlds, ice moons, space, space exploration, science and technology, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainer: What Is Remdesivir and How Does It Treat COVID-19?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE  SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, is an RNA virus. This means the coronavirus uses nucleosides as the building blocks of its genetic material, according to University of Maryland, Baltimore County biochemist Katherine Seley-Radtke.Writing for media outlet The Conversation, Seley-Radtke says the virus relies on an enzyme called polymerase to replicate its RNA nucleoside by nucleoside, so that it can make more copies of itself.Gilead's remdesivir is an antiviral and a nucleoside analogue, or a chemical compound that is structurally similar to naturally occurring nucleosides. During replication, remdesivir could trick the polymerase into mistaking the antiviral drug, which resembles adenosine, for the genuine article.After this happens, the antiviral is taken into the new RNA strand and stops the polymerase from replicating more of the RNA, which should suppress the virus. Preliminary results from May suggest the drug improved patient survival rate and time recovery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/02/4015326/4015326_D616A9A644314435855727F618753CE8_200702_4015326_Explainer__What_Is_Remdesivir_and_How_Does_It_Tr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2, COVID-19, coronavirus, pandemic, remdesivir, polymerase, RNA, genome, nucleoside, nucleoside analogue, adenosine, Gilead, Gilead Sciences, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Pulls Animation Series For an Insane Reason</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUNAN, CHINA  Chinese broadcaster Hunan Television has removed a children's animated series after complaints that it promoted the dyeing of hair. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/02/4015302/4015302_1376F30EF3A84B63BC1710C1A0689195_200702_4015302_China_Pulls_Animation_Series_For_an_Insane_Reaso_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid Single-Handedly Killed Off the Dinosaurs: New Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Asteroid impact gets sole credit for wiping out the dinosaurs 66 million years ago, according to new research. Scientists from the UK say the 10-km wide asteroid that made the Chicxulub crater caused dinosaur extinction without help from volcanoes.According to the study in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, the research team modeled the Chicxulub impact, Deccan volcanism and combinations of the two. The results suggest the asteroid impact was catastrophic enough to have destroyed the dinosaurs on its own."According to the models, Deccan volcanism would have reduced sunlight by just 5 percent at maximum.In comparison, estimates for the asteroid impact's effect is that fallout would have diminished sunlight by 15 to 20 percent. This figure is enough to have guaranteed the complete eradication of the non-avian dinosaurs."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 05:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/02/4015147/4015147_827485579BE34657A4C21F3BE8C85B04_200702_4015147_Asteroid_Single_Handedly_Killed_Off_the_Dinosaur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dinosaur extinction, asteroid wiped out dinosaurs, asteroid impact wiped out dinosaurs, asteroid impact, Chicxulub crater, Chicxulub impact, Chicxulub,  volcanoes, Deccan volcanism, Deccan Traps, Deccan, TomoNews, science, paleontology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Map Underwater 'Lost Continent' of Zealandia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOWER HUTT, NEW ZEALAND  The hidden continent of Zealandia has fascinated scientists ever since the mid-1990s. Now, researchers from GNS Science in New Zealand have mapped the submerged land mass in great detail, showing how tectonic and seismic activity have shaped its evolution.The islands of New Zealand and New Caledonia are the only visible remnants of Zealandia, which was declared a distinct geological continent in a 2017 paper published in the Geological Society of America's journal.Zealandia is a fragment of the supercontinent Gondwana, which began to separate from the northern supercontinent Laurasia around 180 million years when the Atlantic Ocean formed between what are now North America and Africa.Zealandia separated from Gondwana beginning in the Late Cretaceous period. It is argued that it is a continent because it possesses a distinct and well-defined area and is composed of continental crust, not oceanic crust.However, as it began its journey eastward, most of it slid beneath the ocean. Today, 94 percent of Zealandia is submerged. Its highest point is Aoraki, or Mount Cook, in New Zealand, at 3,724 meters, or 12,218 feet.GNS Science is a geoscience research and consultancy organization owned by the government of New Zealand.In a statement, Nick Mortimer, a geologist and lead author of the maps, said:"We've made these maps to provide an accurate, complete and up-to-date picture of the geology of the New Zealand and southwest Pacific area  better than we have had before," he said. "Their value is that they provide a fresh context in which to explain and understand the setting of New Zealand's volcanoes, plate boundary and sedimentary basins."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/03/4015493/4015493_D0AC6E8EBD3045C5B483722AEB24E2C2_200703_4015493_Researchers_Map_Underwater__Lost_Continent__of_Z_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[geology, Zealandia, New Zealand, New Caledonia, map, mapping, cartography, continental drift, Gondwana, eight continent, lost continent, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
