<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Beachfront</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 19:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong democracy figures targeted in recent series of attacks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Multiple pro-democracy activists in Hong Kong have been assaulted or attacked for openly standing up against China, in what critics have dubbed as "White Terror." In September, Stanley Ho, a member of Hong Kong's Labor Party and a candidate in the upcoming local elections, was beaten by four unknown attackers with metal rods and sticks near a park in Sai Kung.His attackers fractured both of his hands and gave him a head wound, according to Hong Kong Free Press and AFP. He was hospitalized after being attacked.Civil Human Rights Front leader Jimmy Sham was attacked by at least four men with hammers while he was on his way to a meeting earlier this month, reports Hong Kong Free Press. Officials found Sham lying on the street and bleeding from his arms and head.Isaac Cheng, vice president of Hong Kong's pro-democracy Demosisto party, was beaten by assailants on his way home at night in September.In a Facebook post, the Demosisto party explained that the 19-year-old was attacked from behind by three men who punched him in the eyes. His glasses flew off his face as a result and Cheng was taken to the hospital for his injuries by party members.Jocelyn Chau was at her booth campaigning when a middle-aged man went up to Chau and tore up her election leaflet, Hong Kong Free Press reports. He was accompanied by a woman who encouraged him to go on. The man punched Chau in the head twice when she asked him to stop littering.The 23-year-old was taken to a hospital after feeling nauseous and dizzy.Another female candidate, Jannelle Leung, an accountant running for district council, was attacked by a man who hit her in the back of her head with an unknown object as she was waiting to cross the road.She didn't suffer any serious injuries from the attack.Hong Kong Democratic Party Lawmaker Roy Kwong was punched and kicked by three masked assailants as he tried to get into his car in late September.The masked assailants targeted Kwong's neck, the back of his head and his torso while Kwong was seen in a video lying on the ground, protecting his head and arms, as reported by the Hong Kong Free Press. Kwong called for an ambulance after the attackers ran away.Davin Wong, former student union leader of University of Hong Kong, was assaulted by a masked man wearing a white shirt as he waited for the bus at the end of August. Wong told DW News that the masked man used a cane to hit him on his neck and left shoulder. He said he believed the attack was planned.Fear and a lack of trust in the police have led at least some pro-democracy activists arranging their own protection. Hong Kong's police force has denied these allegations and said they pursue all crimes regardless of a person's political affiliation.Hong Kong's Labour Party lawmaker Fernando Cheung stated that the attacks are connected to triads and specifically target pro-democracy protesters, according to the Hong Kong Free Press.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 14:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/31/3914392/3914392_063C46F321474CC4B3C33C1D6943ADF1_191031_3914392_Hong_Kong_democracy_figures_targeted_in_recent_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/29D/20A/29D20A343FDF7BD7AF590CADC76DE871.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong kong white terror, hong kong white terror 2019, hong kong protest, hong kong protest leaders,  hong kong protest leaders attacked, hong kong attack, hong kong assault, hong kong pro-democracy leaders attacked, hong kong pro-democracy leaders assaulted, stanley ho, jimmy sham, isaac cheng, Jocelyn Chau, Janelle Leung, Roy Kwong, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another gender reveal party in Iowa ended in a massive explosion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WAUKEE, IOWA  Iowa's gender reveal parties are blowing up in a major way.The Des Moines Register reported that central Iowa authorities responded to an explosion on Sunday around 5:30 p.m. just outside the Waukee city limits.   According to KCCI, a gender reveal party was set up in a vacant lot off Ute Street. Around 20 people were there for the event. According to Waukee Fire Department Capt. Tommie Tysdal, the property owner used a Tannerite gender reveal boom kit. And what better way to set off a gender reveal boom kit than by shooting it with a rifle.He told authorities that he had warned his neighbors about the possibility of an explosion, but it turned out to be a little bit louder than he expected.  Unfortunately, the blast was so big it shook homes more than two miles away and blew out a neighbor's windows.  Luckily, no one was hurt in the boneheaded incident, which came only one day after another gender reveal party explosion ended in one less member of the family. At this point, maybe people in Iowa should stop making little ones.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 13:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/31/3914347/3914347_A3CBE389A970451EA19108CFE143AD95_191031_3914347_Another_gender_reveal_party_in_Iowa_ended_in_a_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/096/9C6/0969C6AF47BAD0FA16D67A890935DF22.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Gender reveal party, Iowa gender reveal party, gender reveal party fail, gender reveal party accident, Iowa gender reveal party incident, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog survives getting hit and stuck in car bumper</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROTTERDAM, NEW YORK  A Shiba Inu named Coco will live to bark another day after getting hit by a car in Albany and wedged into its grill, then traveling all the way to Rotterdam.According to The Daily Gazette, police say Coco was hit on North Manning Boulevard right before noon on Monday. Rotterdam police Lt. Jeffrey Collins said the driver realized that she had hit something thinking it was a ball or an animal. She pulled the car over to have a quick look, noticed some damage to the front bumper, but not the dog sticking out of the bumper. The driver then started to head for the body shop. Police say she was driving for about an hour when she started to hear loud noises coming from the front end. She stopped again, but this time when she went to check, she noticed Coco sticking out the front of the grill by the license plate. The woman called then called police, who notified an animal control officer who took the dog to the vet for treatment. The police were also able to locate Coco's owner.Coco suffered a broken elbow, which will most likely require a couple of surgeries before she's BARK to a hundred percent. Despite her RUFF ordeal, Coco is doing well.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 13:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/31/3914337/3914337_0850BCBF0EB7411FB52D696F3579586E_191031_3914337_Dog_survives_getting_hit_and_stuck_in_car_bumper_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/59C/FFF/59CFFFA632B95D4A0CDE3ED6F391D98B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Shiba Inu stuck in bumper, Shiba Inu stuck in grill, Shiba Inu in bumper, Shiba Inu dog, dog survives getting hit by car, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to ban 'uncivilized behavior' on subways across China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  The Chinese government has come up with a grand plan to ban "uncivilized behavior" from its subways starting in April of next year.The country's Ministry of Transport has introduced new regulations banning riders from eating, drinking or playing music on loudspeakers while taking the subway, though exceptions will be made for infants and those with certain medical conditions, China Daily reports. Riders will also be forbidden from stepping or lying down on metro seats.The state-run newspaper didn't specify how violators will be punished.According to the Shanghaiist, more than 30 Chinese cities have already come up with their own rules for local subways  many of which already address so-called "uncivilized behavior."Passengers on Chinese subways have been notorious for bad behavior. Chinese commuters have made headlines for chowing down food items such as chicken feet, while others have made the news for cutting their toenails while riding the subway.China probably has a long way to go if it wants to prevent such barbaric behavior from embarrassing the country all the time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 09:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/31/3914173/3914173_4D4F6BA7D4B54A3BA6AAD47123E5B750_191031_3914173_Beijing_to_ban__uncivilized_behavior__on_subways_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China subway, Chinese subway, chinese subways, China to ban uncivilized behavior on subways, uncivilized behavior, china subway train, china subway system, china uncivilized, china to ban eating on subway, chinese subway passengers, chinese behavior,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old man slaps cop in the face</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BINZHOU, CHINA  An elderly man was caught jaywalking on an intersection in the Shandong city of Binzhou on Tuesday and lost his temper when a police officer confronted him. His dangerous antics caused a number of cars to swerve dangerously to avoid hitting him whilst others braked suddenly. When confronted, he began shouting at the traffic officer, asking him, "What are you going to do about it?"The old man then slapped the officer across the face and walked away.The elderly man has since been summoned to the police station, however, Weibo users are concerned that he'll get away with it because of his age.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 08:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/31/3914128/3914128_1D008A187F184B2EA157B7D1C13D1C71_191031_3914128_Old_man_slaps_cop_in_the_face_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/178/545/178545FD161002B8802E6568B3567F68.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Old man slaps police, Old man slaps cop in the face, Chinese man hits police, old Chinese man attacks police, police assault, Chinese police attack, Chinese police old man, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber unveils new designs for Uber Eats food delivery drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DETROIT  Uber unveiled new designs for its Uber Eats food delivery drones at a Forbes Under 30 Summit in Detroit on October 28.The drone will feature six rotors and be able to carry meals for two people, Forbes reports. The drone will perform vertical takeoffs and landings and will be able to fly up to 18 miles per trip. Uber's Elevate Cloud Systems will track and guide the drone to its drop-off location.Uber says the drone will carry meals from restaurants to a specific drop-off location, where an Uber delivery driver will pick up the meal from the drone and deliver it to the customer.The company had previously mentioned it would consider landing the drones directly on top of its delivery cars in the future. These cars would use a QR code to allow drones to correctly identify which car roof to land on.In June, Uber Eats used a previous design of the delivery drone to make a few test deliveries from a McDonald's near San Diego State University.At the summit, Uber stated that it plans to start testing its updated delivery drone in San Diego next summer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 05:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/31/3914050/3914050_B5E94B4CD44B484BACB428AD49ABD6EF_191031_3914050_Uber_unveils_new_designs_for_Uber_Eats_food_deli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/335/4C4/3354C43D178082AF9E628D8CC9C24EE3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Uber eats, Uber eats food delivery drone, Uber eats delivery drone, Uber unveils new design for uber eats delivery drone, Uber eats drone delivery, uber eats drone, uber eats san diego drone, food delivery drones, self-flying vehicles, drone, drone delivery, drone technology 2019, flying food to customers, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese glass bridges
deemed "unsafe"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Chinese outlet, Jiemian News reports on numerous bridges closing due to insufficient "care for safety and management." There is no nationwide standard when it comes to safety, meaning your fate on one of these tourists traps in the hands of individual provincial authorities.The report details a total of 32 glass bridges and walkways being closed in Hebei province over the past 18 months alone. More severely, in many regions, some of these walkways have had issues that sometimes led to fatalities.Most recently, one person was killed and six were injured after falling off a glass slide at a Guangxi scenic spot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/31/3913941/3913941_6D68E3760C714798BADE2F1B3925BA56_191031_3913941_Chinese_glass_bridges_deemed__unsafe__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F49/C07/F49C07FA6AEEC9D8B88F452C62FFD3C7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese glass bridges, glass-bottom bridge fails, bridge fails, glass slides, glass walkways, glass bridge in China, China bridge fails, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Otzi the Iceman's final journey retraced using moss</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH TYROL, ITALY  Frozen plant species buried with Otzi the Iceman has allowed scientists to trace the unusual route he took before his death.Otzi the Iceman was a hunter who died in the Alps 5,300 years ago. His mummified body was discovered near the Italy-Austria border in 1991.According to Science News, he was believed to have died due to freezing temperatures in the Italian Alps. But the discovery of an arrowhead in his left shoulder has led scientists to believe he was deliberately killed.A new study from the University of Glasgow examined fragments of frozen vegetation buried alongside or inside Otzi, which includes 75 different species of mosses and liverworts.Only 30% of the species are local, others were likely transported via Otzi's clothing or inside his gut.According to New Scientist, researchers found a type of bog moss in Otzi's colon that is used to staunch wounds, and may have been used to treat a gash on his palm.His intestines also contained the moss Neckera complanata and traces of pollen.Both moss species are found in low-elevation woodlands, while Otzi was found 3,200 meters above sea level.This suggests the Iceman travelled from the forests below and went through Schnalstal valley on his final ascent.Researcher James Dickson says Otzi the Iceman's route through the gorge was the most stressful way up the mountain, but fits with the assumption that he was hiding and running away from someone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 11:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914864/3914864_647AB5A3E9E04778A200D1A3943FEAB0_191101_3914864_Otzi_the_Iceman_s_final_journey_retraced_using_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D02/B8F/D02B8FF2100F846E35F36E4289AF5BF0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Otzi, iceman, Otzi the iceman, mummy, prehistoric, prehistoric man, Italy, Alps, Alpine mountain, archeology, archaeobotany, bryophytes, moss, bog moss, liverworts, copper age, chalcolithic, ancient murder, cold case, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with 9 toes on left foot has surgery to remove freeloaders</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANWEI, CHINA  A 21-year-old man born with some ultra amazing kung fu grip to the tune of 9 toes on his left foot has finally had the four extra digits surgically removed.According to the Yangcheng Evening News, the man, who goes by the name Ah-jun, since birth has had the ability to almost count to 10 using just one foot.Why did it take so long to get corrective surgery? Thank Ah-jun's superstitious parents. Apparently when he was younger, his parentals took him to see a fortune teller who said the extra toes were "a gift from the heavens." This made his parents reluctant to get surgery, which unfortunately made Ah-jun reluctant to ever wear sandals or show his bare feet.The condition is actually called Polydactyly. It's a rare birth defect that occurs when a person has extra fingers or toes. It's also more common among dudes. But finally after years of only being able to swim in a circle, Ah-jun went to see some surgeons at the Shunde Heping Surgical Hospital in Foshan for help. After a nine-hour long surgery that required a whole bunch of heavy reconstruction, doctors were able to create a new big toe and get rid of the extra foot freeloaders. Ah-jun is now recovering in the hospital and will soon be able to put his best foot forward.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 11:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914847/3914847_54141A3DBEBB4B45A303A196A3FDB1E6_191101_3914847_Man_with_9_toes_on_left_foot_has_surgery_to_remo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9CF/983/9CF983FF275F7A91E130D72F6DF216A1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man with 9 toes one foot, Chinese man with 9 toes on one foot, polydactyly, polydactyly corrective surgery, man has extra digits removed, man has corrective surgery, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadspin writers quit en masse over 'stick to sports' memo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  Most of the staff at Deadspin have unfortunately said adios in an open revolt against a top brass mandate to stick to sports.USA Today reported that the resignations came at the end of a contentious few months between staff and douchey new ownership. According to the New York Post, trouble started on Monday after the editorial director of Deadspin's parent company, G/O Media, issued a staff memo to "write only about sports and that which is relevant to sports in some way."So in typical Deadspin fashion, the editorial staff began filling the site with exclusively non-sports stories. Then on Tuesday, Deadspin deputy director Barry Petchesky said that he'd been axed for not following the directive. Petchesky tweeted, "Hi, I've just been fired from Deadspin for not sticking to sports." The Washington Post reported that this then led to close to a dozen Deadspin writers and editors announcing their resignations over Twitter in protest on Wednesday and Thursday. According to Business Insider, shortly after that the Gizmodo Media Group issued a statement over Twitter accusing the company's CEO, Jim Spanfeller, of "curtailing [Deadspin's] most well-read coverage because it makes him personally uncomfortable."   Many long time readers, sports nutz and fellow journalists have all taken to Twitter to commend the former Deadspin staff for their integrity and courage. Apparently in an attempt to deaden the backlash, G/O has shut off all comments on Deadspin. Maybe it's time for a name changeperhaps just call it DEAD from now on.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914843/3914843_FA082C7159C142699663F3DF59F44D2E_191101_3914843_Deadspin_writers_quit_en_masse_over__stick_to_sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61C/228/61C2288973831BF127A61704443B3E32.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Deadspin, Deadspin writers quit, Deadspin stick to sports memo, Deadspin writers resign, G/O Media Deadspin, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA plans orbiter mission to Pluto</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN ANTONIO  NASA has commissioned Southwest Research Institute to study the possibility and the cost of a long-term Pluto orbiter mission.NASA and Southwest Research Institute aim to send an unmanned spacecraft to study Pluto and two other Kuiper Belt Objects for a total of two years, according to a press release from the research institute. For the mission, the institute will work to develop a new spacecraft with a new payload design.According to the press release, the spacecraft would have a larger payload than the New Horizons space probe and carry more advanced instruments.The press release didn't detail which exact instruments the space probe could potentially carry.The institute previously lead NASA's New Horizon mission, in which the New Horizon space probe was able to fly past Pluto and its five moons and reach Kuiper Belt Object (KBO) 2014 MU69, also known as Ultima Thule, the farthest object visited till date.The spacecraft captured high-resolution images of Pluto but wasn't able to enter Pluto's orbit as it was traveling fast at 50,700 kilometers per hour, according to Phys.org. Researchers will deliver their results to the National Academy Planetary Decadal Study in 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 09:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914728/3914728_C10AE85FBFE34143B27EDD18C77DA2EE_191101_3914728_NASA_plans_orbiter_mission_to_Pluto_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/21F/2CA/21F2CAEFF71D14DB76C91F326E6F240D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Space exploration, Pluto, Pluto orbital mission, mission to pluto, NASA, NASA mission to Pluto, pluto mission, pluto mission nasa, Southwest Research Institute, orbital mission to Pluto, dwarf planet, Kuiper Belt Objects, dwarf planet pluto, Pluto system orbital tour, Pluto orbit, pluto orbiter mission, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposure to sunlight is good for the bacteria in your gut</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER, CANADA  Exposure to ultraviolet rays may increase biodiversity of the gut microbiome in humans.Canadian researchers find that being under the sun could enrich gut flora and that a novel skin-gut axis may exist, according to a study published in Frontiers in Microbiology on October 24. The researchers say that 21 women volunteers were subjected to three full body exposures to UV rays over one week.Blood samples were tested for vitamin D levels and stool samples were tested for the biodiversity of their gut bacteria.Frontiers Science News reports that half of the participants who regularly took vitamin D supplements experienced no changes to their gut microbiome.However, women who did not take supplements saw increases to vitamin D levels, and their gut microbiome became as diverse as the supplemented group.The researchers state that multiple sclerosis and inflammatory bowel diseases are associated with the lack of sunlight, vitamin D, and unhealthy gut microbiota.The study indicates that there is a direct link between those factors, but it does not identify the causal mechanism.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 09:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914721/3914721_F59F0E7831FA4D549F2E4F1C71FCF4BC_191101_3914721_Exposure_to_sunlight_is_good_for_the_bacteria_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/67A/319/67A3191A9358346C1CBEA5F1A1898F48.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[gut microbiome, gut microbiota, uv light, ultraviolet, sunlight, vitamin, vitamin d, Inflammatory bowel disease,  multiple sclerosis, skin gut axis, skin gut pathway, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android malware infects at least 45,000 devices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA CLARA, CALIFORNIA  Researchers at cybersecurity firms Malwarebytes and Symantec have uncovered an Android trojan called xHelper that is able to reinstall itself even after users have uninstalled it.According to Symantec, the malware has already infected more than 45,000 devices, mainly in the U.S., India and Russia, over the last six months.Malwarebytes explained in a blogpost that the malware is installed through web redirects that take users to web pages that host unofficial Android apps. These unofficial apps include code that installs the xHelper trojan onto a users' phone once these apps have been downloaded.The malware shows users popup ads and notification spam, though it doesn't seem to carry out any sketchy operations, according to Malwarebytes.The ads and notifications lead users to Google's Play Store where they are asked to download more apps  a method by which authors of the xHelper trojan earn money each time these apps are installed.Even if users restore their Android phones back to factory settings or manually uninstall the malware, the xHelper trojan is able to reinstall itself.Some users have said even after disabling the "Install apps from unknown sources" option after manually uninstalling the app, their device was reinfected with the malware in a matter of minutes, according to ZDNet.   Symantec advised users to take precautions and not download apps from unfamiliar sites and to only install apps from trusted sources.The company also advised users to pay close attention to permissions the app is seeking, backup important data frequently and install a suitable mobile security app to protect their device.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 04:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914573/3914573_A703185DB617479F93715D8DF4D52306_191101_3914573_New_Android_malware_infects_at_least_45_000_devi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/726/33B/72633BD2E45469FE0DB6BCB4A45DE845.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[xHelper malware, xHelper malware infects android devices, xHelper android malware, xHelper virus, xHelper app, android apps,  android apps 2019, android phones, Android malware,third-party apps, third-party android apps, suspicious android apps, unremovable malware, malware keeps reinstalling itself, removing unremovable malware, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles could give your 
Immune system amnesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON  Scientists have found that measles is a lot more devastating to the immune system than previously thought.According to the WHO, measles is a highly contagious airborne disease caused by a virus in the paramyxoviridae family.Symptoms of a measles infection usually include a cough, fever, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash erupts on the face and neck after several days, and spreads to the rest of the body over the next three to four days.The Guardian reports that the body has two key lines of immune response in dealing with viruses. Memory B-cells remember previous infections the body has had before and protects against them. Naive B-cells, meanwhile, defend against new infections.A study published in the journal Science Immunology found that measles wipes out a substantial number of memory cells reduces the diversity of the naive b-cells.This causes 'immune amnesia', where the immune system to forget how to respond to infections, leaving the body vulnerable to other diseases.Another study published in Science looked at antibodies in the blood of unvaccinated children in the Netherlands before and after a measles infection.They found that the measles destroyed 11 to 78% of the children's antibody memory bank.According to the BBC, babies are born with limited antibodies that become more varied as they grow older.Measles resets the immune system to an immature, baby-like state, with only a narrow range of antibodies to work with, and a limited ability to fight off new infections.A way to avoid this is by getting the MMR vaccine, which eliminates the risk of catching a measles infection. Revaccination also helps with those whose immune system memories have already been ravaged by the disease.Bottom line, please vaccinate your kids.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 15:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3916142/3916142_A51F82FD54CA454D8CFB026244878D24_191104_3916142_Measles_could_give_your__Immune_system_amnesia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D8F/114/D8F114854AA493BA8B8758335B5E3AB2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Measles, measles infection, autoimmune system, immune system, immunity, immunity amnesia, b-cells, memory cells, memory b-cells, lymphocytes, b lymphocytes, VirScan, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese researchers using live pigs as crash test dummies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Disturbing photos have emerged showing live pigs being used as crash test dummies in China. The results were published for a study in the International Journal of Crashworthiness in January of this year.  According to Metro, fifteen pigs between 70 and 80 days old were starved for 24 hours before being strapped into children's car seats, so they could be used in crash simulations.  The Chinese scientists justified their use of pigs saying the animals' anatomic structure was "similar" to that of human children. The unlucky pigs were supposed to correspond to children aged 6 years old. According to the study, seven of the animals were killed on impact, while the others only lasted 6 hours after crash tests were administered. The pigs suffered injuries ranging from abrasions, contusions, lacerations, bleeding, to fractures.  Pigs were previously used in the U.S. for crash tests up until the 90s, after pressure from animal right's groups ended the practice.   Animal rights groups like PETA have condemned the experiments and have contacted China's Research Institute for Traffic Medicine.Considering how much Beijing pays attention to human rights, PETA's actions will undoubtedly mean the end for all animal experiments in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 13:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3916086/3916086_25A233C96AA647808E8C6E2D19094944_191104_3916086_Chinese_researchers_using_live_pigs_as_crash_tes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E77/EE3/E77EE3A8D373EB067D704958E7866066.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China pigs crash test dummies, China crash test dummies, Chinese researchers pig crash test, China scientists pig crash test dummies, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian pilot lets female passenger fly the plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE UNQUALIFIED SKIES  Unbelievable footage showing a female passenger at the controls of a plane during a scheduled flight has really taken off in good old Mother Russia. According to the Siberian Times, video appearing to show a woman flying the aircraft from the co-pilot's seat was sent to a Russian news website.  In the video, the pilot's voice can be heard giving instructions to Maverick, who is thought to be in her late 20s with zero flying credentials. Russian reports say the incident occurred on a Russian airlines IrAero flight aboard an Antonov-24 from Yakutsk to Batagay. The flight occurred on August 31, but the video has only recently emerged. Investigators will probably spend decades piecing together how this footage made its way public. It is most likely unrelated to the pictures and video of the flight on Anna's IG with the captions "This is unbelievably cool" and "Thank you!"Strangely the account has mysteriously been deleted. According to Russian news, the pilot involved in the Hot Shots incident is Kirill S. IrAero airlines told Russian media that it is now investigating. A spokesman for the company said, "there are doubts that these materials have anything to do with our airline's activities in providing passengers transportation."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 10:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3915995/3915995_E9B46C0EA48E4E8CA780D3FA78F27FE9_191104_3915995_Russian_pilot_lets_female_passenger_fly_the_plan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4A9/B6F/4A9B6FEA0706BAFCDC265D56048F5F2D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Airplane, passenger flies airplane, Russian woman flies airplane, Russian passenger flies airplane, pilot lets passenger fly plane, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese cafe gets backlash for dyeing dogs to look like pandas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENGDU, CHINA  A pet cafe in China couldn't get their hands on actual pandas, so they did what the Chinese do bestimitate.Reuters reports that the owner, 21-year-old Lu Yunning, thought dog, cat, alpaca, raccoon, and duck cafes were all pretty basic, and wanted something novel for his own joint in Chengdu.  He happened to have Chow Chow puppies and got the bright idea to dye them to look like China's fat n' furry national treasure.The gimmick was a hit, drawing in dozens of customers who wanted photos with the panda pups. Some fur parents also signed their own pets up for the panda treatment, which is available for $212.Not everyone's a fan, though. The cafe and its dyeing service have gotten much flak from animal activists, who really want to give Lu a taste of his own medicine. Honestly, Chow dogs are adorable enough as they arewhy mess with a good thing?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 09:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3915967/3915967_855FDA15E3AC47F4BD7646F46392EB73_191104_3915967_Chinese_cafe_gets_backlash_for_dyeing_dogs_to_lo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B78/537/B7853779E7242FE2813B2B223680B97D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Panda pet cafe, panda dog cafe china, panda cafe china, panda cafe, Panda pups, panda dogs, panda dog cafe, dyed dogs, dyed pups, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China dumped 27% more trash into the oceans in 2018</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China discarded 200.7 million cubic meters of waste into its coastal waters in 2018.In a briefing on October 29, China's environmental ministry said that this is a 27 percent increase from 2017 and the highest level in at least a decade. The bulk of the waste was dumped into the delta regions of the Yangtze and Pearl rivers.China is discarding large amounts of trash into its ocean waters in an attempt to clean up its rivers, Reuters reports, citing environmental groups. According to the ministry, the country found an average of 24 kilograms of floating waste for every 1,000 square meters of surface water, almost 90 percent of the waste was plastic. Plastic waste was also found below surface water and on the seabed.China said it plans to designate 30 percent of its coastal waters to be completely off-limits for development as part of the country's "ecological red line" scheme.China is also moving its steel and petrochemical industries to its coastline in order to protect its rivers at the same time, according to Reuters.Huo Chuanlin, from China's environmental ministry, explained in the briefing that they were working to improve on the issue of wastewater from rivers entering into oceans.Huo added that China cannot be blamed for the global ocean plastic pollution crisis, even though the nation is the biggest manufacturer and exporter of plastic products around the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 08:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3915930/3915930_730D4594887B45B8AC1B168FEF21A4D6_191104_3915930_China_dumped_27__more_trash_into_the_oceans_in_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China plastic pollution, china coastal waters plastic waste, china coastal waters, chinese rivers plastic, ocean polluting crises, china plastic, china marine plastic pollution, china plastic ocean pollution, plastic pollution, plastic waste, plastic waste in oceans, ocean plastic pollution, plastic waste in the ocean, plastic polluting the oceans, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A quarter of the world's pigs could die due to African swine fever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD  Mark Schipp, vice president of the World Organization for Animal Health, stated in a press conference on October 31 that roughly a quarter of the pig population worldwide is expected to die off as a result of the spread of African swine fever. African swine fever is spread through bites by infectious ticks, contact through infected animals, contact with objects containing the virus, or by ingesting the meat of infected animals. The disease is spread by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family.Symptoms of the disease include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen, legs as well as diarrhea.The disease can be fatal for pigs, though it isn't transmissible to humans.There is currently no approved vaccine to prevent the spread of the disease, according to the World Organization for Animal Health.The swine fever outbreak has already claimed as many as 100 million pigs in China, the Guardian reports. This has resulted in rising pork prices around the world, mainly due to increasing demand from China.European pork prices have reached a six-year high, while the U.S. has managed to double its sale of pork to China.The African swine fever virus has already been identified in 50 countries around the world, including Poland, Russia, South Korea and the Philippines.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 04:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3915796/3915796_76689F2E2AEA49C29087F4ABCA0C47F6_191104_3915796_A_quarter_of_the_world_s_pigs_could_die_due_to_A_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD0/AFE/FD0AFEBC8B4DED6A53CB2C8B3B25778F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[African swine fever, swine fever news, african swine fever outbreak, pork, pigs, pork products, african swine flu china, african swine fever outbreak, african swine fever 2019, swine fever symptoms in pigs, what is african swine fever, how african swine fever spreads, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA stopped a guy after finding a toilet-paper roller 'gun' in his bag</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWARK, NEW JERSEY  A man trying to ROLL his way through a TSA checkpoint at the Newark Liberty International Airport found it a bit harder to PASS through than usual. Whoever is writing the local press releases at the TSA deserves a big fat raise for this piece titled, "How not to roll through a checkpoint…" It appears that on October 29, an unidentified man was trying to pass security when TSA agents spotted a revolver in his carry-on bag. According to CNN, after a closer inspection, agents were relieved to find out it was only a gun-shaped toilet paper holder. The TSA then DUMPED this line, "yes, this most unusual revolver was not designed to spin bullets. It was designed to spin toilet paper." CNN reported that the TP roller triggered an alarm as it went through the X-ray machine. The agency said, "TSA does not permit travelers to bring real or replica firearms through a checkpoint." The guy was given a few options: take the roller back to his car, put it in his checked luggage, give it to a friend not traveling, or gift it to the TSA.He chose to give it to his pals at the TSA. Hopefully someone there can do some damage with it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 13:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916599/3916599_AD103C332E0C461EA0B00B8292A69F18_191105_3916599_TSA_stopped_a_guy_after_finding_a_toilet_paper_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/691/944/691944504831C30540706DBFDC74E1E5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TSA, Transportation Security Administration, TSA agents, Newark airport, Newark Liberty International Airport, TSA checkpoint, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Delhi starts car rationing in a bid to clean up toxic air pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI  New Delhi is set to combat toxic smog in the city by banning cars with odd and even number plates on alternating days starting from November 4 to November 15. Those who ignore the order will be fined 4,000 rupees, or roughly US$56, BBC News reports. New Delhi's car rationing system was previously used in 2016 and 2017, though it's unclear if the plan successfully brought down the city's pollution levels.According to Reuters, the air quality index which measures levels of PM2.5 in areas across New Delhi has surpassed 900. This has far exceeded the 500 mark which is deemed as  "severe" by the World Health Organization.Authorities in New Delhi have ordered schools to be closed until November 5 and have also ordered all construction work to be halted until further notice.The World Health Organization states that continual exposure to PM2.5 particles increases a person's risk of developing cardiovascular diseases, respiratory diseases and even lung cancer.Factors such as farmers from nearby states burning their crop stubble before winter to clear their fields, and industrial and construction emissions all contribute to worsening pollution levels in New Delhi during wintertime, according to Reuters. The issue is exacerbated as people celebrate the Hindu new year Diwali, usually at the end of October or early November, and set off fireworks.The pollutants linger in the atmosphere and accumulate instead of dissipating due to the wind changing direction after the monsoon season and colder air from the Himalayas. Instead of stronger winds blowing from the east and clearing the air, softer winds blow from the northwest and move the pollutants towards New Delhi and other north Indian cities. During the same time, cold air from the Himalayan mountains descends to New Delhi and other north Indian cities, essentially trapping the toxic pollutants in the cold air.A report by AirVisual, a company that tracks air quality around the world, found that New Delhi was the most polluted capital city in the world in 2018, with Beijing coming in second place.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 11:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916556/3916556_C61578821E754249B1FC33EEF83660D7_191105_3916556_New_Delhi_starts_car_rationing_in_a_bid_to_clean_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/42E/190/42E190E9CC9E1DA526757F0CFC57B3E4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[India pollution, india pollution problem, india pollution control, india pollution city, india pollution solutions, new delhi, new delhi pollution, pollution in delhi, new delhi pollution 2019, new delhi smog, india air pollution, toxic smog delhi, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese pilot lets woman into cockpit during flight to show off</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUILIN, CHINA  A super smooth Air Guilin pilot has been grounded for life after images took off showing a woman in the cockpit during one of his flights earlier this year. According to the SCMP, the images lifted off over Chinese censored social media over the weekend.According to a statement from the airline, the incident occurred on an Air Guilin flight on January 4 from Guilin to Yangzhou. It's a mystery how the image made its way public, but it probably has nothing to do with the picture she posted over social media with the caption, "Thanks so much for the flight captain!! I'm really happy." The SCMP reports the woman has been identified as Chen Yuying, a third-year student at Guilin Tourism University, who wants to be a flight attendant after graduation.  The plastic bimbo can be seen sitting in the pilot's seat posing for a pictureno doubt taken by the pilot. Some Chinese netizens with flight experience said the snap appears to have been taken while the plane was in the air.Unfortunately for Maverick, he was given the ejector seat by Air Guilin. Also for violating China's Civil Aviation Administration rules, he's been prohibited from every flying again. Other crew members from the flight have been suspended indefinitely while an investigation is launched.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 10:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916528/3916528_DE0E0A0CABB746E7B6AA678B4FB33998_191105_3916528_Chinese_pilot_lets_woman_into_cockpit_during_fli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/567/CA7/567CA7F68B38E60D9FE0288D7CAAEF4C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, Chinese pilot, Chinese airplane pilot, passenger in cockpit, China airline passenger, woman in cockpit, woman in cockpit during flight, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct brain to brain interface demonstrated by scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  According to a study published in Nature, BrainNet is the first brain to brain interface to link three people and allow two way communication using only their mind.Two senders and a receiver cooperate in a Tetris-like game, using EEG and transcranial magnetic stimulation.According to the study, each of the senders is provided with a monitor that displays the game, and two LED lights flashing at different frequencies.The senders give a binary yes or no signal to the receiver by looking at one light or the other, which indicates whether the Tetris block should be rotated to win the game.When one sender says yes, a transcranial stimulator informs the blindfolded receiver by stimulating the visual cortex, causing the receiver to see a spot or ring of light.A no response did not engage the stimulator and the receiver did not visualize a light spot or ring.The senders can check the receiver's decision and send corrections via BrainNet if they disagree.The results showed that three people were better than one in playing the game.When researchers flipped the responses of a sender deliberately, the receiver learned to disregard bad information, showing BrainNet can overcome interference or an unreliable player.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 10:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916488/3916488_928B3C7DA70D426E9F4EA84CDEB397E8_191105_3916488_Direct_brain_to_brain_interface_demonstrated_by__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ED9/C9B/ED9C9BC368D03FF5E96CA50D6D966181.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Telepathy, telepathic communication, BrainNet, brain to brain interface, mind to mind interface, brain to brain network, brain to brain communication, Seattle, Washington, direct brain to brain communication, telepathy, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tooth of megalodon found in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY  Researchers found at least 13 prehistoric shark teeth during a diving expedition in the Xoc cenote, a flooded cave in the Mexican city of Merida.Mexico City daily Excelsior reported that morphological analysis suggests one of the teeth belonged to a megalodon, a species of giant sharks that lived from about 23 million to 2.5 million years ago.Megalodons were biggest sharks known to have existed in the world.A megalodon could grow to as large as 18 meters long and its open jaws were 1.8 meters wide, dwarfing the great white shark, according to National Geographic.The researchers told Excelsior they found other teeth belonging to the sawshark and mako shark genuses likely originating in the same geological epochs as the megalodon tooth.Excelsior reported that the Xoc cenote is Merida's third largest flooded cavern and researchers are mapping the cave system. "Xoc" means shark in the Mayan language. A 'cenote' is a natural sinkhole.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916485/3916485_4313FAF69B4543D799D054D88A7C0266_191105_3916485_TOOTH_OF_MEGALODON__FOUND_IN_MEXICO_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F02/279/F02279DCA77F6DF8A1C1E208A129F829.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Megalodon,tooth,prehistoric shark,Xoc cenote,cenote,flooded cave,cave,cavern,cavers,divers,sawshark,mako shark,fossils,paleontology,archeology,anthropology,Merida,Mexico,TomoNews,satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's ear bitten off by knife attacker outside Hong Kong mall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  As protests in Hong Kong rage on, a Mandarin speaker who was apparently from mainland China took offence to pro-democracy protesters at a mall on November 3 using a knife and his teeth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 03:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916262/3916262_53E79B069FFE49A3AD4EE6FCB7354D65_191105_3916262_Man_s_ear_bitten_off_by_knife_attacker_outside_H_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B1F/791/B1F791D1493D569AA60705CA9FCDF529.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong protests, man's ear bitten off during HK knife attack, hong kong protests knife attack, HK protests, HK mass protest, China extradition, China extradition protests, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong,  Hong Kong protest 2019, hk protests latest news, hk protests 2019,hong kong news, hong kong knife attack, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wanted for running 'bootleg' zoo with hundreds of animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROMULUS, MICHIGAN  Law enforcement in Michigan have issued a felony warrant against this man, Javon Pherras Stacks, for alleged animal cruelty, abandonment and neglect following a police raid that seized over 500 animals from a "bootleg zoo" at a Romulus storefront.According to the Romulus Police Department, officials found a ton of animals including rabbits, iguanas, a peacock, a python, kangaroos and hedgehogs at the fake zoo two months ago. They were tipped off by a concerned resident who helped officials locate the animals.After seizing the animals, the police conducted a thorough investigation and have now issued a felony warrant for the 36-year-old.The police said all the animals were given to experts who can take care of them properly.In a Facebook post, officials told the public to contact the police department if anyone knows where Stacks is, or encourage him to turn himself in.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 11:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3917088/3917088_6C20DCA2771F43CF950115EFD36BF9AD_191106_3917088_Man_wanted_for_running__bootleg__zoo_with_hundre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/492/26B/49226B713C9281A545D2F36B2AB103ED.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bootleg zoo, police bootleg zoo, bootleg zookeeper, bootleg zoo romulus mi, bootleg zoo near detroit, animals romulus, police confiscate animals, police confiscate animals from bootleg zoo, animals stories,  man creates bootleg zoo, man houses multiple animals at bootleg zoo, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimpanzee at Chinese zoo filmed enjoying a cigarette</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HEFEI, CHINA  A chimpanzee at a rundown zoo in China was caught on camera having himself a square. According to the Paper, the smoke break took place at the Hefei Wildlife Park in China's Anhui province. Apparently, some d-bag decided to toss away his lit cig directly into the chimpanzee enclosure. A video filmed by a zoo visitor shows the chimp casually pick it up and then have himself a few drags. The male chimp then quickly gets bored and drops the cancer stick onto the ground. The 11 second video has since gone viral and caused widespread anger among the public, with many worried about the animal's health. But honestly, if you solely had to stare at annoying zoo goers all day long, you'd probably want a few drags to calm the old nerves every now and then. A zoo spokeswoman responded to public criticism saying that with tens of thousands of daily visitors and a staff of only 100 people, it was impossible to keep eyes on everyone.She also added that the zoo relies on tourists visiting the center to not act like animals. Good luck with that.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 11:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3917079/3917079_B8D3551DB77B4CA49A0ECF3A192EBD8D_191106_3917079_Chimpanzee_at_Chinese_zoo_filmed_enjoying_a_ciga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B3A/589/B3A589DEC957EB13C1425A86D07475C8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chimpanzee at zoo, chimp at zoo, chimp at Chinese zoo, chimpanzee at Chinese zoo, Hefei Wildlife Park China, Hefei Wildlife Park chimpanzee, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese tourists grab seagull for photos at Kunming lake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUNMING, CHINA  It's that time of year again when Chinese tourists are on the loose. This time it's to torture black-headed seagulls at the end of their yearly migration from Siberia to the Yunnan capital of Kunming.Footage posted to Pear Video, shows one unlucky seagull being mobbed by a bunch of super annoying Chinese tourists. The group was seen at Dianchi Lake grabbing one seagull and forcefully spreading its wings just so they could take some pictures of it. What better way to reminisce than looking through your old photos of you manhandling different animals. The seagull clearly wants absolutely no part of these tourists, who apparently think that shoving some food in its mouth will somehow make it more bearable.     Thankfully some other people at the lake came over to yell at the terrorizing tourists.The geniuses apologized saying they didn't know they weren't supposed to do that, and then hightailed it out of there. Unfortunately for the migrating seagulls, this isn't the first time this kind of thing has happened. It appears to be somewhat of a tradition now with the Chinese.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 11:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3917072/3917072_792BE08440B5427D9D11C87A4B31CF6D_191106_3917072_Chinese_tourists_grab_seagull_for_photos_at_Kunm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A0E/C0C/A0EC0C3DB24CB5EB73A71010BF8A66FC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese tourists, Chinese tourists grab seagull, Chinese tourists Kunming lake, Chinese tourists grab seagull pictures, Chinese tourists behaving badly, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake cop arrested by real cops after chasing suspect vehicle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WILSON, NORTH CAROLINA  Police in North Carolina have arrested a man after he impersonated a cop and joined in on the chase after a potential murder suspect.Wilson police conducted a traffic stop on October 5 at a Food Mart to apprehend a suspect, WNCN reports. As soon as the occupants of the car noticed officers approaching, they fled the scene.The police gave chase when suddenly a Ford Taurus with blue lights drove past the police car, past the suspects' car and cornered the suspect's vehicle between his Taurus and the police car.The man in the Taurus, David Adams Jr., got out of his car and, at gunpoint, ordered the driver of the suspect vehicle to exit his car. Four other passengers exited the suspect vehicle.Adams handcuffed one of the suspects and began searching him. The real police officers had their doubts and ordered him to stop.Adams then left the scene without speaking to the police officers. The police later determined that Adams was not a sworn law enforcement officer and obtained a warrant to arrest him.After searching the suspect vehicle, officers found a handgun, an assortment of pills and US$708.Real police officers then arrested all five passengers in the suspect vehicle. One of the men in the car was the brother of the murder suspect they were looking for.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 07:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3916895/3916895_EEE04635FBF64FC1B2030E8763DED19B_191106_3916895_Fake_cop_arrested_by_real_cops_after_chasing_sus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/84D/93F/84D93F1B611F189E662306696B90D790.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fake cop, fake cop north carolina, fake cop chases after suspect, police stories, fake police,  fake cop arrested for impersonating cop, cop impersonator, cop impersonator arrested, man poses as officer, fake cop chases possible murder suspect, fake cop arrests possible murder suspect, Fake cop in the US, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's 'virtually impenetrable' border wall foiled by $100 saw</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  What does it take to break into a big, beautiful wall? Apparently not very much.According to the Washington Post, the new border wall system U.S. President Trump is building features steel and concrete bollards up to 30 feet tall, and concrete foundation that defeats tunneling.U.S. Customs and Border Protection tweeted on October 24 that it has built 75 miles of Trump's new border wall and aims to finish 450 miles by 2020. The Post reports that although Trump called the wall "virtually impenetrable," smugglers have been able to cut through with cordless power saws costing as little as US$100.They go through the resulting gap one at a time and often move the damaged bollards back in place for future crossings.U.S. officials confirmed that there have been multiple breaches, but added that smugglers targeted sections of the wall not yet equipped with electronic vibration sensors.The BBC reports that when it is completed, Trump's border wall will feature steel barriers, all weather roads, cameras, and other technology.According to the Washington Post, the wall has cost US$10 billion so far.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3916807/3916807_8B1D0EE9099F4C7BAE2B6AFF784F49DC_191106_3916807_Trump_s__virtually_impenetrable__border_wall_foi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C37/EB9/C37EB9A6E1D80EBFD3478BDD761E7985.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Donald Trump, Trump, new border wall, new wall, border wall, wall, power tool, reciprocating saw, smugglers, US-Mexico border, impenetrable, US, politics, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driverless Tesla drives itself through Vancouver parking lot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER  A Tesla Model 3 was spotted driving on the wrong side of the road with no one behind the wheel in Vancouver on Monday. According to Richmond News, a woman filmed the zombie white Tesla slowly moving through a parking lot in a Richmond shopping center at around 2 p.m. Apparently the Model 3 had been activated using the "Smart Summon" function, which allows owners to call their vehicles to their location, or a location of their choosing, within a 200-foot radius using the Tesla mobile app. Reports say the rogue Tesla entered the parking lot on the wrong side of an intersection and then continued for about 50 yards on the wrong side of the road.   The woman who captured the footage said at one point a mall security guard came out and started chasing the empty Tesla down, before a man, thought to be the owner's friend, came out to explain it was being "summoned." Another clip from inside the parking structure shows the Tesla stopped with the owner standing by the trunk. After putting some stuff in, he is then seen driving away. The shopping center told the Richmond News they are aware of the incident and have notified the authorities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 11:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917583/3917583_6AB9C3EB0BD04BB7AAAA16DC3270FAD6_191107_3917583_Driverless_Tesla_drives_itself_through_Vancouver_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B7B/03D/B7B03D5698D628B59BB1D4BA43EEACC1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tesla Model S, Tesla Smart Summon, Tesla Smart Summon app, Tesla drives itself through parking lot, Tesla drives itself on wrong side of road, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists from around the world declare climate emergency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD  More than 11,000 scientists around the world have signed a declaration stating planet Earth is facing a climate emergency, according to a new study published in the journal BioScience.These scientists have outlined six crucial steps for us to take in order to tackle climate change.For the first step, the scientists say that we must replace fossil fuels with clean renewables.Next, we must cut down emissions of methane, hydrofluorocarbons and other climate pollutants. Scientists say this could reduce short-term warming trend by over 50 percent in the next few decades.Thirdly, the scientists stated that restoring and protecting ecosystems such as forests and grasslands, would not only benefit organisms that live in these ecosystems but also naturally isolate and take in more carbon dioxide pollutants in the atmosphere.For the fourth step, the study says we must eat more plant-based food and reduce our consumption of animal-based products. This would reduce methane emissions from animals such as cattle and free up land for growing vegetables instead of livestock.The scientists added that we need to reduce food waste as roughly a third of all food products end up in the trash.Next, the study says we need a carbon-free economy that focuses on our biosphere and environment instead of focusing on hitting economic goals related to GDP growth and the pursuit of wealth.Lastly, scientists say we need to stabilize the global population to ensure social and economic justice for everyone living on this planet.After analyzing 40 years of climate data, researchers stated that global surface temperature, sea levels, ocean acidity and ocean heat content are all steadily on the rise.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917532/3917532_AD7B5C664FCD4685A3A755E613F5C660_191107_3917532_Scientists_from_around_the_world_declare_climate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B41/D5A/B41D5A019EA9FE2C9DE66EA49AE02233.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Climate change, climate emergency, climate crisis, scientists declare climate emergency, world scientists declare climate emergency, climate crisis 2019, climate emergency declaration, climate emergency 2019, world scientists climate change, climate catastrophe, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voyagers find new clues
about the solar system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Washington  The latest data sent from Voyager 2 brought new insight and questions about the boundary region where the sun's influence ends and interstellar space begins.According to NASA, the sun's energetic influence projects a bubble around the solar system called the heliosphere, Reuters says.NASA reports that as Voyager 2 crossed the border region, or the heliopause, it registered an unexpectedly sharp difference in magnetic particles and plasma density.Comparing the data from Voyager 1, researchers found the heliopause is thinner and less changeable by solar cycles than thought previously, the New York Times reports.The New York Times reports that the sun creates the heliosphere bubble by blowing solar wind, or charged particles that are mostly hydrogen.University of Iowa Professor Don Gurnett told the New York Times that solar winds clash with interstellar winds in the bubble's outer region, which could explain why a sharp boundary was formed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 08:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917496/3917496_357CB23AAE46409B97204C916DFDE210_191107_3917496_Voyagers_find_new_clues_about_the_solar_system_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3AB/46B/3AB46B58F6C5D3FD0F612FA9457C0385.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Voyagers, Voyager 1, Voyager 2, sun, solar system, heliosphere, heliopause, NASA, US, solar wind, solar winds, interstellar wind winds, interstellar, outer space, space TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.3 Million pound house is making people 'ill'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PINNER, MIDDLESEX, U.K  One home in the U.K, is making headlines for its strange decor.  The home in Pinner, Middlesex has been making headlines for its' unusual interior after it was listed on Rightmove, a U.K real estate company for a cool 1.3 million pounds which is about 1.7 million dollars.The detached five-bedroom "family haven" has puzzled would-be buyers and netizens with its strange - and large collection of plug sockets and recessed lighting.Every wall appears to be absolutely covered in sockets. Sockets that're piled on top of one another and don't even lineup. The strange thing is, no one knows why, not even the homeowner. Speaking to The Sun Online, 45-year-old tech boss and homeowner, Devang Gandhi said the property was already like that when he bought it six years ago. "The sockets are very handy because you don't have to pull the cables.""Wherever you want to stick in the plug, you can stick it in for the TV, DVDs, stereos.""You have separate plugs for everything rather than having wires everywhere.""It's very nice."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 06:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917417/3917417_FD6637D9968849FFA613793A93F9066C_191107_3917417_1_3_Million_pound_house_is_making_people__ill__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/639/B25/639B252655CBA9D26D0A13657728DE8B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[House with sockets, house with lots of sockets, house with sockets, house makes people ill, home DIY, too many plugs house, strange house, strange decor, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App developers had improper access to user info on Facebook</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook says roughly 100 app developers had improper access to user data from video streaming apps and social media management apps through admins that authorized the apps' access to Facebook groups.According to a news release from the company, at least 11 apps accessed names and profile pictures of group members in the past 60 days even though Facebook says it made changes in April 2018 to prevent app developers from accessing this information.The company explained that following the changes, group members had to opt-in in order to allow apps to access their information.Facebook says it has since removed this access for those app developers even though the social media giant says it didn't find any evidence of the apps abusing their access to user information.The company didn't mention how many users were affected by the breach.Facebook has been working to restrict developer access to user data since March 2018, following the Cambridge Analytica scandal in which the consulting firm gained access to user data from 87 million Facebook users, CNBC reports. As a result, the company suspended tens of thousands of apps in September.The social media giant was also ordered to pay a US$5 billion fine to the Federal Trade Commission over its privacy policies.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 03:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917340/3917340_9F8AE3E65A3749309F4DA852D91EF00C_191107_3917340_App_developers_had_improper_access_to_user_info__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/750/2E9/7502E9E7493302FCE8272BF4069C0678.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Facebook, facebook privacy, facebook scandals, facebook user data scandal, facebook privacy concerns, facebook data breach, app developers could access user info on facebook, facebook user data breach, facebook software developers, facebook software developers access user data, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers to pay people $3,300 to be infected with H1N1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARYLAND  Getting sick with the flu could get you a couple of Gs from scientists eager to study the pesky little virus.According to WBALTV, researchers at the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases are looking for volunteers to participate in a flu study, for the generous sum of $3,300.All participants need to do is get the H1N1 virus sprayed up their sniffer, and stay a week in an inpatient facility until they stop being infectious.During that time, researchers are hoping to glean as much information as they can from the sneezing, heaving, feverish virus-filled volunteers. Sounds like a lovely time.Curiously, there's not much info about treatment, but it's a medical facility  surely they'll administer one...right?Guess there's at least the sweet sweet cash. Worth it?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 02:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917322/3917322_62CA1990D11541D4B83866BECE756880_191107_3917322_Researchers_to_pay_people__3_300_to_be_infected__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F17/662/F176627829300DD7C4EF2C7725B49617.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Flu research, H1N1 virus, H1N1, flu, flu test, paid research, flu season, flu symptoms, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild boar frozen in fear on a Chinese glass walkway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHUN'AN, CHINA  A wild boar was found on a glass walkway frozen to the spot.The pig pressed himself to the side of the walkway before lying down, likely out of fear of the 230-meter drop. According to the video, officers from the local forestry bureau reached the scene and rescued the boar.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 13:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918248/3918248_F3D039D216BB4D8EB70D4F9FC40729F4_191108_3918248_Wild_boar_frozen_in_fear_on_a_Chinese_glass_walk_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B7C/25E/B7C25E173B70349640BFA687FC1FA2CA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Boar on Chinese bridge, Chinese glass bridges, glass-bottom bridge fails, bridge fails, glass slides, glass walkways, glass bridge in China, China bridge fails, Chinese boars, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China parking lot has super wide spaces for female drivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGSU, CHINA  A parking lot in China has come up with an ingenious plan to help female drivers.  According to NetEase, a parking structure in the Jiangsu city of Taizhou has unveiled a "women-only" section with super duper large spaces, because as we all knowwomen have a really tough time when it comes to parking.   And because the spots are reserved for females, they are also painted pretty in pink.Reports say the spaces are apparently 50 percent bigger than regular parking spaces for manly men.  But of course since these parking spots are made in China, they're clearly not all the same size. Maybe the bigger ones are for the fatter female drivers?? Either way, China is clearly leaps and bounds ahead of the West when it comes to battling sexism and discrimination. The Me Too movement could stand to learn a few things from the trailblazers out in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 13:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918242/3918242_92CDCFA7C3E5417BA8C6DCA401F4D191_191108_3918242_China_parking_lot_has_super_wide_spaces_for_fema_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2CC/8B1/2CC8B13393811FE163AC7B4A0B7467E0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China female only parking spots, China female only parking spots, China extra wide parking spots, extra wide parking spots women, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army of cockroaches found camping out in man's ear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUIZHOU, CHINA  A 24-year-old man complaining of strange scratching noises in his ear was happy to hear it was only a small gang of cockroaches. According to a report on Weibo, the guy was at home in the Guangdong city of Huizhou sleeping one night last month, when he woke up because of sharp painful scratches inside his ear. After having a family member have a quick peek into his right ear, he was suggested to immediately get his butt over to the hospital.The man rushed himself over to the emergency room at Sanhe Hospital at around 4:40 a.m., understandably looking pretty freaked out.When ENT doctors had a look inside, they were shocked to find not one, not two, not three, but a small ARMY of cockroaches taking up residence in dude's ear canal. To be exact, there was one big mother cockroach and then 10 adorable little baby roaches.   Doctors found some minor damage to the man's ear canal, but nothing serious. He was discharged the same day and sent packing with some ointment and cream.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 12:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918218/3918218_C25373158E3541F6A7BA7DBAC5F46F83_191108_3918218_Army_of_cockroaches_found_camping_out_in_man_s_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F8/91C/8F891CDAC9559A8D3506D232932F8A25.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cockroach, cockroaches, cockroaches in ear, China cockroaches in ear, family of cockroaches, China cockroach ear, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China orders online gaming curfew for minors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Fun-loving Chinese officials have decided to drop the hammer on online video games for minors in an attempt to battle gaming addiction. According to the BBC, the super fun restrictions were released on Tuesday by the CCP. Gamers under 18 will now have a curfew. They'll be banned from playing online games between 10 p.m. at night until 8 a.m. in the morning.The new rules say they will also be limited to 90 minutes of gaming during the week and three hours on weekends and holidays. The BBC reports that the new guidelines also have restrictions on how much minors can spend. Gaming aficionados between 8 to 16 years old can spend up to $29 dollars a month, while 16 to 18 year olds can blow up to 57 bucks on their gaming accounts. According to NPR, Chinese officials will also require everyone to register accounts for online games using their real name and phone number, so it's easier for the government to track how much you're playing. Jesusnanny much??China is one of the world's biggest gaming markets. According to market research firm Niko Partners, digital gaming revenue in China will hit $33 billion in 2019. Will these new rules actually help cut down on gaming addiction? Or will we suddenly see an increase in parents of these gamers suddenly registering for online games?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 12:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918215/3918215_678946A5C48E420ABFA5F0B6CB4A3822_191108_3918215_China_orders_online_gaming_curfew_for_minors_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DFD/424/DFD424955BE0A8D5042C9E8BE4C89325.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China online gaming, China online gaming curfew, China gaming curfew, China gaming curfew minors, online gaming, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British tourist eaten by shark while on vacation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REUNION ISLAND, FRANCE  An unnamed tourist from the UK was vacationing with his wife in Reunion Island when tragedy struck.The man and his wife were spending a week-long vacation on the island when the 44-year-old decided to go on a swim by himself on November 2, the Herald Scotland reports. His wife reported the man as missing when he didn't return from his swim. Authorities then launched a full search including a helicopter and boats.Even divers were called to look around the coral reef in the area, while sniffer dogs were patrolling the island.Eventually scientists examined five fish caught around Reunion Island and found a severed hand with a wedding ring inside one of the shark's stomach.The man himself has yet to be found. According to the report, the man may have drowned and his corpse could have attracted the shark to chomp down on his hand.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 03:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3917876/3917876_600C6774589E40B1976ADDF062793383_191108_3917876_British_tourist_eaten_by_shark_while_on_vacation_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15E/32B/15E32B1F13F2D810E1066A08E6223828.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[British swimmer, british tourist, british tourist stories, tourist eaten by shark, british tourist eaten by shark, shark attack stories, craziest shark attack stories, shark attack stories 2019, fatal shark attack, fatal shark attack stories, animated shark attack stories, crazy holiday stories, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Air Force is researching orbital solar power systems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALBUQUERQUE, NEW MEXICO  The U.S. Air Force wants a space system to generate solar energy and then beams it to forward operating bases.The U.S. Air Force wants to develop a system that generates solar energy in space, converts it to radio frequencies, and then beams it to forward operating bases."Colonel Eric Felt told Stars and Stripes, "Energy is a strategic enabler and potential vulnerability for our nation."Remote outposts that rely on fuel for energy need to be supplied by convoys and protective escorts, which the enemy could target.The air force states that harnessing solar energy in space offers advantages such as providing power around the clock in all weather conditions.The project developers also said another application of the system is to supply energy to remote communities.According to Stars and Stripes, the system is envisioned as a constellation of satellites with ten thousand square meters of solar panels.The solar energy system would steer its beams at specific locations electrically, rather than having to turn mechanical arrays.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 02:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/09/3918392/3918392_F294242F5C8643C3A1CD72987A2B4DE2_191109_3918392_The_U_S__Air_Force_is_researching_orbital_solar__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C94/79A/C9479A7EEEBF14C152714DB365E60A9F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Space-based solar power, space, solar power, solar energy, SSPIDR, Space Solar Power Incremental Demonstration and Research, US, air force, Northrop Grumman, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shoots neighbor in the chest with crossbow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST LOTHIAN, SCOTLAND  A Scottish man was shot in the chest with an arrow after a feud with a crazed neighbor.The High Court in Glasgow was told Raph Muir got into an argument with Shaun Reynolds over "anti-social behavior," the Daily Record reports.Muir then grabbed two crossbows he kept at home and aimed one of them at Reynolds' chest. The 31-year-old was heard screaming at Reynolds saying, "I'm not leaving here until you are dead."Reynolds ended up with an arrow stuck in his chest, which he pulled out.The 46-year-old only sustained one "superficial" wound on his chest.Scottish firearms police officers arrived at the scene and ordered Muir to lie on the ground and then arrested him. While searching his home, the police found three crossbows, a chainsaw, a baseball bat and a knife.According to the Daily Record, the Muir later told the police that he wanted to "murder people" who bothered him while he was at home.The crossbow attacker pled guilty to attempted murder at the High Court in Glasgow. He now faces a lengthy jail term and is due to be sentenced next month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 12:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/11/3919502/3919502_A7C824CC5DE547D5B3F6959A6D2BF65F_191111_3919502_Man_shoots_neighbor_in_the_chest_with_crossbow_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/142/CF4/142CF421FDB42B18121E418C3FF6E7FB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man arrow chest, man shoots neighbor with crossbow, crossbow shooting, crossbow shooting scotland, man ends up with crossbow arrow on chest, man crossbow arrow chest, crossbow targets, crossbow shooting stories, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Bloomberg warming up for 2020 White House race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALABAMA  Looks like the Democratic race for the White House in 2020 just became a little less of a snoozefest as billionaire former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg signals he's ready to rumblemaybe.According to the failing New York Times, Bloomberg submitted paperwork last Friday ahead of a deadline to enter the 2020 presidential primary in Alabama.The move is a necessary step to join the scramble to take on the Teflon Don in next year's election. The 77-year-old towering giant has yet to formally announce his candidacy, but many of his friends and allies say he intends to throw down. That's because he apparently thinks the current Democratic candidates all suck. He may be right.The overstuffed Democratic field currently has hands on Joe Biden, Native-American Elizabeth Warren and heart stopping Sanders leading the pack.The problem with Biden is that he's a borderline idiot, while Warren and Sanders are way too progressive for the average U.S. voter. As for Trump, he told reporters on Friday that, "there is nobody I'd rather run against than little Michael."Wellif the Democrats continue on their current trajectory, Trump may just get his wish.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 12:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/11/3919496/3919496_DE231FA0DF24473B99DA760C66D9756F_191111_3919496_Michael_Bloomberg_warming_up_for_2020_White_Hous_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/040/5F3/0405F3E595394F8DE68582442A4FEAC2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Michael Bloomberg, Michael Bloomberg president, Michael Bloomberg presidential bid, Bloomberg v Trump, Micheal Bloomberg Democtratic candidate, Bloomberg White House 2020, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critically endangered porpoise
found dead with bricks tied to it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YUEYANG, CHINA  Chinese fishermen discovered a critically endangered Yangtze Finless Porpoise dead in a lake in the most barbaric way imaginable. According to a post on Weibo by Toutiao news, fisherman of Dongting Lake in Yueyang alerted authorities when they came across the dead animal on Thursday. Photo and video evidence posted by the East Dongting Ecological Protection Association documented an 18-centimeter long slash down the animal's belly, and how a rope with two bricks on the end had been tied to its tail.The porpoise measured 1.52 meters in length and weighed 43 kilograms.According to WWF, The Yangtze Finless Porpoise is critically endangered with an estimated population between a mere 1,000 and 1,800.The Yangtze Finless Porpoise is known for its "mischievous smile" and high level of intelligence comparable to that of a gorilla.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 05:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/11/3919279/3919279_88489C554FFA4B30BB6F5D690FF7C031_191111_3919279_Critically_endangered_porpoise_found_dead_with_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DA3/ADD/DA3ADD4FC1579A978635077F442F7AC5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Yangtze Finless Porpoise, Chinese Porpoise, Porpoise found dead with bricks tied to it, animals protection, endangered species, critically endangered, endangered animals, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First new HIV strain identified in nearly 20 years: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ABBOTT PARK, ILLINOIS  A joint study by Abbott Laboratories and the University of Missouri has identified a new subtype of the HIV strain for the first time in 19 years.A press release from Abbott Laboratories explains that three different samples of the HIV virus were obtained from the Democratic Republic of Congo, one in 1983, one in 1990 and a third one in 2001.Scientists weren't able to test the third sample because technologies at the time prevented the researchers from doing so. Now, scientists have developed next-generation sequencing technology to allow them to build a complete genome sequence from the third HIV sample.After analyzing the HIV virus, the researchers have identified it as the HIV-1 Group M subtype L.In the news release, one of the authors of the study, Mary Rodgers, principal scientist at Abbott Laboratories, said that identifying new viruses is like "searching for a needle in a haystack."Rodgers added that the new sequencing technology was like a "magnet" that allowed them to find the needle.According to CNN, current HIV treatments are able to fight different types of virus strains. It is believed to be able to fight this newly identified HIV strain as well.The study concluded by saying that additional strains of HIV could be spreading around in the Democratic Republic of Congo or elsewhere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 02:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/11/3919209/3919209_D6AD4EB4D3EC45EFBD3EFA3E45B07978_191111_3919209_First_new_HIV_strain_identified_in_nearly_20_yea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5AC/206/5AC20600F16E4C288C8542D43698112C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[HIV, HIV strain, new HIV strain, new HIV strain discovered,  HIV virus, HIV strains, hiv strains and subtypes, evolution of HIV, scientists detect new strain of HIV, discovering new HIV strain, new HIV subtype, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clownfish use UV light vision under the sea: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. LUCIA, AUSTRALIA  A joint study from the University of Queensland and the University of Maryland has found that a particular species of clownfish called the Amphiprion akindynos is able to see ultraviolet light.Sara Stieb, a researcher involved with the study, explained in a University of Queensland news release that these fish live close to the water's surface, where UV light is able to easily penetrate through water.The study says that part of these fish's eyes have photoreceptors that are able to detect both ultraviolet light and violet light. With UV light vision, the fish can identify their kind as white stripes on a clownfish reflect ultraviolet light.This unique ability allows clownfish to communicate with one another over short distances as bigger fish aren't able to see UV light.The fish also uses ultraviolet light to find food it typically eats such as zooplankton. These appear as darker dots as they absorb UV light, making it easier for clownfish to locate them.Stieb said that the fact that these fish have this special ability makes sense because of their environment and what they consume.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3920012/3920012_6B5BE6C3A3DA4BF587D30DD3FDABD01B_191112_3920012_Clownfish_use_UV_light_vision_under_the_sea__Stu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F38/175/F38175A5B9BBD00C6F67C6B04AB7D7BD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Clownfish, finding nemo fish, clownfish UV light, clownfish can see UV light, fish sees UV light, ultraviolet light fish, fish sees ultraviolet light, Finding nemo fish sees ultraviolet light, finding nemo fish UV light, Amphiprion akindynos, seeing UV light, fish sees UV light, Amphiprion akindynos UV light, anemonefish, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protester shot by cop at point-blank range</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Police in Hong Kong fired three live rounds during a city-wide strike, hitting at least one pro-democracy protester.RTHK reports that around 7:15 a.m. on Monday, masked protesters throwing debris onto an intersection in Hong Kong's Sai Wan Ho were confronted by a traffic policeman.In a live video posted by Cupid News, a protester in a white hoodie is seen approaching the officer, who reaches for his service pistol.The officer initially pointed his gun at the man at point-blank range, before putting him in a headlock.When another protester approached, the policeman turned his gun on him and fired a round into his torso from a distance of less than half a meter.Two more people, one in black and one in gray, came forward to grapple with the officer, who then fired two more shots. In the video, the protester in black can be seen falling to the ground.Riot police soon arrived to help subdue a large crowd of angry people. They had begun demanding an explanation for the shooting, and were pepper sprayed in return.According to the Hong Kong Free Press, an anonymous source told Ming Pao that two people had been shot, and that the first one, identified only as a 21-year-old man, was injured in the kidney and liver, with his renal vein crushed.He had needed cardiopulmonary resuscitation after his heart stopped once, and CNN reports that he remains in critical condition according to the Hong Kong Hospital Authority.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 12:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919992/3919992_63EE761E1EC8438780334489579CA0D6_191112_3919992_Hong_Kong_protester_shot_by_cop_at_point_blank_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4BF/7E4/4BF7E4566A3852E140EBC77BB1B8710D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[HK protest, Hong Kong protester, HK protester shot, Hong Kong police, HK police, Hong Kong, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk wants to build offshore ports for SpaceX rocket ships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HAWTHRONE, CALIFORNIA  SpaceX is developing Starships, reusable rocket systems that will be used for fast travelling and space exploration.According to SpaceX, Starship's first stage booster named Super Heavy features 37 Raptor engines that will make Starships the most powerful launch systems ever built.Super Heavy is designed to separate from Starship and land itself while the spacecraft continues on its trajectory with its six Raptor thrusters.The Super Heavy booster and Starship will both be capable of reentry and reuse.SpaceX CEO Elon Musk told Space.com that the design utilizes 301 stainless steel because it is cost effective and resilient to the heat of atmospheric reentry.SpaceX claims that Starships will be fast enough to go between anywhere on Earth in less than an hour.Musk tweeted in June that a Starship will carry one hundred passengers in its cabin and up to a thousand when using its cargo hold.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 12:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919976/3919976_01C81E0DF63D483CA7058D9A9C85CEBD_191112_3919976_Elon_Musk_wants_to_build_offshore_ports_for_Spac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/94B/33D/94B33DB63A0B709BF836932DCECDEB51.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Elon Musk, Musk, SpaceX, Starship, spaceport, offshore space port, super heavy, orbital vehicle, space, big falcon rocket, bfr, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speeding Porsche goes airborne into second story of building</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOMS RIVER, NEW JERSEY  A speeding Porsche lost control and went airborne into the second story of an unoccupied New Jersey building.According to CBS New York, two men are sadly no longer around after a freak morning accident on November 10.Police say 22-year-old Branden DeMartin was driving a Porsche Boxster with 23-year-old Daniel Foley in the passenger seat. According to authorities, the sports car was traveling northbound on Hooper Avenue at Fast and Furious speeds. The car then appears to have lost control and crossed over the southbound lanes, before hitting the curb. The Porsche then started tumbling before hitting a ditch which launched it up into the second floor of an office building, landing upside down.  Police say it was around 6:30 a.m. when the vehicle and bodies were found. CBS New York reported that firefighters and other responders pushed out bricks out of the way, so that a crane could lift the car out around noon. After the Boxster was towed away, investigators stayed on scene for several more hours.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919953/3919953_4E4918EDAC3F4838A28E7AEF9A26B5B6_191112_3919953_Speeding_Porsche_goes_airborne_into_second_story_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FCE/135/FCE1355BAE1FAEAEFB9AF8EA4A2F3EE5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Porsche accident, Porsche crash New Jersey, Porsche crash Toms River, Porsche crashes 2nd story, Porsche accident 2nd floor, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk wants to build offshore ports for SpaceX rocket ships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HAWTHRONE, CALIFORNIA  SpaceX is developing Starships, reusable rocket systems that will be used for fast travelling and space exploration.According to SpaceX, Starship's first stage booster named Super Heavy features 37 Raptor engines that will make Starships the most powerful launch systems ever built.Super Heavy is designed to separate from Starship and land itself while the spacecraft continues on its trajectory with its six Raptor thrusters.The Super Heavy booster and Starship will both be capable of reentry and reuse.SpaceX CEO Elon Musk told Space.com that the design utilizes 301 stainless steel because it is cost effective and resilient to the heat of atmospheric reentry.SpaceX claims that Starships will be fast enough to go between anywhere on Earth in less than an hour.Musk tweeted in June that a Starship will carry one hundred passengers in its cabin and up to a thousand when using its cargo hold.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919910/3919910_8006FDB1D55442E3AE15AE5EA1145A72_191112_3919910_Elon_Musk_wants_to_build_offshore_ports_for_Spac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AC7/6B5/AC76B5BDA49C36056F8A55D672892E6B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Elon Musk, Musk, SpaceX, Starship, spaceport, offshore space port, super heavy, orbital vehicle, space, big falcon rocket, bfr, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes workers spotting making chicken sandwich on trash can</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FAIRFAX, VIRGINIA  As Popeyes chicken sandwich continues to cause chaos in overcrowded lines across America, it looks like things are pretty nuts behind the scenes as well. Stomach-gurgling photos obtained by TMZ show Popeyes workers at one restaurant in Fairfax actually putting the sandwiches together over a garbage can in the kitchen. TMZ reports that the snaps were taken last Friday and show one employee working like a maniac slapping them together on top of a tray that was resting on top of a trash canYUMMY!According to the owner of the franchise shop, the restaurant had only been open a few days, and then it happened to get hit with a 100 chicken sandwich order. The owner also tried to shift the blame, telling TMZ that all the employees were brand new and didn't know any better. He also said the trash bin was empty at the time. Ohthat's reassuring.He has since ordered a table which arrived this week, so unfortunately, no more trash can chicken sandwiches.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 10:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919900/3919900_60CA842F618A4FDA8E5ED8682437C2CF_191112_3919900_Popeyes_workers_spotting_making_chicken_sandwich_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C9E/917/C9E91730CB10EEBCD7F6BD0595F34DBB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Popeyes, Popeyes Chicken Sandwich, Popeyes chicken sandwich trash can, Popeyes chicken sandwich on trash can, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender reveal party causes plane crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TUKEY, TEXAS  An unnamed couple in West Texas chose innovation over safety when they used a crop-duster to reveal the gender of their baby on September 7th.The intended plan was to pour 350 gallons of pink water by the gender reveal party, instead, the plane crashed. According to an accident report by the National Transportation Safety Board, 49-year-old pilot and friend of the couple Raj Horan was flying at a low altitude with a passenger when the plane "got too slow" and stalled before crashing and flipping over.  An inspector of the National Transportation Safety Board also noted that the aircraft wasn't designed to carry two people, and was actually a single-seat plane.Pilot Raj Horan was not injured, however, his passenger Jennifer J. Hurrell suffered minor injuries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919803/3919803_510B227A359845EAB6EDDD02FE0B32C6_191112_3919803_Gender_reveal_party_causes_plane_crash_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F45/FC5/F45FC57A90FBBE2477FB110AD53A5D4A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Gender reveal gone wrong, gender reveal party accidents, gender reveal party, plane crash gender reveal, gender reveal accidents, gender reveal fails, plane fails, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inebriated man busts jet door, delays flight in Thailand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Thailand  A "crazed" flier tore the emergency door right off the hinges moments before an airplane's scheduled takeoff, according to the Bangkok Post.A drunk bubba ripped open the emergency exit of an Airbus A320 in Thailand on Thursday in a desperate bid to do we don't know what.Fox News reports that other passengers saw a foreign male "explode in a bizarre outburst" on the Chiang Mai to Bangkok flight on Thursday afternoon.The unnamed man then ran down to the emergency exit over the left wing and proceeded to brute force the thing, Fox News cites the airline as saying.Did we say that the plane was just about to take off? Because it was.The man popped the door clean off the cabin wall in a stupendous display of, well, stupid strength, causing the emergency slide to inflate and 86 sober passengers to scream in terrified chorus.Thai police tackled the maniac and dragged him off the plane, but his antics delayed flight for an hour and caused over $19,700 property damage.The Bangkok Post reports that Thailand's aviation authorities have yet to identify the motive behind the insane escapade.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919681/3919681_34035883FB2648A5A0DDCF5334E402A4_191112_3919681_Inebriated_man_busts_jet_door__delays_flight_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/991/E23/991E23E7BFDFE842029067A5BBF50025.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Angry man, drunk man, Airbus, A320, emergency exit, emergency door, Chiang Mai, Bangkok, Thailand TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby fish found consuming plastic waste, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONOLULU  A new study led by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration's Pacific Islands Fisheries Science Center has found prey-size plastics present in larval fish nurseries in surface slicks off the west coast of the island of Hawaii.According to a news release from the NOAA, surface slicks are created when waves converge near coastlines and form ribbons of smooth water. These contain large amounts of plankton for larval fish that live in the surface slicks.The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, found seven times more plastic present in the surface slicks than larval fish.Researchers also found that plastics were 126 times more concentrated in the slicks than surface water off the coast of the same island.Scientists involved in the study dissected hundreds of larval fish from the surface slicks and found that pelagic fish species, including swordfish and mahi-mahi, and larval fish, such as triggerfish, all contained tiny pieces of plastic in their stomachs.This is the first time these fish species have been found consuming plastic just days after being spawned.Jamison Gove, a researcher from the NOAA who was involved with the study, stated in the agency's news release that it is alarming that larval fish are surrounded by plastic waste and are consuming plastic at such a vulnerable stage in their life.Scientists are unsure of the impact of plastic ingestion on larval fish. The study says that plastic could affect their development or even reduce their rate of survival.Previous studies had found that plastic ingestion in adult fish causes gut blockage, malnutrition and accumulation of plastic toxins.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920490/3920490_8BD65718819B497A8C19DAA6B6C8CD5D_191113_3920490_Baby_fish_found_consuming_plastic_waste__study_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2A0/FF1/2A0FF19B571C32AED1FB3769AF063C47.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Larval fish nurseries, plastic in larval fish nurseries, pre-size plastic, fish nursery habitat plastic, hawaii fish nurseries, hawaii island, plastic pollution, plastic waste, plastic contamination, plastic in ocean, surface slicks, surface slicks plastic, surface slicks plastic pollution, surface slicks larval fish nurseries, surface slicks fish nurseries plastic, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters clash with police at universities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Ongoing protests have been taking place in Hong Kong for 24 consecutive weeks.Around midday on November 12, protesters in black clothing as well as office workers took to the streets and occupied an intersection in the city's business district, Central. The police fired tear gas in the afternoon and detained roughly 12 people, CNN reports. According to the Hong Kong Free Press, separate protests took place at a campus of the Chinese University of Hong Kong on the same day. Masked protesters in black had put up barricades on the university campus to prevent the police from entering in the morning.This led to a clash between the protesters and the police in the afternoon as activists threw bricks and petrol bombs at the officers while the officers fired tear gas and projectiles into the campus.According to CNN, this caused an empty car to catch on fire.Protesters also dropped bricks from a footbridge at Hong Kong Polytechnic University while other protesters throw chairs and traffic cones at passing traffic from another footbridge near the University of Hong Kong.This comes a day after a 21-year-old protester was shot in the torso by a police officer at point-blank range.Protests began in June over an extradition bill that would allow suspects to be extradited for trial to mainland China.Those against the bill believe that Beijing may use it as a way to extradite political activists, dissidents and other critics in the city. The protests have now snowballed into massive anti-government and pro-democracy protests.The Hong Kong government has since suspended the bill, though the activists still have four other unmet demands, the BBC reports. The fifth demand, which was to suspend the bill, has already been met.The four other demands include: amnesty for all the protesters who were arrested, an independent investigation into alleged police brutality; implementing complete universal suffrage across the city; and for the Hong Kong government to stop characterizing the protests as "riots."The Hong Kong government has not officially suspended classes, though some schools and universities have announced cancellation of classes due to the ongoing protests, CNN reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 12:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920481/3920481_AB11831A0A6A4648B8F3B9B763D5970D_191113_3920481_Hong_Kong_protesters_clash_with_police_at_univer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/485/5BF/4855BF9E749FC9AF4C178193A8048D12.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong protests, HK protests, China extradition protests, Hong Kong protest 2019, Chinese University of Hong Kong, Chinese University of Hong Kong protests, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney+ slammed with technical glitches on launch day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BURBANK, CALIFORNIA  Disney launched its much anticipated online streaming service Disney+ on Tuesday in selected areas, only to be immediately slammed by technical glitches. BBC reports that social media was flooded with people complaining about problems accessing the site, while other users shared screenshots of Disney-themed error messages. According to glitch-tracker Down Detector, there were only 8,300 complaints about Disney+ issues over a 15-minute period starting at 9 a.m. Eastern Standard Time. Reuters reported that some people trying to get on Disney+ were instead treated to a Mickey Mouse on a blue screen, with a message telling them to exit the app and try again. According to Reuters, other users had trouble locating the Disney+ app in Apple's App Store.  Disney claims that the glitches were caused by excessive demand. Disney+ hasn't been rolled out worldwide yet. It's currently only available in the U.S., Canada and the Netherlands.The service costs $7 a month and features about 500 movies and 7,500 TV episodes. It was designed to take on Netflix and Amazon Prime. Disney said it was "working quickly" to fix all the glitches. Until then...Netflix anyone?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920421/3920421_8B5EA542890D4C05965ABCF47B43F31D_191113_3920421_Disney__slammed_with_technical_glitches_on_launc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/62D/BB8/62DBB8AC38E2B9466A81B57CD1FFBC3F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Disney, Disney+, Disney+ technical glitches, Disney+ glitches launch day, Disney+ streaming service, Disney+ vs Netflix, Netflix, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo monkey in China takes phone and goes online shopping</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHANGZHOU, CHINA  A crafty little monkey in China was able to get a hold of its keeper's smartphone and did what everyone else is doing these daysmade a bunch of online purchases. According to a report on Jiangsu TV, the hilarious incident happened at the Yancheng Wild Animal World in the Jiangsu city of Changzhou.Looks like zoo worker Lu Mengmeng was using her phone to look at some stuff online one day while she was working with the animal, when the monkey got hungry. Lu then left the room to get some food, but forgot to bring her phone. A few days later, a bunch of packages showed up at the office addressed to Lu. She thought it was strange because she didn't remember ordering anything. She then went back to check the surveillance video and found that the monkey was the culprit. Footage shows the monkey picking up the phone before going on an online shopping spree. Lu told media that the monkey has grown up watching her play on her phone and make purchases over Chinese e-commerce site Taobao. Apparently the monkey knows how to shop too, because Lu says she plans on keeping the stuff. Guess that's what you call monkey business.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920417/3920417_2D9C5D2B9DCE45139F5A27067C993BDA_191113_3920417_Zoo_monkey_in_China_takes_phone_and_goes_online__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F00/F8B/F00F8B0DE27C0A7C9196F5C2A283C7B8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Monkey makes online purchases, monkey online purchases, Chinese zoo monkey, China zoo monkey online orders, zoo monkey uses smartphone, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese man crashes his car straight into a hospital</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A BMW came crashing through a hospital waiting room on Saturday, narrowly missing a mother and her two children. As the mother holds her infant, the car smashes through the door sending her and her children sliding across the floor before hitting the ground.Unfortunately, a sleeping man takes the brunt of the impact and is pushed backward by the force before being flipped over and wedged in by the car. After a second, a man appears from the passenger side surprisingly undisturbed, leaving with a baby in his arms.The footage has since made its rounds on Chinese social media with netizens speculating the urgency of the man's need to get his baby to the hospital. The accident location is so far unreported as is the reason why this happened.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920397/3920397_B1C210996EAA4735BABEFB05314A566E_191113_3920397_Chinese_man_crashes_his_car_straight_into_a_hosp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6D4/F48/6D4F4859EDDF92F0979419B94214D82C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man crashes car hospital, Chinese driver fail, Car accident, Chinese car accident, crash into hospital, car crash,  Chinese viral video, car crashes into hospital, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan man uses battle ax to strike down home intruder</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KALAMAZOO, MICHIGAN  A man in Michigan managed to hold his own during a home invasion thanks to some eccentric hobbies.According to Wood TV, 36-year-old Ben Ball was playing video games in his Kalamazoo apartment late Wednesday night when someone who once dated his ex-roommate came knockin' and eventually kicked the door in.Now, a more conventional American household would have a gun or baseball bat around to use as a weapon, but not Ben. Ben does ritualized combat for fun, and has an arsenal of replica weapons from the Middle Ages.So when that intruder burst in, your man Ben thought fast and grabbed a battle ax replica that he calls "my baby." He wielded it against the intruder, 33-year-old Alex Rawls, striking him once in the torso.The pair then grappled with each other all around the apartment and pretty much destroyed the place before Rawls finally made a run for it.Police who arrived at the scene deployed a K9 unit to follow the trail of blood that Rawls oh-so-conveniently left. Kalamazoo County officials say Rawls' wounds were substantial enough that he had to spend a night at the hospital before being thrown to jail, and is now facing home invasion charges.Officials say avoiding robbers or intruders is usually the best course of action for most folks. Not everyone does combat every weekend and has an arsenal of weapons stashed at home, but hey,  if you got the goods, use 'em.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 08:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920344/3920344_780CF8CE728948BF9557B8FED1B30632_191113_3920344_Michigan_man_uses_battle_ax_to_strike_down_home__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/914/56D/91456DB7DF5FC389EF48C6A6396A933D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Home intruder, battle axe, medieval weapons, ritualized combat, medieval combat, man axes home intruder, battle axe replica, LARP, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New sustainable international airport planned for Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  British architectural firm Zaha Hadid Architects and Sydney-based Cox Architecture have won a competition to build the new Western Sydney International Airport.According to the British architectural firm's website, the airport draws inspiration from landscape surrounding the area and the region's cultural heritage.The new airport will make use of a sustainable design to allow sunlight to enter its interior. The airport's eco-friendly design will also include natural ventilation and water recycling to increase energy efficiency.The airport will be built in four stages. The project's initial stage is expected to be completed in 2026.The airport will be able to accommodate 10 million annual passengers after the first stage is complete, according to Zaha Hadid Architects. The number of passengers will increase to up to 82 million once the entire project is complete in 2060.Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison told ABC News Australia that the airport is set to become the largest gateway to Australia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 05:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920247/3920247_F95A6949E6EC494885757E487AA80F9C_191113_3920247_New_sustainable_international_airport_planned_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C38/4C9/C384C9CE647CEC3AC7AE479FD4C4C069.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Architecture, Western Sydney Airport, Sydney Airport, Zaha Hadid architecture, Cox architecture, western sydney airport design, western sydney airport construction, new western sydney airport, western sydney news, western sydney airport competition, winning western sydney airport design, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese woman wants to give away her extra kidney</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINYU, CHINA  A woman with three kidneys from the city of Xinyu in China's Jiangxi province is looking to give one away, according to Peach Video.The unnamed woman had frequent urges for number one and pains in the waist that flares up if she slept for more than six hours. Ouch!Having enough of this nonsense, our kind hearted heroine went to the hospital.After some x-rays, the doctor told the unnamed woman that she has a triple. No, not three babies, three kidneys, with an extra on the right. Although the woman volunteered to donate the surplus organ, no surgery was performed.Doctors told Peach Video that they generally favor "more conservative treatment plans" and the would be good samaritan is recovering.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920161/3920161_F68F208549694CA9AF4F98962D501599_191113_3920161_Chinese_woman_wants_to_give_away_her_extra_kidne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BFE/DA1/BFEDA127D215DD895F9B03500F3DCFE0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Kidneys, extra kidney, Xinyu, Jiangxi, China, medical, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless guy dumps bucket of hot mudbutt on L.A. woman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  A woman had herself quite a crappy night after some random guy dumped a bucket of hot man-made chocolate sauce over her head. NBC Los Angeles reported that Heidi Van Tassel was getting into her car after dinner near the Hollywood Walk of Fame when it quickly turned into the walk of shame. According to NBC L.A., a male resident of the streets ran across Hollywood Boulevard and got her out of the vehicle, and into the middle of the street. That's when he introduced a bucket of hot runny twos right onto her dome.Unfortunately, the human Hershey's syrup then got everywhere all because of some gravity. NBC Los Angeles reported that paramedics arrived and rushed Van Tassel to Hollywood Presbyterian Hospital where she was then tested for infectious diseases. She now needs to be retested every three months.  According to court records, the man with muddbutt was identified as Jere Blessings, and was charged with battery and taken to jail. However because he had mental issues, he was eventually assigned to a residential facility for treatment. He was released in August. As for Van Tassel, she says the incident has given her PTSD. In this case, guess that means post traumatic stress doo doo.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 11:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/14/3920970/3920970_0447E6AB62ED4CDB9A2D58A399F6CCA5_191114_3920970_Homeless_guy_dumps_bucket_of_hot_mudbutt_on_L_A__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE1/882/CE1882CB1ED1E5D3D4AC2737EFD6556C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Woman in L.A., man dumps bucket, man dumps bucket on woman, Heidi Van Tassel, Hollywood Walk of Fame, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murderer who briefly died says
his life sentence is now served</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IOWA  66-year-old Iowa inmate, Schreiber was sentenced to life without parole in 1997 for first-degree murder, but says since he died momentarily after falling ill, his life sentence is now served. Schreiber developed large kidney stones back in March 2015 which led to septic poisoning. Citing court documents, The Des Moines Register state that he was rushed to a local hospital where his heart was restarted five times.In April 2018, he filed for post-conviction relief claiming that because he died at the hospital, his life sentence has already been served and therefore should be released immediately.He goes on to say that he was sentenced to life without parole, "but not to life plus one day."The district court found his claim "unpersuasive and without merit."On Wednesday, the Iowa Court of Appeals backed the district court, agreeing that Benjamin Schreiber's sentence isn't up until a medical examiner declares he is deceased.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 10:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/14/3920933/3920933_698303D5CCBA4874B067B9AC5EA50C7C_191114_3920933_Murderer_who_briefly_died_says_his_life_sentence_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ED0/7B0/ED07B0719252401DBDD336146A8EF073.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Murderer says life sentence over, inmate briefly dies, prisoner dies, prisoner says life sentence served, prison death, prison fails, Murderer dies then resuscitated, Life Sentence complete, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans unveiled for Smart Forest City in Cancun, Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANCUN, MEXICO  Italian architectural firm Stefano Boeri Architetti has unveiled design plans for a "Smart Forest City" in Cancun.The site would consist of 400 hectares of green space and feature public parks and private gardens, according to the architectural firm's website. The Smart Forest City would contain green roofs and more than 200,000 trees that would be able to absorb approximately 116.000 tons of carbon dioxide.The company explained that the area would be surrounded by a ring of solar panels and agricultural fields to provide renewable energy and food for the city. The development's agricultural fields would be irrigated by a water channel connected to an underwater maritime pipe.The site would use electric and semi-automatic vehicles instead of traditional vehicles for both residents and visitors.Visitors to the forest city would be required to leave their traditional vehicles at the city's outer edge.According to Stefano Boeri Architetti, the development would house an advanced research center for international organizations and companies that are interested in our planet's sustainability issues.The proposed plan would reforest the area and build the Smart Forest City instead of a shopping district.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 05:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/14/3920774/3920774_96B37A09E9F74107AA823CC23F836AF9_191114_3920774_Plans_unveiled_for_Smart_Forest_City_in_Cancun___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/180/66F/18066F82DE963FE731A9DD62D451BDE1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Forest city, smart forest city, mexican smart forest city, smart forest city cancun, cancun mexico, cancun forest city, green forest city, forest city mexico, mexico green space, Stefano Boeri Architetti, Stefano Boeri Architetti forest city, Stefano Boeri Architetti smart forest city, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Protein: Vegetarians will soon feast on air-based meat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA  Air Protein says it has launched a meat substitute made of chemical compounds and other elements harvested from the air in a press release on Tuesday.CNet reports that the faux meat utilizes carbon dioxide, oxygen and nitrogen.According to Air Protein, a proprietary technology converts the elements into a protein that contains the same amino acids found in animal meat.The technology is developed from NASA's concept that recycles carbon dioxide from astronauts with microbes called hydrogenotrophs, which convert the gas into edible protein.The company says the process is a sustainable food production alternative that helps to reduce the use of agricultural chemicals and stress on arable land.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 02:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/14/3920698/3920698_4952E0C1D0A64D22ADBAB0BB41E02F1B_191114_3920698_Air_Protein__Vegetarians_will_soon_feast_on_air__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/531/40B/53140BA6C85595DB101351EF207F4282.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Air protein, Kiverdi, substitute meat, imitation meat, faux meat, vegetarian, vegetarianism, air based meat, sustainability, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese student falls off Huashan mountain while taking selfie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUASHAN MOUNTAIN   A Chinese University student met her untimely end while taking a selfie from one of China's most famous mountains.The Paper reports that at the end of October, university student Xiao Deng went up China's Huashan Mountain in Shaanxi  best known for its steep cliffs and deadly, pee-your-pants plank trails.The 21-year-old had been taking selfies all the way up the mountain and sharing it with classmates in a WeChat group, before suddenly going radio silent.Her university in Hunan went to the cops a day later, and told her family she was missing.Police checked the surveillance at Huashan, and saw that Deng had been taking a selfie on an observation deck on the western part of the mountain.While framing the shot, she made a misstep that caused her to fall back past the 60-centimeter chain fence and off the edge of the cliff to her death.The management at Huashan National Park said it wasn't responsible for the incident, since Deng was an adult who ignored safety warnings. Still, it said it would give the family "humanitarian aid" to the tune of 40,000 yuan, or $5,700.The girl's mom, though, thinks management is fully to blame, because of the too-low fence.I mean, sure, Huashan needs to step up its guardrail game and actually have one that does its job, but actions  like ignoring warnings  do have consequences.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921686/3921686_B9F31E87E4BA42EFA4B29BBAC654EF31_191115_3921686_Chinese_student_falls_off_Huashan_mountain_while_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/196/9D1/1969D19CE003AEDFDE89A9F5D82C1009.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Selfie death, chinese student, huashan, student falls off mountain, student falls off huashan, huashan mountain accident, selfie accident, huashan mountain, mount huashan, mountain cliff, dangerous mountains, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman goes blind in one eye from staring at phone too much</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA  A woman in China is looking at things a bit differently after losing sight in her left eye from over excessive mobile phone usage. According to a Pear Video report, a woman from Shenzhen in China's Guangdong province had spent an entire night staring into her smartphonenot so smart.When she woke up the next morning, after about five minutes things started to get blurry in her left eye until she couldn't see anything.Cyclops then hightailed it over to Songgang People's Hospital where doctors quickly zeroed in on the cause. Looking at her bright mobile screen all night had caused blood vessels to burst in her eye. Doctors said images taken of her eye revealed large patches of blood on her retina, obstructing her vision. Luckily for Left Eye, physicians were able to use a laser to drill a small hole in her retina to let the blood flow from the burst vessels, which allowed her to regain her vision. Reports say she's now recovering from the procedure. Hopefully someone gave her a phone to look at to pass the time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 12:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921595/3921595_15ACE7FAABC4445C994970B37B73C5CF_191115_3921595_Woman_goes_blind_in_one_eye_from_staring_at_phon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F6A/BCE/F6ABCECE01ABD9988C29325E1179F7F9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Woman goes blind phone, woman blind phone, woman blind phone usage, temporary blind phone usage, China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian airline passenger used a body double for his fat cat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  A Russian cat owner is now short a few hundred thousand air miles for sneaking his fat cat aboard a flight using a hairbrained scheme involving a cat double. He should have gotten away with it too, but for some unexplained reason, his air carrier Aeroflot found out. It was most likely entirely unrelated to the man's Facebook post about the entire thing. BBC reports that 34-year-old Mikhail Galin was flying from the Latvian capital of Riga to Vladivostok, which had a stopover in Moscow. Traveling with Mikhail was his furry feline friend Viktor. Everything was going along PURR-fectly, until Aeroflot staff refused to let Mikhail take Viktor into the passenger cabin for the second leg of his flight because of weight restrictions. Aeroflot rules state pets weighing more than 17 pounds have to be shoved in the luggage hold. Viktor was tipping the scales at 22 pounds.   So what did Galin do? He delayed his flight so he could find a skinnier cat double to pass the airline's weigh in. He returned the next day with the Viktor-lite version the next day and got past the check-in desk. Mikhail then gave back the smaller cat to its owner at the airport before getting on the plane with Viktor for his flight to Vladivostok. After his Facebook post about the entire ordeal went viral, Aeroflot took notice and decided to strip Galin of all his air miles.The cat was contacted for comment, however by the time of publication TomoNews wasn't yet able to find out whether Viktor's miles are still good.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 11:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921532/3921532_E867FC2F5F944F488105368F2835271D_191115_3921532_Russian_airline_passenger_used_a_body_double_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE3/3C6/EE33C6D3FEAD1CDC3C42CDA2FFEF7CF7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fat cat, cat body double, Aeroflot cat weight limit, passenger brings fat cat, body double cat Aeroflot, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffe hit by van dies and falls on jeep, killing Swiss tourist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KRUGER NATIONAL PARK, SOUTH AFRICA  A South African safari took a tragic turn on Sunday when a giraffe was hit by a tourist van, which then fell onto another passing jeep in Kruger National Park. CNN reports that a taxi van carrying 13 tourists was driving through the park when a giraffe suddenly stepped out onto the road.  After being struck by the taxi, the giraffe then fell on a rental safari vehicle carrying two occupants traveling in the opposite direction. The rental was driven by a Swiss national.  The collision unfortunately killed the giraffe and left the driver seriously injured. He later succumbed to his injuries at the hospital.  The passenger of the rental vehicle and two other tourists from the taxi van also suffered minor injuries. A press release from the South African National Parks urged the public "to always be watchful of all kinds of species while driving on the roads in the Park."The statement also added, "these animals have a right of way." According to CNN, giraffes stand from 14 to 19 feet tall and can weigh as much as 2,800 pounds. Both vehicles involved in the crash sustained serious damage. Park officials are now investigating the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 11:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921528/3921528_1ED156E82BC84E908273526E52E4973D_191115_3921528_Giraffe_hit_by_van_dies_and_falls_on_jeep__killi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/154/3D5/1543D5CBEFBEC3EF4535AAD702DB3C29.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Kruger National Park, giraffe car accident, giraffe tourist car accident, Kruger National Park giraffe car accident, Swiss tourist Kruger, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eco-friendly supertall skyscraper planned for China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANJING, CHINA  U.S.-based architectural firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill has won a competition to design Nanjing's newest skyscraper, the South HeXi Yuzui Financial District Tower.The tower's design plans were inspired by the Yangtze River, according to the project website. The 500-meter-tall building will be able to reflect light, just like the Chinese river, while its exterior will be made up of efficient glass to reduce the amount of solar heat that enters the building.The architectural firm states that the building will incorporate eco-friendly features such as multiple green spaces and harvest rainwater from its sky gardens.The structure aims to become one of the tallest buildings to achieve LEED-Gold certification when completed in 2025.The tower will include an open-air observatory with a 360° view of the city.In addition to the supertall skyscraper, the company will also design other smaller office towers and residential towers as part of a larger development in the district.The new financial district will have access to the riverfront, public transportation, public parks and other facilities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 02:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921233/3921233_2899E46D45F4465398A6FCC734EDAF49_191115_3921233_Eco_friendly_supertall_skyscraper_planned_for_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE3/FD5/EE3FD52FC5AEFC6D8E974A2FC7D56098.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Skyscrapers, China skyscraper, supertall skyscrapers, supertall skyscrapers in China, Nanjing skyscrapers, Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill Architecture, South HeXi Yuzui Financial District Tower, South HeXi Yuzui Financial District Tower nanjing, eco-friendly skyscrapers, energy-efficient skyscrapers, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat put in solitary after masterminding mass feline breakout</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#FreeQuilty #QuiltyNotGuilty #NoMoreDoorsHOUSTON, TEXAS  A six-year old cat named Quilty was sentenced to solitary confinement at an animal shelter, according to CNN.According to Friends for Life shelter, the cat's alleged crime was helping his oppressed feline brethren to escape the shelter.Shelter staff said that the firebrand was accused of inciting mutiny among the aged internees of the senior cat room and orchestrating mass escape on multiple occasions.Worse for his human jailors, Quilty is something of a feline Houdini.According to staff, Quilty would jump then pull on the door handle to open the door, allowing 14 other cats to escape.Quilty was nicknamed "Door Ninja" for his prowess at escape and also "Spicy A-hole."The liberated cats would roam the facility until they were caught and surveillance footage later identified Quilty as the culprit.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921206/3921206_503D8ADF8F224F66BEEAE6CB6CDB20A7_191115_3921206_Cat_put_in_solitary_after_masterminding_mass_fel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/052/8AD/0528AD2C26C41B508648A173473EBA0A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Quilty, free quilty, cat, door ninja, spicy, rebel cat, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian carp linked to decline of native fish in Mississippi River</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TRAVERSE CITY, MICHIGAN  New research has linked invasive species of Asian carp to a decline of native sport fish in the Mississippi River and some of its tributaries.According to a study published in the journal Biological Invasions, there are four types of Asian carp  grass, bighead, silver and black carp  in this river system.The study focused on the silver carp because the species is more abundant in the Upper Mississippi, where the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers has been collecting data on fish for two decades.Asian carp were originally introduced to help clear out algae and weeds in sewage ponds and fish farms in the 1960s and 1970s. They escaped, entered the Mississippi River and started migrating north.The study suggests that this may have led to a decline of native sport fish such as the yellow perch, bluegill and white and black crappie during early life stages due to a dearth of plankton, which both silver carp and sport fish compete for.While analyzing fish data between 1994 to 2013, researchers found that the number of sport fish had declined by roughly 30 percent in infested areas of the Mississippi and Illinois rivers.Meanwhile, the study found that the number of native sport fish had increased by approximately 35 percent in sections of the Mississippi River farther upstream where the Asian carp had not arrived.Researchers considered other factors such as flooding, water temperatures and sediment pollution, though none of them were found to have had a significant impact on native sport fish population.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922850/3922850_E0E400B522574108802D02D77EBB6482_191118_3922850_Asian_carp_linked_to_decline_of_native_fish_in_M_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA5/D0E/BA5D0E4A98D6BED853228010CE707D4B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Asian carp, silver carp, silver carp invasion, silver carp invasive species, invasive species mississippi river, silver carp mississippi river, mississippi river, mississippi river native species, Upper mississippi river system, sport fish, mississippi river fish drop, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to search for fossils on Martian crater</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARS  NASA plans to send its Mars 2020 rover to search for signs of ancient life on Mars' Jezero Crater.In a news release, the space agency pointed to a recent study published in the journal Icarus which identified mineral deposits called carbonates along the crater's inner rim. The study says that a lake was at the site of the Martian crater more than 3.5 billion years ago.NASA says its Mars 2020 rover will collect rock core samples from the Martian surface, noting that carbonates on the crater could be preserving signs of past life.Scientists say these mineral deposits could also reveal how the red planet evolved from having liquid water and a thicker atmosphere to a cold, dry desert. Carbonate minerals are formed as carbon dioxide and water interact with one another.NASA also pointed to another study which found hydrated silica, minerals that are also capable of preserving ancient life, on the edge of the Jezero Crater. This could be an ideal location for the Mars 2020 rover to search for buried microbial fossils, especially if the minerals are located at the crater's bottom layer.NASA's Mars 2020 rover will be launched from Cape Canaveral, Florida in 2020.The Mars 2020 mission is part of a larger project by NASA that includes lunar missions in order to prepare humans to eventually explore the red planet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922844/3922844_0DB38F9FB9E7436EAA4A8773A155C4F8_191118_3922844_NASA_to_search_for_fossils_on_Martian_crater_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9D7/024/9D7024DDA7731C10BFCB6E0DF9988225.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA, space exploration, Mars, Mars mission, NASA Mars mission, Mars 2020, NASA Mars rover 2020, NASA Mars 2020, red planet, mission to mars, mars mission nasa, Jezero crater, Jezero crater Mars, Jezero crater Mars mission, NASA mars fossils,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian council floods right after rejecting climate measures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VENICE, ITALY  The Veneto regional council flooded for the first time ever last Tuesday  just after it happened to reject measures to address climate change. CNN reports Venice was a bit on the wet side last week after being slammed with the worst flooding in more than half a century. According to a Facebook post by Democratic Party councilor Andrea Zanoni, the council chamber in Ferro Fini Palace began to look like Waterworld around 10 p.m. local time, as councilors were debating the 2020 regional budget. In the post, Zanoni said the rejected amendments included measures to fund renewable energy, replace diesel buses with greener ones, scrap polluting stoves and reduce plastics impact. Regional council spokesman confirmed with the most trusted name in news that the council was flooder after discussing the amendments of the 2020 budget without watering it down with specific details. According to the council's website, meetings were moved to Treviso last Thursday and Friday because of the flooding.    Venice Mayor Luigi Brugnaro said last week the historic flooding was a direct result of climate change, and you know, he's probably right.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922838/3922838_720852379827473397BD31E1372881D7_191118_3922838_Italian_council_floods_right_after_rejecting_cli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B8E/C6A/B8EC6A6E843B2959215679E6FEA9EC93.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Italian council floods, Italian council floods climate change, Venice flooding, Veneto regional council flooding, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate with Popeyes chicken sandwich melts internet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST PALM BEACH, FLORIDA  As the Popeyes chicken sandwich craze continues to sweep across the country, people have gone to increasingly impressive lengths to get their hands on it, none more so than Marcus J. Elliot. The Daily Mail reports that last week, 22-year-old Elliot, who goes by the social media handle Frank Gutta, went viral after images of him munching on an infamous Popeyes chicken sandwich send the internet into a meltdown. Images posted to Elliot's Facebook page and shared across Twitter shows the inmate sitting back in his cell on his cot enjoying the $3.99 chicken sandwich. In his Facebook stories, the captions say "trying to see what all the hype bout," and "Thanks Bae." The photos were shared on Twitter by a user on November 14 and has since racked up more than 67,000 likes and 23,000 retweets. Online records show that Eliot is doing time at the West Palm Beach Community Release Center, and is expected to get out in September 2020. He is currently listed as being on the community watch, which means he's allowed to work in the community before returning back to the holding facility.  In the meantime, hopefully his bae will keep the supply of chicken sandwiches coming.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 11:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922826/3922826_B48454ACDBDD48C7B0F41568EE3279B1_191118_3922826_Inmate_with_Popeyes_chicken_sandwich_melts_inter_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61C/0BC/61C0BC6385B0B2D058B34C3162DA70C0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Popeyes, Popeyes chicken sandwich, inmate Popeyes chicken sandwich, Popeyes chicken sandwich prison, Popeyes chicken sandwich jail, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tests strategic nuclear missile in Bohai Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China has test launched a new submarine launched ballistic missile named the JL-3.The country's Defense Ministry told the Global Times in a conference on June 27 that the UFO sightings earlier that month was the result of a test launch conducted in the Bohai Sea.According to the Global Times, the missile was observed by Chinese netizens in Shandong, Shanxi, Hebei and Henan.Jane's 360 reported that the trajectory was consistent with a flight path toward the desert areas in the west that China uses for missile tests.The National Interest reports that the JL-3 features a multiple warhead design capable of carrying China's hydrogen bombs.An unnamed source told the South China Morning Post that the finished JL-3 will achieve a range of 9,000 kilometers.According to the National Interest, the completed missile will be able to reach Washington D.C. when fired by a submarine.The South China Moring Post reported that the missile has a shorter range than the US Trident II because China has not made significant breakthroughs in submarine design.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 09:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922759/3922759_D9A7B4A0DA624A81902E710D54F75567_191118_3922759_China_tests_strategic_nuclear_missile_in_Bohai_S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7B3/D17/7B3D176DDEC8764AE387E13E00D1FECB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, ballistic missile, submarine, flight test, missile test, nuclear weapons, JL-3, Giant Wave 3, ICBM, SLBM, Bohai Sea, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HK police officer shot with
arrow during university siege</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  The battle for Hong Kong's democracy has taken to new heights as a police officer was shot by an arrow during a siege of Hong Kong's Polytechnic University campus in Hung Hom, Kowloon.  On Sunday, the pro-democracy protesters on campus rained Molotov cocktails down on riot police and their vehicles in one of the longest days of fighting since the demonstrations began nearly six months ago.Police retaliated by pummeling front-line protesters with rounds of tear gas and water cannons.According to the Hong Kong Free Press, during the skirmish, a member of the police's media liaison team, who are typically dressed in blue vests, was "struck in the calf by an arrow" at around 2 pm.Police took to Facebook to warn protesters that if they continued to use petrol bombs and bows and arrows, they would respond by using minimum force and, given no other choice, live rounds.Worryingly, the Hong Kong Polytechnic University issued a statement announcing that, "dangerous chemicals" had been stolen from laboratories and that they scolded the protesters for "damaging the campus."Furthermore, for the first time, the Hong Kong police deployed a Long Range Acoustic Device mounted on an armored truck that emits high-pitched noises. According to The City Broadcasting Channel, a news outlet run by students from the City University of Hong Kong, the sonic device was used for, "about three seconds"  at around 2:20 pm and caused slight discomfort to its reporter.According to a police statement, the man shot by the arrow is conscious and was sent to the hospital for treatment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922717/3922717_113D7C06069D4870A038A3E52F6A3C17_191118_3922717_HK_police_officer_shot_with_arrow_during_univers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/267/EC3/267EC3FE0D054F87B8A627268B3BDAED.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Police officer shot with arrow, Hong Kong demonstrations, Polytechnic University, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, freedom protests, TomoNews, police arrow shot, police arrow Hong Kong, Police storm university, injure officer with arrow]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes chicken sandwich is causing traffic mayhem in Jersey</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUTHERFORD, NEW JERSEY  Traffic in Jersey is a heckuva lot more brutal than usual, and it's all thanks to the chicken sandwich everyone and their mother wants to get their hands on.According to the Bergen Record, insane demand for the chicken sandwich at a Popeyes in Rutherford, New Jersey is causing traffic to back up all the way to a state highway. It's extra horrible during rush hour.The location shares a single driveway with Starbucks, so it's always been a headache. But now that the caffeine junkies have been joined by chicken sandwich fanatics, it's a nasty migraine.Rutherford police have had it, and put up an electronic sign outside the Popeyes that says "A sandwich isn't worth a ticket. Do not delay traffic."Basically, people would rather wait a lifetime at the drive thru and inconvenience a whole city just so they don't have to get out of the car. Meanwhile, going inside and picking the sandwich up themselves takes all of 10 minutes.For real, people need to get up, get going, and get over themselves. Some of us have places to be and better food to eat.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 14:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923420/3923420_4E2E07C8D4724941922A8B6FEB44AEE3_191119_3923420_Popeyes_chicken_sandwich_is_causing_traffic_mayh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/25A/8AD/25A8ADAB806FF64CF7B0372D6CB494EE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Popeyes chicken sandwich, Popeyes, chicken sandwich, New Jersey Popeyes, Popeyes traffic jam, New Jersey traffic, Starbucks, caffeine junkies, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Disney+ accounts stolen by hackers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BURBANK, CALIFORNIA  Hackers started targeting Disney's new streaming service just hours after it was launched on November 12.Hackers were able to gain access to users' Disney+ accounts and lock them out of all of their devices that had access to the service, according to an investigation by ZDNet.They were also able to change the email address and password of the user's streaming service account, essentially taking over the account.The report suggests that hackers may have stolen user credentials through keylogging or via malware designed to steal data. In some cases, hackers may have used emails and passwords leaked from other websites to gain access to the Disney+ accounts.The ZDNet report suggested Disney+ could provide multi-factor authentication for a more secure login to prevent hackers from gaining easy access to user accounts through previously used passwords.The report also advised users to set unique passwords for each online account.The streaming service is currently available in the U.S., Canada and the Netherlands.Thousands of Disney+ accounts were found for sale on hacking forums online, with prices ranging from US$3 to US$11. An authentic Disney+ account costs US$7 per month.The report even found free Disney+ accounts online that are available to be shared with others in the hacking forum.According to ZDNet, Disney has yet to respond to requests for comments on the streaming service's security issues.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 14:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923415/3923415_FD11FE65035A47AD9D1C78E40657EA19_191119_3923415_Thousands_of_Disney__accounts_stolen_by_hackers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7FE/18A/7FE18A1BC386E02F76FA608108BEE466.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Disney, Disney+, Disney+ hacked, Disney+ hacked accounts, Disney+ accounts stolen, Disney+ accounts stolen by hackers, Disney+ video streaming service hacked, Disney+ glitches, Disney customers hacked,  Disney+ technical glitches, Disney+ glitches launch day, Disney+ streaming service, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran blocks internet access amid mass protests over gasoline prices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN  Iran started restricting access to the internet on Friday, November 15, with nearly all access to the internet being restricted by Saturday, November 16, according to a report from NetBlocks, an organization that monitors worldwide internet access.The organization says Iran now only has five percent of ordinary levels of connectivity to the internet. This comes amid protests against the government's plan to hike gasoline prices.The Iranian government plans to increase prices for rationed gasoline by 50 percent, the New York Times reports. Those who purchase gasoline that exceeds the ration limit will face a 300 percent increase in fuel prices.The Associated Press pointed out that even with increased prices, gasoline in Iran still remains among the cheapest in the world  with one liter costing approximately 15,000 rials, or around 13 cents.According to the NetBlocks report, some of Iran's largest mobile network operators including MCI, RIghtel and IranCell, all fell silent around 6:00 p.m. on Saturday.Authorities must work with internet service providers and mobile data providers to shut down all internet connections, reports Wired.Alp Toker, director of NetBlocks, told Wired these telecoms would also need to overcome protections in a network system which are meant to make the system resilient in case of accidental outages or bugs. Toker noted that Iran's initial internet slowdowns may have been due to these very protections in the leadup to the now almost complete internet shutdown.The clampdown on internet service is believed to be designed to limit the number of people attending protests and to hinder media coverage, according to NetBlocks. Apps such as WhatsApp and Instagram have also been blocked.NetBlocks stated that the ongoing internet disruption is the most severe recorded in the nation ever since President Hassan Rouhani came to power.The organization also noted that this is the "most severe disconnection" tracked by the organization for any country in terms of its "technical complexity and breadth."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 14:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923412/3923412_7AF064EA1F86408DB45DCF5FFF6672D9_191119_3923412_Iran_blocks_internet_access_amid_mass_protests_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9D2/8AE/9D28AE96CCDA4D79E469DF6A8A362A3A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Iran, Iran protests, Iran protests 2019, iran protests internet, iran shuts down internet, iran shuts down internet fuel protests, iran gasoline, iran internet, iran internet censorship, Iran blocks internet, Iran blocks internet access, iran blocks all internet access, iranian protests gasoline, Iran anti-government protests, Iran gasoline hike,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger shares snap of crusty feet hanging over headrest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  An airline passenger posted a horrifyingly hilarious selfie of herself and a pair of stanky feet hanging over her headrest. The image boarded Reddit last week with the caption, "This is the one thing I am most worried about before getting on a plane." It has since taken off for some strange reason that we can't quite seem to put our foot on. The photo shows an unidentified woman with someone's bare, slightly crusty, and dirty dogs resting conveniently on top of the headrest.  It's unclear what airline the funky feet photo was taken on, but it appears to be one that has seats.   Reddit users were quick to put their foot down in opposition to the appalling behavior with suggestions ranging from reasonable to hilarious.  But remember folks, next time you're flying, please keep your feet to yourself.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 13:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923403/3923403_5A1E05013CF24B1DB5A738697DB60E04_191119_3923403_Passenger_shares_snap_of_crusty_feet_hanging_ove_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B89/274/B892743BA87B37BDE469807D34904C9C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Feet on headrest, feet hanging over headrest, airline passenger, airline passenger feet on headrest, feet resting on headrest, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popeyes worker fired for bringing son to make chicken sandwiches</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLONY, TEXAS  Popeye's has been causing all types of commotion across the country as everyday Americans seem to be losing their minds all over a chicken sandwich. According to Inside Edition, the demand has been so intense that one Texas father decided to enlist the help of his familyaka, his son. It appears the man took bring your son into work day a bit too literally after a customer captured footage of the tiny worker wearing a Popeyes apron helping prepare chicken in the kitchen. According to the customer, the Popeyes in question, located in the Dallas suburb of Colony, had a line out the door and was getting slammed with orders for the infamous chicken sandwich. Unfortunately for the father, there are those pesky federal and state child labor laws that forbid minors from working.Obviously those people working in the federal and state offices haven't tried the sandwich yet. Too bad for the dad, he's now out of a job after the owner of the Popeyes franchise gave him the boot. Hey, at least they weren't making the chicken sandwich on top of a garbage can.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 11:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923352/3923352_22EB9CD3BE234030BC19F38A11ADE03A_191119_3923352_Popeyes_worker_fired_for_bringing_son_to_make_ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/79B/44B/79B44B2F25D9148E713E18FEB8601525.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Popeyes, Popeyes chicken sandwich, Popeyes chicken sandwich demand, Popeyes Colony Texas, Popeyes worker, Popeyes worker fired, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters try to escape
uni after skirmish with police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Protestors had started to flee the blockaded Polytechnic University on monday, with the Hong Kong police force meeting them with tear gas and rubber bullets; multiple arrests were made, with those caught being aggressively detained. Protestors claim that even though they were trying to leave, they were being boxed in by the authorities.A 23-year-old protestor inside the university campus told CNN by phone, "Of course, we want to leave." "We are still quite safe currently in the campus, but if we try to leave ... they will arrest us." "They are just everywhere surrounding the campus."The protester added, "Currently, around me, we just want to escape, we don't have any equipment to help us fight."He later fled unharmed and knows of roughly 50 more individuals who escaped, some by abseiling down a rope to waiting motorbikes or running along train tracks.More worryingly, police confirmed to CNN that assault rifles being carried by riot police Monday afternoon, were in fact, "ready to use."Demonstrators, however, will be more frightful than ever after a video surfaced on Monday of apparently detained protestors being loaded onto a train near the border of China for speculated extradition.According to Taiwan News, the footage is sparking dread online that the pro-democracy protesters are in fact being sent to a detention center in communist China, similar to the so-called "reeducation camps" used to imprison innocent Uighurs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923273/3923273_78E706639180483285CC3A7118BACC5F_191119_3923273_Protesters_try_to_escape_uni_after_skirmish_with_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2F2/CE6/2F2CE6D3D1BF69F93C86F84B2C465ACE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong demonstrations, Polytechnic University, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, freedom protests, protestors sent to detention camps, TomoNews, Police storm university, TomoNews, students escape university]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Neptune's moons 'dancing' to avoid one another?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA  Thalassa and Naiad appear to be locked in an intricate "dance of avoidance" that keep their respective orbits stable, according to NASA.  Thalassa and Naiad are described as small and tic tac and shaped, with computations of their mass and size showing the density of ice water.Thalassa circles Neptune every seven hours and thirty minutes, while Naiad completes the circuit every seven hours, but on an orbit tilted by five degrees relative to Thalassa.Viewed from Thalassa, Naiad appear to dance in a wave like pattern, passing twice from above and twice from below.NASA researchers said this behavior between celestial bodies is called a resonance, but the specific pattern of these moons have never been seen before.According to researchers, Neptune disrupted its original satellite system when it captured its giant moon, Triton.The disruption caused Naiad to veer into a tilted orbit before it settled into the ballet-like resonance with Thalassa.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 08:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923208/3923208_D73798D404744201ABF982A7DB226862_191119_3923208_Why_are_Neptune_s_moons__dancing__to_avoid_one_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/594/EED/594EED2E1A6477AEC62E85189CFE5FE0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Neptune, Thalassa, Naiad, moons, dance of avoidance, dance, resonance, space, NASA, JPL, astronomy, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man punches firefighters for taking too long to put out car fire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS  A man whose car was on fire went after two firefighters for being too slow to rescue his car.According to the St. Louis Post-Dispatch, police got a call around 5:50 p.m. on November 15 that a car had caught on fire after crashing into another vehicle.KMOV reports that firefighters arrived and began trying to put out the fire. But the owner of the burning car was impatient and thought they were doing it way too slowly, so what does he do? He starts punching two of them, because sure, that'll get 'em to do it MUCH faster.Video taken by a witness shows the man being held down on the ground by firefighters. When he's let go, he lunges at them.He then tries to throw a punch at one of the firefighters, who deftly ducks, and tackles the dude to the ground.The man was taken into custody, but firefighters have said they didn't want him charged, and would like instead to see him get the help he needs.That's gonna be a whole lotta counseling and anger management classes, but guy still lucked out with these good guys.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/20/3923793/3923793_4C6761684D234DAB99F698A0609A12F1_191120_3923793_Man_punches_firefighters_for_taking_too_long_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0B3/E0D/0B3E0D442D771F79439F5B79B16763F8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man punches firefighters, man fights firefighters, car fire, trashy, trashy behavior, caught on video, caught on camera, st louis firefighters, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last few protesters hold out 
inside Hong Kong university</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#HongKong #HongKongProtests #HongKongpoliceHONG KONG  Few protestors remain at the Hong Kong Polytechnic University as supplies and outside support dwindle into the third day of the police siege, reports Hong Kong newspaper and TomoNews sister publication Apple Daily.CNN reported on Tuesday that only around 50 or so remained at the campus.About ten protestors tried to escape the campus as medics left. Riot police officers tackled runners and beat them with clubs. The police later described them as 'masked rioters' in a Facebook post.Speaking at a press conference on Tuesday evening, a spokesperson for volunteer medics treating protestors told Apple Daily that they are evacuating because of the diminishing number of protesters. The spokesperson added that no supplies are reaching the campus.Apple Daily reports that dozens of protesters left voluntarily after displaying hypothermia symptoms. Parents told the newspaper that many of those who surrendered to police are missing.Hong Kong police claim to have identified or arrested an estimated 1,100 people in the school and its surrounding areas, including 600 who left voluntarily as of Tuesday at 3pm.Citing Hong Kong's Hospital Authority, Apple Daily reports that 354 people were wounded in the ten hours between midnight and 10pm yesterday.A Taiwanese student told the paper that she was scared to leave because she did not know if she would be beaten or shot at despite public assurances. She was reportedly evacuated after the interview.Meanwhile, Beijing hinted that it may upend Hong Kong's legal system after the autonomous territory's High Court ruled the police ban on masks as unlawful.A spokesman of the National People's Congress said the issue, "can only be judged and decided by the NPC Standing Committee, and no other organ has the right to judge or decide," in a statement published by Chinese state-run Xinhua News Agency on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/20/3923781/3923781_7A1EDDD837804EBE840E1ABC41F76A88_191120_3923781_Last_few_protesters_hold_out__inside_Hong_Kong_u_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9E7/591/9E75913E01F576FAA0E3CA36DDF236E5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong, Hong Kong Protests, Hong Kong Police, Hong Kong PolyU, Hong Kong Polytechnic university, china vs hong kong, hong kong university police siege, hong kong university police seige, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists create slippery toilet coating that stops deuces sticking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STATE COLLEGE, PENNSYLVANIA  Some scientists at Penn State University have been working on some serious crap. According to the BBC, Nittany Lion researchers have created a super slippery toilet coating that could potentially help save massive amounts of water in crappers around the world. The team from Penn State say the coating cuts the amount of water needed to get rid of those man-made logs by 90 percent. They say it also prevents bacteria from taking over toilet bowls and helps cut down those ultra-fragrant odors associated with destroying the can. The spray is more slippery than Teflon, but doesn't really like getting pissed on, so it needs to be reapplied after around 50 flushes. The scientists hope this new crap will help cut back on all the perfectly good water we flush down the john every day. Every day, more than 141 billion liters of water are used to get rid of those ones and twos. According to their findings, which were published in the journal Nature Sustainability, the amount of fresh water needed to flush the world's toilets every day is six times Africa's total water consumption. Think about THAT your next visit to the can when you do your business.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 05:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/20/3923637/3923637_C14B5202CA9743A09209A766E090B0FD_191120_3923637_Scientists_create_slippery_toilet_coating_that_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1EE/8A2/1EE8A21B6C39157A80400DBB33C632DA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Slippery toilet coating, scientists create toilet coating, ultra-slippery toilet coating, Penn State University toilet coating, slippery toilet coating spray, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped hoarder rescued
after massive junk cave-in</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANLEY VALE, AUSTRALIA  An unnamed elderly hoarder living in Canley Vale near Sydney was trapped for about sixteen hours after her stockpile fell on her.Australia's Nine News reports that the stash included eighties fashion mags and food from the 1990s.Neighbors told 9 News that the woman and her husband have been hoarding for as long as they can remember. Apparently, the mess got so bad that her husband started sleeping in the car.The woman's solitary bliss was rudely interrupted when a treasure trove of goodies collapsed on her Sunday evening. After she failed to respond to his regular check-up call the next morning, her husband called in the emergency services.Nine News reports that neighbors saw rescuers break into the house via a side window.The woman was saved, but apparently the situation was so bad that special equipment and training designed for earthquake rescue were used to dig her out of nearly a tonne of debris.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 01:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/20/3923528/3923528_654B90C8DCC94E758C7F82E9EA2B6803_191120_3923528_Trapped_hoarder_rescued_after_massive_junk_cave__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6B2/CDA/6B2CDAAD48178A9730BDD54E51107D23.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hoarder, hoarder house, Canley Vale, Sydney, trapped, junk, emergency, rescue, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago's new tower may become the second tallest in the city</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  American architectural firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill has unveiled updated design plans to build a 1,422-foot tall skyscraper in Chicago.The top of the tower will curve inwards.The skyscraper is part of a larger project that includes an overhaul of nearby buildings as well as the iconic Tribune Tower.The structure will include commercial spaces as well as parking at the bottom, Dezeen reports. The building's upper part will include a hotel, rental apartments and condominiums.Upon completion, the skyscraper would become Chicago's second tallest building, surpassing Trump International Hotel & Tower, which stands at 1,380 feet.Developers of the project are still waiting for zoning approval, reports the Chicago Tribune. The designers of the skyscraper updated their initial plans as residents of the area raised concerns about traffic and security near the Chicago River.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 08:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/21/3924241/3924241_EF2683E2AD7B4AA6A87C5A2CB7A15913_191121_3924241_Chicago_s_new_tower_may_become_the_second_talles_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/197/21B/19721B6165D4346701DFDCC5DB2A5C3C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chicago, chicago skyscrapers, the second tallest skyscraper in chicago, chicago skyscrapers new, chicago architecture, new skyscrapers, Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill,  Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill architecture, Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill chicago, Michigan Avenue landmark, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two men boiled alive after their car falls into sinkhole in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENZA, RUSSIA  A sinkhole opened up in a Russian parking lot, swallowing up one car. Metro reported that the freak accident occurred at a parking lot in Penza. According to local media, another vehicle had driven over the same parking spot minutes before, but noticed steam coming from the ground, so quickly hightailed it out of there. That's when the two men driving in a Lada Largus pulled up and parked in the spot. After the guys stopped the car, the asphalt collapsed right under them.  The men died "almost instantly" after being sprayed by 167 degrees Fahrenheit water inside the sinkhole. Local media suggested that a hot water pipe had burst under the parking lot, causing the sinkhole. In Russia, hot water is piped to buildings underground during the crazy cold winters.  The two men have not been publicly identified. The accident is now being investigated by authorities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/21/3924028/3924028_C38D05CB70C64F66B33F6EFCBA631A9E_191121_3924028_Two_men_boiled_alive_after_their_car_falls_into__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/897/79B/89779B15B6AE2D0E03914C91D816B57F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sinkhole, sinkhole swallows car, car falls into sinkhole, Russia car sinkhole, Penza car sinkhole, Russia sinkhole accident, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airbus' VSR700 conducts first flight in France</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARIGNANE, FRANCE  A prototype of the Airbus Helicopters' VSR700 Unmanned Aerial System successfully performed its first test flight at a drone testing center in southern France on November 8.A press release from Airbus stated that the aircraft performed multiple takeoffs and landings, with its longest flight lasting roughly 10 minutes.On its website, the company says that the VSR700 has a maximum speed of 185 kilometers per hour. The aerial vehicle was tethered with 30-meter cables while conducting the test flight.The company says the aircraft will eventually be cleared to fly without a cable.Airbus said aerial vehicle was based on the Helicopteres Guimbal's Cabri G2 and will be able to operate on ships with other helicopters.The VSR700 will feature an advanced flight control system, a payload bay in place of a cockpit and a specialized set of avionics. The company explained that the aircraft will also be capable of carrying multiple full size naval sensors as it has an endurance of eight hours with full payload.Airbus had previously conducted a test flight of another version of the same aerial vehicle, called the VSR700 Optionally Piloted Vehicle, in 2017.The VSR700 Unmanned Aerial System will perform test flights with French company the Naval Group for the French Navy in 2021.The aircraft is being pitched for the French Navy's airborne drone system program scheduled for 2028, according to Naval News.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/21/3924019/3924019_A5B5CF3894A7481CA158D6C904990EEF_191121_3924019_Airbus__VSR700_conducts_first_flight_in_France_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA0/E0E/BA0E0E87223C5587BCCC160D470CAB40.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[VSR700,  VSR700 drone, VSR700 aircraft, Airbus Helicopter, Airbus, Optionally Piloted Vehicle, Airbus Optionally Piloted Vehicle, VSR700 Unmanned Aerial System, VSR700 prototype, VSR700 prototype performs first flight, drone copter, unmanned drone copter TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly mosquito brain-infecting virus claims 6th victim in Michigan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. JOSEPH COUNTY, MICHIGAN  A farmer from Michigan passed away from complications related to the Eastern Equine Encephalitis virus on Saturday, November 16, according to local news station WNDU.Health officials in Michigan say six people from the state have now succumbed to the deadly virus.The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention states on its website that the virus is spread from avian hosts to mosquitoes. The mosquitoes carry the virus and transmit it to humans.The CDC says that after contracting the virus, a person may become sick with one of two types of illness: systemic or encephalitic.A systemic infection includes flu-like symptoms such as fever, chills or malaise.An encephalitic infection includes symptoms such as fever, headache, vomiting and swelling of the brain.Most people infected do not develop any symptoms. According to CDC statistics, around 5 percent of those infected develop an encephalitic illness. Those older than 50 or younger than 15 are at a greater risk of developing this severe form of the illness.There is currently no human vaccine available against the virus.The CDC advises the public to use insect repellent with active ingredients such as DEET, picaridin or lemon eucalyptus oil.Officials also advise the public to wear long-sleeved clothing and to close windows to prevent mosquito bites.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/21/3924014/3924014_69DB0E42AC09485B97CA65816FBFEFD9_191121_3924014_Deadly_mosquito_brain_infecting_virus_claims_6th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C8B/7AE/C8B7AE4DA04017856B61BE66944AEC0F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mosquitoes, mosquito bite, mosquito infection, mosquito virus,  brain virus, mosquitoes brain virus, EEEV, eastern equine encephalitis virus, eastern equine encephalitis symptoms, eastern equine encephalitis michigan, michigan farmer eastern equine encephalitis virus, mosquito virus brain, mosquito borne disease, brain infecting mosquito virus, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after shooting
at his own car that was stolen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLOOMINGTON, INDIANA  Police arrested a man after he chased down his car that had been stolen and squeezed off a few at the fleeing thief.37-year-old Paul Clark, was warming up his car outside his apartment Monday morning, but when he looked out of his window he saw his 2004 Chrysler 300 being stolen.The incident occurred around 5:30 a.m with local police saying Clark then armed himself and grabbed the keys to his girlfriend's SUV.Clark tracked the thief down to the Marathon gas station at East Winslow Road and South Walnut Street.Citing Bloomington Police Department Captain Ryan Pedigo, Fox59 says Clark took aim and popped off 13 shots at the suspect before the criminal managed to flee once again.Police later found the stolen Chrysler abandoned at a nearby apartment complex, they say, there was no blood inside and unfortunately, they didn't find the thief.Several calls about the commotion alerted the cops to the Marathon station where officers recovered 13 shell casings.Police later arrested Clark on charges of criminal recklessness with a deadly weapon, pointing a firearm and carrying a handgun without a license.Captain Ryan Pedigo warns that Clark taking the law into his own hands could not have only seriously injured civilians but could have killed someone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/21/3924009/3924009_2D0270476C784A03AE73513ACC7B517B_191121_3924009_Man_arrested_after_shooting_at_his_own_car_that__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7DA/E75/7DAE75A033EE0E19015809A3EE75A533.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bloomington, stolen car, man chases down own car, vigilante fails, vigilante, vigilante heroes, terminator animation, terminator funny, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shoots up strip club over rejected debit card</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WATERLOO, IOWA  An Iowa man went crazy outside a gentlemen's club, and all over a declined debit card. Some people and their tempers.The Waterloo-Cedar Falls Courier reports that according to court records, James Allen Wells showed up at a Waterloo strip club late Friday, and got himself a lap dance.The 67-year-old bust out his debit card to pay for the private service, but it got declined. Upset, Wells stormed out of the club, pulled out a .38-caliber revolver, then went trigger happy shooting five rounds in the parking lot. Let me get this straight  dude stiffed the club and essentially got a free lap dance, and HE'S mad? Boomers these days.According to the Coutrier, Wells' five shots hit a bunch of parked vehicles, including a Dodge Durango, a Chrysler Town and Country, and a Chevy Impala.He then got into his own car and skedaddled, but got into a short chase with some cops who tried to pull him over for speeding.Wells eventually crashed his car into a curb and ended up getting apprehended by officers following a short scuffle.He has since been charged with criminal mischief, reckless use of a firearm, assault on a peace officer and reckless driving.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924983/3924983_45B9EF730626465BAE6259A0FC0643EE_191122_3924983_Man_shoots_up_strip_club_over_rejected_debit_car_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E10/84B/E1084BAFB56D9F3307855A5A40102EBA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[man shoots club, iowa man opens fire, declined debit card, rejected debit card, james wells, police chase, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors put first ever human in suspended animation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE Doctors have put at least one human in suspended animation, the New Scientist reports.They performed it as part of a trial to save gunshot or stabbing victims who may have minutes to live.Maryland University researcher Samuel Tisherman told the New Scientist that traumatic injuries could result in massive blood loss and then cardiac arrest, robbing the brain of oxygen.Irreversible damage would occur to the brain within five minutes and the patient's survival rate is less than five percent, according to the New Scientist.Tisherman said that the emergency preservation and resuscitation technique, or EPR, replaces all of the patient's blood with ice-cold saline solution.The researcher explained that EPR reduces the need for oxygen by cooling the body and brain, which gives surgeons two hours to repair the injuries. According to Tisherman, the trial will compare EPR's results on a group of ten patients to a control group. Both groups will be treated at the university's hospital.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 11:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924886/3924886_A232895FD4C14CF48E75E44BEFE63CD4_191122_3924886_Doctors_put_first_ever_human_in_suspended_animat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5CF/333/5CF33302FBB722FD4DE3E64AA286A20E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Suspended animation, Baltimore, University of Maryland, heart, saline solution, critical medicine, critical care, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man was dead for 3 years before he was found in apartment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DESOTO, TEXAS  A Navy veteran who lived in Texas had been deceased for around three years before his body was discovered inside his apartment. According to WFAA, Ronald Wayne White had a job working for a defense contractor, which caused him to have to travel extensively. White, who would have been 51 when he died, had moved several times over the years but always kept in touch with his family. Three years ago, those calls suddenly stopped. Unfortunately, his mother in New York didn't have enough money to hire private investigators to help locate White. And because of his travel history, several police departments were unable to treat the case as a missing persons case. Authorities say White's rent was automatically withdrawn from his bank account every month. Police told WFAA that White's body was discovered when apartment workers were investigating units where no water had been used for a long period of time. The third-floor apartment was new and had all the windows sealed. Inside the residence were diabetes medications dated 2016. Police say there was zero indication of foul play. Toxicology tests have been ordered to determine his cause of death.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924868/3924868_CA5979DC534C4A059F20F7E762A9708C_191122_3924868_Man_was_dead_for_3_years_before_he_was_found_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B35/44E/B3544E260E7713C2534B701A5B5DFEF3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man dead 3 years in apartment, navy veteran dead 3 years in apartment, Ronald Wayne White, Ronald Wayne White DeSoto, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man has over 700 tapeworms from eating undercooked meat in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANGZHOU, CHINA  A Chinese man who had been suffering from headaches and seizures was found to have a whopping 700 plus tapeworms taking up residence throughout his body. According to Pear Video, 43-year-old Zhu Zhong-fa from Hangzhou in Zhejiang province started feeling a bit funky about a month ago. Looks like he had eaten some hotpot with a few too many slices of infected and undercooked porkYUMMY.Zhu got himself over to a hospital at Zhejiang University where he was found to have a colony of around 700 tapeworms all over his body.     According to doctors, the little suckers were found in Zhu's brain, lungs and chest cavity. Doctors say the worms had already caused damage to the patient's organs. According to the WHO, when tapeworms get into the central nervous system, they can cause neurological symptoms, including epileptic seizures. Well, that's good to know. Hopefully your appetite has kicked in by now. Hotpot anyone?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 09:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924779/3924779_4653EDBF678546619C75C220DDE80C73_191122_3924779_Man_has_over_700_tapeworms_from_eating_undercook_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/05C/70F/05C70F3A767868D5EE1320D7296205D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tapeworms, man has 700 tapeworms, man tapeworms brain, man tapeworms over, tapeworm infestation, China 700 tapeworms man, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'tortured' ex-British consulate worker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A former employee of the UK consulate in Hong Kong claims he was tortured by Chinese authorities, reports CNN.In a Facebook post on Wednesday, ex-UK Hong Kong consulate worker Simon Cheng says he took part in the city's protests but did not break any laws.Cheng approached protesters on Telegram and other social media as part of his job to evaluate travel alerts and protect British citizens, he says in a Facebook post on Wednesday.He was returning from a business trip in August in Shenzhen when police arrested him on the Chinese side of the West Hong Kong Kowloon railway station.According to Cheng, he was then handed over to State Security Bureau officials and detained in Shenzhen.Speaking to CNN, Britain's Foreign Secretary Dominic Raab said he summoned the Chinese Ambassador to express outrage at the brutal and disgraceful treatment of Cheng. China responded on Wednesday with foreign minister Geng Shuang telling reporters that Cheng made a full confession and that the public security bureau "guaranteed all his rights and interests according to law."CNN reports that Cheng fled to an unnamed third country following his detention and is currently seeking asylum.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 05:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924603/3924603_9D15A62FDDE846C9BC706C6B0655AA55_191122_3924603_China__tortured__ex_British_consulate_worker_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/227/B35/227B351B4B70A5DD2FF80DA3FB8956A2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Simon Cheng, toture, Hong Kong, Shenzhen, China, Ministry of State Security, secret police, human rights, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family lugs uncle's corpse to
insurance company to prove death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KWADUKUZA, SOUTH AFRICA  According to South Africa's News 24, the KwaZulu-Natal family took the drastic measure to get their roughly US$2,000 payout after video of the incident went viral, thus shaming insurance company Old Mutual.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 03:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924566/3924566_45EA1D1890FE498D912FA68EE27C9A29_191122_3924566_Family_lugs_uncle_s_corpse_to_insurance_company__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/77C/88C/77C88C7C34515E66C0F87DA9263655F6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[South African family carry corpse to get insurance money, funeral fails, insurance fails, Old Mutual, South African body video, South African funeral body video, family take body to the shop video, TomoNews, satire, viral video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero gym teacher wrecks rifle-wielding shooter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VELIKA PLANA / SERBIA  Physical education teacher Slavoljub Stojadinovic has been hailed a hero after stopping a crazed gunman at his high school.Serbia's Beta News Agency reports that Stojandinovic was coaching at the gym when a student told him that his help was urgently needed because of trouble in the philosophy class."The daily Blic reports that the trouble turned out to be a gun toting maniac pumping bullets into the ceiling and trying to take hostages."According to the BBC, the Ministry of Education later said the gunman had an automatic rifle."Stojadinovic told Beta News that the gunman fired twice at his head and missed. The PE teacher disarmed the alleged gunman and kept him subdued until law enforcement arrived.[CUT 4] The BBC reports that the gunman was the only person injured in the incident.Stojadinovic told Beta News that although he had been wearing bandages on his hand, the wound was not a result of his struggle with the gunman.[VIDEO 1]According to the BBC Serbia, the police later recovered explosive material in the gunman's bag.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926179/3926179_B076EE75C48E47B38CD651AFF3FAF4B5_191125_3926179_Hero_gym_teacher_wrecks_rifle_wielding_shooter_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/715/615/71561550E38C887A8B1E12137AA20127.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hero, coach, PE teacher, Slavoljub Stojadinovic, gunman, school shooting, high school, Veliki Plana, Serbia, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A third of Africa's tropical plants could go extinct: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AFRICA  A new study from the journal Science Advances suggests that roughly 7,000, or 33 percent, of African plant species risk extinction.The researchers focused on two International Union for Conservation of Nature Red List criteria, related to habitat decline and future population reduction, and developed an algorithm to assess more than 20,000 plant species' risk of going extinct.Based on the assessment, four African regions  Ethiopia, west Africa, central Tanzania and the southern Democratic Republic of the Congo  in particular were found to be the most vulnerable, with more than 40 percent of local flora potentially being threatened with extinction.Species at risk include local trees, herbs, lianas and shrubs.The study also pointed to ecoregions concentrated in West Africa that include large numbers of threatened species, specifically the Inner Niger Delta savanna, Sahelian Acacia savanna, Guinean mangroves, western Guinean lowland forest and Guinean montane forests.Researchers said these plant species are threatened by deforestation, climate change and population growth.In addition, scientists found another third of flora species in the region that is likely rare and could potentially risk extinction in the near future.Co-author of the study, Gilles Dauby, from the French National Research Institute for Sustainable Development told the Guardian that these species could likely be threatened if human pressure increases in tropical Africa.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926168/3926168_0FBB952F4FCE402BB4A4A2D42E41DA4B_191125_3926168_A_third_of_Africa_s_tropical_plants_could_go_ext_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2AC/AD7/2ACAD7F090354CD882A7DC99751D4DA1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Africa, African plant species, African flora, tropical African flora, African flora risk extinction, African plant species face extinction, endemic trees  Africa, climate change, climate change plant species, threatened species, african tropical plants, climate change Africa, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong pro-democracy camp wins big in local elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Hong Kong held its local district council elections on Sunday after almost six months of anti-government protests.Voter turnout was more than 71 percent, up from 47 percent in 2015, BBC News reports. The elections are considered to be a test for the current Hong Kong government.The city has a total of 18 district councils, of which the pro-democracy camp won 17, according to the South China Morning Post. District councils mainly advise the government on local issues concerning their district, such as the use of public facilities and public services.Several prominent pro-democracy activists including Jimmy Sham, who was attacked by masked assailants with hammers last month in Kowloon, managed to win district council seats in the local elections.The district councils may play a significant role when electing Hong Kong's chief executive in 2022.This is because the city's leader is elected by a 1,200-member committee, which includes 117 members chosen by district councillors. In this system, whichever campclaims the majority of votes, has the ability to claim all 117 of these seats.This could influence who is chosen to be the city's chief executive as the pro-democracy camp already held roughly 400 committee seats before the district council elections.As six out of 70 seats are reserved in the city's Legislative Council for district councillors, the pro-democracy camp may also secure seats in the Legislative Council as the majority.Hong Kong's Legislative Council has the ability to enact, amend, repeal laws or even start an impeachment process against the city's leader.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926162/3926162_4153D561CCAC4A99B9CD7E09D832D4A5_191125_3926162_Hong_Kong_pro_democracy_camp_wins_big_in_local_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong elections, hong kong elections explained, hong kong elections 2019, hong kong district elections, hong kong news, hong kong vote, hong kong voting, hong kong local elections, hong kong local elections results, hong kong district council elections, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman caught stealing 8 pairs of jeans by wearing them</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VENEZUELA  A shoplifter in South America tried to pull a Joey Tribbiani by wearing the clothes she was planning to steal all at once.According to The Sun, the incident is believed to have occurred at a store in Venezuela, and involved an unidentified woman and her bizarre plan.No one knows how she did it, but the crafty lady put on pair after pair after pair of denim jeans  on top of the pair she already had on! How she even managed to walk, let alone move with that much denim on is another mystery. But she did it, and got as far as the exit before security noticed what was up.In a video that has since gone viral, Miss Skillz is seen inside a bathroom, peeling each jean layer one by one. The man filming her counts each one while trying really hard not to laugh. He eventually getting a grand total of eight. It's unclear if the lady was arrested for charged for any crime, but now that she's famous online, here's hoping she'll think twice next time before shoplifting.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 09:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926104/3926104_01CE2EA755C249DF941ED280A7AEAAA4_191125_3926104_Woman_caught_stealing_8_pairs_of_jeans_by_wearin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/570/479/57047982DCFE9E29AD3BB44865B3FA35.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Shoplifter, shoplifter caught on cam, woman steals jeans, woman steals 8 pairs of jeans, jeans 8 pairs, 8 pairs jeans, venezuela, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China increases coal power capacity, despite climate pledge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  A new report by Global Energy Monitor found that China has increased its coal power capacity by 42.9 gigawatts between January of 2018 and June of 2019. That is enough energy to power 31 million homes, according to the BBC. The report notes that the rest of the world decreased its total coal capacity by 8.1 gigawatts during the same time period.Researchers involved with the study say China would need to reduce its current coal capacity by over 40 percent, from 1,027 gigawatts to 600 gigawatts or less, by 2030 in order to keep its Paris climate agreement pledge to limit the rise in global temperatures to below 2°C.The report found that China is constructing 121.3 gigawatts of coal plants and is likely to revive 26.4 gigawatts of other existing coal-related projects that are currently suspended, or a total of 147.7 gigawatts of coal power capacity.This is almost equivalent to the European Union's existing coal power capacity, which stands at 150 gigawatts.China continues to finance a quarter of all coal plant projects around the world, in countries such as South Africa, Pakistan and Bangladesh, the BBC reports.China has invested heavily in clean energy, though the country continues to invest in coal power.Co-author of the study Christine Shearer from Global Energy Monitor, called China's coal power expansion plans "far out of alignment with the Paris Agreement."Shearer said that China needs to make significant reductions to its coal power capacity instead of continued expansion over the coming decade.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 05:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3925938/3925938_B7886784A1F543648E37F7F9612E8416_191125_3925938_China_increases_coal_power_capacity__despite_cli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, china coal power plant, china coal plant, china coal power, coal power plant pollution, new coal plants in china, coal plants, climate change, climate warning, climate change china, coal power capacity, coal plant pollution, paris agreement, paris agreement china, china coal surge, china coal power capacity, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High rise park views turn out to be awesome plastic lake in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHANGSHA, CHINA  When you got the big bucks in China, you got to have the big baller view to go with it.According to the SCMP, lucky suckers who purchased units in a brand new residential high rise that touted "park views" were treated to that and so much more. The development located in the Hunan provincial city of Changsha promised "high vegetation cover" and a "park lifestyle."The real estate developer then translated that into the magnificent beauty of a fake blue lake created with gorgeous man-made plastic. They then topped that off with a luxuriously elaborate fake bridge that spanned the entire pretend lake. And who needs actual grass covering the larger open areas when you have grass block paving that is usually seen in driveways or parking lots instead. That counts as vegetation.     If you've got your bathing suit ready so you can test out the crystal clear waters you're unfortunately out of luck. After the story went viral and complaints started rolling in, the developers ended up tearing up the fake plastic pool, leaving the crappy concrete foundations underneath. Guess we'll just have to wait and see what kind of magic the developers will put in its place.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926673/3926673_BBE9AEC7A93E43C490B1ACB0527406DB_191126_3926673_High_rise_park_views_turn_out_to_be_awesome_plas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E9F/12F/E9F12F4BA8C50F520CAEEC1279276EDA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fake plastic lake, China fake plastic lake, China high rise fake plastic lake, China fake, Made in China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing police force just cloned 6 K-9 dogs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Beijing's boys in blue introduced six new members into the police force that you might have trouble telling apart from each other. That's just because they were all cloned.  CBS News reports that the young officers were sporting shiny new badges, uniforms and collars. The six clones are the result of work between the Beijing Municipal Bureau of Public Security's Police Dog Base and private pet-cloning company Sinogene. According to CBS, four of the doggos were born in the same litter in August. Their DNA is more than 99 percent identical to the two Belgian Malinois donor dogs. The donors were selected for their RUFF and tough performance on the police force. According to the Chinese authorities, police dogs lose some of their abilities as they get older, so naturally why not turn to cloning. The goal of the cloning program is to create a K-9 police force with greater efficiency and shorter training periods. The police dog base said it would be watching the cloned recruits closely during their training. That's all good and fine, but when are they going to start cloning humans? China needs more of those.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926655/3926655_CF5AA6D2772549F1BD8D60D9C0D87C44_191126_3926655_Beijing_police_force_just_cloned_6_K_9_dogs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5A8/B6C/5A8B6C5637A00347498927260EC14D78.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Beijing clones K-9s, China cloned dogs, Beijing police cloned K-9s, Beijing police cloned dogs, cloned police dogs, China cloning, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbits are being sucked into plane engines in Ireland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBLIN  Rabbits are being sucked up into plane engines as they taxi down runways at Ireland's Dublin Airport. The Irish Post reported 11 rascally rabbits have been "ingested" by engines in 2019, while 44 hares have been rescued and relocated away from the airport. Apparently, bunnies and high-performance plane engines don't pair well together and pose a greater risk than bird strikes. According to the Irish Post, chopped-up rabbit gunks up the propellers and engine bits a lot more than birds. The rabbit pieces attract more scavenging birds to the runways which then increases the likelihood of a bird strike. Airport workers have been using flare guns and netting to keep the bunnies from bouncing into harm's way. According to the report, the rabbits that are caught are released back into the wild by under the supervision of the National Parks and Wildlife Services.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926650/3926650_5EACD891CAD949CEBE0059438A105ACB_191126_3926650_Rabbits_are_being_sucked_into_plane_engines_in_I_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/106/648/106648B2883A36E7F4CDA57DFA3B285F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Rabbits on runways, rabbits sucked into engine, rabbits plane engines, hares plane engine, rabbits Dublin Airport, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog puts car in reverse, does doughnuts for about an hour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORT ST. LUCIE, FLORIDA  A Florida dog decided to take his owner's car for a quick spin around the cul-de-sac last week in Port St. Lucie. According to Port St. Lucie police in a statement to the New York Post, the owner apparently made a wrong turn onto the street, which prompted her to stop and get out of the vehicle to assess her situation. She then absent mindedly closed the door with the car still running and her black labrador Max inside. According to WPTV, that's when Max hopped into the driver's seat and popped the car into reverse. Max then proceeded to do doughnuts slowly in reverse for about an hour or so as neighbors, and eventually police watched on. He was doing pretty well too, not hitting anythingat first. In the end, he did love tap a mailbox and some garbage cans, but let's give him a break. It WAS his first time behind the wheel. WPTV reports that police finally put a stop to the joyride after punching in the passcode into the driver's side door. Police say no one was hurt in the oh-so-Florida-esque incident. As for Max, maybe he'll spin this into a part-time job as an Uber or Lyft driver.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926647/3926647_5C8D55C0BC1649F1A7DEF68822C996FA_191126_3926647_Dog_puts_car_in_reverse__does_doughnuts_for_abou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/751/5AA/7515AA176AA4C3B75DA69B1F56F73429.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dog drives car, Florida dog drives car, Florida dog puts car in reverse, dog doughnuts car, dog drives car for hour, dog in car, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu shot not as effective in people who are overweight, obese</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Scientists have found that the flu vaccine is less effective for people with excess weight.A study from the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill found that vaccinated obese adults have twice the risk of flu or flu-like illnesses compared to vaccinated healthy-weight adults.This is a pretty huge problem, considering two-thirds of the adult population in the U.S. has issues with excess weight.NPR reports that during the 2009 flu outbreak, health experts noticed the infection was worse in individuals who were significantly overweight.The virus grows to higher concentrations and spreads deeper in the lungs.Heavier individuals were also more likely to spread the disease.A University of Maryland study found that more of the virus came out of the exhaled breath of those who were overweight or obese.According to Chapel Hill nutrition professor Melinda Beck, the metabolic shift in people's bodies caused by gaining excess weight affects immune system cells.So although obese people may still make an antibody response, their T-cells aren't functioning, so they can still be infected with the flu despite being vaccinated.Apart from the obese and overweight, elderly people also face the same problem.Because of this, scientists are now working to develop a next-generation flu shot that can address these vulnerabilities, though it has years to go before it's ready.In the meantime, they say people should still continue to get vaccinated, regardless of size or body weight.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926603/3926603_C1FAFB66C65744A196EFB1F65F2C9864_191126_3926603_Flu_shot_not_as_effective_in_people_who_are_over_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Flu shot, fly vaccine, obese, overweight, flu shot efficacy, flu vaccine efficacy, flu season, flu, influenza, influenza vaccine, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somebody shotgunned winged freedom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS, MISSOURI  A female American bald eagle took two pellets to the wing last week, ABC News reported on Tuesday citing state conservation officials.They say a landowner sighted the bird hanging around the same area for a few days in a row before he reported her.The bald eagle named "Dorothy Parker" by rescuers was down but not out.The department says the wounded bird tried to flee agents by hopping away. They eventually caught her with a blanket.According to the department, University of Missouri's Raptor Rehabilitation Project is taking care of the eagle's broken wing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 13:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3927280/3927280_9E51256B9D0947B682D4E5BA3E196985_191127_3927280_Somebody_shotgunned_winged_freedom_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E17/C0D/E17C0DD29FAB6A1C1E8A69506A2FDFC8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[American bald eagle, bald eagle, shot, Paris, Missouri, rescue, animal rescue, raptor rehabilitation project, animals, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man creates dating app where he is the only guy allowed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GREENSBORO, NORTH CAROLINA  Swiping left or right to find mister right can be easier said than done in today's overcrowded world of dating apps.That's why 31-year-old North Carolina native Aaron Smith might have possibly created the best dating app of all time called Singularity. Why is it called Singularity? Because while it allows as many women to sign up as possible, Smith is the only guy available on the appGENIUS.After striking out on traditional dating apps, Aaron noticed all of them had a major deficiency. Talking to CBS affiliate WFMY, Smith said, "the biggest problem with the other apps is that my face is not featured prominently."So what do you do when you have so much competition? You eliminate the competition. Aaron explained, "If life gives you lemons, you should first make lemonade. Then make sure no other companies can produce or distribute their own soft drinks. So the only game in town is lemonade." So Smith got his software engineer friend Scott McDowell to design Singularity for him. Women using the app won't be flooded with endless pictures of guy after guy. Instead, they just get different pictures of Smith. Smith even made a hilarious commercial for his dating app. He hasn't had a ton of downloads yet, but the app is still in its early days.So ladies, what are you waiting for? Download Singularity today and start swiping.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 13:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3927275/3927275_8B9BCB81A52841178523D614D37C7C87_191127_3927275_Man_creates_dating_app_where_he_is_the_only_guy__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE6/AC1/BE6AC122955D82DBCAF42B844B343E84.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dating apps, online dating apps, Singularity dating app, Singularity, man creates dating app, Aaron Smith Singularity, Aaron Smith dating app, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest radio telescope planned for Australia &amp; S. Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA / SOUTH AFRICA  Designs for a next-generation radio telescope called the Square Kilometer Array, have nearly been finalized while construction will commence in Australia and South Africa in early 2021.The telescope itself will be built in two different phases called SKA 1 and SKA 2.SKA 1, which will soon begin construction, includes two instruments, SKA1-Low and SKA1-Mid.SKA1-Low will consist of 130,000 antennas and will be located in western Australia, according to Australia's Telescope National Facility. While SKA1-Mid will have 130 parabolic dish antennas and will be located in South Africa.SKA1-Low will operate in frequencies between 50 and 350 megahertz while SKA1-Mid will operate in frequencies between 350 megahertz and about 15 gigahertz.According to Square Kilometer Array's project website, the telescope will be hundreds of times faster at mapping the sky than other current radio astronomy facilities. The telescope will cover an area of one square kilometer.The website states that it will be strong enough to detect faint radio signals by cosmic sources that are billions of light years away.Square Kilometer Array's website states that the radio telescope is intended to be in operation for over 50 years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 08:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3927101/3927101_76B52B4914F048C19B6B00D35F9DFCD0_191127_3927101_World_s_biggest_radio_telescope_planned_for_Aust_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3FC/910/3FC9104BFD49893D409E09B68D5F9D31.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Radio telescope, giant radio telescope, Square Kilometre Array, Square Kilometre Array South Africa, Square Kilometre Array Australia, SKA telescopes, SKA telescope in South Africa,  World's largest radio telescope, square kilometre array radio telescope project, radio telescope how it works, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists to use 'Coral IVF' to restore Great Barrier Reef</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA  Scientists from Australia's Southern Cross University have come up with a technique called "Coral IVF" to restore coral in damaged parts of the Great Barrier Reef.Researchers captured millions of coral larvae during mass spawning events that occur following the full moon in the months of November and December. These larvae were then co-cultured with an algae called zooxanthellae, which was grown in a lab to have higher thermal tolerance.According to a news release from the university, these corals are now living in 'coral nursery' rearer pools designed by the research team.Scientists say the rearer pools allow the baby coral to be 'turbo-charged' due to the algae which increases their chance of survival. Optical sensors were added to track the progress of the baby coral.The team now has six rearer pools housing millions of coral larvae. These corals will be dispersed onto damaged parts of the Great Barrier Reef to help form new coral communities.Peter Harrison, a researcher from the university's Marine Ecology Research Center who was involved with the study, said the technique is similar to a "battery pack" which allows the coral to soak up the algae and potentially gain more energy to grow faster.If the project is successful, "Coral IVF" could be used as a blueprint to help restore damaged or dying coral reefs around the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 07:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3927036/3927036_C51D93D24F8741758D894F2D2EABE089_191127_3927036_Scientists_to_use__Coral_IVF__to_restore_Great_B_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5F4/621/5F462102E38D3B60CE13D62387A0F42E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Great barrier reef, Great barrier reef new coral, spawning new coral, Great barrier coral, coral IVF, coral IVF great barrier reef, coral larvae, coral nursery rearer pools, coral babies, turbo-charged coral babies,  great barrier reef dying coral, coral floating nursuries, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New leak exposes China's brainwashing camps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG / CHINA  China has built a vast camp system in Xinjiang and interned about a million Uyghurs. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, or ICIJ, says that a new leak has revealed the conditions in the system.The Guardian reports that the documents contain instructions for officials to "never allow escape."The orders demand constant surveillance with no blindspots and establishing guard towers and layers of fences and walls, according to the Guardian.The BBC reports that every aspect of life in the camps is controlled. The document shows that a detainee must take a fixed position for bed, for workshop, and for lunch queues. The BBC reports that the documents include orders to enforce strict discipline for sleeping, waking, closing doors and roll calls.Chinese officials claimed the camps give lessons on Chinese language and citizenship, but former detainees described them as harsh brainwashing sessions, the New York Times reports.According to the BBC, the camps established a points system based on the detainee's ideological transformation and compliance. The Guardian reports that those who loses points could be transferred to a higher tier of security camps and see their internment increased from the required term of one year.The ICIJ says the documents also revealed the extent of China's AI-powered domestic surveillance program. The predictive system tracks VISAs application records, use of encrypted apps and facial recognition to flag thousands of people for searches and detention.Speaking to the BBC, China's UK ambassador Liu Xiaoming dismissed latest Uyghur internment camp revelations as "fake news," in a press conference on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 05:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3926976/3926976_C9F5107E05BB41F68AEAD52364182C94_191127_3926976_New_leak_exposes_China_s_brainwashing_camps_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B61/AFE/B61AFE08F1D5098818FFB0846261FD30.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, Xinjiang, Uyghur, internment camps, detention camps, indoctrination, brainwashing, human rights, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find microplastic particles in European rivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  Researchers from the Tara Ocean Foundation, an environmental research organization, collected water samples from nine rivers across Europe and found microplastic particles present in every sample.Scientists traveled aboard a research ship called the Tara, across Europe's coastline for six months between May to November and collected 2,700 water samples, according to the foundation's website.These samples were collected from different sites on rivers which included the Thames, Elbe, Rhine and Seine.The microplastic particles found were less than 5 millimeters in size and were mostly microbeads or secondary microplastics, which are formed from larger plastic pieces due to exposure to sunlight.The organization stated that these samples will be analyzed in laboratories in the next 12 to 18 months in order to determine their composition, degradation and their origins.The project's aim is to identify the source of microplastic pollution and its impact on marine life.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 04:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3926916/3926916_77E37610B0924CEF9784FDC12358F5B0_191127_3926916_Scientists_find_microplastic_particles_in_Europe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/542/FE1/542FE12C6837EEDC4E431C4B1040A5DF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[microplastics, microplastic pollution, microplastic pollution europe, microplastic pollution european rivers, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, Tara Ocean Foundation, microplastics in rivers, plastic pollution europe, European seafronts microplastics, european seafronts microplastic pollution, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cows rocking VR goggles in Russia to help with milk production</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  A dairy farm near Mos-COW has finally come up with a use for VR headsetsputting them on cows. According to Interesting Engineering, RusMoloko dairy farm in Russia looks a bit on the futuristic side with dairy cows runningokay, maybe not runningwalking around with fitted VR goggles. The goggles have been specifically designed for dairy cows to see if technology can help trick the animals into relaxing in order to produce more milk.   So do the cows just watch MOOOO-vies all day? Sadly, no. The headsets show a red-focused color scheme, which copies the shades of summer and is supposed to make the cow think it's standing in a field. According to Moscow's agriculture ministry, designers created a unique VR summer field based on several studies showing cows are better at perceiving shades of red than blue or green. Russian officials claim the initial testing of the VR goggles have gone well. Apparently the cows won't shut up about them. A spokesperson for the agriculture ministry said, "during the first test, experts recorded a decrease in anxiety and an increase in the overall emotional mood of the herd." Now we just need to see if this leads to more milk, either way, quite a MOOO-ving story.  In the meantime, expect Google and Facebook to think of ways to start showing these cows ultra annoying personalized ads.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927828/3927828_DDAA74ED7F1749CFAC58044FB2B4141C_191128_3927828_Cows_rocking_VR_goggles_in_Russia_to_help_with_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3BC/1F2/3BC1F23FA585FDD9295E4207DB5CCCF5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cows wearing VR goggles, cow VR goggles, dairy cow VR goggles, Russia dairy cows VR goggles, virtual reality goggles, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead Thai deer found with seven kg of plastic waste in stomach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN THA, THAILAND  A wild deer living in a Thai national park was found to have seven kilograms of trash in its stomach.Kriangsak Thanompun, a director from the Khun Sathan National Park in northern Thailand said the male deer had been eating plastic for a "long time" before it succumbed to death.The deer was found on November 25, by a patrolling officer, the BBC reports. According to the Bangkok Post, the animal appeared to have some hair loss and deterioration at his hoofs and was thin in appearance.An autopsy conducted on the wild deer found items such as rubber gloves, instant noodle packets, coffee packets, plastic bags and even underwear stashed in its stomach.Officials believe all that trash had blocked up the poor animal's gastrointestinal tract, though a further investigation will be launched.Thailand is a major producer of plastic waste due to strong demand in the nation, though it lacks an effective waste management system to recycle plastic, according to the Bangkok Post.Roughly 75 billion pieces of bags are thrown away in Thailand every year, the BBC reports, citing Greenpeace. Thanompun told BBC Thailand that the park plans to implement a scheme to get locals in the area to help collect discarded plastic and other waste.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 11:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927808/3927808_4B725217E9DA4FC3AA6A65A253CABC06_191128_3927808_Dead_Thai_deer_found_with_seven_kg_of_plastic_wa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/97C/600/97C600375E617945169834B3F968003C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Thai deer plastic, Thai deer,  plastic pollution, plastic found in deer, thai deer found dead, Khun Sathan National Park, animal plastic consumption, animals consuming plastic, deer eating plastic, trash in deer's stomach, deer with plastic, plastic waste in deer's stomach, Thailand plastic waste, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first malaria vaccine introduced in Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AFRICA  The World Health Organization has implemented a large-scale malaria vaccine pilot program for 360,000 children across Africa.The vaccine, called RTS,S, is being tested in Malawi, Kenya and Ghana, and is being administered to children upto the age of 2.However, experts have raised concerns about the vaccine's efficacy, durability and safety. Four doses of the vaccine offer only 30 percent protection from severe malaria, for roughly three years.Children who received vaccinations were found to have a 10 times higher risk of meningitis than those given a control vaccine.A fact sheet by PATH Malaria Vaccine Initiative, an international non-profit organization, says the vaccine is designed to trigger the immune system when malaria parasites enter the bloodstream via mosquito bites.The vaccine blocks the parasite from infecting a person's liver, where it could potentially multiply and reenter the bloodstream to infect red blood cells. This is when symptoms of malaria usually starts to appear.Initial symptoms of malaria include fever, headache and chills. In more serious cases, children may develop severe anaemia or respiratory distress.Children under the age of 5 are the most vulnerable to the disease, according to the World Health Organization.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 11:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927803/3927803_15969AE1511645D9A27DEE5B6448A4EC_191128_3927803_World_s_first_malaria_vaccine_introduced_in_Afri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE2/CD4/BE2CD45E444547228B1750A8FE36279C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Malawi, vaccine, malaria africa, malaria vaccine africa, malaria, malaria vaccine, malawi vaccine malaria, malaria vaccine 2019, malaria vaccine child, rts s vaccine, rts s vaccine malawi, malaria cases, immunization, immunization for malaria, malaria shots, malaria shots africa, World's first malaria vaccine, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterans, airlines push back against untrained service animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Back in the day, a dog dumping runny deuces inside a plane full of passengers was the stuff of nightmares. Now, thanks to 'emotional support animals' it's an increasingly typical reality.The New York Times reports that cheapskates who want their pets to fly for free turn to websites offering service animal "certification."This has led to a boom of untrained dogs, birds, rodents, reptiles and amphibians in plane cabins...and lots of disgruntled staff.Meanwhile, the people with legit, properly trained service animals are getting a bad rep.It's even worse for people with disabilities that aren't visible, like brain injuries or PTSD.This is why veterans and disability groups are now wanting new transportation rules, and local or federal regulations that would necessitate animal certification for public spaces. According to the New York Times, airlines are working to cut down on the number of animals onboard.Some are sympathetic to the veterans, and already have policies that make it harder for those who are just out for a free ride.Airlines have also joined forces with veteran groups to crack down on bogus emotional service animals. This means only allowing species that can fulfill service functions, aka, probably not a hamster, sloth, or turtle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 09:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927715/3927715_7A94A9918F4542A98CC51B2AD8BFBF14_191128_3927715_Veterans__airlines_push_back_against_untrained_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/187/FFB/187FFBA1F6F603AE8253F4E8707E5309.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Emotional support animals, service animals, support animals, service animals plane, support animals plane, veterans, disabled, disabilities, hidden disabilities, invisible disabilities, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voyager 2 probes outer limits of the solar system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Voyagers were launched 42 years ago, but Voyager 2 took the longer route to interstellar space.Live Science reports that Voyager 2 detected a fiery plasma wall in the heliopause, where the sun's outward blowing solar winds clash with cosmic rays. This barrier protects the solar system by repulsing and weakening cosmic rays.Citing NASA, Live Science reports that Voyager 1 could not detect the wall because its sensors malfunctioned. However, as Voyager 2 crosses the heliopause, it found holes in the protective shell and temperatures twice as high as past models predicted.According to BBC, the sun's energies charge particles into an ionized plasma state and shoot them out to form solar winds and the heliopause.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 09:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927682/3927682_54790DB015404441A9F987323FB9600F_191128_3927682_Voyager_2_probes_outer_limits_of_the_solar_syste_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/195/223/195223FF3E4C68166D5A23C509A0FF0A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Voyagers, Voyager 1, Voyager 2, sun, solar system, heliosphere, heliopause, NASA, US, solar wind, solar winds, interstellar wind winds, interstellar, outer space, space , TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeChat is banning Chinese Americans for political speech</title>
      <description><![CDATA[This week on Made in China: Tencent's WeChat has started banning and censoring Chinese-American citizens for commenting on the recent Hong Kong elections.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 04:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927534/3927534_3D63BCDF2AF94D63B51732629A5DFDC1_191128_3927534_WeChat_is_banning_Chinese_Americans_for_politica_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2A5/F65/2A5F65E1CE72C150C5F19C36A07D51FC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[WeChat bans Americans, Americans blocked by WeChat, Tencent censorship, Tencent WeChat censor Americans, Hong Kong elections, Chinese censorship, viral China, Made in China, Chinese videos, viral video, Chinese viral video, Tomonews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 French soldiers perish in helicopter collision</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAMAKO, MALI  A helicopter collision in Mali has taken the lives of 13 French soldiers in France's worst military loss in four decades.On Monday evening, a French Tiger attack helicopter was reinforcing troops on the ground chasing after militants in Mali when the helicopter collided with a Cougar military transport helicopter around 7:40 p.m. local time.The incident occurred near the Mali's border at Burkina Faso and Niger.The two aircraft crashed near each other, killing all 13 French soldiers on board, including an officer and six commandos, according to the BBC. An investigation has been launched to discover the cause of the collision, the heaviest single French military loss since a 1983 attack in Beirut killed 58 paratroopers.In a tweet, French President Emmanuel Macron expressed "deep sadness" and called the soldiers "heroes."French lawmakers observed a minute of silence for the fallen soldiers on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 02:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927488/3927488_6DAF40D8D73142EFB61746CF570232F7_191128_3927488_13_French_soldiers_perish_in_helicopter_collisio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/543/DDC/543DDCC9245FAD1E275500FAE46FA59E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[France helicopter collision, France Mali, french troops in mali, french troops in mali 2019,  french military mali, french troops killed in mali, france mali helicopter collision, helicopter collision, french military helicopter collision, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's only brown panda in captivity kind of gets adopted</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANXI PROVINCE  The world's only brown panda held in captivity has been adopted by a U.S.-based charity last week. According to China's fake news media Xinhua, Qizai is a 10-year-old male with a one-of-a-kind brown and white coat because of a genetic anomaly. According to Next Shark, he was adopted by Colorado-based nonprofit Pandas International founded by Suzanne Braden and Diane Rees in 2000. The group is committed to the conservation of pandas. Here's the catch, Qizai will continue crashing at the Qinling Giant Panda Research Center located in China's northwestern Shaanxi province. The arrangement is that Pandas International is granted access to himwhatever that means. The panda non-profit will also get regular updates about his life. UPDATES likehe ate, he pooed, he slept?The Chinese breeding center allowed for the group to adopt Qizai for life to thank them for their daily work and for donating vaccines, lab instrument, baby panda crib and milk powder.   Apparently there have only been five brown-and-white pandas spotted since 1985. According to World Wildlife, there are currently, 1,864 pandas living in the wild around the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927470/3927470_BB487A9527AA417EA7D5C75315E2FC56_191128_3927470_World_s_only_brown_panda_in_captivity_kind_of_ge_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F0/8DD/1F08DD687CDF1BE7DA0DFC125AB2327E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Brown panda, brown and white panda, brown panda adopted, Qizai brown panda, Qizai brown panda adopted, Pandas International, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bubble barrier' could stop plastic waste in rivers from polluting our oceans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMSTERDAM  Dutch-based startup "The Great Bubble Barrier" says that air bubbles could stop plastic waste in rivers from reaching the ocean.The company says its program features a pipe and air compressor that generate bubbles and a trap system that gathers plastics on the canal of Amsterdam's Westerdok.New Atlas reports that a previous trial collected 86 percent of riverbourne plastic trash.The company states that the barrier's diagonal placement uses the water flow to guide the plastic waste to the catchment system on the riverside for collection.The pipe supplements the garbage collection boats that also clean 42 tonnes of plastic trash from the canal each year.While boats could not gather submerged plastic objects, the bubble barrier generates upward flow that brings the plastics to the catchment system on the surface.The company also claims that the bubble barrier pumps oxygen into the river, which prevents algae blooms and bolsters the aquatic ecosystem.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 16:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/30/3928508/3928508_DC7BF8B1469C4F60B037AEDA86E91A89_191130_3928508__Bubble_barrier__could_stop_plastic_waste_in_riv_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/470/4CC/4704CCEBF6DECCBAD783EAC39F412881.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Great Bubble Barrier, bubbles, plastic waste, plastic pollution, plastics, Westerdok, Amsterdam, Netherlands, environment, ocean, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea fires two short-range missiles towards the Sea of Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG  North Korea launched two unidentified short-range projectiles from the country's South Hamgyong province towards the Sea of Japan on Thursday, November 28, around 4:59 p.m. local time.Both missiles flew around 380 kilometers and reached an altitude of roughly 97 kilometers, according to South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff. The two missiles were fired within 30 seconds of one another.North Korea confirmed that the projectiles were launched from a super-large multiple rocket launcher system. The country's state agency KCNA says the launcher system has a "continuous fire system."This is North Korea's fourth test of the missile launcher system, reports Yonhap News Agency. It was previously tested on August 24, September 10 and October 31, earlier this year.Japan has yet to confirm if the missiles landed in the nation's Exclusive Economic Zone.South Korea's military called on North Korea to immediately "stop such moves," adding that consecutive missiles launches won't help in easing tensions on the Korean Peninsula, Yonhap reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928443/3928443_96973B038E5345718A7600F4C4FDE7B4_191129_3928443_North_Korea_fires_two_short_range_missiles_towar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[North korea missile launch, North korea missile test, north korea rockets, north korea missile, kim jong un, north korea weapons, north korea, north korean missile, north korea fires missile, short range missile, unidentified projectiles, Multiple Launch Rocket System, Multiple Launch Rocket System north korea, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flesh-eating bacteria meets woman's eye sockets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, TENNESSEE  A woman had one hell of an eye opening experience after her eye sockets got a bit too up close and personal with some flesh-eating bacteria.According to a case report in The Journal of Emergency Medicine, a 58-year-old woman showed up at the emergency room after her eyes had been bugging her for five days. The report published on Nov. 7, said the woman had been suffering from eye pain and swelling which had gotten progressively worse. According to Live Science, an eye exam found her to have pretty intense swelling around both her eye sockets as well as a bunch of goo discharging from her eyes. At first, doctors thought she might have the bacterial infection cellulitis, which affects the skin and underlying tissue. She was given antibiotics, but when her symptoms got worse, physicians worried that it could be necrotizing fasciitis. A tissue sample confirmed their fears. Necrotizing fasciitis is a bacterial infection that destroys the skin and muscle tissue and can quickly spread throughout the body. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, people can become infected when bacteria enter the body through breaks in the skin, including cuts and scrapes, burns and surgical wounds. It's unclear how the woman picked up the infection, but she had been taking medication for arthritis that weakened her immune system, leaving her more susceptible to severe infections. The woman had to have several surgeries to remove the damaged and affected tissue, and received antibiotics to treat the specific strains of bacteria she was infected with. After 13 days in the hospital, she was able to go home. She left in stable condition and luckily didn't experience any vision loss.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928434/3928434_1E8502A7DA9A431398EFA3E57CA97ABB_191129_3928434_Flesh_eating_bacteria_meets_woman_s_eye_sockets_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5FA/4B9/5FA4B9574195A28C7E9AC6D7D69E5BCF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bacteria, bacterial infection, eye bacterial infection, eye infection, eye socket infection, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge purifying towers proposed to clean Delhi's air</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DELHI, INDIA  An Indian architectural firm is proposing to build huge air purifying towers that will tackle air pollution in Delhi.Studio Symbiosis Architects says that its 60-meter-tall Aura towers will form an air cleaning system to protect city residents from pollution, including PM 2.5 particulate matter.According to DesignBoom, the structure's aerodynamic designs include spiraling contours that draw in polluted air and expel clean filtered air. The pressure differentials enables the tower to pull PM 2.5 particles into its internal filtering chamber. The architects claim the smaller iteration of the Aura tower with a height of 18 meters could clean 32 million cubic meters of air per day.The firm says the taller towers will form a protective ring around Delhi's city borders to keep pollution out, while the 18 meter towers will be built by pollution hot spots inside the city.Pollution detecting drones and air cleaner attachments for cars will also form an integrated system with the towers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 11:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928325/3928325_3285EABBE92645A98FAA2DA6B2D565AE_191129_3928325_Huge_purifying_towers_proposed_to_clean_Delhi_s__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B06/871/B0687159312C8137F7C1489A398DD8DF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Aura tower, Aura towers, Studio Symbiosis, air pollution, pm 2.5, Delhi, India, environment, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex &amp; Violence is for Kids?! YouTube Overrides TomoNews</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Taipei  We ask why YouTube has set 140 of our videos with themes of sex and violence as "Made for Kids."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 09:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928246/3928246_DA8B70C8732A479EAA4D23BF7616F1A8_191129_3928246_Sex___Violence_is_for_Kids___YouTube_Overrides_T_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/33B/489/33B48988F86CF86595C43B63C767D873.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Safe for kids? Youtube safe for kids? COPPA, YouTube COPPA, YouTube rules COPPA. FTC, COPPA update, kid-safe, content not for kids, TomoNews, Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, Upcoming changes to youtube, COPPA YouTube fine, COPPA YouTube update, COPPA YouTube settings, YouTube algorithm, Youtube Algorithm change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple surprises their Denny's waitress with a new car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GALVESTON, TEXAS  A kindhearted couple gave a Texas waitress a brand new ride after finding out she walked 14-miles every day for work.According to KTRK, waitress Adrianna Edwards works at Denny's and said she has to walk seven miles just to get to the restaurant. A Galveston couple found out about Adrianna's story during breakfast on Tuesday. They also found out that she was saving money to buy a car. That's when the generous couple hopped on over to a car dealer and bought a 2011 Nissan Sentra. A few hours later, they returned to the Denny's and gave Edwards the surprise of her life. The couple, who requested to remain anonymous, gave Edwards the ride with no strings attached. Okay, maybe with one tiny string. They asked that hopefully one day Edwards can return the favor and pay it forward. And with Adrianna's new wheels, her five hour commute to and from work is now only a half an hour.  She told KTRK, "I still feel like I'm dreaming. Every two hours, I come look out my window to see if there's still a car there. When I see somebody in need, I'll probably be more likely to help them out to do everything that I can to help them out."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 08:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928215/3928215_851B97DF18DE4D7CAA665E45258727FF_191129_3928215_Couple_surprises_their_Denny_s_waitress_with_a_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9DE/883/9DE883DC52331FBDFD3446E5CA306C5A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Denny's, Denny's waitress gets new car, Denny's patrons buy car for waitress, waitress walks 14 miles to work, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamer sells friend's $1m character for $500</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SICHUAN, CHINA  A Chinese gamer sold his friend's character several hundred thousand dollars short of its $1m plus value, reports the South China Morning Post.According to Sichuan High Court, mega rich gamer Lu had been letting his pal Lee play as his character on MMORPG "Justice Online".The South China Morning Post reports that Lu had sunk close to $1.4m US dollars into the character. Lee then tried to sell the character back to Lu on the NetEase server.  However he made a $1.4m typo by mistakenly selling the character to the wrong guy for just $500.Lee explained that he was dizzy from too much gaming.An enraged Lu sued everyone including Lee,  the buyer and NetEase. According to the South China Morning Post, the court settled the case last week. Netease revoked the transaction and the buyer got nearly 13 large in damages.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 02:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928013/3928013_AB5048DD2EC74CCEBF6D04B46B31FE89_191129_3928013_Gamer_sells_friend_s__1m_character_for__500_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AF9/042/AF9042D36728D75542290309B76FB377.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, Sichuan, Justice Online, NetEase, $1.4 million, character, expensive typo, gaming, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
