<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Beachfront</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>China lifts ban on use of rhino and tiger parts for medicine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China has allowed the use of rhino and tiger products in medicine, alarming conservationists who say it will hamper efforts to protect them from extinction.China's State Council recently announced the partial lifting of a 25-year-old ban which will now allow the use of tiger and rhinoceros parts for scientific, medical, or cultural use.According to the New York Times, powdered rhino horns are used in Chinese traditional medicine to treat fevers and food poisoning, while tiger bone wine is believed to increase virility. Both have no proven benefit.The Chinese government claims the trade will be strictly controlled, and products must only be sourced from animals that are bred in captivity, excluding those in zoos.But conservationists say the move will only fuel black market trade in wild animal parts, endangering the estimated 30,000 rhinos and 3,900 tigers still in the wild.The move is a complete turnaround from Beijing's previous efforts in championing climate change initiatives and banning the domestic ivory trade. Experts speculate that the sudden easing of the ban may be a push to encourage Chinese traditional culture and medicine, reports Time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/10/31/3722689/3722689_C8202FDEEC3649C5BE74E445D1A8783A_181031_3722689_China_lifts_ban_on_use_of_rhino_and_tiger_parts__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/614/B80/614B806E48480A83B9E2DFDB6691634F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese medicine, endangered animals, rhino horns, tiger bone wine, tiger bone, illegal trade, wild animal parts, wild animal trade, poaching, China, extinct animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Trojan horse" antibiotic could help with fight against superbugs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  A new antibiotic has shown promising results after bypassing several multidrug resistant bacteria in early clinical trials.The trials were conducted on a total of 448 patients with kidney or urinary tract infections, according to a paper published in The Lancet.The antibiotic, cefiderocol, was able to enter the bacteria as it hid among iron molecules.Bacteria in our bodies usually look for iron molecules as our bodies' natural response to an infection is to create a low-iron environment, to stop the bacteria from multiplying.Once cefiderocol is inside the bacteria, it is able to kill it as other antibiotics.However, larger trials would still be needed to ensure the effectiveness of the "trojan horse" antibiotic.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 08:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/10/31/3722595/3722595_2FE1F4E4D2404504BB81977F4E51E79D_181031_3722595__Trojan_horse__antibiotic_could_help_with_fight__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E82/4C7/E824C78B1BC54FFC92CA86DDF516306B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, usa, antibiotics, trojan horse, superbugs, bacteria, trojan horse antibiotic, multidrug resistant bacteria, cefiderocol, antibiotic enters bacteria to kill it, iron molecule, antibiotic resistance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man torches home after trying to fight spiders with fire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FRESNO, CALIFORNIA  A man in California learned the hard way that there are way less destructive methods to purge your house of eight-legged crawlers.The Fresno Bee reports that the man had been house sitting his parents' Fresno house when he discovered venomous black widow spiders on the brick exterior.Instead of going with bug spray, Einstein got a blowtorch to exterminate the arachnids, but ended up setting the house on fire too.According to the Fresno Fire Department, the flames penetrated through a small crack in the bricks and lit up the flammable material inside, which then shot fire straight up to the attic.Twenty-nine firefighters thankfully managed to contain the blaze, but the inferno still dropped $10,000 worth of damage to the attic and second storey. Ouch.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 02:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/10/31/3722398/3722398_DA622828D6BA4432AE3BD7E6FB84C7C6_181031_3722398_Man_torches_home_after_trying_to_fight_spiders_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/050/084/05008450A786D2215C0424A9A7132217.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, spider, blowtorch, black widow, black widow spider, how to kill spiders, how not to kill spiders, house fire, home fire, housesitter, house sitting, man sets home on fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Germany's parliament and chancellor are elected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GERMANY  Every four years, German voters take to the polls to elect members of the Bundestag, which then selects the next chancellor.Germans cast two votes, one for a candidate and one for a political party. This determines how the 598 seats in the Bundestag will be divided among the political parties. The process is called a personalized proportional representation system.The first vote for the candidate, will be on the left side of the ballot while the second vote, for a political party, will be on the right side of the ballot, according to CNBC.The newly-elected parliament then votes for the chancellor. The chancellor would need to receive more than half of the votes to be elected.As there are multiple political parties, the chancellor also needs to receive votes from other smaller parties along with his or her own party or form coalitions in order to receive an absolute majority of votes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 02:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/10/31/3722390/3722390_3A861E66A8E54071B2304A24D05F48D9_181031_3722390_How_Germany_s_parliament_and_chancellor_are_elec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA5/2C6/BA52C6B8D1307D40947F47F4062DE028.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Germany, German elections, German parliament, Germany bundestag, German voting process, German chancellor, How German elections work, german elections explained, German election process]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No survivors found yet in Indonesia plane crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#LionAir #JT610 #planecrash #IndonesiaJAKARTA, INDONESIA  No survivors have been found after an Indonesian plane carrying 188 passengers and crew crashed into the Java Sea on Monday.Lion Air Flight JT610 left Jakarta Monday morning at 6.20 a.m. bound for Pangkal Pinang. According to plane tracking service FlightRadar24, contact was lost with the aircraft not long after take off.An Indonesian civil aviation official told the Agence France-Presse that the Boeing 737 Max 8 plane was carrying 188 passengers and crew. Indonesia's Search and Rescue agency told the Jakarta Post that everyone onboard is believed to be dead.Citing Indonesian officials, Malaysia-based newspaper The New Straits Times reports that the plane is believed to have crashed waters of the island of Java. Debris and airplane seats have been found, as have the remains of some passengers.Citing an online post from Indonesian TV presenter Conchita Caroline who flew on the plane's penultimate flight on Sunday the Associated Press reports that she claims that flight was held back for engine checks. The engines used by that Boeing 737 Max 8 are called CFM LEAP-1B. Caroline told the New York Times, she could see the right engine shaking.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/10/31/3722361/3722361_B00187F57BB342A0A21580A3E413091D_181031_3722361_No_survivors_found_yet_in_Indonesia_plane_crash_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/131/91D/13191D004B9156CAC2FF8C6AF514C177.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Indonesia plane crash, plane crash indonesia, indonesia plane crash survivors, lion air, indonesia plane crash 2018, java plane crash, jakarta, boeing, TomoNews, Satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant emerald weighing 1.1kg
found in Zambian mine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAGEM, ZAMBIA  Gemfields, the world's largest producer of green stones, has discovered a giant, green emerald in Zambia.The emerald weighs more than 1.1 kilograms and was discovered in Kagem, the world's largest emerald mine located in Zambia.A statement released by Gemfields said that the emerald has "remarkable clarity and a perfectly balanced golden green hue."Emeralds in the Kagem mine were reportedly formed 450 million years ago due to a rare combination of in situ minerals and magma from the Earth's crust which then developed into emerald crystals.The gem is being called "Inkalamu" which means lion in the local Bemba language in Zambia.The uncut emerald was discovered in an open-pit mine on October 2 by a geologist and a veteran emerald miner.Several pieces are expected to be cut from the 5,655-carat emerald and will be auctioned in Singapore this month.Most of the emeralds in the world are mined from Zambia, Colombia and Brazil. As a result, emeralds are even more precious than diamonds due to their scarcity.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/01/3723470/3723470_1620517D3D2C46DA9D592153CE0A7C8A_181101_3723470_Giant_emerald_weighing_1_1kg_found_in_Zambian_mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BB2/ED8/BB2ED8D74B135B125491387DEDE5B8F5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, emeralds, Zambia, gemstones, emeralds zambia, emerald stones zambia, green stones, Kagem emerald mine, Inkamalu, Lion Emerald, Zambian emerald crystal, giant emerald unearthed in Zambia, jewelry, jewels, gems, gemstones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vineyard worker killed by grape-harvesting machine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NAPA COUNTY, CALIFORNIA  Some less than pleasant news through the grapevine after a vineyard worker had an accident involving a grape harvesting machine.According to CBS San Francisco, 49-year-old Napa resident Leon Marcelo Lua was picking grapes at the Beaucanon Winery around 12:30 p.m. on Monday. According to his family, Lua was working on the ground next to a grape harvesting machine, when a piece of his clothing got yanked into the machine. Lua was instantly pulled into the harvesting machine and immediately began pushing up daisies. Cal Fire first responders responded in minutes to the report of a worker stuck in a grape-picking machine. Unfortunately, it was too late to do anything. Cal OSHA is now investigating the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 11:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/01/3723423/3723423_71B6741AB7544CA0ACAA26F899DEF713_181101_3723423_Vineyard_worker_killed_by_grape_harvesting_machi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DB1/4A7/DB14A732ABCAFEB226E9B0265561D31F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, grape-harvesting machine, grape picking machine, grape-harvesting machine accident, vineyard worker]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay penguin dads welcome their first baby chick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  Just weeks after winning over the internet, Sea Life Sydney's same-sex penguin couple have become proud parents to their very own chick.According to a press release from the aquarium, male Gentoo penguins Sphen and Magic had become inseparable before breeding season, and are constantly waddling around and going for swims together.When the pair began making a nest, they were given a dummy egg to practice incubating, and ensure they wouldn't be left out of the season.The lovebirds did such a bang job that their dummy was soon swapped for a real one, and they became full-fledged parents on October 19.As to whether it's a boy or a girl  Baby Sphengic's gender won't be determined for another two months.The as yet unnamed baby will stay with its dads for the first five to six weeks of its life. Once big enough, the chick will shed its baby fluff, and before you know it, it'll be sporting big penguin feathers and getting swimming lessons.The happy family will be hanging out at the aquarium to welcome visitors, so if anyone wants a dose of cuteness, feel free to come on down.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 07:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/01/3723231/3723231_40FD860F78F84DF6BDF08127235C6208_181101_3723231_Gay_penguin_dads_welcome_their_first_baby_chick_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/798/11C/79811C42241502486520E082EB7F7891.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, penguins, cute penguins, gay penguins, baby penguin, penguin chick, penguin couple, penguin dads, sphengic, baby sphengic, baby animals, cute animals, cute babies, sphen, magic, sydney aquarium]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angela Merkel stepping down as chancellor in 2021</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERLIN  Looks as if Germany's Angela Merkel is beginning her slow motion auf wiedersehen after announcing that she will step down as chancellor in 2021. Following a disastrous showing by her center-right Christian Democratic Union party in recent state elections, Merkel dropped the bomb at a news conference in Berlin. The lame duck, who has been chancellor since 2005, also said she she would be stepping aside as party leader, a position she has held since 2000.   Merkel has long insisted that the chancellor should also be the leader of the ruling party, and that it was dangerous to have too many cooks in the kitchen.She's suddenly cool with dividing the roles between two people. Who would have guessed? But how long can one of Europe's most powerful politicians last, now that her coalition government is increasingly unpopular and unstable? After 13 years at the helm, was this finally a case of the migrant that broke the camel's back? Who will carry the torch as the global counterweight to Trump-esque nationalists now?     What's clear is that the vultures are circling. Will she even last until 2021?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 04:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/01/3723123/3723123_39FB6C356DEB4AE18DBFB41FCFF6C273_181101_3723123_Angela_Merkel_stepping_down_as_chancellor_in_202_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B5E/936/B5E936CA2650E11002DA5784E29F56BD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Angela Merkel, Merkel stepping down, Merkel stepping down CDU, Merkel stepping down chancellor, Merkel Germany]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate seats up for grabs, could Democrats win back the Senate?</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  A total of 44 Democrats and 50 Republicans are up for reelection, with six toss-up seats available.Democrats are projected to win one of two Senate seats in play for Minnesota, as well as Washington, California, New Mexico, Hawaii, New York, Virginia, Maine, Vermont, Rhode Island, Massachusetts, Connecticut, Delaware and Maryland, according to politics site and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics.Polling data shows Democrats are also likely to win in Ohio, Pennsylvania and West Virginia. The other seat for Minnesota, as well as seats for Wisconsin, Michigan and New Jersey, are also leaning Democrat.Republicans are projected to win in Utah, Wyoming, Nebraska and one of two seats in play for Mississippi. Republicans are also likely to win the other seat for Mississippi, as well as for North Dakota, while Texas and Tennessee are leaning Republican. If Democrats win the majority in the Senate, they could possibly move to impeach Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh and President Donald Trump.Only a total 19 federal officials have been impeached in U.S. history: a senator, a cabinet secretary, 15 judges and two presidents. The first president to be impeached was Andrew Johnson in 1868 after he dismissed Edwin M. Stanton as secretary of war. President Bill Clinton was impeached in 1998 on charges of perjury and obstruction of justice in the wake of his affair with a White House intern.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 12:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/02/3724177/3724177_365D62DA58304D8196D84A9220581F92_181102_3724177_Senate_seats_up_for_grabs__could_Democrats_win_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/53C/534/53C53436BC99D7C5510247E3D1D57854.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, US Senate, US Senate elections 2018, US Senate elections, Democrats, Republicans, US elections, could Democrats win back the Senate, US Senate seats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seas are absorbing way more heat than we previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  The world's oceans have absorbed considerably more heat than previously estimated, according to a new study. The results, published in the journal Nature on Wednesday, found that seas around the globe may be absorbing up to 60 percent more heat since the 1990s than earlier estimates calculated, according to Scientific American. Researchers calculated the oceans have absorbed around 13 zettajoules of heat energy every year between 1991 and 2016, CNN reports.The findings suggest the earth is more sensitive to greenhouse gas emissions than previously thought. Rather than relying on direct ocean measurements, the researchers looked at the amount of oxygen and carbon dioxide in the atmosphere since 1991. As oceans warm up, their ability to absorb oxygen and carbon dioxide decreases, thus more of those gases remain in the air. By measuring the changes in atmospheric oxygen and carbon dioxide levels, while also controlling for other factors such as human greenhouse gas emissions, the team was able to estimate how much heat the oceans have absorbed over the past few decades. Warmer oceans could potentially lead to sea levels rising faster than forecasted, dying off of coral reefs, increasingly powerful storms, faster rates of melting sea ice and affecting ocean currents, CNN reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 11:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/02/3724122/3724122_90568CB8AA1F4FDBAB795151C7D86A88_181102_3724122_Seas_are_absorbing_way_more_heat_than_we_previou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4F7/0BD/4F70BD1A70041F23B260B390E19C0077.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, oceans absorbing heat, global warming, climate change, seas absorbing more heat, greenhouse gas emissions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adolescents who quit weed see rapid improvements in memory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MASSACHUSETTS  Adolescents who regularly use cannabis but stop for 30 days have better memory and improved cognition compared to those who continue to use pot, according to a new study. According to NPR, a study published in the Journal of Clinical Psychiatry on Tuesday found that when young people stop using marijuana their verbal learning and memory improve. Researchers at Massachusetts General Hospital looked at 88 participants age 16- 25, who were regular users of marijuana. According to the study's lead author, Randi Schuster, director of neuropsychology at Massachusetts General Hospital's Center for Addiction Medicine, the researchers recruited a range of participants. Some of the young people smoked once per week, while others smoked almost daily. Participants were randomly assigned into an abstaining group or a non-abstaining group.  Volunteers had their urine tested weekly and were also given a variety of tasks testing their attention and memory. Researchers found that after four weeks, there was no noticeable difference in attention scores between the two groups. However, memory scores for nonusers improved, while users' memory scores remained relatively steady. The study concluded that adolescents learn better when they are not using cannabis, and that some of the deficits from usage appear to be reversible.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 11:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/02/3724113/3724113_EF28B744AF6A427FA9CE88917B0B3A00_181102_3724113_Adolescents_who_quit_weed_see_rapid_improvements_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DD8/D4A/DD8D4A7D6D48BA13728E72DBA82DFF5B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, adolescents cognition, memory loss, improved cognition, attention]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese teen killed by sign after sticking body out of car roof</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGXI, CHINA  A Chinese teenager's life was cut tragically short after he crashed into a sign while riding through a highway with his body out the car.The incident happened last Sunday along a highway in Jiangxi, when a 13-year-old boy was seen sticking his torso out of the sunroof of a moving silver sedan, Beijing Time reports.Two men who were in a car behind the boy spotted the shenanigans and began recording, all the while laughing and poking fun at the child.The pair can be heard joking that he might hit a low-hanging sign that was coming up, only to be shocked into silence when the boy's head actually smashes into the sign, causing him to immediately fall back on the top of the car.The man driving the car the boy was riding in appeared to call for help. However, local media reports later confirmed the teen died in the accident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 10:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/02/3724087/3724087_5D48C5AE5237407499E1FE6491A892BE_181102_3724087_Chinese_teen_killed_by_sign_after_sticking_body__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/23B/273/23B273FD6777C44DA5D32D13F92A1B20.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, chinese teen, teen crashes into sign, freak accident, accident, tragic accident, sunroof, highway accident, road accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. birthright citizenship explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S.  Birthright citizenship is defined as a constitutional right for any child born in the United States to automatically gain U.S. citizenship.The 14th Amendment states that "All persons born or naturalized in the United States, and subject to the jurisdiction thereof, are citizens of the United States and of the State wherein they reside."The amendment was ratified in 1868 to guarantee citizenship for all. This included former slaves, who at the time didn't have the right to own property, roam freely or even stay in the country.However, it was still never clearly defined whether or not children born of immigrants in the U.S. were automatically U.S. citizens.Then came the case of Wong Kim Ark. Wong was the son of Chinese immigrants and was born in California. After he returned from a trip to China in 1895, the federal government tried to stop him from re-entering the U.S. under the Chinese Exclusion Act. His case ended up in court, and after a years-long battle, the Supreme Court in 1898 ruled that Wong was in fact a U.S. citizen, as he was born in the U.S. Meanwhile, despite all this, Native Americans were still consistently denied rights given to others born in the U.S. until Congress finally granted citizenship to all Native Americans in 1924.President Donald Trump has announced plans to issue an Executive order to end birthright citizenship, the Supreme Court would still have the power to overturn the Executive order and interpret the Constitution on its own.Other than the U.S., there are 30 other nations in the world that recognize birthright citizenship including Argentina, Brazil, Canada, Panama and Mexico.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/02/3723867/3723867_E490027D27D44FD98707946E632739CA_181102_3723867_U_S__birthright_citizenship_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/94D/C66/94DC66FFC13A1405506C5F8766781420.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, birthright citizenship, jus soli, us birthright citizenship, US Constitution, the 14th Amendment, explaining US Birthright citizenship]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the Democrats be able to impeach Trump or Kavanaugh?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  The upcoming midterm elections are poised to determine whether or not the Democrats can take back the House and the Senate.Members of the Democratic Party have said they will push for impeachment for President Trump and Justice Brett Kavanaugh should they regain control, NBC reports. But how exactly will this be possible?The impeachment process begins with the House Judiciary Committee reviewing charges against an official and determining if there are grounds for impeachment.The full House of Representatives votes on one or more articles of impeachment, and if at least one gets a simple majority vote, the official is indicted and considered impeached.From there, the proceedings move to the Senate for a trial presided over by the Supreme Court Chief Justice, with the Senate acting as jury.In order to get a conviction, a supermajority, or two-thirds of the senators must find the official guilty. Once convicted, he is immediately removed from office.The Democrats will need to win 218 seats during the midterm elections to regain control over the House of Representatives and initiate impeachment proceedings. Polls indicate that they have a good chance of doing so, according to CNN and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics.However, the Democrats are much less likely to win enough seats in the Senate to ensure a two-thirds majority vote for conviction.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/05/3725557/3725557_E2D64DF5B30C414DAA50B73CC17B6363_181105_3725557_Will_the_Democrats_be_able_to_impeach_Trump_or_K_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/332/69C/33269CA08987C09FF0F2DE271D6C6629.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, trump, kavanaugh, impeachment, donald trump, brett kavanaugh, how to impeach, US impeachment process, impeachment trial, democrats impeach trump, democrats impeach kavanaugh]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Airways flight from hell finally lands after 3 days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  British Airways turned what should have been an eight-hour flight home into a hellish three-day ordeal for over two hundred passengers.The BBC reports that flight 2036 was supposed to leave Orlando past 7 p.m. on Thursday, but passengers were forced to disembark due to a technical issue four hours after waiting in the plane.They were put in a hotel for the night, but the nightmare continued with more delays, plus lack of communication from BA, whose preferred method of updating passengers was via letter.The flight flew out of Florida over a day later, but was forced to divert to New York after the plane started dumping fuel and lowering the landing gear in mid-air.At JFK, it was hours before a BA rep showed, only to tell the disgruntled travelers they had no food or drinks, and not enough accommodations due to the New York Marathon.Stranded passengers were forced to sleep on the cold hard airport floor for over five hours, among them a young cancer survivor and a toddler celebrating her birthday.Eventually, they were all herded back onto a plane and finally made it back to London Sunday morning.Passengers are still furious at having to endure the flight from hell, especially since they say British Airways has yet to apologize sincerely, according to the New York Post.The airline put out a statement saying sorry, but it also claims its ground team cared for the travelers while they were trapped in New York.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/05/3725542/3725542_62544C8824334ECB981F01D023BE4E3A_181105_3725542_British_Airways_flight_from_hell_finally_lands_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/D55/126/D551266381284D1A8C93DDD5E4A53131.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, flight from hell, british airways, plane trouble, flight delay, delayed flight, flight cancellation, cancelled flight, turbulent travel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can cell phone radiation cause 
cancer in humans?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO   Researchers found evidence of links between tumors in male rats and exposure to radio frequency radiation.According to a final report released on Thursday by the U.S. National Toxicology Program, about 3,000 rats and mice were exposed to whole body radio frequency radiation nine hours a day for up to two years. Rats began exposure to the radiation in the womb while mice started at 5-6 weeks old. The radiation used in the experiment was similar to those emitted by 2G and 3G mobile phones. These results do not apply to Wi-Fi signals or phones that use 4G or 5G technologies, these use different methods of signal modulation that the NTP did not study in their research.The rodents lived in specially designed chambers with isolated rooms where a transmitting antenna subjected the rats to RFR fields with frequencies of 900 and 1900 megahertz. The study found evidence that radiation exposure was associated with the emergence of tumors in the hearts, brains, and adrenal glands of male rats. However, cancers found in female rats and male and female mice weren't conclusively linked to radio frequency radiation exposure.The research cost $30 million and was ongoing for a decade. The NTP's goal was to gather information on the effects of mobile phone radiation on rats in response to the increasing universality of cellphone use among humans.However, NTP scientists and the U.S. Food and Drug Administration stated that the results of the research do not directly affect humans since the rodents were exposed to extreme levels of cellphone radiation, which surpass the current safety limits on mobile phone radiation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/05/3725535/3725535_2691B58430EA47CD86DD048F082D0491_181105_3725535_Can_cell_phone_radiation_cause__cancer_in_humans_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/211/458/211458CCA56A62EE3EB19FB3C32047C4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, phone radiation, cellphone radiation, cancer, rats, tumor, experiment, mobile phones, cellphones, radiation, health, technology, cancer research, research, rats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant caravan begins 'route of death' through Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO  Thousands of Central American migrants have resumed their march toward the United States on Sunday after disagreements a day before over the route north.  According to the Associated Press, most of the approximately 4,000 migrants are now moving along what some are referring to as the "route of death" to the town of Cordoba around 124 miles away. The next portion of the journey will be one of the longest yet, as the migrants will now have to pass via the sugar fields and fruit groves of Veracruz, a state where hundreds of migrants have gone missing in recent years due to kidnappers looking for ransom payments. A large majority of the migrants are trying to escape rampant poverty, gang violence and political unrest in the countries of Honduras, Guatemala, El Salvador and Nicaragua. Mexico now has three caravans totalling more than 6,000 migrants spread out over 300 miles of highway in the states of Chiapas, Oaxaca and Veracruz. President Trump has ordered more than 7,000 active duty troops to be deployed throughout Texas, Arizona and California along the Mexican border in response to the caravan. According the Associated Press, President Donald Trump could sign an order next week allowing for mass detention of migrants caught entering the U.S. and bar anyone caught crossing illegally from claiming asylum.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 10:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/05/3725513/3725513_0385560730F947CAADCC230377FA356A_181105_3725513_Migrant_caravan_begins__route_of_death__through__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D9D/92F/D9D92F773F8F031DD2833DA4AED2A403.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, migrant caravan, migrant, President Trump, US southern border, US Mexico border]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog shoots hunter in the back in freak hunting accident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAS CRUCES, NEW MEXICO  A hunter in New Mexico nearly crossed over to the great beyond after his doggie best friend pulled the trigger on him.The Las Cruces Sun News reports that Sonny Gilligan had gone to hunt jackrabbits in the desert west of LAs Cruces on Thursday, and had taken his dogs Charlie, Scooter, and Cowboy with him.While in the backseat, his 120-pound lab-rottweiler mix Charlie got his foot on Gilligan's shotgun. When the dog slipped and fell off the seat, his paw caught the trigger, causing the firearm to shoot.The bullet tore through the driver's seat straight through Gilligan's back, breaking a couple of his ribs and shattering his collarbone. Amazingly, the 74-year-old managed to call for help.The lucky man had to undergo a bunch of surgeries, but is now on the way to recovery. Still, all he could think about was his boys.Poor Charlie and his brothers were sent to doggie jail, aka animal services, after the shooting, but have since been busted out by Gilligan's human son.Gilligan says he's forgiven Charlie for very nearly sending him to the afterlife, adding that it really was just a bizarre freak accident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 04:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/05/3725285/3725285_4DC61B1A93D14257A6049FECB01AAF45_181105_3725285_Dog_shoots_hunter_in_the_back_in_freak_hunting_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/833/1B4/8331B4471A6C934B5DDC068BC5B30F0C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, freak accident, hunting accident, dog shoots man, dog shoots owner, man shot by dog, shooting accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare mandarin duck mysteriously pops up in NYC</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  There's a hot new celebrity in the ponds at Central Park, and obsessed New Yorkers are all lining up to see him.The BBC reports that back in October, Manhattan Bird Alert directed the city's collective attention to a lone mandarin duck that seemed to have suddenly showed up among the city's usual waterfowl - catching eyes with its multi-colored mohawk, pink bill, and orange sail feathers. The rare bird is native to East Asia, so the fact that it's in the middle of the Big Apple is a bit of a mystery.Eagle-eyed watchers who spotted a tag on its leg thought it may have escaped from somewhere, but the Central Park Zoo claims it's not theirs, reports CNN.It's possible the bird came from a private owner. Then again, it's illegal to have a pet duck in New York, so not like anyone's gonna come forward.The brightly colored rock star has been attracting huge crowds of locals and tourists alike, and has since become a social media phenomenon.Not only does the Mandarin have its own hashtag and Twitter account, it's also inspired numerous artistic tributes.Like New York Magazine said, it's definitely the city's most eligible bachelor.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 13:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3726275/3726275_83D227D8BD87473A8488342F9612A363_181106_3726275_Rare_mandarin_duck_mysteriously_pops_up_in_NYC_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0D5/F21/0D5F21FF94D889E67F38B3DA7FAB314F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mandarin duck, rare duck, rock star duck, central park, central park duck, nyc ducks, bird watching, manhattan bird alert]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google workers stage global protest over women's treatment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GOOGLELAND  Thousands of Google workers around the world staged walkouts last week to protest claims of sexual harassment and gender inequality. Googlers in Tokyo, Zurich, Berlin, Singapore and New York took part in the protests. According to the BBC, workers want to see changes in how sexual misconduct allegations are handled in house, especially an end to forced arbitration, which would finally allow victims to sue.The walkout was held after news came out that Google actually gave former executive Andy Rubin a $90 million payout and kept details of sexual misconduct allegations that led to his resignation on the down low.Rubin, credited as the creator of the Android mobile operating system, denies the allegations. The New York Times, which dropped the Rubin story, also reported on several other sexual misconduct allegations by other Google executives. According to some workers involved in the walkout, bosses had told them not to speak with the media, while others were told to refer reporters to Google's PR department. In response, Google CEO Sundar Pichai went into damage control in an email to all staff saying, "I understand the anger and disappointment that many of you feel. I feel it as well, and I am fully committed to making progress on an issue that has persisted for far too long in our society… and, yes, here at Google, too."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3726155/3726155_A3847CBC83DD4897B4245A2CE67B08F6_181106_3726155_Google_workers_stage_global_protest_over_women_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/649/B77/649B77219C8F19EA706537BF5D9D9E54.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Google protests, Google walkout, Google Walkout for Real Change, Google workers protest, Google]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's border wall could threaten wildlife and plants</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  If the Trump administration's proposed border wall goes ahead with construction, plants and wildlife could be threatened in Texas. According to NPR, the federal spending bill approved in September includes $1.6 billion in 2019 for wall construction, which could begin as early as February.  In October, the Department of Homeland Security issued a waiver to 28 laws protecting public lands, wildlife and the environment in order so that construction could go ahead. In July, scientists published a paper highlighting the negative impacts of the border wall on wildlife by eliminating, degrading or fragmenting habitats. A wall would block access to water and food, and inhibit seasonal migrations. According to Phys.org, in a letter published in March in the journal Frontiers of Ecology and the Environment, other researchers also expressed worry the wall could damage the increasingly rare Tamaulipan thornscrub ecosystem. Other species that would be affected are the endangered wildflower Zapata bladderpod and the threatened whiskerbush cactus.  According to the researchers, negative impacts could be reduced by limiting physical barriers and accompanying roads, while considering building structures that allow animals to pass through and barrier alternatives like electronic sensors.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3726145/3726145_3EB90FEBE8374BECABAACDA9A1CD6379_181106_3726145_Trump_s_border_wall_could_threaten_wildlife_and__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DAD/C30/DADC303F21204DE3F6FC3E2BFA572733.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, President Trump, Trump border wall, US southern border wall, border wall wildlife, border wall plantlife]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet dog gets poisoned by dog-hating neighbors in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A woman had just moved back to China from California when tragedy struck.A woman surnamed Lee, said her 8-year-old golden retriever was hated by her neighbors in China. She said they routinely threatened to kill her dog, reports The Shanghaiist.Lee claims they added rat poison to chicken meat and spread it on her lawn where her pet used to play.Lee said the dog ate just one bite and ended up dying a few hours later, screaming and crying, fighting to survive.Lee said she took her case to the Chinese authorities but they dismissed her case, saying that hundreds of dogs die by poison on a daily basis.She said that a number of Chinese netizens were accusing her of damaging the reputation of China.Lee said she and the golden retriever were planning to relocate to Europe next year. However, she will now fight for her dog and other animals as China currently has no laws to protect animals.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 09:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3726091/3726091_5C290B2448464F10984900506490B6D0_181106_3726091_Pet_dog_gets_poisoned_by_dog_hating_neighbors_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4E4/314/4E43148376E4537A7C7E97D52BE48862.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dog, woman, China, dog poisoned by neighbors in China, dog poisoned by neighbors, Animal abuse, rat poison, golden retriever, chicken meat containing rat poison, Chinese neighbors, golden retriever poisoned by rat poison]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excessive screen time linked to anxiety, depression in kids</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO  A new study has linked excessive gaming, watching TV, or on smartphones to anxiety and depression in kids as young as two.Research published in Preventive Medicine Reports found that children and teens may have less curiosity, self-control, emotional stability, and a greater inability to finish tasks after just an hour of screen time a day.Researchers analyzed a random sample of over 40,000 surveys from the 2016 National Survey of Children's Health, which looked at kids aged 2 to 17.Adolescents aged 14 to 17 face the highest risk. Those who spent more than seven hours a day on screens were twice as likely to be diagnosed with anxiety and depression than those who spent only an hour.But younger kids and toddlers whose brains are still developing were also affected. Preschoolers with high screen use were twice as likely to lose their temper. Forty-six percent of youngsters were also more likely to not be able to calm down once excited.The findings validate the daily screen time limits set by the American Academy of Pediatrics  one hour for ages 2 to 5, and two for school-aged kids and adolescents.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3726055/3726055_D87E25EC081F4656AB275FBE1CA224CE_181106_3726055_Excessive_screen_time_linked_to_anxiety__depress_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/24D/DAC/24DDAC6CDE6F3CA7666172027F918AED.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, screen time, mental health, anxiety, depression, kids mental health, children mental health, excessive screen time, smartphones, gaming, television, social media]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrants' diverse gut bacteria changes once they move to U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S.  Geographical location impacts the diversity of microbes present in a person's body, with some places corresponding to much more microbe diversity than others, according to a study published in the journal Cell.The study found that immigrants tend to eat a more Westernized diet, rich in sugar, fats and protein after arriving in the U.S., resulting in a 15 percent loss of microbiome diversity.The dominant species of the gut bacteria changed from a bacteria called "Prevotella" to a bacteria called "Bacteroides," which is commonly found in Western microbes. The "Prevotella" bacteria helps in digesting fibrous foods commonly found in Asia.As microbiome diversity in the body decreases, the risk of obesity and diabetes increases.The study was conducted with the Hmong and Karen community from Southeast Asia and found that first and second generation U.S. immigrants had an additional drop of 5-10 percent of gut bacteria, and ended up with similar gut bacteria to those whose families have a longer history in the U.S.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3726044/3726044_2D0F30F2640D4DC3B538D76E3DD93A02_181106_3726044_Immigrants__diverse_gut_bacteria_changes_once_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D19/84F/D1984FC0DE0DB27C88EAFA9A60AD65B7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, immigrants, bacteria, gut bacteria, Prevotella, microbes, Bacteroides, microbiome diversity, diverse gut bacteria, microbes in human body, diverse gut bacteria changes after immigrating to US, diversity of microbes, diverse microbes immigrants]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California teacher caught on video punching teenage student</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  A California teacher has been arrested after he was caught on camera getting into a fistfight with a 14-year-old student.The Los Angeles Times reports that the fight went down in band class, and began when Maywood Academy music teacher Marston Riley asked the teen to leave the classroom for not wearing the proper uniform.Cellphone video taken at the scene shows the boy refusing, instead coming at Riley with a mouthful of profanity and racial slurs and hitting him with a basketball. In response, the 64-year-old teacher calmly takes out his phone to call for backup, but when the vitriol continues, he walks to the teen and swiftly decks him in the face.Footage shows the two going at it as other students scramble to move away. Riley is seen delivering more blows before campus staff intervene and pull the boy away.He was apprehended by police afterwards on suspicion of child abuse and is out on $50,000 bail. The teen, meanwhile, was taken to the hospital for his injuries, but has since been released.CBSLA reports that parents in the community are furious that a teacher would physically harm a kid, but Maywood faculty members and students are backing the teacher up.A GoFundMe page has even been set up to help Riley with any fines or fees, and has thus far raked in over $56,000.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3726034/3726034_9764E576D2C947739D5F09C37C7C3C81_181106_3726034_California_teacher_caught_on_video_punching_teen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/342/BED/342BED86E542D770D35FFF880DFFC633.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, teacher student fight, teacher student brawl, teacher beats up student, teacher hits student, teacher punches boy, viral video, caught on camera, marston riley, maywood academy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could the Democrats win the U.S. House of Representatives?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA   There 435 voting members of the U.S. House of Representatives representing the 50 states. All 435 seats are up for election every two years.Republicans currently hold 237 of these seats. Democrats hold 193. There are seven vacant seats.As of midnight on Election Day, Democrats were expected to win 203 seats, while Republicans were expected to win 194. Thirty-eight races were considered to be toss-ups, according to politics site and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics. For the Democrats, 173 of the seats were considered to be safe, 15 seats were likely go to the Democrats, and 15 were leaning toward the Democrats.For the Republicans, 149 seats were considered safe, 20 were considered likely to be won by the GOP, and 25 were learning toward the Republicans.Among the 38 races that were too close to call, Democrats currently hold five of these seats, while the Republicans hold 33. This means the Democrats have to defend far fewer seats than the Republicans.A total of 218 seats are needed to gain a majority in the House of Representatives. According to statistical analysis site FiveThirtyEight, as of Nov. 1 the Democrats had an 85 percent chance of taking back the House.States are divided into a certain number of districts based on their population size, in order to send a proportionate number of representatives to the House. Every state is guaranteed at least one seat, no matter how small its population.In some states, the party in power will draw up district lines to give it an advantage in as many Congressional races as possible. This process is called gerrymandering.According to the Washington Post, studies show this happens more often in states controlled by Republicans, though Democrats also engage in the practice.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 06:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3725931/3725931_C838ABB7A356468F8815F34BFCBB518C_181106_3725931_Could_the_Democrats_win_the_U_S__House_of_Repres_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3D7/050/3D705037527EBD4DF767E4215E27233D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Democrats, Republicans, US House of Representatives, US elections, US House of Representatives elections 2018, US House of Representatives seats, could Democrats win back the House of Representatives]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor removes kidney from woman who needed back surgery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WELLINGTON, FLORIDA   A West Palm Beach woman who went to the hospital for some back surgery ended up leaving minus one perfectly good kidney. According to WPTV, Maureen Pacheco checked into Wellington Regional Medical Center in April 2016 to have back surgery to alleviate pain she was experiencing from a car accident. Dr. Ramon Vazquez was tasked with cutting Pacheco open, so that surgeons could go in and perform the surgery. Unfortunately, Dr. Vazquez thought one of Maureen's healthy kidneys was a cancerous tumor, so he removed it without her consent.Pacheco recently settled a lawsuit against her doctors, including Dr. Vasquez, however a complaint filed by the Florida Department of Health against Vasquez is still ongoing. According to Pacheco's lawyer, Vasquez probably won't lose his license and would most likely just have to pay a fine and be required to do some more medical education.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 03:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/06/3725846/3725846_76CA3203BC374F3B92E5D888476908F5_181106_3725846_Doctor_removes_kidney_from_woman_who_needed_back_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/174/E5A/174E5A5870977F966BE8C0C775BFE939.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, back surgery, surgery, kidney removed, kidney removed by accident, surgeon removes kidney accidentally]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea unveils first Kim Jong Fatty official portrait</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA  Pyongyang has unveiled what is believed to be the first official portrait of Kim Jong-un, thereby announcing his promotion to full on god. While North Korea is literally littered with official portraits of his father and grandfather  Kim Jong Il and Kim Il Song  the young Kim was initially seen as just a successor rather than a leader. But thanks to delightful 2018 that saw the young dictator meet with the world's biggest orange and North Korea's brethren down south, Kim has now officially reached Yeezy-status.  According to the BBC, the portrait, which features a smiling Kim in a suit and tie, was on display during a recent visit by Cuba's president.According to NK News, the portraits are usually made by Pyongyang's Mansudae Arts Studio and are subject to strict regulations. It appears with the new release of this official portrait that Tons of Fun's cult of personality is getting an upgrade. At this rate, we may be lucky enough to see a second official portrait. The world waits in anticipation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 12:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/07/3726818/3726818_19CFBC6755AE4E5AB49C8BE48C3FF5D7_181107_3726818_North_Korea_unveils_first_Kim_Jong_Fatty_officia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/02B/68E/02B68EDA5B447E8459E35899C2E4B4D2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Kim Jong-un official portrait, Kim Jong-un, North Korea, Kim Jong-un first official portrait, Kim Jong-Un Donald Trump]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists to test if antimatter falls upwards</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SWITZERLAND  Scientists at CERN plan to drop antimatter into a vacuum chamber to see if gravity affects antimatter the same way it affects matter.Antimatter is identical to matter in every way, except that it has a negative charge, according to New Atlas.If matter and antimatter touch and interact with one another, they cancel each other out and annihilate each other.In the first experiment, the scientists plan to conduct is called the ALPHA-g experiment in which the researchers will trap antihydrogen atoms in a vertical vacuum chamber and test to see what effect gravity has on the atoms.In the second experiment called GBAR, antihydrogen atoms generated from antiprotons will be subjected to a fall of 20 centimeters to see what effect gravity has on them.Scientists predict that antimatter should fall down like regular matter, but there is a one in a million chance that it could fall up instead.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 08:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/07/3726646/3726646_F009000F42C44940A983D46F2D740AC0_181107_3726646_Scientists_to_test_if_antimatter_falls_upwards_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/676/BCD/676BCD8E89D72C870AF71FCB9AB71526.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, science, physics, antimatter, matter, matter vs antimatter, CERN, gravity experiment, antimatter explained, antimatter gravity experiment, antimatter CERN experiment, does antimatter fall upwards]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runaway train travels 57 miles with no driver before derailment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA  A train carrying a bunch of iron ore in Australia took off without its driver, and then ran away for 57 miles before being derailed.The driver had gotten off the locomotive to check something out when the train decided it was leaving  without him, according to the Australian Transport Safety Bureau.The BHP freight train then took off at 45 mph down the track with no one on board for about 50 minutes. According to the BBC, the train was originally scheduled to go from Newman mine to Port Hedland, but unfortunately had to be deliberately derailed at around 5:30 a.m. local time.  The train was derailed by a remote control center in Perth.About a mile of railroad track was completely destroyed because of the derailment.The Australian Transport Safety Bureau said they have begun an investigation to find out what caused the train to take off on its own.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 07:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/07/3726581/3726581_3F0C59FC7CE04563BE4D99EBCD526F1E_181107_3726581_Runaway_train_travels_57_miles_with_no_driver_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE2/4AE/BE24AE51AB090A389F81172990E5786B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, train, Australia, runaway train, runaway australian train, runaway train in australian, australian train, freight train, BHP, train forcibly derailed in australia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan would consider hosting US warships on Taiping Island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI, TAIWAN  Taiwan would consider allowing U.S. warships access to the largest of the Spratly Islands in the South China Sea for regional security purposes if requested by Washington. In response to a hypothetical question at the legislature on Monday, Taiwan's defense minister, Yen Teh-fa, said Taiwan could allow U.S. vessels to dock at Taiping Island, according to the SCMP. Six different countries including Taiwan and China lay claims to parts of the South China Sea. At the parliament panel meeting, Yen said Taiwan would consider allowing US vessels access to Taiping Island for humanitarian or regional security grounds if it were in the best interests of the country. According to lawmaker John Chiang, the regular presence of US aircraft carrier groups in international waters of the South China Sea were aimed at keeping China's military expansion in check. The U.S. Navy routinely conducts freedom of navigation sorties in international waters near the islets of the South China Sea, which draws heavy protests from China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 07:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/07/3726574/3726574_40502E816BA24ED88326A6370578A560_181107_3726574_Taiwan_would_consider_hosting_US_warships_on_Tai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/838/D57/838D5708D9C614BE84CBF4D526C6E075.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwan Taiping Island, South China Sea, Spratly Islands, US Navy, US warships]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boiling mud pool threatens California infrastructure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA   A boiling mud pool originating from a geyser is slowly making its way in Southern California. According to Los Angeles Times, the mud pool, dubbed the "Slow One," began moving six months ago, advancing at an unprecedented rate. It began covering a distance of 18 meters over a few months, but now covers the same distance in a single day.The geyser is in close proximity to the San Andreas fault and is a result of seismic movements in the area. According to Live Science, earthquakes created deep fractures underground that allowed gases to move to the earth's surface, creating boiling mud pools heated by carbon dioxide.Despite its closeness to the famous fault, there is no data suggesting that the recent activities could lead to a large earthquake. However, local authorities are fearful for the damage this geologic phenomenon could cause to local infrastructure.Boiling mud has already forced the Union Pacific Railroad to build temporary tracks after the mud seeped through a barrier they had built to prevent it from damaging the railroad. The geyser is also threatening damage to a petroleum pipeline, fiber-optic telecommunications lines and a portion of a major highway.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/07/3726568/3726568_8473EFEF2F63438589B6679FB5456108_181107_3726568_Boiling_mud_pool_threatens_California_infrastruc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FDA/53D/FDA53D9F53F25D0F5FD2163B08747A5B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, geyser, geyser eruption, mud pool, california, earthquake, geology, seismic, damage, infrastructure, nature, San Andreas, earthquake.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NZ fisherman rescues 18-month baby floating in the ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH ISLAND, NEW ZEALAND  A fisherman in New Zealand has saved an 18-month-old baby from drowning in the sea.Gus Hutt was fishing on Matata Beach in North Island when he saw a tiny being floating in the water. He reached out to grab it, thinking it was a doll, reports BBC News.The baby instinctively started squeaking. This is when Hutt realized the doll was actually a child and it was alive.Hutt's wife Sue was quick to alert authorities who said that there was only one couple with a baby staying in a holiday camp in the area.Sue then wrapped the baby in towels and went to find his parents. The baby's mother was overwhelmed when the baby was found and reportedly screamed.Emergency services arrived and took the baby to the hospital for a routine checkup. The baby was confirmed to be doing okay. Apparently the baby had been holidaying with his parents when he escaped from his parents' tent by undoing the zipper and headed for the ocean.Rebecca Salter, the owner of the holiday camp, called the incident a "freakish miracle" and said they were lucky for the way things turned out.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 03:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/07/3726429/3726429_517BD6830BB84061AE049A1E4239B8B0_181107_3726429_NZ_fisherman_rescues_18_month_baby_floating_in_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D20/B9C/D20B9CB723F4FF32144DB00DDB6EC9D8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, New Zealand, fisherman, baby, toddler, ocean, sea, fisherman saves baby floating in sea, 18 month old]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Elections 2018: Democrats take the House of Representatives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#Midterms #midterms2018 #Elections WASHINGTON  The Democratic Party won control of the House of Representatives in Tuesday's miderm elections for the first time since 2010.According to the latest information from political news site and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics, the Democrats won 28 seats. This put their total number in the House of Representatives at 223. A party needs 218 seats for a majority in the House.Meanwhile, the Republicans have lost 28 seats and won 198 of the total 435 available. According to the polling website 270 to Win, the winners of 14 seats that have yet to be declared. Five of those are expected to go to the Republican party. But even if the GOP ends up winning all of them, they still wouldn't be able to keep the House as the Dems already have the majority.That's bad news for U.S. President Donald Trump and the Republican Party. Previously they had control of the House and the Senate. The latest data from Real Clear Politics says they've held onto the Senate, winning 52 of the upper house's 100 seats. However, the loss of the House of Representatives will make it harder for Republicans to deliver on their policy agenda.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 11:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/08/3727474/3727474_D93F0A649D6541A99CBFC2B310915A1B_181108_3727474_U_S__Elections_2018__Democrats_take_the_House_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1E9/B3C/1E9B3C0E34ECC07FE5D8B347C4FB4ACD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, US elections, house of representatives, US House race, US midterm elections, US midterm elections 2018 results, us election 2018, election 2018, washington, republicans, democrats, election explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With House control will Democrats try to impeach Trump?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Now that the Democrats have taken back the House of Representatives, does this mean a presidential impeachment is in the works?According to CNN's national exit polls, 40 percent of voters want President Trump impeached. Seventy-seven percent of Democrats supported the move, compared to only five percent of Republicans and 33 percent of independents.With Democrats now in control of the House, they can initiate impeachment proceedings with an investigation by the House Judiciary Committee, and then vote to impeach with a simple majority.To get a conviction, they will need a two-thirds majority vote in the Senate. But with the Republicans remaining in control of the Senate with a 51-seat majority, this outcome is unlikely.While impeachment is a possibility, democratic leaders have indicated it is not the priority. They are, however, expected to launch investigations into the Trump administration.The Democratic House has plans to look into the president's tax returns, which he has refused to disclose, and restart the investigation into possible collusion with Russia.In response, Trump has threatened a 'warlike' response should the Democrats use their newly acquired investigative powers on him, adding that there may be retribution from the Republican Senate, reports Bloomberg.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/08/3727373/3727373_98C18E3960464AE58D58AA4781FEBAC3_181108_3727373_With_House_control_will_Democrats_try_to_impeach_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FBA/EBC/FBAEBCB6DA33015B91D00F923F4C4B24.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US midterms, midterm elections, midterms, midterm election results, impeachment, trump impeachment, trump, democrat house, republican senate, democrats, kavanaugh]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China debuts its most advanced stealth drone yet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  The China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation has debuted a next-generation stealth combat aircraft called CH-7.According to the Global Times, the unmanned aircraft has a wingspan of 22 meters, a length of 10 meters, and a cruise altitude of 10 to 13 km. It also has the ability to stay in the air for 15 hours.The CH-7 is capable of launching weapons such as anti-radiation missiles, long-distance precision-guided bombs, and more. It can also intercept radar electronic signals and detect high-value targets.The combat aircraft is currently at the AirShow China 2018 exhibition in Zhuhai from November 6 to 11.The aircraft is scheduled to make its first flight in 2019 and will be available for mass production by 2022 if everything goes according to plan.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/08/3727367/3727367_52FAE333151F4885A09FC040250B1100_181108_3727367_China_debuts_its_most_advanced_stealth_drone_yet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/48A/26F/48A26FCD86C71DB3E56509B918A29B3D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, stealth drone, CH-7, China CH-7, combat aircraft, china combat aircraft CH-7, AirShow China 2018]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China ups security spending for Xinjiang re-education camps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA  Beijing has massively upped security expenditures in Xinjiang, where it's reported to have detained ethnic Muslim minorities.According to an analysis of Chinese government budget by U.S. think tank the Jamestown Foundation, spending on security-related construction in the western region of Xinjiang rose by 213 percent in 2017.The spending pattern is consistent with the construction and operation of highly secure political re-education camps meant to detain Uighurs.Mass disappearances of Uighur minorities since 2017 likely resulted in imprisonment in these camps, where former detainees say they had to endure intense political and cultural indoctrination.But while prison spending increased by 94 percent, formal prosecutions stagnated, indicating that many are detained without a trial or with minimal due process.China claims the institutions are vocational training centers, but figures show vocational spending in the same year actually decreased by 7 percent.The country's human rights record is set to be reviewed by the UN human rights council, which is expected to focus on its treatment of minorities like Uighurs and Tibetans, reports the Guardian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 04:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/08/3727166/3727166_9979FEA3463F4A40B58FBCB2426E7134_181108_3727166_China_ups_security_spending_for_Xinjiang_re_educ_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B8/996/3B8996602455CF37D7216E663701B789.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, uyghur, uighur, xinjiang, uyghur crackdown, uyghur camp, china surveillance, minorities, Muslim minorities, ethnic minorities, China, education camps, China human rights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can we prove
the earth is round?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EARTH    Our planet's shape can be verified in many ways. Disclaimer: We can't promise these facts  will convince flat-earthers. But hey, it's worth the shot … right?Earth's globe-like shape can be easily observed in the shadow it casts on the moon's equally round surface. The shadow is always curved at any given time of the lunar phases.Earth's round edges can also be seen in the horizon. Objects nearing it seem to "appear" and "disappear," depending on which way they are moving. We can see this effect when we observe ships in the ocean. If we were to see the horizon from above, we would also be able to see Earth's surface curve at the edges. Earth's circular form also determines the time zone differences we experience. Time zones are a result of Earth's rotation on its axis.Its spherical shape allows for this as its sides would be exposed to sunlight at a given time while the other side remains dark. This would not be possible over a flat surface. We can also observe the properties of other planets in our solar system. According to Futurism, planets' spherical shapes allow for an equal distribution of gravity. If Earth were a disc-like body, its gravity would pull us at different degrees depending where we stand. Gravity cannot be distributed evenly on non-spherical surfaces.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 02:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/08/3727086/3727086_FCCB2DA2848942FE9C62490DC9BFA23A_181108_3727086_How_can_we_prove_the_earth_is_round__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/298/79B/29879B867F7B63A204E04CBC7EB1BBAB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, sphere, globe, earth, flat earth, earth is not flat, gravity, curve, horizon, surface.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese singer Kris Wu accused of using bots on iTunes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Canadian-Chinese singer Kris Wu has been accused of encouraging his Chinese fans to use bots to boost his new album sales. According to Hot New Hip Hop, Wu's latest album November Rain was bought 14 million times in 24 hours, with seven of its songs making it into the US iTunes Top 10. The little known artist outside of China bumped Ariana Grande and Lady Gaga of top spots on iTunes in the States temporarily. A since deleted tweet from Ariana Grande manager Scooter Braun accused the singer and his team of using bots to game the iTunes sales charts.Bots are algorithms that can generate automated clicks to inflate streaming numbers and sales figures.   Wu has 158,000 followers on Twitter, which is blocked in China and 45 million followers on China's Weibo. According to Variety, an insider told them that following patterns of high-volume purchases on iTunes of "Antares," Wu's album sales were acquired fraudulently and will not count toward the iTunes sales chart reported to Nielsen.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/09/3728088/3728088_AFE25963B3BF43438BB6BBF48B314EDC_181109_3728088_Chinese_singer_Kris_Wu_accused_of_using_bots_on__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1C0/0F3/1C00F36675B469DD0BC3C2DC52F29EC0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Kris Wu bots, Chinese singer Kris Wu, Chinese Kris Wu bots, Kris Wu bots iTunes, Kris Wu iTunes controversy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's how vote recounting works in Florida</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FLORIDA  With extremely close margins in the races for U.S. senate and agriculture commissioner, and a governor's race that is nearing the threshold, it appears as if Florida could be headed for recounts.According to the Miami Herald, unofficial statewide results have to be reported to the state elections office before a recount can be officially ordered. Counties must turn in their unofficial returns by noon on Saturday, Nov. 10. The secretary of state is required to order a machine recount if the margin in a statewide election is less than 0.5 percent. Losing candidates can refuse a recount. If an automated recount is ordered, the second round of unofficial returns would be due from counties by 3 p.m. on Thursday Nov. 15.    In a machine recount, damaged ballots are copied, all ballots are re-scanned and then the number of total votes cast according to the machines are compared with the number of votes initially tallied by the county.If the machine recount numbers are similar, the vote is counted as accurate. And if the margin in the race is larger than 0.25 percent, the results are counted as official. If the margin after the second round of machine counting falls below 0.25 percent, then Florida can order a manual recount for federal and state elections. A manual recount involves counting each overvote and undervote by hand. An overvote refers to voters marking more choices than permitted on the ballot. An undervote means the voter made no choice or fewer than the number of allowable choices on the ballot.   On Nov. 16, overseas and military ballots are counted. Counties need to give official returns by noon on Nov. 18. Official results from counties are then certified by the state on Nov. 20.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/09/3728075/3728075_67C0B389D9D748D1A114605174DB2089_181109_3728075_Here_s_how_vote_recounting_works_in_Florida_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/01C/6FF/01C6FFFBB4856243A3148329797662D3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Florida vote recount, vote recount, manual recount, machine recount, Midterm elections 2018, Florida recount, 2018 midterms, recount explainer, recount explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midterm elections made history with many notable firsts</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  The midterm elections turned out to be a historic night of firsts for Native American, Muslim, LGBT and female candidates. According to NPR, congress will see its first Native American and Muslim congresswomen, its first lesbian mom in Congress and the first openly gay man elected as a governor. South Dakota and Maine elected their first female governors, Tennessee and Arizona are sending their first women to the Senate, and Massachusetts and Connecticut selected their first black women to the House. According to CBS News, Democrat Sharice Davids, a member of the Ho-Chunk Nation, won Kansas' 3rd District seat, while Democrat Debra Haaland, a member of the Pueblo of Laguna won in New Mexico's 1st District to become the first Native American congresswomen. Democrats Ilhan Omar of Minnesota and Rashida Tlaib of Michigan both won their house races to become the first Muslim women in Congress. In Colorado, Democrat Jared Polis became the first openly gay man elected as governor. According to CBS News, more than 90 women were elected to the House, making it the most number of women to win House seats in American history.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/09/3728060/3728060_A855AC4B4ED844AEBE0788D04E7DB424_181109_3728060_Midterm_elections_made_history_with_many_notable_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B3E/779/B3E77968FB61517FD8D7E144549BD1E1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Midterm elections, Midterm elections 2018, Midterm election firsts, Midterm elections notable firsts, Elections historic firsts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update on the U.S. Senate Race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  A total of 44 Democrats and 50 Republicans were up for reelection, with six toss-up seats available.Democrats were projected to win one of two Senate seats in play for Minnesota, as well as Washington, California, New Mexico, Hawaii, New York, Virginia, Maine, Vermont, Rhode Island, Massachusetts, Connecticut, Delaware and Maryland, according to politics site and polling data aggregator Real Clear Politics.Polling data shows Democrats were also likely to win in Ohio, Pennsylvania and West Virginia. The other seat for Minnesota, as well as seats for Wisconsin, Michigan and New Jersey, were also leaning Democrat.The Democrats won in Washington, California, Montana, Michigan, two seats in Minnesota, Wisconsin, Michigan, Rhode Island, Ohio, West Virginia, Virginia, New York, Massachusetts, Connecticut, New Jersey, Maryland, Pennsylvania, Delaware, New Mexico, Hawaii. They also flipped Nevada. Two independents in Maine and Vermont will caucus with the Democrats, giving them a total of 46 seats, according to Real Clear Politics.Republicans were projected to win in Utah, Wyoming, Nebraska and one of two seats in play for Mississippi. Republicans were also likely to win the other seat for Mississippi, as well as for North Dakota, while Texas and Tennessee were leaning Republican.Republicans won in Utah, Wyoming, Nebraska, Texas, Tennessee and one of two seats in Mississippi. North Dakota, Indiana, Missouri and Florida, though the Florida Senate race appears to be headed for a recount. The Republicans now hold 51 seats in the Senate, not including Florida.[c]Real Clear Politics has not yet called Arizona, and the other seat in Mississippi. Republicans look set to win both.In total, the Democrats lost three seats. The GOP gained two or three, if Florida is included, maintaining control of the Senate. Even in the unlikely event that the Democrats win the seats in Arizona and Mississippi, and win a possible recount in Florida, the Republicans will still keep control of the Senate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/09/3728054/3728054_E98EBAD609E04E11988036216A3DDB9C_181109_3728054_Update_on_the_U_S__Senate_Race_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B34/CDF/B34CDF23FC4A22F0E0992214850E6623.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, USA, US elections, senate elections, democrats, republicans, U.S. senate elections update, US senate race]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hormone aids regeneration
of amputated limbs in frogs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEDFORD, MASSACHUSETTS  A new wearable bioreactor could be the first step towards limb regeneration.Researchers led by Tufts University scientists have developed a wearable bioreactor that uses progesterone to induce tissue regeneration. The device was tested on adult aquatic African clawed frogs, a species already capable of partial limb regeneration.The 3-D printed bioreactor is made from silicon and filled with hydrogel. The gel is a mix of silk proteins that aid healing and progesterone, a hormone that prompts tissue repair.According to their study, published in the journal Cell Reports, frogs in the experiment had one of their hind legs amputated approximately at the center of the femur. The wounds of the frogs were either treated with the bioreactor, protected by the device without progesterone or left untreated. All groups had their devices removed after 24 hours. After nine and a half months, the the group that had worn the bioreactors with progesterone grew a paddle-like structure with bones, nerves and blood vessels. Those which did not grew a cartilaginous spike-like structure. The use of progesterone proved to alter the limbs at an functional and anatomical level. Scientists hope this finding takes us a step closer to technology that could aid regeneration of human amputated limbs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/09/3727913/3727913_C102DB84D39A47D281A628CB3EBF3F5C_181109_3727913_Hormone_aids_regeneration_of_amputated_limbs_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7C6/FB7/7C6FB7149CA4FB759F6A3496FEC3F628.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, silk, hydrogel device, spike, frog, bioelectricity, regeneration, limb, bioreactor, research, study, experiment.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China sets sights on ultra-fast train ala Hyperloop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHUHAI, CHINA  China plans to develop next-generation vehicles similar to Elon Musk's Hyperloop.Reuters reports that Chinese automaker Geely has signed a deal with the China Aerospace Science and Industry Corp. to build a network of ultra-fast trains.The proposed system will use magnetic levitation to allow the trains to float inches above the rail tracks, which eliminates ground friction and increases speed. Like the Hyperloop, the trains will be propelled through vacuum tubes to reduce air resistance.Though not technically supersonic, the trains will travel faster than conventional ones at speeds of up to 1,000 kph, with an aim to reach 4,000 kph in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 06:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/09/3727890/3727890_050976866E2A4327A5F01642BF07E9F0_181109_3727890_China_sets_sights_on_ultra_fast_train_ala_Hyperl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15D/4EB/15D4EBDE55B23F0F3A84EEE931E78C00.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, supersonic train, china supersonic train, maglev, hyperloop, elon musk, future transportation, next generation trains, Geely, CASIC]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousand Oaks shooter died from self-inflicted gunshot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THOUSAND OAKS, CALIFORNIA  A dozen people are dead after a gunman opened fire inside a packed bar in California on Wednesday night.USA Today reports that over a hundred college students were inside the Borderline Bar & Grill in Thousand Oaks for Country College Night when gunman Ian David Long approached outside and shot the security guard with a .45-caliber Glock 21.The 28-year-old then threw a smoke bomb inside the premises and shot at employees near the front, before firing into the crowd of people on the dance floor.Scared patrons began fleeing. Some used bar stools to break the windows and escape.Others ran out the back, hid under pool tables, in the attic, or in the bathroom.Ventura County deputy Ron Helus was first at the scene with a highway officer. They engaged the suspect in a shootout, but Deputy Telus was shot several times and later died. In all, 12 people were killed in the shooting.According to the Los Angeles Times, Long was dead when officers found him at the scene, and an autopsy later determined he had died from a self-inflicted gunshot.Long had been a former Marine machine gunner, and is said to have carried the attack out with military efficiency, though authorities have yet to determine a motive.A former coach described him as physically combative during his teen years, while  a mental health specialist that assessed him recently thought he could be suffering from PTSD.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 10:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/12/3729630/3729630_A372D04A8ED946EFBE4317A8FE45AF30_181112_3729630_Thousand_Oaks_shooter_died_from_self_inflicted_g_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/802/7B4/8027B41A9E5938EEEA360A5A434B3D43.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, shooting, mass shooting, thousand oaks, thousand oaks shooting, california shooting, timeline, california shooting timeline, shooting victims, ian david long, borderline bar, college party]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida man catches largest
python in South Florida</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD, FLORIDA  A man nabbed a 5-meter-long Burmese python, the largest one found in South Florida to date.Snake hunter, Kyle Penniston is now being hailed a hero in his hometown of Homestead, Florida and for good reason. He managed to catch the largest Burmese python in South Florida to date and he gave it a good battle.Penniston was riding along a levee when he spotted a snake in the water. He stopped to to catch it, as was his duty as a snake hunter for the South Florida Water Management District.  Little did he know he was going to come face to face with a 5-meter-long beast. Penniston tried pulling it out of the water but received gnarly snake bites instead. Unfortunately, not even his pistol could save. The bullet he wanted to use to finish the beast was jammed in the chamber. Finally, the snake tired of wrestling Penniston and that's where he took the chance to drag her out into the dirt road. He then  successfully  loaded his gun and as he nicely put it, euthanized it.Burmese pythons have been labeled an invasive species in the Florida Everglades. According to the South Florida Water Management District, "Eliminating invasive species such as Burmese pythons is critical to preserving the rare Everglades ecosystem." .Talk about man vs wild.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 07:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/12/3729461/3729461_1A789BFA2C894FE68DB562676E6BD0DC_181112_3729461_Florida_man_catches_largest_python_in_South_Flor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA7/BC4/BA7BC4F08D6643663E700C1CF6E85AC7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, enormous, python, python snake, python vs man, snake vs man, burmese python, giant snake, Florida, everglades, everglades national park, fight, battle, man vs wild, huge snake, huge python, wildlife]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard scientists think this maybe an alien probe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.SA.  New theoretical research by Harvard scientists suggests that the solar system's first interstellar object might be an alien probe.Oumuamua was first observed by the Panoramic Survey Telescope and Rapid Response System in Hawaii in October 2017. The name means "a messenger that reaches out from the distant past" in Hawaiian.Research published in the journal Nature last year says it is the first interstellar object to enter our solar system and said it would travel inside it for over a year. Scientists weren't sure if it was an asteroid or a comet, so they referred to it as an interstellar object. Oumuamua is 800 meters in length and 80 meters in width, according to Astronomy.com.Scientists speculated last year that it may consist of materials like metals or rocks.A yet-to-be-published theoretical study accepted in Astrophysical Journal Letters puts forward a number of theories on the object, including ideas that it may be extraterrestrial in origin. They theorize Oumuamua might be using a light sail to travel.This technology uses light to propel objects through space. The researchers write that it could be used to transport cargo between planets or stars. Another theory, the researchers describe as a "more exotic scenario", is that Oumuamua is a fully working space probe sent to Earth by an alien civilization. However this claim has been disputed by other astronomers.Astrophysicist Alan Fitzsimmons told the AFP that this wasn't evidence of alien life.He explained that Oumuamua has already show characteristics similar to that of a comet from another star system.When NASA observed it last year, they said the object was traveling at 64,000 kph. The space agency noted Oumuamua would exit the solar system in January 2019 after passing through Saturn's orbit. Its next destination is the Pegasus constellation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 07:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/12/3729430/3729430_3D1327B094354C70A50473F1B6C61428_181112_3729430_Harvard_scientists_think_this_maybe_an_alien_pro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4A1/879/4A18795D115138CBE9AB7BDC5FEC2080.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Oumuamua, oumuamua update, oumuamua harvard, Harvard, alien spacecraft, oumuamua trajectory, solar system, interstellar object, oumuamua interstellar object, interstellar oumuamua, alien probe, space rock, harvard scientists claim space rock could be alien probe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese principal fired for mining crypto in school where he worked</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A Chinese school principal has been fired after he was found stealing the school's internet bandwidth and electricity to mine cryptocurrency.Apparently Lei Hua, the school principal, used to mine crypto at home with a mining machine, but after he found out how expensive it was to do this, he decided to move it to the school where he worked.Lei had since acquired eight more mining machines and shifted one of the machines to the dormitories at his school, and added the rest in the electronics lab of the school, according to Live Bitcoin News.School teachers had complained of the noise caused by the machines, but the principal found multiple excuses and blamed the air conditioners or heating devices.As expected, the 24-hour mining operation became a strain on the school's electrical cables and internet speeds also went way down.Teachers also grew suspicious when they noticed a rise in electricity bills to roughly 14,700 yuan, or about US$2,114.The principal was fired while all his profits were confiscated by the Chinese Communist Party, as crypto mining isn't legal in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 05:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/12/3729400/3729400_72BC8B4ED9974D1F8EE50DB882C7DF14_181112_3729400_Chinese_principal_fired_for_mining_crypto_in_sch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5AD/09E/5AD09E304180A42504C358E1FE895954.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cryptocurrency, China, china principal cryptocurrency, china principal sacked over mining crypto in school, crypto, chinese principal fired over mining cryptocurrency, mining crypto in china, mining cryptocurrency in china, mining crypto while on the job]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xinhua News Agency unveils creepy AI news anchors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUZHEN, CHINA  Chinese state media is using "virtual" anchors to read the news.Xinhua News Agency partnered with search engine Sogou.com to create artificial intelligence news anchors. These are said to be digital composites that deliver the news.he composites use the likeness of real Xinhua presenter. However, facial expressions and mouth movements are synthesized and animated via deep learning.AI anchors are able to read out any text inputted by human editors into its system, using synthetic voices created through composite audio recorded from the human anchors.The virtual anchors are reportedly able to read out any text written by human editors into their program. This is said to use synthetic voices created through composite audio recorded from human anchors.Xinhua has two AI anchors, one delivering news in English and another in Chinese. They claim these can work 24 hours a day on its website and social media.The state-run agency claims the virtual clones can present the news as naturally as their human counterparts, but anyone who's seen the broadcast knows that's fake news.Experts likewise pointed out that the computerized voice and dull delivery take out the connection that viewers typically form with human anchors, who are often seen as trusted public figures.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/12/3729329/3729329_5B497C8ADF7E4B2E968DDF44B160E4C5_181112_3729329_Xinhua_News_Agency_unveils_creepy_AI_news_anchor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/715/28A/71528A073DDEB5995089736E02F1088F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, AI anchor, AI news anchor, artificial intelligence, Xinhua, Xinhua AI anchor, virtual news anchor, AI clone, creepy, unsettling, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Power mushroom' converts 
light into clean energy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOBOKEN, NEW JERSEY  A team from the Stevens Institute of Technology have developed a 'power mushroom' able to create renewable energy. According to their study, published in the paper Nano Journal, the team used button mushrooms due to their optimal levels of humidity and temperature which make them exceptional hosts to bacteria.  They then employed 3D printing technology to create a pattern of graphene nanoribbons on the cap of a living mushroom. They then printed cyanobacteria on top of the pattern using special 'bio-ink'.This bacteria was selected due to its efficiency in converting sunlight to energy. According to researchers who participated in the study it has 'an internal quantum efficiency of nearly 100%.'This type of interaction is being called 'engineered bionic symbiosis'. The mushroom provides the cyanobacteria with shelter and nutrients which allows the bacteria to thrive and in turn create more energy. Exposing mushroom to light triggers cyanobacterial photosynthesis during which the bacteria releases electrons that are in turn captured by the strips of graphene.According to a news release by the American Chemical Society, the team managed to generate 65 nanoamps of electric energy.  I guess we could say mushrooms are both nutritious and...energizing?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 01:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/12/3729289/3729289_F385362C31684B6F987ADF22A17D6916_181112_3729289__Power_mushroom__converts__light_into_clean_ener_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CCD/62F/CCD62F7F8D875FA2B76DBF565F2F06E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, clean energy, renewable energy, renewable and nonrenewable sources, clean energy, clean energy technology, bioengineering, climate change.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa Ana winds could feed Woolsey fire in California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA  Fire officials are concerned high Santa Ana winds forecasted for the next several days could help spread the 85,500-acre Woolsey fire in Ventura and Los Angeles counties.   According to the L.A. Times, the fire, which has killed two people and caused the evacuation of more than 250,000 people from Malibu to Thousand Oaks, was only 15 percent contained as of Sunday night. The forecast is calling for wind gusts of 40 miles per hour or stronger over the next few days. According to officials, the blaze has destroyed more than 177 buildings, with around 57,000 structures still at risk.Firefighters are now concerned that potential wind gusts could suddenly change directions, affecting the fire.  Strong winds could also hamper the effectiveness of aerial water and retardant drops. As of Sunday, several parts of Los Angeles and Ventura counties  including Malibu, Agoura Hills, Westlake VIllage, Hidden Hills and parts of West Hills, Monte Nido, Gated Oaks and Topanga  remained under voluntary or mandatory evacuation orders. Wildfires across the state have burned nearly 200,000 acres and killed at least 31 people, according to fire officials.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/13/3730310/3730310_C4B6F1E41A3F4ADE8DE9B53CD6A066A8_181113_3730310_Santa_Ana_winds_could_feed_Woolsey_fire_in_Calif_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8E8/F39/8E8F3952B7C764E3BA6DE00C345373FA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, California fires, California wildfires, California Woolsey fire, Santa Ana winds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Flat Earthers now think Earth is actually a big doughnut</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DOUGHNUT EARTH  If you've always been one of those Flat Earthers who didn't quite buy into the pizza-shaped theory of the planet, here's an idea you can sink your sweet tooth into  the earth is actually one big old Dunkin Donut. According to Lad Bible, a Flat Earther with the username Varuag back in 2012 posed this gem to the Flat Earth Society, "I have a theory that the Earth is in fact shaped like a torus (a donut-shape). However, light is curved so we cannot tell."He then compiled a list of answers for 11 frequently asked questions his Krispy Kreme theory was likely to encounter. Here are some of the best ones. Why hasn't the donut hole been been discovered? Light bends and follows the curvature of the torus, making the hole "unseeable." How does light curve? Radio waves are reflected by the atmosphere and apparently on torus-earth, so is light. The farther light travels, the more it curves, by the time it reaches the atmosphere, it can be reflected. As light travels around the corners of the atmosphere, it curves every time so that's why the Earth looks flat. When you're standing in the middle of the donut and look up, why don't you see the other side of the donut? Well dummy  as light passes through the first atmosphere, but by the time it reaches the second atmosphere it has diminished enough to be reflected into space, so you see space. He also goes on to explain how night and day occur, why we have seasons, and a HOLE lot more.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/13/3730203/3730203_FFD98016A7F940E3AC10F7B17195E55B_181113_3730203_Some_Flat_Earthers_now_think_Earth_is_actually_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/649/6FF/6496FFE14BE6DF3821267C4085E5CF5C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, flat earth, flat earthers, flat earth society, earth doughnut shaped, torus shaped earth, donut earth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Marvel comics creator Stan Lee dies aged 95</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Marvel Comics legend Stan Lee passed away this week.A representative for his family told the Hollywood Reporter that Lee died early Monday morning at the Cedars-Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles. He was 95. Lee was the man behind much of Marvel's superhero roster.  He co-created many iconic characters including Spider-Man, the X-Men, Hulk, Avengers, Iron Man, Thor, Black Panther, Daredevil and so much more.A statement by Lee's family the Hollywood Reporter read: "Stan was an icon in his field. His fans loved him and his desire to interact with them. He loved his fans and treated them with the same respect and love they gave him."Many took to social media to pay tribute to the legendary comic book writer, includingIron Man actor Robert Downey Jr.  He wrote on Instagram, "I owe it all to you. Rest In Peace Stan"In a post on Marvel.com, the company and their parent organization Disney paid tribute to Lee, writing: "Marvel and the entire The Walt Disney Company salute the life and career of Stan Lee and offer their undying gratitude for his unmatchable accomplishments within their halls. Every time you open a Marvel comic, Stan will be there."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/13/3730004/3730004_0E0FF74B1C8344119C10533A98D68A18_181113_3730004_Legendary_Marvel_comics_creator_Stan_Lee_dies_ag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BEF/6DD/BEF6DDE3F856D41245B2767A544759EF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,stan lee,stan lee dead,stan lee dies,stan lee life,marvel,marvel comics,iron man,spider-man,tribute,RIP Stan Lee,Stan Lee tribute,Comic book news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China plans to control the weather</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA   The Chinese Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation is planning to send rain-inducing machines across the Tibetan Plateau to increase rainfall in the region.Tens of thousands of machines will be installed on the Tibetan mountains and is expected to increase rainfall by up to 10 billion cubic meters a year over an area of 1.6 million square kilometers, reports the South China Morning Post.The machines will produce fine silver iodide particles which would then be lifted into the air with the winds.These particles will then be circulated into the atmosphere.Each rain machine is expected to create a 4.8-kilometer-long strip of clouds.Lei Fanpei, the president of the corporation, told the South China Post that modifying Tibet's weather "is a critical innovation to solve China's water shortage problem."The mountains of Tibet provide a huge source of water in China as its glaciers and underground reservoirs supply water to the Yangtze, Mekong and the Yellow River. However, this isn't the first time China made plans to modify the weather. The country has manipulated the weather during the 2008 Beijing Olympics in order to prevent it from raining during the event.China had even artificially induced snow a couple of years ago in Beijing, according to a report from China Daily.China plans to monitor the system through weather satellites and supplement silver iodide particles from planes and drones in order to maximize its effect.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 03:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/13/3729923/3729923_FB79A50465DE44EB951E5C6B37D59DC4_181113_3729923_China_plans_to_control_the_weather_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/534/FCD/534FCD4ABFA453907628A18E4E7C09BF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, weather, space, china to control weather from space, China weather system, rain-inducing machines, china weather control, china weather machine, rain-inducing machines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hotel in Bali could help suck island dry</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALI, INDONESIA  A project to develop a Trump hotel in Bali could threaten the island's water supply. On August 14, 2015, then presidential candidate Donald Trump signed an agreement in collaboration with Indonesian investor Hary Tanoesoedibjo's MNC Group to develop the Trump International Hotel and Tower Bali, according the the SCMP. The proposed "six-star" resort and 18-hole golf course are set to be built on a cliff-top site previously home to the Pan Pacific Nirwana Bali, according to the SCMP. Of particular concern is the proposed development's environmental impact on the water supply. According the NPR, Audubon International estimates the average American golf course requires about 312,000 gallons of water a day.According to Deutsche Welle, over half of Bali's groundwater is used by the island's tourism industry. The industry's water demands are putting Bali's rice terraces and subak irrigation system at risk. Deep borewells drilled by hotels and villa-based resorts have led to saltwater leaking into and contaminating groundwater. According to Vice, the tourism industry has caused as many as 260 of Bali's 400-plus rivers to dry up.If the Trump development is completed as planned, it would be the largest resort on the island.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 02:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/13/3729917/3729917_2F725EBAF97E4345906D81897A49C5DB_181113_3729917_Trump_hotel_in_Bali_could_help_suck_island_dry_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3CB/E0C/3CBE0CED4FB8EA16704EE27D25356EDD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Trump Hotel, Trump Hotel Bali, Trump MNC Group, Trump, Hary Tanoesoedibjo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo trial begins amid heavy security</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  The trial of accused Mexican drug lord Joaquin 'El Chapo' Guzman has begun in New York amid unprecedented security measures.According to the New York Times, the El Chapo case will be heard by an anonymous jury, each of whom are driven to and from their homes to the Federal Court in Brooklyn by armed escorts."Heavily armed federal marshals and officers with bomb-sniffing dogs have been deployed to stand guard outside the courthouse. Inside, visitors must pass through metal detectors before entering the courtroom.El Chapo himself is transported from solitary confinement in Manhattan to court via police motorcade, which includes an ambulance and SWAT team, and shuts down the Brooklyn Bridge each time.More than a dozen witnesses are set to take the stand during the trial, and risk retribution by doing so. Because of this, the court has taken steps to conceal their identities, and have even barred courtroom artists from drawing them, reports Al Jazeera.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 15:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/14/3731048/3731048_92828C60A9A64568AC8BE7513C4113F0_181114_3731048_El_Chapo_trial_begins_amid_heavy_security_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F80/4D0/F804D0355057AF2213A857012F710A08.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, el chapo, chapo, chapo trial, security measures, guzman trial, heavy security, armed escorts, SWAT, security detail]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filipina flight attendant breastfeeds passenger's baby</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHILIPPINES  A flight attendant on a Philippine Airlines flight who breastfed a passenger's hungry baby has touched hearts across the internet. According to Next Shark, Patrisha Organo was working on a domestic hop, when she heard a crying baby. After approaching the mother to ask what was wrong, it turns out she had run out of baby formula.   With no baby formula on board, Organo did the next best thing, she offered to breastfeed the baby herself, which the mother happily agreed to. They headed to the galley, where Organo fed the 9-month-old baby until she quietly fell asleep. The mother and baby were then escorted back to their seats where they enjoyed the rest of their flight.    Organo shared the snap over Facebook on November 7. It has since racked up more than 183,000 likes and nearly 39,000 shares.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 11:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/14/3730887/3730887_8F5559B730D84B889BD3287472E9D87D_181114_3730887_Filipina_flight_attendant_breastfeeds_passenger__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D29/54B/D2954B64BF4F7774F77CAB6FD56E13B1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, flight attendant feeds baby, flight attendant feeds hungry baby, flight attendant feeds passenger's baby]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lit AA worker naps in plane cargo hold, wakes up in Chicago</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  An American Airlines baggage handler at Kansas City International Airport reportedly got blasted last month and somehow wound up in the windy city.The guy was working on the ramp for the Saturday Oct. 27 American Flight 363 from Kansas City to Chicago, according to USA Today. Apparently, he was pretty sleepy and decided to take a nap inside the cargo hold.Citing law enforcement, USA Today reports that the flight left at 5:52 a.m. local time with the employee on board. No one knew he was missing.He wasn't found until an hour after the plane landed at O'Hare International Airport, reports Chicago-based WGN9. The station reports that he told the cops he was drunk and fell asleep.The man wasn't charged with anything and returned to Kansas City on another flight. American Airlines said they suspended the baggage handler and are investigating what transpired.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 07:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/14/3730713/3730713_8EBEFE1B0DD44CE788E32F865D936CFE_181114_3730713_Lit_AA_worker_naps_in_plane_cargo_hold__wakes_up_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/813/EF9/813EF94DF60088C9DDFCE31A2B085DE7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, American Airlines, crazy plane stories, plane stories, baggage handler, american airlines baggage handler, Kansas city, chicago, drunk baggage handler ends up in chicago, baggage handler falls asleep in cargo hold, baggage handler ends up in chicago after falling asleep in cargo hold, funny cabin stories, funny plane stories, crazy plane stories, try not to laugh clean, funny airplane videos, funniest airplane moments, funny flight stories, funny flying stories]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stan Lee: A Marvel-lous life, an animated tribute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#RIPStanLee #StanLee #MarvelMarvel's Stan Lee passed away on Monday this week at the age of 95.Born Stanley Morgan Lieber in 1922 in New York, he got his start in publishing when he joined Timely Comics in 1939 as an assistant. Timely would later become Marvel.Lee's first credit was in a 1941 Captain America book. But World War II was booming in Europe and, just like Cap, Lee joined the U.S. Army. He served as a signals officer for three years until 1945.Around the same time, Lee was made interim editor in chief at Timely after senior creatives left. Little did Lee know then, but he'd hold onto that temporary post until he left in 1972. But near the end of the '50s, Lee was low and fed up with comics altogether.Deciding to switch gears, Lee co-created flawed and relatable characters throughout the 1960s. Spider-Man, Iron-Man, Thor, The Hulk, Black Panther, the X-Men, Doctor Strange, the Avengers and more would debut in Marvel comics during this time. The rest is history. Stan "The Man" Lee was back. Lee is said to have been deeply involved in the creation of many of the books during his era as Marvel's editor in chief, but he also found time to inject some wisdom into his art.Lee wasn't afraid to get political. Marvel comics featured his monthly column, aptly titled "Stan's Soapbox."  There he promoted books, but also blasted bigots, racists and wrote on all sorts of social commentary. And that was circa 1960s USA, a very different time from 2018.Lee was intrinsic to the Marvel brand and remained so throughout the '70s and beyond.He's been an executive producer on almost all films involving Marvel characters, plus he's had something like a bazillion cameos in them. That's not even mentioning his many other projects.The world is a sadder place without you Stan, but here's to you and your legacy.  Excelsior!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 04:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/14/3730613/3730613_CBBA5959F9524018B78C796B6A4DCC4A_181114_3730613_Stan_Lee__A_Marvel_lous_life__an_animated_tribut_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6F5/44D/6F544D312C29231EC57C3FECAE0DFB22.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, stan lee, stan lee dead, stan lee dies, stan lee life, marvel, marvel comics, iron man, spider-man, tribute, RIP Stan Lee, Stan Lee tribute, Comic book news, stan lee tribute, stan lee documentary, stan lee biography, stan lee, autobiography, amazing history, tributes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden North Korean missiles bases seen on satellite images</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  Satellite images have located 13 of an estimated 20 undeclared missile operating bases in North Korea.Specifically, the Sakkanmol missile base, which is around 85 miles from Seoul, is shown in satellite images to be located amidst mountainous terrain.The Sakkanmol missile base includes barracks, underground facilities to house the transporter-erector-launches (TELs) or mobile-erector-launchers (MELs), and vehicle maintenance and storage, according to a study by a Washington think tank.Satellite images also show the base's checkpoint, headquarters building, maintenance depots and entrances to underground tunnels that could potentially hide the missiles and the trucks that transport them.The missile operating bases are not launch facilities. However, missiles could be launched from there in an event of an emergency.Victor Cha, a prominent North Korean expert, claims the missile bases are actively in use and are not "decaying."This comes amid reports that North Korea was dismantling a key missile site in July.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 04:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/14/3730575/3730575_EE477FD47159435BB7E2BEF4A42B4F62_181114_3730575_Hidden_North_Korean_missiles_bases_seen_on_satel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/766/A1C/766A1C3B0D9AAF0509F0E46EFE7BCFBC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north korea, missile bases, missile operating bases, north korean missile bases, north korean missile program, north korea news, north korean nuclear program, North Korea nuclear program]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two explorers to trek across the Antarctica solo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA  Two explorers began their expedition earlier this month to try to cross Antarctica on their own, without any support.Colin O'Brady is a seasoned athlete who has a world record in climbing the top of the highest peaks in all seven continents in just 132 days, while Louis Rudd decided to make this expedition to honor his friend who taught him about polar exploration.O'Brady and Rudd began their journey on the Ronne Ice Shelf, which is 600-feet thick, in Antarctica and plan to finish on Ross Ice Shelf, taking around two months, reports the New York Times.They could be skiing up to 12 hours a day in winds of up to 100 mph, according to Gear Junkie.To make their trip, the two men had to carry equipment such as sleeping bags that can withstand temperatures of -40 degrees Fahrenheit, portable solar panels, cross-country skis, satellite phones, and a GPS tracker among other things.During their expedition, they will have to carry Nordic sleds, called pulks, with them along with food, cooking fuel, camping gear and skis covered with synthetic skin for better traction.The only person who has successfully completed a solo journey on Antarctica is Felicity Aston who went on a 1,084-mile solo journey from the Ross Ice Shelf to the Ronne Ice Shelf on Antarctica and received a Guinness World Record, according to reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 02:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/14/3730498/3730498_31C7FAC0509D42BBAF975D7E91624A61_181114_3730498_Two_explorers_to_trek_across_the_Antarctica_solo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DD8/FB0/DD8FB0A509664D3887EBA5F222C30FC7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Antarctica, Antarctica expedition, ski, skiing, antarctica 2018, Ross Ice Shelf, Ronne Ice Shelf, Colin O'Brady, Louis Rudd, polar exploration, antarctica exploration, antarctica expedition, two men attempting to cross antarctica solo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donkey and emu couple waiting for their forever home together</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCE, NORTH CAROLINA  An emu and a donkey fall in love after being abandoned at a farm in North Carolina.The Charlotte Observer reports that the interspecies couple came together on a farm in Kershaw, South Carolina where they and other animals were abandoned after the owner mysteriously vanished.Rescuers from the Carolina Waterfowl Rescue said that the two seemed to have really bonded during their time at the farm, so much so that when they were brought to the shelter, separating them became an issue.Jack and Diane  names picked out by the followers of Carolina Waterfowl Rescue's fan page  did not take well to the split. Jack, the donkey, wailed and cried in despair while Diane, the emu, frantically paced around her enclosure. The separation even became violent when Jack began attacking other donkeys in his enclosure. Rescuers quickly resolved that it was best to keep the loving couple together as they appeared to only be at peace if they shared their living space. Once they were back together, Jack and Diane resumed their romance and, according to a rescuer at the shelter, even "sleep and cuddle together."The two are now Facebook celebrities with hundreds of fans lining up to give them a forever home. Let's hope they don't get separated again!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 01:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/14/3730482/3730482_E80FC52B723A4584B1EDBFD0B8B3D4F6_181114_3730482_Donkey_and_emu_couple_waiting_for_their_forever__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8AD/20E/8AD20E0AC98D94E6E57B177A81416A1C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, interspecies love, love, love is love, animals, awww, emu and donkey fall in love, emu and donkey fell in love, carolina waterfowl rescue, cute, animals, cutevn, funny animals video, cute animals videos, cute and funny animals videos.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congo's Ebola outbreak is the worst in its history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BENI, CONGO   The latest Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is expected to last until mid-2019.The outbreak in the country's North Kivu Province has already killed more than 200 people, reports CNBC.Ebola commonly affects humans and nonhuman primates, and is caused by an infection with a group of viruses within the genus Ebolavirus, according to the CDC.The disease spread extensively in the town of Beni in North Kivu Province due to the dense local population, but also because of "tradi-modern" health centers, which patients tend to visit even though they aren't regulated.These health centers reportedly didn't have running water for handwashing, and patients would reuse needles to inject medicine.The WHO told reporters it will be "at least another six months" before they can declare the Ebola outbreak over, according to NBC News.This is the tenth Ebola virus epidemic the Democratic Republic of Congo has faced since its first epidemic back in 1976.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 07:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/15/3731387/3731387_E637E1F41FD349439E0A8DECB2956544_181115_3731387_Congo_s_Ebola_outbreak_is_the_worst_in_its_histo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FC4/66A/FC466A40D7CCF14E75CA5C519475B6CB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ebola virus, virus, viral outbreak, Congo, DR Congo, ebola outbreak, congo ebola outbreak, ebola outbreak in congo, ebola outbreak in congo 2018, ebola outbreak news, ebola outbreak congo 2018, worst ebola outbreak in history]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyal dog waits nearly 3 months for dead owner to return</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A video of a dog waiting patiently for his deceased owner to return has gone viral in China.Apparently, the devoted dog had been waiting for 80 days for his owner to return, standing guard at a railing in the middle of a road in Hohhot, Inner Mongolia. The dog's owner passed away in a car accident on that same road in August of this year, the Straits Times reports.The story has touched hearts all across China and according to reports from BBC, locals have been giving the canine little bits of food. The dog has been compared to Hachiko, a Japanese dog who waited 9 years for his owner to return in the 1920s  despite his master's passing.Volunteers will seek a new home for the dog if they can't reach the family of the dog's owner, according to reports from Chinese media.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 06:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/15/3731327/3731327_0C27818A305C4FD6942DF04B3E4C73C5_181115_3731327_Loyal_dog_waits_nearly_3_months_for_dead_owner_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F3F/7E7/F3F7E78BF1FB4B4225D807CBD8D31138.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, sad dog stories, dog stories, this will make your cry, china, dog, loyal dog in china, loyal dog in china waits for owner for 80 days, loyal chinese dog waits for owner, dog loyalty videos, dog loyalty stories, dog loyalty to owner,  dog waits in the middle of the road for deceased owner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of cat mummies, statues discovered in ancient tomb</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EGYPT  Egypt's Ministry of Antiquities has announced that dozens of mummified cats and wooden cat statues have been discovered in the ancient city of Memphis, Egypt.Along with the mummified cats and wooden cat statues, a painted wooden cobra and a crocodile sarcophagi were also found.Gilded statues of a lion, a cow and a falcon were also discovered, along with wooden snakes and crocodiles.Objects such as amulets, canopic jars and papyri baskets were also discovered in the tomb.The artifacts are regarded to be around 6000 years old.Ancient Egyptians were often buried with their mummified animals and statues as a way to bring pets with them to the afterlife.The animals were also buried as food offerings for not just the deceased, but as offerings to the gods as well.The ministry is hoping the discoveries will attract more tourists to visit Egypt's heritage sites.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/15/3731272/3731272_A1D7E3C7453E4B98A60F26B4E4015CB9_181115_3731272_Dozens_of_cat_mummies__statues_discovered_in_anc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/67D/FF9/67DFF901AD9BE3EDB5A0C2137EC70EFC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, egypt, mummies, egyptian mummies, cat mummies, cat statues, ancient egyptian tomb, mummified cats, crocodile sarcophagi, mummified animals, egypt mummies found, egyptian mummified cats, egyptian cat statues]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laundry balls that mimic coral could help reduce plastic pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MAINE   A laundry ball designed to catch microfibers from clothes could help reduce the plastics pollution entering the ecosystem. At four inches in diameter and made from recycled rubber, the Cora Ball imitates the way a coral reef filters tiny particles from flowing water. When washed with clothing, the laundry ball captures microfibers that come off during the wash. According the company, the ball captures between a quarter to a third of the microfibers per wash. A typical household 13-pound laundry load can shed up to 700,000 microfibers, says marine science researcher Imogen Napper form the University of Plymouth in the U.K., as reported by the BBC.The little plastic fibers are too small for water treatment plants to remove, so many of them make it into the oceans.According to the BBC, researchers say one cubic meter of ocean can contain 100,000 pieces of microplastic, which can then be consumed by marine life, to be eaten by humans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 04:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/15/3731255/3731255_DC1DE68EF66D44E68B3FD4F73C1449B5_181115_3731255_Laundry_balls_that_mimic_coral_could_help_reduce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A5E/49B/A5E49B7AB08046BB0CDE81819E72254E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic pollution, microfiber pollution, cora ball, laundry ball, microplastics pollution, microplastics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean "ghost boats"
wash up on Japanese coasts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  "Ghost boats" presumed to be from North Korea have washed up on the coasts of Japan.The Associated Press reports the number of ships has increased dramatically in recent years. One-third of these 'ghost boats' touch ground on the coasts of Japan's northern island of Hokkaido. Some are carrying dead bodies.The North Korean boats might be travelling into farther and more dangerous waters in an attempt to reel in larger catches and increase sources of protein for the country. North Korea is struggling to provide its people with sustainable food sources.The boats most likely cannot withstand rough seas due to their deteriorated states. Japanese coast guards say 95 boats have washed up in Japan so far this year, forcing them to increase security measures. The number is expected to rise and even surpass the 104 boats found last year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 01:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/15/3731164/3731164_757E2F6FF9DC430EB33E2A0719340302_181115_3731164_North_Korean__ghost_boats__wash_up_on_Japanese_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0A5/969/0A59698C7974BD4E0F0EC1A50C58D980.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Japan, North Korea,Tokyo, ghost ship, shores, fishing, food shortage, north korea ghost ship, dprk ghost ship, north korea escape, fleeing north korea, dprk escape]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's fight against smog continues this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China's air quality has again started deteriorating due to heavy pollution.The government has issued a revised air quality plan for the region. This is because pollution-prone cities in north China are set for more heavier smog this year than ever before.Northern Chinese cities have already seen four bouts of smog since early October, reports the South China Morning Post.Apparently, Chinese officials are blaming the weak winds and high humidity for the smog.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3732248/3732248_8CB7ED25C4414518AD2890D246DCFBCA_181116_3732248_China_s_fight_against_smog_continues_this_year_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/538/0D4/5380D426FC087EF96B133A5B90C05E83.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, smog, pollution, winter smog, china pollution, northern china, smog in china, china air quality, china smog problem, china smog 2018, air pollution in china, china's fight against smog]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple and homeless dude busted for fake GoFundMe scam</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW JERSEY  The touching story of a homeless dude giving his last 20 bucks to help a Jersey woman buy gas was actually all part of a plan to get strangers to donate money to the fake good Samaritan. According to the AP, Burlington County prosecutor Scott Coffina announced criminal charges against the couple who lied to newspapers and TV stations along with the homeless guy who was in cahoots with them the whole time. The over $400,000 donated to homeless man Johnny Bobbitt will be refunded to people who gave him money through a GoFundMe page set up by the couple, Mark D'Amico and Katelyn McClure. According to the prosecutor, "the entire campaign was predicated on a lie. It was fictitious and illegal and there are consequences." What other people refer to as karma. Bobbitt was shackled by U.S. Marshals in Philly on Wednesday night, while D'Amico and McClure turned themselves in on Wednesday night and were released. All three Einsteins were charged with theft by deception. According to authorities, nearly every part of their story was fake. McClure never ran out of gas. Bobbitt never saw McClure in trouble and definitely give her any money. Prosecutors began investigating after Bobbitt said he wasn't getting all the money raised on his behalf. He later sued the couple.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3732175/3732175_B251FE8EF5C0484898E21A806276578E_181116_3732175_Couple_and_homeless_dude_busted_for_fake_GoFundM_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/137/525/13752503BAF0A09DB8891D317C529F06.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, GoFundMe, GoFundMe scam, Johnny Bobbitt GoFundMe, Mark D'Amico, Katelyn McClure, D'Amico McClure GoFundMe scam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant caravan starts arriving at U.S.-Mexico border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S.-MEXICO BORDER  Groups of Central American migrants who have made their way across Mexico and are looking for asylum in the United States have begun arriving in the border city of Tijuana. According to NBC 7 News, the first groups of migrants began arriving on Sunday, Nov. 12 in trucks and buses. An estimated 1,660 migrants were in the Tijuana area as of Thursday. According to CNN, Mexico's Baja California state have estimated that as many as 9,000 more migrants could eventually arrive at the border. Many of these migrants will now begin the long asylum process. People who fear for their safety in their home country because of their race, religion, nationality, political beliefs or membership in a group can apply for asylum. To be considered, an individual must apply for asylum within a year of reaching the U.S. An applicant is allowed to stay within the U.S. while their case is pending. Individuals seeking asylum are housed in detention centers until they can be interviewed. In the U.S. while waiting for a court hearing, applicants must wear ankle monitors. According the CNN, migrants seeking asylum will most likely have to wait several weeks, if not longer, because of current bottlenecks at US ports of entry.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3732162/3732162_8620FBAD444A4C8B9672C06AD6D1452D_181116_3732162_Migrant_caravan_starts_arriving_at_U_S__Mexico_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/42A/F78/42AF78E24D42CEE5C13B9BC50680C364.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, migrant caravan, migrants, US Mexico border, asylum, asylum process]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omnidirectional urban wind turbine wins James Dyson Award</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  An omnidirectional wind turbine meant to hang from skyscraper balconies has won first prize in the 2018 James Dyson Awards. According to New Atlas, the O-Wind Turbine  a crooked, vented spherical device  is designed to generate electricity in the chaotic wind conditions of urban areas. Modern cities and their skyscrapers alter wind patterns, causing three-dimensional vortices where wind is constantly changing directions.  Taking inspiration from NASA's "tumbleweed" technology, a team from Lancaster University designed a turbine with a somewhat spherical shape, covered in vents that have large inlets and small outlets for air to pass through. Because of Bernoulli's principle, differences in pressure cause the turbine to rotate clockwise around a single fixed axis regardless of which direction the wind comes from. The rotational energy from the turbine can then be used to run a generator and produce electricity. According to team member Nicolas Gonzalo, the device could allow, "people living in apartments to generate their own electricity."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3732156/3732156_19E0E3BCFAD346F8AD9DBA02B280365C_181116_3732156_Omnidirectional_urban_wind_turbine_wins_James_Dy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A58/8FE/A588FE710A6038974E838D5933EAD07F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, urban wind turbine, omnidirectional urban wind turbine, o-wind turbine, o-wind omnidirectional wind turbine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Article 13: Why YouTube may go dark in Europe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS  YouTube may soon start blocking Europeans from viewing content on the platform due to radical new proposals for European copyright law known as Article 13.        Currently, individuals are responsible for ensuring they are within their rights to publish copyrighted material to the internet. The new law, Article 13 of the EU's Copyright Directive, changes this. It places enhanced responsibility on the website. Online platforms would be expected to have automated checks in place to filter out uploads containing copyrighted content.YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki explained in a Nov. 12 post on the YouTube Creator Blog that songs such as Despacito use various copyrights, and not all rights holders are known. It's because of this uncertainty and the financial risk associated with it, that YouTube may block Europeans users from viewing such content in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 07:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3732000/3732000_0A1D1EB26DDC4B34BE108187BBFA676D_181116_3732000_Article_13__Why_YouTube_may_go_dark_in_Europe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/525/53F/52553F0B815001C7A4EA8FCF5189B552.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, youtube, article 13, copyright directive, copyright law, article 13, memes, copyright safe, copyright news, copyright in Europe, Copyright online, Article 13 effects, European law, European parliament, YouTube, Automation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the European Union makes and passes laws</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS The European Union makes laws that shape 28 nations of Europe.According to European Parliament information, E.U. legislation is ideated by the European Commission. After a law is drafted there, it's sent onto the European Parliament for a reading. If the parliament wants amendments, it will note them, before sending them onto the next step in the process.The council may alter parliament's amendments to the draft, and send it back to them for a second reading. If parliament accepts, the proposal becomes law. They can also ask for further changes and if the Council accepts these, it becomes law.If not, both can choose not to adopt the draft or enter into negotiations known as 'concilation'. During this, an equal amount of parliamentarians and council members attempt to agree on a joint text for the draft. If they can't agree, it isn't adopted.If they do agree, the draft is sent back to both the parliament and council for a third and final reading. At this stage, no more amendments can be made to the draft.  Both have to approve the draft text for it to become law. If either rejects it, the proposal is discarded.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3731994/3731994_5B5BB6F927EE448982F314C59D573EE1_181116_3731994_How_the_European_Union_makes_and_passes_laws_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A3D/D8A/A3DD8A267ADBD39E26BD4995286CEF65.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, eu explained, european union laws, european union explained, how does the eu make laws, europe, brexit, european parliament, european council, european commission, europe explained, europe laws, difference between eu and national law, laws, legislation, how stuff works]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warriors offering $100 monthly passes with zero court view</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OAKLAND, CALIFORNIA  The Warriors sent out an email to fans this week announcing the release of an "In The Building Pass."Fans will get the honor of stepping foot inside Oracle Arena for every home game for $100 a month, according to ESPN. What does an "In The Building Pass" get you? Well  not a seat, actually you aren't even allowed into the seating bowl. You're not even allowed to see the actual court.Fans dumb enough to blow money on this pass will have access to the arena's bars and restaurants and will have the privilege getting to watch the game on TV in the club areas. Purchasers of the pass will have a chance to receive lame Warriors giveaways if they are one of the first 10,000 people in the arena. What's the point of being one of the first people in the arena if you have no seat and zero view of the court? Fans can purchase up to four "In The Building" passes, which are non-transferable. Golden State plans to sell 200 sucker passes each month. The Warriors currently have 44,000 people on their season-ticket waiting list.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3731894/3731894_B9C9D4973952413D8306992F50227BDF_181116_3731894_Warriors_offering__100_monthly_passes_with_zero__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EC7/270/EC7270CC18396C05ED73CA2EA98AAA1C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ...]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas woman KABOOMS wedding dress to celebrate divorce</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LACOSTE, TEXAS  A Texas woman decided to celebrate her divorce with a big bang  literally  by blasting her wedding dress to smithereens.After a court finally put Kimberly Santleben-Stiteler's presumably disastrous 14-year marriage to rest, she and her family threw a divorce party to mark the occasion, reports the Fort Worth Star-Telegram.She wanted to simply burn her wedding dress, but her dad and brother got the brilliant idea to turn it into an exploding target using 20 pounds of explosive tannerite.So on Saturday night, the 43-year-old went full-on target practice with the dress, shooting it with a rifle from 200 yards away.She hit the bullseye on her first shot, which caused a massive blast and a bang so loud it was heard from 15 miles away.Concerned messages immediately started pouring in from people around the county who heard the explosion. But for Santleben-Stiteler and her family, it was simply liberating. Thank god for closure.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 03:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3731858/3731858_4FADC65138A24CD99A360038D572310D_181116_3731858_Texas_woman_KABOOMS_wedding_dress_to_celebrate_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/537/E1C/537E1C542730462CA5F949C451804D37.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, divorce party, burn the dress, wedding dress, divorcee, target practice, tannerite, crazy breakup, crazy divorce, crazy breakup stories, how to get closure]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Fred Flintstone jokingly nabbed for speeding in footmobile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WESLEY CHAPEL, FLORIDA  Halloween may be over, but that didn't stop one Floridian from getting into character.According to the Pasco County Sheriff's Office, Bedrock's premiere working class caveman was spotted in Wesley Chapel, Florida on November 4, complete with his prehistoric smart car.The faux Fred Flintstone, whose real name is Don Swartz, took to the streets in his foot mobile, but was apparently going way too fast for the cops' comfort.A Pasco County deputy gave him a speeding ticket, which didn't really blow over well, and caused Twinkletoes to go full caveman on the officer.Mr. Flintstone was later released, but his foot mobile was seized by the Sheriff's Office, and is now part of their fleet.Really though, the whole thing was part of a mock arrest and vehicle seizure, and no Fred Flintstones or foot mobiles were hurt in the making of this PSA.Their message? Speeding may be okay in the Stone Age, but in Modern Day Florida, you better yabba dabba don't.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 03:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3731852/3731852_D5427A97C49E44DAB8E0A4B250D7F325_181116_3731852_Florida_Fred_Flintstone_jokingly_nabbed_for_spee_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D06/E9C/D06E9C58A6E2486297701B687611AC5C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fred flintstone, bedrock, fred flintstone costume, flintstones, footmobile, fred flintstones footmobile, yabba dabba doo, speeding]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon picks New York and DC area for new headquarters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Washington and New York    After 14 months of deliberation, Amazon announced that New York and Virginia are their final choice for the location of their new offices. Amazon's new headquarters, dubbed HQ2,  will be divided between New York City and Arlington, Virginia. Both offices will cover 371,000 square meters and generate 25,000 new jobs.An additional Amazon operation center will be opened in Nashville. The site will span almost 93,000 square meters and generate $230 million in investment as well as open 5,000 full-time job positions.According to Amazon, taxpayers in New York will pay  $48,000 per job, $22,000 in Virginia and $13,000 for Tennessee. According to The New York Times, Amazon will receive more than a billion dollars in tax incentives.Other cities in the country had offered the tech giant even higher incentives. According to The Baltimore Sun, the city of Montgomery County in Maryland had the biggest offer with a bid of over $8 million which included tax incentives and infrastructure and transportation improvements. According to The Amazon blog, the cities were ultimately chosen due to their transit access, diverse talent and business environment. The e-commerce giant has made its move, let's see if it pays off.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 02:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/16/3731807/3731807_AF9559B22B6D4C47A24D5E6FFAB6E15C_181116_3731807_Amazon_picks_New_York_and_DC_area_for_new_headqu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8FB/5AC/8FB5AC42CE4834048BDB2E07AAA2C744.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, technology, consumer tech, gadgets, science, gear, tech, Amazon, Amazon HQ2, New York, Arlington, amazon headquarters, ecommerce, nashville, business, tax, tax incentives, east coast, expansion, queens, new york city, northern virginia, economy, jobs, opportunities, billion.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sues ex for stretching her out with his abnormally long dong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARARE, ZIMBABWE  A woman in Zimbabwe is taking her ex-lover to court, supposedly for loosening her once tight snatch.The 29-year-old had met her 37-year-old  former flame in 2016, while he was still married and her downstairs plumbing was still intact.After falling in love and starting a relationship, she discovered her lover's package was abnormally long and thick.The girl later realized his package was way too impressive, and broke up with him last May after claiming it severely overstretched her poor honeypot.No one knows exactly how big the dude's schlong is, but the hole he left is apparently so stretched out that literally no other man can fill the void.She now wants to get reconstructive surgery on her hooha, and is suing her ex-boyfriend to get him to pay for the $10,000 procedure.No news yet on how the defendant plans to plead, as he has yet to respond to the allegations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 09:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/19/3733663/3733663_958D10D691F748BD84A7A3D0C4FF9EC0_181119_3733663_Woman_sues_ex_for_stretching_her_out_with_his_ab_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7FB/B80/7FBB80C9F4815AD8DF24D04969762254.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, abnormally long penis, stretched out vagina, woman sues lover, large dong, tight snatch, abnormal body parts, body parts, reconstructive surgery, vaginal reconstruction, vaginal rejuvenation, private parts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What will happen if the U.K. goes with Theresa May's Brexit deal?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  If Theresa May's Brexit deal passes into law, what will it mean for the United Kingdom? The Brexit deal consists of two documents. The first is a 585-page agreement ending Britain's relationship with Europe, while the second is a seven-page outline describing the future relationship, according to the Guardian. The transition period would begin on March 29, 2019 and end on December 31, 2020. During this time the U.K. would have to follow all E.U. rules, but would not have membership in its institutions, according to the BBC. The withdrawal agreement would allow for the transition to be extended only once for a limited period, but would require both the U.K. and E.U. to agree for an extension before July 1, 2020. The Brexit draft also includes the calculations for how much the U.K. would need to pay the E.U. to settle all of its obligations.U.K. citizens in the E.U. and E.U. citizens in the U.K. will keep their residency and social security rights after the withdrawal. If by the end of 2020, no long-term trade deal is agreed upon, and if there is no transition period extension, then a backstop of "a single customs territory between the Union and the United Kingdom" would take effect. In a backstop setting, the U.K. is subject to "level playing field conditions" to prevent it from gaining a competitive advantage while in the same customs territory. To exit the backstop it would require bilateral agreement between the U.K. and the E.U.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/19/3733623/3733623_6883C9D456334E8E8F429E335EDBC5CA_181119_3733623_What_will_happen_if_the_U_K__goes_with_Theresa_M_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DFD/E06/DFDE06694F9B1919E84D7212262F821D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Brexit, Brexit draft, Theresa May Brexit, Brexit backstop]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China's plans for the world's biggest supercollider</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  The Chinese Institute of High Energy Physics is planning to construct a particle accelerator over the next decade. According to information from the project's website, it is expected to be situated near Qinhuangdao City, east of Beijing. Dubbed the Circular Electron Positron Collider, the project is expected to be five times more powerful than the Large Hadron Collider in Europe. It will be located in a 100-kilometer underground tunnel.The project will be a double ring collider with electron and positrons beams in separate pipes. It will circulate these in opposite directions.If successful, researchers also plan to build a Super Proton-Proton Collider and use it to collide electrons with positrons. Scientists behind the project expect the collider could potentially generate more than a million Higgs particles and others such as W and Z bosons.The researchers have released the design of the collider and plan to build a prototype before the actual collider is built. Construction on the collider is expected to begin in 2022.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/19/3733563/3733563_61019C0F3D5141D0B7EDC06FECA10A5D_181119_3733563_Inside_China_s_plans_for_the_world_s_biggest_sup_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/848/5B7/8485B771214F746D4DBCE246A934D82A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, Particle Collider, collider, largest particle collider, LHC, china to build the largest particle collider, chinese particle collider, chinese particle accelerator,  chinese circular electron positron collider, CEPC, electrons, positrons, antimatter, Higgs proton, science, physics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic clouds of smoke 
Threaten California residents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA  Deadly wildfires in California continue to burn causing leaving clouds of dangerous smoke along the way. "According to The New York Times, at least 63 people have been killed by 'Camp Fire'  the deadliest fire to date in the state of California  while 200 others are still missing.CNN reported 'Camp Fire' has already burned through 141,000 acres of land and is only 40 percent contained.Toxic clouds of smoke coming from this and other fires are now threatening the health of residents living in nearby areas.Data from government sponsored air quality index site AirNow indicates California currently has the highest level of unhealthy air in the United States.According to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, particles less than 10 micrometer in diameter are the most insidious as they cling to lung tissue and can even be absorbed into the bloodstream.Fine particulate matter from wood fire affect children, the elderly and especially those who already suffer pulmonary and heart diseases. However, according to the San Francisco Chronicle, there is little data regarding long-term health consequences that derive from prolonged exposure to wildfire smoke such as the one California residents are experiencing now.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 07:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/19/3733553/3733553_2B3356244F7A4C6CA755F013842E458E_181119_3733553_Toxic_clouds_of_smoke__Threaten_California_resid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FA2/E71/FA2E71DE6B5371A09B22FE26A5D189B6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, camp fire, sacramento, davis, smoke, safety, campus, california wildfires, fire, wildfire, california, air quality, smoke, lungs, pulmonary disease, smog, campfire, smoke, hazardous, san francisco, unhealthy, air, quality, death toll, residents, hazardous.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New MAGA "Build the Wall" toy available for the holidays</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  Thinking about what to get your kids for Christmas? Well, Keep and Bear has got you covered.The company has launched a new line of building blocks to let kids build a border wall to "keep America safe and strong."In its sales pitch, Keep and Bear refers to the migrant caravan heading to the U.S. and says the wall must be built to 'keep out gangs, criminals and terrorists."The company seems to be cashing in on President Trump's promise to strengthen the border and build a wall against "illegal immigrants."The toy set is aimed at kids five and up, and will apparently include 101 building-block pieces and a bonus Trump figurine wearing a MAGA hard hat. It retails for $29.95 on the company's website.The website also retails other MAGA toys such as "Trump sends Hillary to Prison!Limited Edition," and "Trump and Lady Liberty Limited Edition Collector's Set."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/19/3733480/3733480_F6ECDA3914E347FA8094E3AD4E5863DC_181119_3733480_New_MAGA__Build_the_Wall__toy_available_for_the__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C88/1FA/C881FABC39FA95A2BD65AF01B564448B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, holidays, Trump, MAGA, Christmas, Christmas holidays, Christmas toys, toys for children, MAGA toys, MAGA Build the wall toy, Keep and Bear, New MAGA toy available for Christmas, Build the Wall toy, MAGA Building Blocks toy, MAGA Building blocks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's "Artificial Sun"
hotter than the Sun</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA   China's artificial sun is hotter than THE ACTUAL SUN.  Researchers from China's Hefei Institutes of Physical Science reported its fusion reactor has reached 100 million degrees celsius in plasma, over 6 times the heat generated by the sun's core.The heat is generated within a device called Experimental Advanced Superconducting Tokamak, also known as EAST. The donut-shaped machine supports nuclear fusion by using magnetic fields that keep hot plasma from melting the exterior walls of the device.According to Futurism, nuclear fusion is a thermonuclear process that occurs when the nuclei of two light atoms, usually hydrogen, combine and form a heavier atom, in this case helium. This process results in release of energy in the form of heat and light  the same way by which the sun produces its warmth. Researcher's from the EAST project hope to develop technology that will allow humans to extract clean energy from nuclear fusion. Scientists from the ITER project  a multinational experiment aiming to harness nuclear fusion energy  sustain that fusion fuels are almost infinite and do not release harmful gases into the atmosphere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 04:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/19/3733449/3733449_723133B8C7974CF39C5CCFA364FCC5B1_181119_3733449_China_s__Artificial_Sun__hotter_than_the_Sun_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5D0/A1F/5D0A1F40727980149BCA07DC2946BD83.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic, TomoNews, Satire, fusion, fusion energy, physics, global energy, fusion power, iter, fuel, power, hydrogen, atom, plasma, clean energy, science, explained, explainer, education, explain, science video, awe, reliable, unlimited, source, edutainment, experts, china, future, sun, reactor, power plants, atmosphere, fossil fuels, go green, research, magnetic, source, fusion reactor magnets.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising temperatures may impact male fertility</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  New research has found that sperm counts in male beetles are affected by warmer temperatures.Researchers used red flour beetles as a proxy for humans. They subjected them to five-day "heatwave" conditions of above average temperatures. This damaged male reproductive potential and halved male fertility, according to the study published in Nature Communication.Even if the male beetles were able to procreate in that climate, their offsprings tend to have shorter than average lifespans, according to the researchers. Female beetles were largely unaffected.The researchers also found that successive heatwaves could nearly sterilize males.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 03:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/19/3733421/3733421_60E79443BD194D31898F61827E303BDF_181119_3733421_Rising_temperatures_may_impact_male_fertility_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AC4/440/AC444089C516C3E5776EC910AF970B69.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, climate change, lower sperm count, heatwaves, global warming, rising temperatures, red flour beetles, male fertility, rising temperatures could lower male sperm count, climate change, heat waves lower sperm count in beetles, effects of climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman eats instant noodles for 3 weeks to save money</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANTONG, CHINA  In an attempt to save big bucks for the biggest Chinese shopping extravaganza of the year  Singles Day  a really smart Chinese woman decided to eat nothing but instant noodles for three straight weeks. Singles Day is like Black Friday on juice and apparently is the biggest shopping event in the world. Yay!According to Shanghaiist, a college student named Hong Jia decided to consume only instant noodles in a bid to save some cash for the November 11 shopping holiday. Then a strange thing happened  Hong's body didn't react so well to only being fed instant noodles. And when Singles Day finally rolled around, Hong unfortunately didn't get blow all her money like all the other shopping sheep in China, because she was in the hospital running a high fever. She was forced to spend two days in the hospital  and the cherry on top? She had to blow all the money she saved to pay for her medical bills. Doh!But don't worry, in the end Hong did get to buy something  a face mask. Well, there's always next year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 07:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/20/3734133/3734133_B496A2C7C9744906A363F5AA88E5E43E_181120_3734133_Woman_eats_instant_noodles_for_3_weeks_to_save_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8BA/5A7/8BA5A7C2F7D715783B6C23203811C9A1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, woman eats only instant noodles, instant noodles, China Singles Day, Singles Day November 11, instant noodle diet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spending all your time on social media makes you depressed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA  Spending all your time on "social media" sites like Facebook and IG turns out isn't the greatest thing for your mood.A new study published in December's Journal of Social and Clinical Psychology has found a causal link between the time wasted on social media and depression and loneliness. According to University of Pennsylvania researchers, people who cut back on social media show improvements in their mood and how they feel about life. The U Penn psychologists found that subjects were less depressed and didn't feel as lonely when they limited their social media usage. According to Marketwatch, the study looked at 143 undergrads and tested their mood using seven different scales. Half the students continued using social media sites as normal, while the other half were restricted to 10 minutes per day each for Facebook, Instagram and Snapchat. The study concluded that people who spent less time on social media saw "clinically significant" falls in depression and in loneliness. So if you want to be happier, spend less time on social media and more time just being social.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 07:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/20/3734129/3734129_16F2E767B8EA4ED7A139CF767528D21D_181120_3734129_Spending_all_your_time_on_social_media_makes_you_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/55A/AE4/55AAE48E39284441C70C80D7510A5919.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, social media, social media affects mood, Facebook, Instagram, Snapchat, social media use]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China ramps up efforts to steal U.S. tech secrets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China has significantly ramped up its efforts to steal U.S. technology secrets in the past two years, reports the South China Morning Post.China has reportedly been hacking anything from commercial technology to intellectual property.Micron , a U.S. tech company, was targeted by the Chinese, according to Los Angeles Times.The Chinese reportedly worked with employees of the company to receive trade secrets and stole as much as $8.75 billion in patented U.S. technology.Apparently, Chinese espionage has risen as President Trump has railed against trade policies with China and imposed tariffs on Chinese products.U.S. officials say that the Chinese are growing relentless as they recruit executives and engineers to spill trade secrets.They also rely on an army of domestic hackers to hack digital networks as well as corporate and government emails, according to the South China Morning Post.According to an FBI special agent, China doesn't mind playing dirty as long as they get what want and they "don't care if they get caught or if people go to jail."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 06:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/20/3734093/3734093_5E097E32CA3847BAA56C39B75A81D904_181120_3734093_China_ramps_up_efforts_to_steal_U_S__tech_secret_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4FD/98D/4FD98DE0CDD197084C89179034FFD0C8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, US, technology, tech secrets, china hacking, china technology theft, commercial espionage, chinese espionage, chinese theft of US tech, China stealing US technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannibal turns himself in, yelling he's 'tired of eating human meat'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ESTCOURT, SOUTH AFRICA   A cannibal got so sick of consuming people meat, he surrendered gave himself up to the cops.It was just another day at the Estcourt police station in South Africa until a man walked in, yelling for help because he was "tired of eating human body parts," South African online news site News24 reported.The man claimed he was being forced to consume human flesh, and to the cops' horror, promptly pulled out a severed hand and a maggot-infested foot from a pink school bag. He put them on the counter as proof of his horror story.He then led the police to a small house where he was allegedly being held hostage. Behind a curtain of the one-room abode were several containers filled with human parts and "muthi," traditional South African medicine.According to local authorities, three other men were arrested after the alleged cannibal's confession accused of murder and possession of human body parts. Their victim was a 24-year-old woman who was found dismembered under large rocks. These types of killings are called "Muthi Murders" and are often conducted in hopes they will bring fortune to the perpetrator.One of the accused died earlier this year in an apparent suicide while awaiting trial, South Africa's Sunday Times reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 06:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/20/3734068/3734068_3736558A93E94437BD6EA23A754AE2B7_181120_3734068_Cannibal_turns_himself_in__yelling_he_s__tired_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/715/16A/71516A2369D2AB9CF1A976485205EDF2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, south africa, cannibal, nino mbath, muti, muti murder, cannibalism, pietermaritzburg high court, traditional medicine, human flesh, hand, foot, evidence, dismembered, body, hostage, police, traditional healers, ritual killing, traditional medicine, cannibalism case, human meat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince behind Khashoggi murder, says CIA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISTANBUL  A CIA report found that the death of journalist Jamal Khashoggi was ordered by Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, despite Saudi Arabia's claims that he was not involved.According to the Washington Post, there is no metaphorical "smoking gun" linking the prince to the murder, but officials believe that such an operation would not have happened without his awareness or involvement.The CIA analyzed a phone call supposedly made at the command of the Saudi crown prince, in which Ambassador to the U.S. Khalid bin Salman tells Khashoggi to go to the consulate in Istanbul for his documents, assuring him it was safe to do so.Audio from a listening device planted in the consulate indicates that just minutes after Khashoggi entered on October 2, he was attacked and killed, and later dismembered.Maher Mutreb, a security official and one of the Saudi operatives, is then believed to have made a call to one of the crown prince's aides in Riyadh, informing him that the operation was complete.Some members of the Saudi hit squad have also been linked to Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, having served on his security team and traveled to the U.S. during official visits.While the location of Khashoggi's body is still unknown, Reuters reports that the Turkish defence minister has said his dismembered corpse may have taken out of the country in luggage.Saudi Arabia has offered several contradictory versions of what occurred, and now say an operation to abduct Khashoggi veered off course when he was restrained and injected with an overdose of a drug, which killed him.The Saudi prosecutor's office has announced charges against 11 unidentified people, five of whom could face the death penalty. But U.S. officials say it's unclear if the Saudi government will in fact follow through with the punishment, and when.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/20/3733986/3733986_8BBA39CCD5944D3CAD64C87EACD095A7_181120_3733986_Saudi_crown_prince_behind_Khashoggi_murder__says_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/18B/BFE/18BBFE82F3CE45B26D39CC89B8A333B2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, jamal khashoggi, khashoggi, khashoggi killing, khashoggi murder, saudi crown prince, mohammed bin salman, Saudi journalist, saudi hit squad, CIA report, CIA, saudi consulate, istanbul]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first luxury, underground hotel to open in Shanghai, China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI, CHINA  China's newest luxury hotel is opening its doors, with 16 of its 18 floors underground.The InterContinental Shanghai Wonderland was built vertically along a formerly abandoned water-filled quarry near Sheshan Forest Park and contains a total of 336 rooms.It took more ten years for the hotel to get built, due to various technological difficulties  according to reports from China Daily.Visitors staying in two of the 16 floors submerged 33 feet underwater will be able to enjoy an aquarium view right from their suite.All the rooms were designed keeping the quarry's landscape in mind. This includes the view of the waterfalls from cliffs and a green roof on top of the hotel.The hotel will also generate its own power, heating and lighting through geothermal and solar energy.It covers around 61,000 square meters and includes recreational facilities such as bungee jumping, rock climbing, water sports and even a glass floor skywalk.Architects who designed the hotel had previously designed buildings such as the Burj Al Arab in Dubai and Landmark 81 in Vietnam.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/20/3733973/3733973_026D58B4C26C4C1EBED26B0E5EF74298_181120_3733973_World_s_first_luxury__underground_hotel_to_open__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/089/B3E/089B3E16525EC2009076062F36F2BA2E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, luxury hotels in China, underground hotel, underground hotel in China, underground hotel shanghai, world's first underground hotel, InterContinental Shanghai Wonderland,five star hotel underground,  shanghai, quarry, quarry hotel china, quarry hotel shanghai, underwater quarry hotel, underwater hotel, aquarium hotel room]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six trapped after elevator falls 84 floors inside Chicago skyscraper</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  A pregnant woman, several law students and some tourists were among the 6 people who escaped from a stuck elevator in Chicago last week. The lift fell 84 floors.The Chicago Tribune reports that six people stepped into an express elevator on the 95th floor of Chicago's John Hancock Center around midnight on Friday. Two cables holding the elevator broke soon after.The people inside said they felt the elevator moving fast and saw a dust-like material enter the carriage. The elevator fell 84 floors before stopping at the 11th floor.Firefighters had to use a gooseneck camera to determine the elevator's exact location, before then breaking through a brick wall to open the doors and rescue the people trapped inside.The rescue took nearly three hours. A Chicago Fire Department Spokesman told the Chicago Tribune that none of those trapped suffered serious injuries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/21/3734925/3734925_EB28A16E3D1640CA9C21EAF94831D930_181121_3734925_Six_trapped_after_elevator_falls_84_floors_insid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E6B/B7D/E6BB7D70AC6C32BD2500F738849E833D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[scary elevator story, Stuck lift rescue, elevator falls down, elevator, elevator rescue, trapped in elevator, elevator falls, elevator nightmare, hancock center, hancock center elevator, chicago skyscraper, chicago building, dramatic rescue, rescue stories, rescue stories 911, rescue stories, firefighter rescue, firefighter rescue stories, scary stories with happy endings, scary stories, scary elevator stories, TomoNews, Satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSIRIS-REx set to take Bennu asteroid sample with robotic arm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  NASA's OSIRIS-REx successfully stretched out its robotic arm for the first time in space, as it readies to take a sample from the asteroid Bennu.According to NASA, the OSIRIS-REx is an asteroid study and sample-return mission which launched from Cape Canaveral on September 8, 2016.The spacecraft is expected to reach the near-Earth asteroid Bennu on December 3, and will then prepare to collect a surface sample in July 2020.It will use the Touch-and-Go Sample Acquisition Mechanism or TAGSAM, an 11-foot robotic arm with three articulating joints, a round sampler head, and three bottles of high-pressure nitrogen gas.Once the arm is unfurled and touches the asteroid surface, nitrogen gas is blasted out to stir up regolith, or loose dirt and rocks, which will then be caught by the sampler head.The entire process will take about five seconds. Collected particles will be stored in a canister with nitrogen allowed to escape, leaving between 60 and 200 grams of material.Once sampling is complete, and the material safe inside a heatproof Sample Return Capsule, the OSIRIS-REx will execute small maneuvers to back away from Bennu.The spacecraft will then journey back to Earth and eject the capsule just outside Earth's atmosphere, to land in the Utah desert in September 2023.Bennu is roughly 4.5 billion years old, and as an ancient relic of our solar system's early days, scientists believe it could shed light on how that system was formed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/21/3734897/3734897_4E85BDC6CAFF4F4AA11FA7303B5BF186_181121_3734897_OSIRIS_REx_set_to_take_Bennu_asteroid_sample_wit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/562/433/562433DB04490F53C21A332535701E5F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, OSIRIS REx, satellite, asteroid bennu, Bennu, asteroid sample, NASA, TAGSAM, NASA mission, asteroid mission, NASA spacecraft, regolith]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan gets ready for 2018 midterm elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Taiwan is set to have midterms on November 24 to select candidates for nine different levels of government, also being called the "nine-in-one" elections.  According to the National Interest, the highest levels up for election are the mayoral and county magistrates of cities and counties, down to the level of village wardens and indigenous district councils.  The minimum voting age in Taiwan is twenty years. Voters must fulfill a four-month residency requirement before being allowed to vote.People need to bring three things with them in order to vote, their ID card, their chop stamp and their polling station slip. As there is no absentee balloting, Taiwanese people must return to the cities where they are officially registered in order to cast their ballots. Local elections are held every four years at intervals between national elections.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 12:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/22/3735625/3735625_FAB731FDD879427A8DA7359B8D099CE5_181122_3735625_Taiwan_gets_ready_for_2018_midterm_elections_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EEE/4B9/EEE4B9B597A548F4E76612F27279C5B6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwan elections, Taiwan elections 2018, Taiwan midterm elections, Taiwan nine-in-one elections, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela creates smart card to get China-style social control</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VENEZUELA  Venezuela has taken a page from China's book by rolling out its own authoritarian surveillance tech in the form of smart cards.According to a Reuters report, Venezuela's new 'Fatherland' ID was inspired by China's smart cards, which allow the government to track a citizen's social, political and economic behavior.Venezuela initially wanted cards embedded with RFID chips, which can track location and data. Ultimately, they used QR codes developed by Chinese telecom giant ZTE to reduce costs.ZTE also built a database for the fatherland cards. The cards are linked to employment and income, property, medical history and political party membership.The Venezuelan government has previously provided incentives to cardholders to encourage adoption of the card  giving cash prizes for rallying voters, for example, or a Mother's Day bonus.Citizens are now being forced to get the cards in order to receive public benefits such as medicine, pension, subsidized food, and fuel.Describing the program as 'blackmail,' Hector Navarro, one of the founders of the Socialist Party in Venezuela, claims Venezuelans who have cards have more rights than those who don't.Mariela Magallanes, an opposition lawmaker in Venezuela, previously investigated unenrolled citizens being deprived of subsidized food boxes, and says the government knows who is vulnerable to pressure."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/22/3735338/3735338_9FFD56D2F29A42E8A1C104ED9570D8DD_181122_3735338_Venezuela_creates_smart_card_to_get_China_style__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/368/E58/368E58EA0374756C0C3114C2CEC7E52D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Venezuela, ZTE, ZTE Venezuela, China, surveillance, Venezuela smart ID, fatherland card, Venezuela's Fatherland card, smart ID cards, carnet de la patria, fatherland database, chinese technology, socialist state, high-tech surveillance programs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive ancient termite mounds the size of Britain found in Brazil</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRAZIL  Scientists have uncovered tens of millions of termite mounds dating almost 4,000 years, in a remote part of northeast Brazil.According to a new study published in the journal Current Biology, the mounds were made by a species of termite called syntermes dirus, and spread across 230,000 square kilometers.Each conical mound is about 2.5 meters tall and approximately 9 meters wide.The termite mounds contain 10 cubic kilometers of soil, which is equivalent to roughly 4,000 Great Pyramids.Researchers believe the mounds were built as termites carved out extensive networks of undergrounds tunnels to survive, according to Science Magazine.The underground tunnel allows the termites move swiftly in order to feed on dead leaves of caatinga, a specific type of dry, thorny trees whose leaves only falls once a year.The researchers added, "This is the greatest known example of ecosystem engineering by a single insect species."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 04:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/22/3735266/3735266_2F982BB0893E418C97FC195A1E4D41B5_181122_3735266_Massive_ancient_termite_mounds_the_size_of_Brita_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/122/375/12237515321761544A7CF4402DFE5EC1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Brazil, termites, termite mounds, syntermes dirus, termite mounds Brazil, ancient termite mounds, massive termite mounds, Brazil termite mounds, large termite mounds found in Brazil, brazilian termite mounds, caatinga, great pyramids]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wreck of missing Argentine 
Submarine found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARGENTINA   Argentine Naval officials do not have all the answers yet but have begun investigations to pin down what caused the wreck.The ARA San Juan was on its way back from a routine expedition at the southern tip of South America when it reported technical difficulties.It first reported a short circuit caused by water that had leaked through the submarine's snorkel and dripped on the battery. Shortly after, officials lost contact with the submarine.Argentine newspaper, La Nacion, says a special investigation commission put together by the Argentinian Ministry of Defense reported that a second explosion may have occurred triggering issues in the control systems which then led to the vessel sinking and imploding due to high underwater pressure.  According to the BBC, the wreckage was found by Ocean Infinity  a seabed exploration company hired by Argentinian officials   in a ravine roughly 900 meters below surface. It was carrying 44 crew members.Family members of the crew are now demanding the government begin efforts to recover the remains of the vessel.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 02:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/22/3735207/3735207_57F0390428A84C3797455D7A0D194D14_181122_3735207_Wreck_of_missing_Argentine__Submarine_found_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/211/4A6/2114A6DDEA1D6871C4473A4978A9F853.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Ara san juan submarine, Submarine, San Juan, Argentina, Maritime Transport, argentinian sailors, argentine submarine, mar del plata, argentina, submarine, argentina submarine, atlantic ocean, submarine ara san juan, missing submarine, buenos aires, missing argentine submarine, argentine sub, ara san juan, 44 crew, explosion, search, revelation, oxygen, implosion.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth's interior sucking up more water than previous thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD  Seismic activity around the Mariana Trench have revealed the earth around it could be taking in at least 4.3 times more water than previously thought, according to a new study in the journal Nature.The researchers deployed 19 seismographs to the bottom of the ocean around the trench, and seven land-based seismographs on the Mariana Islands. Two tectonic plates meet at the Mariana Trench, which is where the huge Pacific Plate seems to be sliding under the tiny Mariana Plate, thus letting vasts amount of seawater to pour through the cracks into the earth's crust 30 kilometers below the surface.The researchers believe that the seawater could turn into hydrous minerals due to the high temperature and pressure. The hydrous minerals would then be incorporated into the lower plate and sink deeper into the mantle as the tectonic plate sinks.Chen Cai, lead author of the study, told Live Science there is no missing water in the ocean and that the amount of water going into Earth's interior and coming back out should be equal. However, it appears that there is a disparity, with Chen adding that more studies should be conducted to find out more about the water cycles of our planet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 02:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/22/3735193/3735193_045A9866A6794A81B9D05099FFF0D5DE_181122_3735193_Earth_s_interior_sucking_up_more_water_than_prev_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CA6/E28/CA6E28D355EA6BEB4BA0A62DD9E11088.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, earth, mariana trench, seawater, earth's interior, earth's interior sucks up more water than previously thought, earth is drinking its own seawater, subduction zone, earth's deep interior, Hydrous minerals, earth's crust, tectonic plates, water cycles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook hired right-wing PR firm to smear billionaire George Soros</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facesuck admitted on Wednesday it hired a right-wing PR firm to investigate George Soros after the billionaire publicly criticized the company. Faceblow's outgoing head of communications and policy Elliot Schrage was forced to fall on the grenade for hiring Definers Public Affairs in a memo first reported on by TechCrunch. Schrage said that, "In January 2018, investor and philanthropist George Soros attacked Facebook in a speech at Davos, calling us a menace to society."   Later, when a group called Freedom from Facebook emerged, Faceplant sent the Definers to find some answers. The Definers learned that Soros was apparently funding some of the groups members. Both CEO Mark Zuckerberg and COO Sheryl Sandberg had said they had no knowledge Definers had been hired until the news was made public by a New York Times report last week.  Looks like the NYT report jogged Sandberg's memory, who then tried to walk back her denial saying that Definers work had "crossed her desk."Sandberg then tried to explain that the reason they hired a right-wing PR firm was not to spread anti-Semitic conspiracy theories about Soros. Apparently, Facebites was just looking for good old fashioned dirt to smear on Soros instread.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/23/3736257/3736257_540040BD48B248ECB0554F640EA9D6FA_181123_3736257_Facebook_hired_right_wing_PR_firm_to_smear_billi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/382/01B/38201B8B34DDE1D544826E2AB61042A7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Facebook, Facebook v George Soros, Facebook Definers Public Affairs, Facebook Soros, Mark Zuckerberg, Sheryl Sandberg]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South China Sea: New PRC structure could be military</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH CHINA SEA  A new Chinese structure in the South China Sea maybe for military purposes, according to a report from an American think tank.Reuters reports that recent satellite imagery reveals a newly built platform on Chinese-claimed Bombay Reef in the Paracel Islands, that's topped by a radome and solar panels.The purpose of the new structure is unclear. It could be a navigational aid for transiting ships, but the same function can be served by buoys or an already existing lighthouse.According to U.S. based think tank The Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, it's more likely to be military in nature. This is because the reef is directly adjacent to major shipping lanes that run between the Paracels and Spratly Islands.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/23/3736069/3736069_4A0009C302A8405DB3335785A405F3A2_181123_3736069_South_China_Sea__New_PRC_structure_could_be_mili_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/64E/B2E/64EB2EFC341FCF562A51769F934D6F2C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, south china sea, bombay reef, paracel islands, south china sea dispute, paracels, radome, radar, solar panels, south china sea shipping lane, spratly islands]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan to hold a referendum on marriage equality this Saturday</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#Taiwan #TaiwanElection #GayMarriage #Referendum #MarriageEqualityTAIWAN  Taiwan is preparing to vote in an historic vote on marriage equality.On Nov. 24 voters will be asked five referendum questions on same-sex marriage.One question, drafted by opponents to same-sex marriage, asks if voters believe marriage should be restricted to between a man and a woman.Another question, also drafted by same-sex marriage opponents, asks if the voter agrees that education about homosexuality should not be taught in elementary and junior high school under Taiwan's Gender Equity Education Act.Voters will be asked another question, createdby supporters of same-sex marriage, if education about homosexuality should be taught in elementary and junior high school under the Gender Equity Education Act.Another question, drafted by same-sex marriage supporters, asks if the voter agrees to guarantee the rights of same-sex marriage couples under Taiwan's Civil Code. And one question, drafted by same-sex marriage opponents, asks if voters agree that the rights of non-married same-sex couples who live together can be protected.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 06:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/23/3736005/3736005_7B87964321F74F798019E758F87BB2C2_181123_3736005_Taiwan_to_hold_a_referendum_on_marriage_equality_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/45D/782/45D782F2CEE87D23BA753F68F9109307.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, taiwan gay marriage referendum, taiwan gay marriage vote, taiwan marriage equality, LGBTQ vote taiwan, Taiwan, marriage equality, gay rights, taiwan gay rights, LGBTQ, taiwan gay marriage vote, gay marriage referendum in taiwan, taiwan referendum 2018, taiwan referendum on marriage equality, gender education taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC suggests all of America should avoid romaine lettuce</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMERICA  Health officials are warning U.S. consumers not to eat any romaine lettuce as it could be contaminated with a strain of E.Coli.The outbreak has already spread to 11 states across America, along with two provinces in Canada, according to the CDC.Thirty-two people have already become sick from eating contaminated romaine lettuce in the U.S., according to the BBC.The CDC is encouraging the public to throw out all romaine lettuce and to wash and sanitize drawers and shelves where the romaine lettuce was stored.The recent outbreak is believed to be caused by a strain of E. coli identified as O157:H7 which produces a Shiga toxin. Symptoms of infection can include diarrhea or hemolytic uremic syndrome, a type of kidney failure.In order to prevent E.Coli infections, the CDC encourages people to wash their hands thoroughly before and after preparing and eating food, wash fruits and vegetables under running water and to cook meat thoroughly to kill harmful germs.FDA Commissioner Dr. Scott Gottlieb told CNN that he believes the recent E.Coli outbreak could be associated with the end of harvest season in California as most romaine lettuce in the country in harvested from that region. The CDC, public health officials and the FDA conducting investigations into the E.Coli outbreak.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 05:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/23/3735988/3735988_7E7F48E2D22643508BBE0A80C87BCB80_181123_3735988_CDC_suggests_all_of_America_should_avoid_romaine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/127/CB1/127CB15E1D864362B31A5D1FB6B32C23.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, E. Coli,  E. Coli outbreak, US, Canada, romaine lettuce, romaine lettuce e coli, romaine lettuce e coli outbreak, romaine lettuce recall, romaine lettuce linked to e coli outbreak, e coli romaine lettuce, e coli symptoms, e coli outbreak 2018, e coli infection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese merry-go-round blasted for using real horses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENGDU, CHINA  With all the knockoffs in China, it hardly comes as a shock that they also have fake merry-go-roundsunfortunately, they use real horses. According to Ladbible, the amazing ride is located at the Shuangliu Wanda Plaza shopping center in Chengdu.The pitiful looking ride consists of four horses strapped to metal frames as they are forced to walk around on a motor-driven platform. Suckers need to shell out 50 RMB, or about 7 bucks, for a four-minute, fun filledminus the funride. A sign posted next to the ride describes it as "different from traditional wooden horses, you can really experience the fun on horseback and let your child indulge. Let you and your child be brave."The unlucky horses reportedly are forced to carry little brats for about four hours a day.   According to the Shangma Equestrian Club, which owns and runs the ride, the carousel is a good way for the horses to get exercise. Noit's not. A manager also tried to tell the Beijing News that the ride isn't cruel to animals. Yesit is.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 03:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/23/3735894/3735894_298E0F5BAAA242BEB30DD592117C8729_181123_3735894_Chinese_merry_go_round_blasted_for_using_real_ho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/52E/F2F/52EF2F1B417121BC58BDC97706245A52.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China merry-go-round, China carousel, China carousel real horses, China merry-go-round real horses, China real horse carousel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA's new Mars probe
just days away from landing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA  Mars will be receiving another visitor from its neighboring planetNasa reports by the time NASA's InSight lander descends to Martian soil it will have travelled 480 million kilometers and spent six months travelling through space.  The probe will land on Elysium Planitia, a plain just 600 kilometers from Curiosity's landing site located near the equator.According to NASA, the InSight lander is packed with two cameras that will aid with navigation and an instrument deployment arm that will place research devices on the planet's surface.It carries three main instruments: A seismometer that measures Mar's seismic waves and detects meteor impacts, a heat probe that will penetrate 5 meters into the surface of the planet to measure its heat flow and interior temperature and two antennas called RISE that will help determine the size and composition of the planet's core. As InSight enters Mars' atmosphere it will emit radio signals subbed 'tones' these signals will be relayed to NASA by two space crafts flying behind the lander called MarCOs. The tones carry key information regarding the entry, descent and landing of the lander.  Engineers at the flight control center will be passing down a lucky jar of peanuts during the landing, a tradition that started in 1964 during the successful landing of Ranger 7  the first space probe to successfully transmit images of the moon back to Earth]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 01:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/23/3735843/3735843_DDCF1E74DF9D4F5E860B6DAB10880B58_181123_3735843_NASA_s_new_Mars_probe_just_days_away_from_landin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5B9/1C5/5B91C52BE90FADAFCF0D07D8476D7E87.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, science, Video, Seeker, current events, education , educational, discovery news, mars, space, NASA, insight, lander, insight lander, mars exploration, explore, can we live on mars, colonize, travel, space travel, land on mars, spacecraft, astronaut, survive on mars, space exploration, NASA mission, 2018 launch, insight lander update, insight lander mission, Curiosity, Elysium Planitia, NASA engineers, Vandenberg Air Force base, santa barbara, launch date, explainer, atmosphere, explained, Astronomy, Geodesy, Seismology, Mars Cube One, MarCO, going to mars, can we go to mars, nasa insight, watch nasa insight, insight heading to mars, NASA news, space news, what is mars insight, mars insight news, insight on rockets, how will insight launch, mars spacecraft, what is insight's mission, does mars have water, water on mars, could there be life on mars, what will mars insight do.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India struggling to retrieve U.S. missionary's body from island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH SENTINEL  Indian authorities have said retrieving the body of the killed American missionary from North Sentinel island could be difficult. According to CNN, police and the fishermen who reported seeing 26-year-old John Allen Chau's body last week, went close to the island on Friday and Saturday in an attempt to find a way to recover the body.   The police and fishermen saw a group of islanders armed with bows, arrows and spears guarding something on the beach, the New York Times reported.According to Dependra Pathak, a top police official in the Andaman and Nicobar Islands, "we have mapped the area with the help of these fishermen. We have not spotted the body yet but we roughly know the area where he is believed to be buried." Pathak added the Sentinelese were patrolling the beach around the same spot Chau was killed. Instead of approaching to retrieve the body, police sketched out the crime scene and then sailed away. North Sentinel Island is home to one of the last remaining untouched hunter-and-gatherer societies left in the world. It's about the size of Manhattan with an estimated population of about a few dozen people. India has kept the island off limits in order to prevent Sentinelese from catching modern illnesses and to keep trespassers from being killed.According to Indian law, people are not allowed to travel within five nautical miles of the  island and the Indian Navy patrols is day and night.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/26/3737927/3737927_1C92718FB9E24F9BBC677D5B7F64829E_181126_3737927_India_struggling_to_retrieve_U_S__missionary_s_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B84/90A/B8490A2DEF92C108EE646A25F4CCCF7C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US missionary killed, US missionary body retrieval, US missionary North Sentinel Island, North Sentinel Island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money launderer busted with $400,000 in washing machine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMSTERDAM  Dutch authorities found about $400,000 stuffed into the drum of a washing machine last week during the arrest of a suspected money launderer. According to CNN, Dutch po po arrested the man last Monday while checking for unregistered residents in western Amsterdam.Looks like police records listed the home the suspect was found in as having no residents, but when authorities did a search of the home, they discovered the cash stashed in the washing machine. The police also found several cell phones, a gun and a money-counting machine during the raid. The identity of the 24-year-old suspect has not been made public. A photo released by the police shows bundles of €20 and €50 packed inside the washing machine. According to police, the raid was apparently part of an investigation into housing fraud, money laundering and other forms of crime.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/26/3737915/3737915_636F252CBC624E19A2BF28FFF1FD50E7_181126_3737915_Money_launderer_busted_with__400_000_in_washing__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AC3/CD2/AC3CD2636585BE0C30D8EACAAFF2E5AB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, money laundering, money launderer, money hidden washing machine, money hidden in washing machine, police raid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man purchases a storage unit for $500 and finds $7.5 million inside</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  A man purchased a second hand storage for $500 and opened it up and found $7.5 million.Apparently the man bought the second hand storage for $500 and found a safe inside.They then called a person to help open it up. When it didn't work, they called a second person to help.They initially expected the safe to be empty, but to their surprise, it was far from it. Instead, the safe was filled with a pile of bills amounting to $7.5 million.An attorney contacted the man claiming to represent the people who originally owned the storage unit and offered a reward of $600,000 for returning the cash, according to The Blast.The man reportedly declined at first, but then accepted a second offer to keep $1.2 million and return $6.3 million.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/26/3737892/3737892_AFB54392FD5142A2A89EB491EEB43412_181126_3737892_Man_purchases_a_storage_unit_for__500_and_finds__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE0/150/FE015095411F67D6ABB3CE575F6125F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, USA, storage unit, man finds 7.5 million inside storage unit, locked-up storage units, storage unit finds, storage unit auctions, 7.5 million found in storage unit, cash, physical cash, dollar bills, stack of cash, millions of dollars found in storage unit, cash found in storage unit, most cash found in storage unit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineers at MIT fly first
plane with no moving parts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  Engineers at MIT have managed to fly an airplane with no moving parts. The aircraft was designed to resemble a glider, it weighs roughly two kilograms and has a 5-meter wingspan. The plane has two rows of wires under its wing. The row at the front end of the wing carries 20,000 volts of positively charged particles called ions. The ions are then attracted to the row on the back end of the wing which carries a negative charge of 20,000 volts. As the ions move to the back row they collide with neutral air pushing it behind the glider and generating electroaerodynamic thrust, driving the aircraft forward. This air is called ionic wind.According to their study, published in the journal Nature, the team tested the glider inside a gym where it managed to sustain flight and travel 60 meters, making it the first solid state flight  or flight without moving parts like turbines and propellers.Engineers participating in the study hope this technology can be the first step towards designing aircrafts that are quieter and do not emit combustion emissions. Engineer Steven Barret says the team was inspired by the futuristic space crafts from Star Trek. Let's hope the technology they've developed lives long and prospers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/26/3737764/3737764_1889FFEDE1DE43C8BB1B2D66A7B4E18C_181126_3737764_Engineers_at_MIT_fly_first_plane_with_no_moving__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/33C/7DD/33C7DD8E4F4EA9D44AF56FF3549B1D7C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, science, nature video, ionic wind, ion, electroaerodynamic propulsion, lifter, MIT, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Barrett, Steven Barrett, aeronautical engineering, flight, wright brothers, ion drive, engineering, power converter, hover car, electrode, battery, electric, plane, glide, glider, thrust, electric vehicle, technology, tech, sci, explained, explainer.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild turkey wreaks havoc on Rhode Island town</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JOHNSTON, RHODE ISLAND  Everyday is turkey day in this small Rhode Island town, but that's not exactly a good thing.The Guardian reports that when three wild turkeys arrived in Johnston, Rhode Island in May, the locals warmed up to the new residents fairly quickly. They gave them snacks and took photos. Someone even made a Facebook page.It was all in good fun until the birds started coming after people. Animal Control managed to catch two of the turkeys, but the third managed to make a run for it.Six months later, the turkey is still on the lam. It's repeatedly halted traffic with its wily-nily crossing of the highway, and trapped people in their cars with vicious pecking attacks.The bird is both quick-witted and quick on its feet, and keeps outsmarting the humans. It's learned to recognize animal control vehicles, so officers have had to use undercover cars.They even got a net gun, only to have it malfunction as they crept up on the bad bird. And as if things weren't hard enough, the turkey's also started sleeping up telephone poles and trees to avoid capture.The mayor reckons the feathered menace won't leave because it's acquired a taste for Starbucks muffins and Smashburger fries. Then again, maybe it just enjoys turning the tables on humans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/26/3737717/3737717_98D8EFFDD73C4FD388C5DE3939E6C9F1_181126_3737717_Wild_turkey_wreaks_havoc_on_Rhode_Island_town_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/283/FA5/283FA515B396AE69A6F8D36A5F39AAAE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, turkey, wild turkey, turkey on the loose, johnston turkey, turkey attack, wild turkey attack, troublesome turkey, al capone turkey, rhode island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Tulip tower planned 
for London City</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  The Tulip observation tower is the newest architectural proposal for the city of London. The sci-fi-esque building was designed by British international architecture studio 'Foster + Partners' who have previously designed the London City Hall and the famous Gherkin. If approved, construction could begin as soon as 2020 and conclude in 2025.The tower would act as a cultural attraction and become the city's tallest skyscraper soaring 305 meters above ground. According to a press release from the architecture firm, it will be equipped with education facilities, gondola pods, sky bridges and a sky bar and restaurants with a 360-degree view of the city. The skyscraper would be made of concrete, steel, aluminum framing and high performance glass. The architecture company seem to be into sustainability, making room for 284 cycle parking spaces which is what they claim to be the equivalent to taking 28 cars off the street.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/26/3737593/3737593_A020EF52824846CF9254EC5C16D5DC34_181126_3737593_New_Tulip_tower_planned__for_London_City_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6BB/FD9/6BBFD9F541924EC6706779E1B5E01AFB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Foster, Partners, London, Architecture, News, gondola, attraction, tourism, skyscraper, slides, skyscrapers, tower, concrete, glass, 360 views, visitor attraction, viewing galleries, experience, sky bridges, glass slides, gondola pod, sky bar, restaurants, 360 degree views, pocket park, rooftop garden, green walls, National Park City, sky bar, design, innovation, art]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Orwellian social credit system to start by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  The Chinese government has yet another trick up its sleeve to keep citizens on lock down.According to Reuters, China is planning to launch a social credit system that will assign  "personal trustworthiness points" as a means of monitoring citizens and businesses.Trustworthy individuals will reportedly be provided with more access to society while individuals who are blacklisted will be severely restricted.Credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, character traits, behavior, preferences, and interpersonal relationships will all be considered in calculating a credit score.Data gathered by the system could impact an individual's access to public services and employment. It may also affect a citizen's ability to start a business. People with high trustworthy scores could be given easier market access.Participation is currently not mandatory. Once it becomes required, however, people with low scores could be punished with slower internet speeds, denied travel, and access to certain restaurants, night clubs, golf courses.Beijing plans to implement its social credit system by 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 02:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/26/3737582/3737582_8143E8908C184D57876DDEFA13340B15_181126_3737582_China_s_Orwellian_social_credit_system_to_start__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/05C/2F0/05C2F0AD96097F4B74432AD7D514EA7C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, social credit system, Big Brother, China Social Credit System, China state surveillance, China social credit score, china social credit score system, orwellian, dystopian, black mirror]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarcophagus opened to reveal 3,000-year-old mummified woman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LUXOR, EGYPT  A centuries-old coffin containing a well-preserved mummy was recently unveiled in Egypt  the latest in over a dozen ancient discoveries since the beginning of the year.Reuters reports that on Saturday Egyptian authorities opened a 3,000-year-old sarcophagus to reveal the mummified remains of a woman named Thuya, marking the first time such an artifact was unveiled in front of international media.The sarcophagus was one of two found earlier this month in the Al-Assasif necropolis on the western bank of the Nile river.The first was a rishi-style coffin from the 17th dynasty that had been opened earlier and examined by officials.Other finds include five colored masks and around 1,000 Ushabti statues, miniature figurines of servants to serve the dead in the afterlife.The Guardian reports that according to Egypt's antiquities ministry, the tomb belonged to a mummification supervisor at the Temple of Mut in Karnak.Workers had to remove some 300 meters of rubble over five months in order to get to the tomb, the ceiling of which was adorned in colorful paintings that depicted the owner and his family.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3738671/3738671_D08C66E06B334377869258C876232B55_181128_3738671_Sarcophagus_opened_to_reveal_3_000_year_old_mumm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/48C/687/48C6879807A225063A75C50F212AB071.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mummy, mummies, the mummy, sarcophagus, mummified woman, egyptian tomb, necropolis, afterlife, egypt, archaeology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese scientist claims to create world's first CRISPR babies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A scientist in China has been under scrutiny for allegedly using CRISPR, a gene-editing tool, to create the first gene-edited babies.In describing his process of gene-editing, He Jiankui said he first "washed" the sperm to separate it from semen and then placed the sperm into a single egg to create an embryo during in vitro fertilization.After the embryo was 3 to 5 days old, CRISPR-cas9 was used to remove a gene called CCR5.The scientist claims he previously experimented on editing the DNA of mice, monkey and human embryos in his lab for several years.He claims he altered the DNA to make the babies immune to HIV, according to the Associated Press. He also claims the gene surgery was a success and produced twin baby girls.The participants of the study were reportedly told that gene-editing was similar to a vaccine and were made to sign a consent form in which they were told that gene editing on an embryo has never been tried before and carries risks.An immediate investigation has been ordered into He's claims of having created the world's first genetically-edited babies, according to the National Health Commission of the People's Republic of China.The hospital He claims to have conducted the research in has denied any involvement with the surgery and said the babies weren't born there.Shenzhen Hermonicare Women's and Children's Hospital also said they plan to conduct an internal investigation on two doctors in their hospital that the Chinese scientist claims were also involved.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/27/3738477/3738477_CE0EC80B506644168EF2C2B46AEB1177_181127_3738477_Chinese_scientist_claims_to_create_world_s_first_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0C9/191/0C9191FD506C9ECA259FC16CDBCB5514.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, crispr babies, crispr china, crispr gene editing, 
Chinese scientist, chinese scientist gene edited babies, chinese scientist genetically edited babies, CRISPR, CRISPR technology, gene-editing, DNA, editing DNA, world's first genetically edited babies, CRISPR-cas9, CCR5, altering human DNA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK farmer crushed by forklift driven by his pet dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  Derek Mead, 70, was tending to his fields using a forklift truck when tragedy struck, reports the Telegraph.He stopped the truck and got off the vehicle to open the gate, leaving his Jack Russell terrier inside the vehicle. This is when the dog ended up hitting the shuttle lever.The forklift began moving ahead, fatally crushing Mead against the gate.A post-mortem examination found that Mead suffered spinal fractures and traumatic asphyxia due to the accident.Mead's family said they are still grieving for the loss of their father and will focus on continuing his legacy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 04:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/27/3738217/3738217_D62F28A700CC4818ABF6D3C271513CA8_181127_3738217_UK_farmer_crushed_by_forklift_driven_by_his_pet__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CF9/EC7/CF9EC74353D1044BCFA96CD10ACF5B9F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, UK, farmer, UK farmer, pet dog, Jack Russell terrier, forklift, forklift accidents, forklift accident UK,  farmer crushed to death by forklift driven by his dog, Jack Russell terrier, dog accidentally crushes farmer to death]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Leaning Tower of Pisa is straightening itself out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PISA, ITALY  The Tower of Pisa may be known for its distinctive tilt, but recent years have seen it becoming slightly more upright.The BBC reports that the Tower of Pisa was constructed on a layer of clay and sand that was softer to the south, and began to tilt by the time the third storey was being built.To compensate for this, the next five levels were constructed with one side shorter than the other, resulting in a structure that is not only tilting, but is also curved.By 1990, the marble tower was leaning six degrees, or 13 feet, according to CNN. Officials feared it might topple over and closed it to the public for corrective work.Cables were attached to the third storey to stabilize the tower. Counterweights and braces were added while soil was removed from the north side to allow it to straighten out.Experts say the Tower of Pisa is now stable, and has lost 1.5 inches of its tilt over the past 17 years, from its reopening in 2001 to the present.CBS reports that at its current pace, it may take another thousand years for the tower to straighten out completely. So tourists and Instagrammers shouldn't worry - the famous leaning landmark will still be available for photo-ops for a good long while.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 03:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/27/3738196/3738196_FB18FBA4CC3A466AA90F3A1CB6146A9A_181127_3738196_The_Leaning_Tower_of_Pisa_is_straightening_itsel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E68/01D/E6801DF0006DF03738BB490411C04616.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, leaning tower of pisa, tower of pisa, leaning tower, pisa, marble tower, pisa restoration, bell tower, italy tower, tower of pisa explainer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea creature inspires breakthrough in water treatment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW HAVEN, CONNECTICUT  Researchers have taken inspiration from a sea creature to create a new kind of water treatment.According to the study published in the journal Nature Nanotechnology, coagulation is a chemical water treatment process that causes colloidal and suspended water-borne particles to group into formations and settle. Conventional coagulants like aluminum sulfate remove large particles but cannot capture smaller dissolved contaminants.Researchers from Yale and Peking University sought to address this issue. They modeled a nanocoagulant after the sea anemone Actinia to remove a broad range of contaminants in a single step.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3739112/3739112_10469D3A15514F358AB7483D41754131_181128_3739112_Sea_creature_inspires_breakthrough_in_water_trea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE8/D29/BE8D29E136976074F211DCEC18722883.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, water treatment, actinia, sea anemone, sea creature, coagulation, water coagulation, nanocoagulant, multifunctional nanocoagulant, coagulant, water filtration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Space bugs' onboard ISS 
could pose risk to astronauts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE    Researchers from the California Institute of Technology studied bacteria retrieved from the ISS space toilet and exercise platform.According to their study published in the journal BMC Microbiology, all five strains that were analyzed proved to be resistant to several common antibiotics such as penicillin, rifampin, cefazolin, cefoxitin and oxacillin among others. They showed a level of intermediate resistance for ciprofloxacin and erythromycin.Researchers reported that the microbes found on the ISS are a variety of the Enterobacter, a bacterium that causes diseases in newborns and people with weak immune systems.According to experimentation through computer modelling, there is a 79 percent chance that the bacteria could be pathogenic  or likely to cause a disease in humans.Researchers are concerned about the health risks the propagation of such bacterias could pose for astronauts in future missions. The team stated that ''in vivo" experiments would help further understand the true levels of pathogenicity of the bacteria in humans. For now the bacteria are not threatening the lives of astronauts living in the ISS, but researchers will keep a close watch in order to prevent health risks for future expeditions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 07:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3738938/3738938_BD9175F3F2C44F1C95BB9C3AB1D8AE5C_181128_3738938__Space_bugs__onboard_ISS__could_pose_risk_to_ast_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0C3/EA9/0C3EA9E9985B478C552C793A752FDF18.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, current events, science, ISS, space, bacteria, International space station, NASA, astronauts, disease, space exploration, microbiology, research, health, toilet, pathogenic, superbugs, antibiotic, antibiotic resistance, enterobacter, physics, technology, explainer, tech, California Institute of Technology, humans, microbes.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China facial recognition nabs jaywalker, too bad it was a bus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NINGBO, CHINA  A facial recognition system in China proved that it definitely recognizes faces, even ones on the side of a bus. According to Mashable, some cities in China have rolled out facial recognition tech at intersections in a bid to identify jaywalkers and then blast them with a good dose of public shaming. Beijing's goal is to dissuade behavior it deems unacceptable by recognizing the person's face, checking it with a database, then putting their personal information on public screens. According to Abacus, one camera at the Jiangxia Bridge East intersection in Ningbo knocked a home run when it nabbed one famous jaywalker. Unfortunately, it had to be called back after it turned out to be a bus ad. Apparently, the bus was driving through the intersection when the facial recognition scanned the face of a businesswoman on an advert and then plastered her face all over the public screen.  Ningbo's traffic po po later said over their Twitter knockoff Weibo that they made a mistake and that the system had been updated.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 06:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3738895/3738895_63BB03F4F8B9431D87912A4C131E3532_181128_3738895_China_facial_recognition_nabs_jaywalker__too_bad_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F42/EEF/F42EEF8DC0A5FE86F4EB38B6BF1777BD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, China facial recognition, China facial recognition jaywalker, China facial recognition fail, facial recognition failure]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman drives onto train tracks because of her GPS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUQUESNE, PENNSYLVANIA  A woman was paying a little bit too much attention to her GPS while driving around the Pittsburgh area last week. According to WFLA, late last Wednesday night, the police got a call about a vehicle on the wrong trackliterally, as the car was on the railroad tracks. When the po po showed up on scene the driveraka Google Mapstold them "her GPS advised her to go this way." A Facebook post from the City of Duquesne Police Department said the woman was totally sober and had no medical conditions affecting her decision-making. When one of the commenters blamed the driver's common sense for not kicking in when the GPS told her to turn onto the tracks, the cops were kind enough to respond. "Just to be clear. This vehicle was going straight on the highway and veered off. There was no turn involved here."Unfortunately, Magellan's car had to be towed from the tracks and she was given a ticket for careless driving.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 06:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3738877/3738877_962BBA9771214398A4413D316E66B7C0_181128_3738877_Woman_drives_onto_train_tracks_because_of_her_GP_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C27/03D/C2703DF7BE79D21FDF8A35E5A4FCD88C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, GPS, car on train tracks, car on railroad tracks, GPS failure, GPS fails]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of frozen sea turtles wash ashore in Massachusetts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE COD, MASSACHUSETTS  At least 219 cold stunned sea turtles have washed ashore in Cape Cod Bay, Massachusetts over the last week.According to the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, cold stunning occurs when the sea turtles are exposed to extreme periods of cold water temperatures.This impairs sea turtles as they are cold-blooded reptiles and depend on external sources for heat. They do not have the ability to warm themselves in cold water.Turtles with the condition suffer from various symptoms including, a decreased heart rate, low blood circulation, shock, pneumonia and death.Robert Prescott, director of the Massachusetts Audubon Society's Wellfleet Bay Wildlife Sanctuary, told the paper the sea turtles were "flash-frozen" in swimming positions. Prescott added changing weather conditions next week may result in more living turtles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3738816/3738816_03D8D86492C448E2A09DF1DE0137A3A2_181128_3738816_Hundreds_of_frozen_sea_turtles_wash_ashore_in_Ma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/116/1EF/1161EF3D0E87C0B219FBE272769E4F45.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, Cape Cod,  sea turtles, cold stunning, cape cod cold stunning, cold stunned sea turtles, cold spell, frozen sea turtles, sea turtles cape cod, frozen sea turtles, cold weather, frozen sea life, stunned turtles, cold turtles, cold stun turtle, reptiles, nature, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deforestation in the Amazon rainforest 'worst in 10 years': Brazil</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRAZIL  Brazil has recorded its worst annual deforestation figures in ten years.7,900 square kilometers of the Amazon rainforest was destroyed between August 2017 and July 2018, according to the BBC.This represents a 13.7 percent increase from last year's figures.Most of the deforestation took place in the Brazilian states of Mato Grosso and Para.In addition to affecting water supplies, deforestation could also cause the rainforest to start releasing greenhouse gases instead of taking in carbon dioxide from the atmosphere, the National Geographic reports.Carlos Nobre, a climate scientist, said if sixty percent of the forest degrades to a savanna, it could result in five or six years' of fossil-fuel emissions being released into the air.Deforestation was responsible for forty-six percent of Brazil's greenhouse gas emission in 2017, according to the Guardian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 03:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3738804/3738804_874838BDECE14DF397A824142AE4433A_181128_3738804_Deforestation_in_the_Amazon_rainforest__worst_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE4/036/BE403617CC4C13879C0325E1AB680C3E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Brazil, deforestation, tropical forests, Amazon, amazon rainforest, environment, rainforest destruction, tropical forests, brazil deforestation, brazil rainforest deforestation, deforestation in brazil amazon rainforest, brazilian deforestation worst in a decade, brazilian deforestation worst in 10 years]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists propose 'dimming sun'
as solution to climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  Scientists from Harvard and Yale analyzed the possibility of 'dimming the sun' to battle climate change.  If this sounds like it's straight out of a sci-fi movie, it's because it's not real … yet.Fleets of specially designed aircrafts would fly roughly 20 kilometers above ground in the lower stratosphere.Once there the planes would spray tiny sulphate particulates to block sunlight in a process that is known as stratospheric aerosol injection.According to their study, published in the journal Environmental Research letters, this technique could cut the rate of global warming in half.Researchers who participated in the study state it would be a "remarkably inexpensive" process costing around $2 bn to $2.5 bn a year.CNN reported the plan doesn't cover greenhouse gas emissions and could have negative consequences such as extreme shifts in weather and endangering crop yields. It's important to note that the engineers behind this are not suggesting this is the ultimate solution to climate change, but just wanted to estimate technology costs of stratospheric aerosol injection.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/28/3738734/3738734_867DF480094543E8A2A6B699481E3CEA_181128_3738734_Scientists_propose__dimming_sun__as_solution_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C3B/CFF/C3BCFF6A35EF7262665A8CB2F0505842.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, news, science, tech, technology, sun, space, aerosole, harvard university, global warming , climate change, climate engineering, planetary engineering, environmental research letters, harvard, greenhouse gases, emissions, sulfate, global dimming, sun dimming, solar radiation management, conspiracy, temperature rise, temperature rising, sea levels rising, droughts, weather, extreme weather.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot misses landing because he was catching some ZZZs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA  A small plane missed its landing in Australia by about 30 miles or so because the pilot was sleeping in the cockpit. According to the BBC, Maverick was the only person on the freight flight from Devonport to King Island in Tasmania on November 8.Apparently, the Vortex Air Piper PA-31 plane was set to finish a 150 mile trip and touch down at 7:15 local time. With some time to kill, the pilot set the aircraft on autopilot, and according to a Vortex Air statement, "unintentionally fell asleep while in command of the aircraft.""The issue became apparent when air traffic control was unable to contact the pilot in-flight and the aircraft traveled past the intended destination point," the statement said. According to The Australian newspaper, air traffic control made several radio calls to pilot while he was counting sheep. Goose eventually woke up and turned the plane around to land safely on King Island. Looks like the pilot had almost no sleep the night before due to a personal crisis. According to the AP, the Australian Transport Safety Bureau and the Civil Aviation Safety Authority are investigating the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/29/3739910/3739910_934C5E4EC8944EA9ADC2F4364782667E_181129_3739910_Pilot_misses_landing_because_he_was_catching_som_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D26/621/D266218896D9F35F8DA0CDA46C3C1EC6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, napping pilot, sleeping pilot, pilot asleep, pilot misses landing, Vortex Air pilot asleep]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions rise amid sea clash between Russia and Ukraine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CRIMEA  Tensions between Russia and Ukraine rise after a naval confrontation near the Kerch Strait.Two Ukrainian gunboats and a tug boat departed from the Black Sea port of Odessa and headed Mariupol, a coastal city on the north coast of the Sea of Azov, on the morning of sunday November 25th.According to BBC, as the boats approached the Kerch Strait they were intercepted by Russian boats. Russian coast guards fired at the Ukrainian vessels, ramming one of its ships against a Ukrainian boat.Russian fighter jets and helicopters patrolled the area around the strait as the boats attempted to approach the channel. They also blocked the bridge with a tanker.Ukrainian authorities claim six crew members were injured during the encounter while Russian authorities maintain only of the sailors suffered injuries.The BBC reports, Russian President Vladimir Putin told German Chancellor Angela Merkel that the Ukrainian navy had 'ignored the rules of peaceful passage in the territorial sea of the Russian Federation'. According to AP,  that Ukrainian President Petro Poroshenko has announced martial law in regions bordering Russia, Belarus, and the separatist region of Trans-Dniester.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/29/3739906/3739906_7A0C028E6531410F863317E70AC8064B_181129_3739906_Tensions_rise_amid_sea_clash_between_Russia_and__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/980/A0D/980A0D80250EF16157F6ABAAB5389E47.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, crimea conflict, ukraine, russia, ukraine russia conflict, crimea russia, crimea 2018, crimea patrol, ukraine russia ship, ukraine martial law, ukraine ships, ukraine crimea, crimea, kremlin, kiev, kerch strait, black sea, tension, escalation, Ukraine declaring martial law, ukraine attack, ukraine attack russia, ukraine cyber attack, ukraine mortar attack, russian army attack ukraine, grad missile attack ukraine, G20, Petro Poroshenko]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers turn plastic bottles into versatile aerogel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE  Researchers from the National University of Singapore have found a way to convert plastic bottles into an ultralight super material with various applications.Eco-Business reports that the process involves plastic bottles made from polyethylene terephthalate or PET. These are first shredded into fibers and combined with several chemicals, including hydrochloric acid and polyvinyl acetate.The solution is put in a sonicator where it is mixed using sound energy, then freeze-dried to produce an aerogel that is soft, durable, and flexible. One plastic bottle can produce an A4 sheet of aerogel.According to a press release from the National University of Singapore, the aerogel is versatile, and can serve unique functions depending on the surface treatments. When coated with an amine group, it can be used in pollution masks to absorb dust particles and carbon dioxide.It can absorb large amounts of oil when incorporated with various methyl groups, and withstand temperatures of up to 620 degrees Celsius when coated with fire retardant chemicals.Researchers have listed several practical uses for the aerogels, like cleaning oil spills, building insulation, or as a lightweight thermal lining for firefighter coats.The fabrication process is also quicker and more cost-effective than conventional methods, and easily scalable for mass production. Because of this, the team is hopeful that the technology can help decrease the damage brought about by widespread plastic pollution.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 09:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/29/3739714/3739714_0B7802838BCC43EDB673F5E26651FE93_181129_3739714_Researchers_turn_plastic_bottles_into_versatile__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8D0/57A/8D057A5BE27057BFBC19CCCD2921F9D3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic bottles, aerogel, plastic pollution, plastic waste, PET bottles, plastic bottles, recycling, plastic recycling, national university of singapore, NUS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite now has over 200 million players worldwide</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  Fortnite hit an impressive milestone now that over 200 million people around the world have played the action-packed battle royale game. According to Bloomberg, that's a 60 percent increase from the 125 million registered users in June.Fortnite is an immensely popular free-to-play battle royale game made by Epic Games, which was released in September 2017. It has since epicly taken over gamers across the globe.   The game tosses 100 players onto a shrinking island, and then pits them against each other to see who's the last one standing.  According to LadBible, part of the reason the game continues to increase in popularity is Fortnite continually updates with new skins, games modes, weapons and seasons. Fortnite is also available on multiple devices from cell phones to video-game consoles like PS4 and Xbox. Epic Games makes an epic amount of money by charging players for items like outfits and props. According to Bloomberg, in October Epic was able to raise $1.25 billion bucks from investors in a deal that valued the company at $15 billion bones.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 09:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/29/3739656/3739656_1DF24C88EA2A40FCB516B995A00D89C6_181129_3739656_Fortnite_now_has_over_200_million_players_worldw_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D4A/924/D4A92439EF6CB164D9026A5603A6A5DF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Fortnite, Fortnite 200 million players, Fortnite Epic Games, Epic Games, Fortnite players]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first tunnel boring machine arrives for the Grand Paris Express</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FRANCE  The first tunnel boring machine or TBM to be used for the Grand Paris Express has arrived.The Grand Paris Express project was announced in 2007 and is aimed at developing Greater Paris into a green metropolitan area.The machine will be more than 100 meters long and 10 meters in diameter and will be assembled onsite at Champigny Plateau, according to The Construction Index.Once assembled, the TBM will be able to drill at a depth of 55 feet below the surface at a rate of 10 to 12 meters a day, according to Railway Technology.It will be used to drill a 2.2 kilometer long connecting tunnel between the Champigny operating center and the main tunnel from Line 15 South at Villiers-sur-Marne.The Grand Paris Express plans to build new lines and open to the public in stages starting from 2022, in time for the 2024 Summer Olympics.The express is expected to carry two million passengers a day and run automated trains every 2 to 3 minutes once it opens.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 05:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/29/3739520/3739520_3AC2EB2E281B4B58B2908752AD12A711_181129_3739520_The_first_tunnel_boring_machine_arrives_for_the__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A4E/EEF/A4EEEFA8FE64C82D00CBF33E53946EFE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Grand Paris Express, France, Paris, grand paris express, paris metro, paris train, tunnel, long tunnel, paris tunnel, grand paris express metro, grand paris express english, tunnel boring machine, tunnel boring machine in action, 2024 summer olympics, grand paris express project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's beer belly was actually 77-pound cancerous tumor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DOWNEY, CALIFORNIA  A man who for years was teased by his friends for his "beer belly" is now walking around minus a 100 pounds after finding out it was actually a cancerous tumor. According to CBS Los Angeles, 47-year-old Hector Hernandez noticed that something was wrong in July of this year. For years his belly had been getting bigger, but this arms and legs kept getting smaller. Hernandez finally went to get a CT scan, which revealed a retroperitoneal liposarcoma, a cancer that begins in the fat cells around the abdomen. According to Dr. William Tseng, a surgical oncologist at USC's Keck School of Medicine, these types of tumors are usually 20 to 30 pounds, but Hernandez's had grown to be a whopping 77-pounds.  Hernandez was tipping the scales at 300 when he went in for surgery. After a six hour procedure, he came out 100 pounds lighter. Doctors are going to keep a close eye on Hernandez, but at least for now he is cancer free.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 04:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/29/3739465/3739465_7169C63594B243ADAB41E172D3B67372_181129_3739465_Man_s_beer_belly_was_actually_77_pound_cancerous_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8D2/224/8D2224B1D6FE224D76A5C5FFD051E6E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, beer belly was tumor, beer belly tumor, tumor removed, cancer free, man beer belly was tumor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man hangs onto glider after pilot forgets to attach harness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SWITZERLAND  You ever get that hanging feeling? One American tourist got a bit more than he paid for while vacationing in Switzerland.Chris Gursky and his wife Gail were holidaying and decided to try hang gliding for the first time, with Gail taking off first.As they were taking off, Chris realized that his pilot forgot to attach his harness to the glider. It was too late as they started going higher and higher into the sky.He was clinging on for his life 4,000 feet in the air for almost two minutes, hanging onto the glider and the pilot.Gursky was about to lose his grip when the pilot successfully landed them into a field, with Gursky hitting ground first.However Gursky did end up breaking his wrist and tearing a muscle as they hit ground at 45 mph.Gursky said he plans to go hang gliding again as he couldn't enjoy it the first time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 02:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/11/29/3739370/3739370_834D8DA2B1074446873FB574DB648B6D_181129_3739370_Man_hangs_onto_glider_after_pilot_forgets_to_att_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/29F/147/29F1474E1BAEE3174144FB8A160618FF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Switzerland, american tourist, hang gliding, hang glider, first time hang glider, hang glider not strapped in, hang glider not attached, hang glider switzerland, hang gliding without harness, hang gliding gone wrong, swiss mishap]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
