<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Beachfront</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 19:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese airlines cancel 176 flights over route dispute with Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI / BEIJING  Taiwan and China are locked in a fierce dispute over new flight routes, with Chinese new year travelers bearing the consequences.Bloomberg reports that China Eastern Airlines and Xiamen Air have cancelled 176 flights during the February 15 to 20 lunar holiday, affecting roughly 50,000 passengers.The Chinese carriers failed to get approval on four flight routes over the Taiwan Strait, which passses within 7.8 kilometers of the country's territorial line at its nearest point.Taiwan says the routes pose a safety threat since they come close to airspace used by Taiwanese commercial and military aircrafts.CNN reports that China Eastern airlines accused Taiwan of "violating the humanitarian needs" of passengers and their families, while China's Civil Aviation Administration condemned authorities for refusing to give approval, according to Bloomberg.But Taiwan says it hadn't been consulted over the routes, as it should have been under a 2015 agreement.Taiwanese passengers have been advised to take other flights, though military planes will be deployed at Taiwan-controlled Kinmen to to transport citizens to the main island.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 10:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538471/3538471_BC855BEA89DF448D82576B7653B772DA_180131_3538471_Chinese_airlines_cancel_176_flights_over_route_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1B6/D98/1B6D988FE4B3DA6CF17AAD6B69F8F0D0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China Taiwan conflict, China Taiwan tension, flight dispute, flight routes, cancelled flights, chinese new year, lunar new year]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombie satellite found by civilian radio astronomer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZOMBIEVILLE, SPACE  A long-lost NASA "zombie" satellite has been found by an civilian astronomer after being missing for more than a decade.A signal from a NASA "zombie" satellite, lost in 2005, was detected last week by amateur radio astronomer, reported the Smithsonian Mag. Scott Tilley received a signal from a spacecraft numbered 2000-017A, 26113. That's NASA's missing IMAGE satellite.After being launched in 2000 by the space agency, the satellite was thought long gone after scientists lost contact with it in 2005. The satellite was sent into space to investigate Earth's magnetosphere, the space around our planet controlled by our planetary magnetic field.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538421/3538421_DBAF72E8BEF24BC285D7155240BCD785_180131_3538421_Zombie_satellite_found_by_civilian_radio_astrono_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8C3/F53/8C3F5327448E4E51BBF1E8360870300E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, zombie satellite, zombie nasa satellite, zombies, nasa, lost nasa satellite, nasa satellite, IMAGE satellite, zuma satellite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man visiting family in hospital, gets sucked right into MRI scanner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MUMBAI, INDIA  A 32-year-old man in India at a Mumbai hospital was sucked into an MRI machine Saturday night.According to India's Indian Express, Rajesh Maru was accompanying his mother-in-law to BYL Nair Hospital for an MRI scan. Maru was asked to carry an oxygen cylinder for a staff member, who assured him the machine was switched off.Maru was asked to carry an oxygen cylinder for a staff member who assured him the machine was switched off. When Maru entered the MRI room, the machine's high-powered magnets grabbed him like a tractor beam while he was still holding the cylinder.Maru's hand became caught between the MRI machine and the cylinder, with the magnetic field making it impossible for him to pull away. As Maru's mother-in-law cried for help, he was freed and rushed to the emergency room.Unfortunately, Maru did not survive the freak accident. Preliminary reports suggested he died from inhaling liquid oxygen that leaked from the cylinder.The hospital told AFP that an investigation had been launched into the cause of the accident. Maru's family have been given the equivalent of US$7,845 in compensation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538413/3538413_4B71082059944EB3878984D6F1479F01_180131_3538413_Man_visiting_family_in_hospital__gets_sucked_rig_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6D4/967/6D49677776CC464E8E79B0D7E1EEE96B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, MRI scanner sucks man, mri scanner sucks, man sucked into MRI machine, mri scanner magnet, mri scanner magnetic field, Mumbai, India]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mounties catch cougar strolling in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALBERTA, CANADA  A Canadian cougar was sighted by the Royal Canadian Mountain Police last month.The animal was spotted in Banff National Park by mounties and shared in a 7-second clip that's been viewed nearly 50,000 times.The cougar is Canada's biggest cat and can be found in different areas of the country, including Alberta and British Columbia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538410/3538410_BE818AD654F54F3A8A4C30D9CAF23BF5_180131_3538410_Mounties_catch_cougar_strolling_in_Canada_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FFC/08B/FFC08B6E31D84862AAA43A75F20366D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cougar caught on camera, cougar caught on tape, cougar in canada, royal canadian mountain police, cougar on street, banff national park]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crazy police chase dash cam shows blazing trailer in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA  Crazy police dash cam footage coming out of Queensland, Australia shows a car towing a trailer on fire with cops in pursuit.Police say the driver drove with the trailer in tow for 20 km while it was ablaze. Amazingly, the driver survived and, according to the Queensland police service, "is assisting police with their investigations into the matter."Authorities captured the footage of the incident on the early hours of January 18.The trailer also reportedly set fire to some surrounding bushland.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 09:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538407/3538407_50879EE74BCB461FAFDD1D82632AFE56_180131_3538407_Crazy_police_chase_dash_cam_shows_blazing_traile_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/28B/103/28B103F9247B4FB6A7A61F27A82D03AB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, trailer on fire, car towing fail, car towing trailer on fire, crazy police dash cam, queensland police service, car towing trailer fail, towing fails, car towing trailer on fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater sound waves key to early tsunami warning system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARDIFF, UNITED KINGDOM  Mathematicians may have devised a way to calculate the size and force of a tsunami well in advance, using underwater sound waves.A tsunami is a series of waves caused by the displacement of a large volume of water. Waves can surge as high as 100 feet and devastate coastal areas, reports Scientific American.Tsunamis are mainly caused by underwater earthquakes and are currently detected using pressure sensors and buoys. However, the system relies on a tsunami physically reaching a buoy to trigger an alarm.Scientists at Cardiff University in Wales have found that an early warning system can be developed by using a hydrophone to record acoustic gravity waves radiating from an earthquake.The waves carry information about the earthquake and can be used to determine the characteristics of a forthcoming tsunami, allowing for early detection.In the future, the team aims to be able to activate a tsunami alarm in near real-time, within seconds of recording the signals.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 08:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538357/3538357_AD8B652A3F654B3FB3C043810DDEAEAE_180131_3538357_Underwater_sound_waves_key_to_early_tsunami_warn_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/51E/2B2/51E2B2E4598241E8AA2A86F175F3F6F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[tsunami, tsunami warning, early tsunami warning, tsunami detection, natural disaster, sound waves, early warning system, hydrophone, dart buoys, TomoNews, News]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars astronauts could eat goo made from their own deuces</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STATE COLLEGE, PENNSYLVANIA  Researchers are developing a system that uses microbes and human waste to make food. In the future, astronauts traveling to Mars will need to recycle and reuse as much as possible, including their feces, CNET reported.  Scientists from Penn State University have been able to create a substance, as geosciences professor Christopher House describes as "a little bit like Marmite or Vegemite where you're eating a smear of 'microbial goo.'"The system introduces microbes into the waste, which then break it down through anaerobic digestion. The researchers then took the methane released during the process to grow the microbe Methylococcus capsulatus, which is used in animal feed and is a good source of protein and fat. The research was partly funded by a NASA grant, as the agency looks for creative solutions for eventual manned missions to Mars.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 07:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538276/3538276_4701D1A22AD9400A9B2DBB6240C8B85F_180131_3538276_Mars_astronauts_could_eat_goo_made_from_their_ow_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5D3/38A/5D338A6E8D254A189A4848059F00A3F1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Mars missions, astronauts recycle waste, astronauts recycle human waste, Mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got $500 to burn? Elon Musk can help you out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HAWTHORNE, CALIFORNIA  Billionaire industrialist Elon Musk's Boring Company has made 20,000 very unboring flamethrowers. The Tesla CEO says you'll be glad you bought one to use in a zombie apocalypse and the hordes of undead. However, Musk added that he's totally not secretly creating a zombie apocalypse to generate demand for the device. By Monday evening, Boring had taken 10,000 preorders. That's a cool $5 million. If the Space X CEO is secretly planning to doom the planet with a real life Walking Dead, there's always Mars. We're just not sure how one of those of flamethrowers would work in the Martian atmosphere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/01/31/3538075/3538075_D33A3EEA2AFA47E883B74AF680BB022D_180131_3538075_Got__500_to_burn__Elon_Musk_can_help_you_out_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/787/FC1/787FC10F95D94F4FA90FB0E3991356BD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, elon musk flamethrower, elon musk flamethrowers, boring company flamethrower, zombie apocalypse survival, space x, tesla, mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United says emotional support peacock can't fly with owner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWARK, NEW JERSEY  A peacock was denied entry to a United flight in Newark Liberty International Airport on Sunday, reports Live and Let's Fly.The bird belongs to a Brooklyn artist named Ventiko and is her emotional support animal, reports the Daily Mail. Ventiko offered to pay United for Dexter's seat, but the airline wasn't said he was too big.  In an Instagram post following the incident, Dexter wrote that he spent 6 hours waiting to get on a flight but his human friends were now going to drive him to Los Angeles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539403/3539403_9018B7D5618D4692994F6B14063C0EE9_180201_3539403_United_says_emotional_support_peacock_can_t_fly__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3FD/CC8/3FDCC8F4374B04A40687E33C15FF8B6A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, emotional support peacock, emotional support animals, emotional support animals in plane, united airlines, dexter the peacock, ventiko]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii worker who sent missile alert thought threat was real</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONOLULU  The employee who sent out a bogus missile threat in Hawaii has been fired, while the rest of the agency is under intense scrutiny.The New York Times reports that on January 13, Hawaii residents and visitors received an alert on their phones warning of an incoming missile. The alert triggered mass panic in the state before being confirmed as false nearly 40 minutes later.The state government initially said a worker at the Hawaii Emergency Management Agency mistakenly clicked on the wrong button, blaming the interface for being confusing.But an investigation by Hawaii state officials and the FCC now reveals it wasn't an accident.According to the investigation report, the mishap began when a supervisor conducted an unplanned drill. He announced 'exercise, exercise, exercise' to indicate it was a test, but for some reason also threw in, 'this is not a drill.'While most employees understood it was practice, one trigger-happy worker believed it was a real emergency and sent out the alert.When everyone realized what happened, the worker was told to cancel the alert, but he reportedly froze and did nothing.The Honolulu Civil Beat reports that it's not the first time it's happened either. Said worker previously confused separate fire and tsunami drills for the real thing  though thankfully no panic buttons were pressed during those incidents.In the future, maybe find someone who doesn't freak out so easily?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539326/3539326_D83091EE6B214F6199E27FF479910A68_180201_3539326_Hawaii_worker_who_sent_missile_alert_thought_thr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/244/331/244331CF4CEF9CE0CF0EA2348548771A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, hawaii missile threat, hawaii missile alert, panic button, drill, emergency drill, missile alert, missile warning, emergency, Hawaii]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung enters cryptocurrency mining chip business</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  Samsung Electronics has made a chip designed to specifically mine for cryptocurrency. The company made the disclosure in its latest earnings report, the BBC reported. Samsung's foundry business is manufacturing an Application Specific Integrated Circuit (ASIC), which is a specialized processor custom-designed to mine for cryptocurrency. Mining refers to the solving of complex mathematical equations as a way to verify cryptocurrency transactions. People who use their computers to mine are given digital coins in exchange.Korean media claims the company made the move as a joint venture with an unnamed Chinese distribution firm, according to TechCrunch.  Samsung already produces high-capacity memory chips for GPUs (graphics processing unit), which are used for computer graphics but are also used to mine cryptocurrency.  According to Korean paper The Bell, the tech giant began mass producing the chip earlier this month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539255/3539255_EA8FD6022A824662B3DEB99C767A2032_180201_3539255_Samsung_enters_cryptocurrency_mining_chip_busine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B9D/3C8/B9D3C80277B1006972F877AFBE4CA957.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency mining chips, Samsung ASIC mining chips, Samsung ASIC chips, Samsung cryptocurrency chips]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows man trying to carjack two cars and failing both times</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPRINGFIELD, CONNECTICUT  Surveillance video released by a Connecticut gas station shows a man failing miserably at attempting to carjack two vehicles.The video shows 32-year-old Juan Laporte attempting to take a woman's car key away from her. However, a bystander quickly helps the woman by kicking Laporte. The second part of the video shows Laporte trying to hijack a red SUV, and his plan was again ruined by the SUV owner and bystanders who jumped into the car and wrestled with him until he lost control of the vehicle crashes into the gas station. Laporte is facing multiple charges in connection with the incidents, including carjacking and assault.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539226/3539226_553C1C7312834C7E8A21063F244F02D5_180201_3539226_Video_shows_man_trying_to_carjack_two_cars_and_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EA5/041/EA504107C45D180241F503097590C2D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, carjack fail video, carjack caught on video, carjack caught on CCTV, carjack man failed, noob criminal, dumb criminal, connecticut]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCTV video shows motorcycle rider crashing into a stopped car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOMEWHERE IN THAILAND  A motorcycle rider somehow failed stop behind a car waiting at a light.According to CCTV footage, a car was seen stopped in front of the red light like it was supposed to, then few seconds later, a motorcycle rider enters the frame and right away got up close and personal with the stopped vehicle.Little information is available, but the biker reportedly failed to survive the accident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539220/3539220_BC85D0EF2D354B5F9D18EA23AC816504_180201_3539220_CCTV_video_shows_motorcycle_rider_crashing_into__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B2D/5EF/B2D5EF09DCB36CEA0C1C7C9F24D9BF4E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, thailand scooter video, riding motorcycle in thailand, thailand traffic camera, thailand traffic video, thailand vehicle , thailand CCTV]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietjet apologizes over inflight bikini performance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  Vietnam's budget airline Vietjet is under fire again for welcoming their national soccer team last Sunday with bikini-clad flight attendants.The event was to welcome the Vietnamese U-23 football team home from the Asian Football Confederation (AFC) Championship that took place in China. After taking second place at the tournament, the young players didn't expect to receive a lingerie show as their in-flight consolation. Players looking embarrassed as attractive cabin crew members mingled with them quickly went viral and Vietnamese netizens were not happy with the 'welcome' gesture.Vietnam's civil aviation agency fined Vietjet with VNĐ[b]40 million (r just over $17-hundred USD), and the flight's chief stewardess was fined with VNĐ4 million ($176 bucks) for "neglecting to inform the captain" of the event.Vietjet said the event was just an improvised stunt by hired models which was not part of the original plan and the airline had learned their lesson.The aviation agency said although Vietjet didn't jeopardise the safety of the flight, the whole thing could still have posed a safety risk, yeah, probably a heart attack.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539197/3539197_0BDAEFF3C2EC47B88FD54EA32488D14F_180201_3539197_Vietjet_apologizes_over_inflight_bikini_performa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BD1/5F9/BD15F964D05944CFF3C0CCBC27E9DF1C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, vietjet air bikini flights, vietjet air flight attendants, vietjet u23, vietjet bikini show, vietjet lingerie show, vietjet air girls, vietjet, vietnam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots ready to battle Eagles in Super Bowl LII</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS, MINNESOTA  Super Bowl LII is here at last as overly amped Philly Bros and uptight Boston fans across the country descend upon Minneapolis. The Eagles have been Cinderellas all season and would love nothing more than to dethrone Brady and his Patriots. The weight of a city rests on the shoulders of Nick Sproles  sorry  Foles, who will be looking his cheese steak combo of Ertz, Jeffrey and Agholor. Nick can flat out run the ball, so can Brady for that matter. The game could very well be decided on the ground.    Brady comes into the Super Bowl with zero playoff chops and will be lucky if he can complete a pass downfield to Amendola or Cooks. Of course Brady also has half-man half-party machine Rob Gronkowski, but can Gronk shake off his latest concussion?    Will the white M.J. show everyone once again why he's the GOAT? Or can the Eagles pull off the upset of the ages?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539038/3539038_A189CDAA8C284A76B21DF520F7F17FF8_180201_3539038_Patriots_ready_to_battle_Eagles_in_Super_Bowl_LI_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/74D/878/74D8787BCFFEC8130A0687FD374BDF66.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Super Bowl,Super Bowl 52,Super Bowl LII,Super Bowl preview,Super Bowl Taiwanese Animation,Patriots vs Eagles,Brady v Foles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots ready to battle Eagles in Super Bowl LII</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS, MINNESOTA  Super Bowl LII is here at last as overly amped Philly Bros and uptight Boston fans across the country descend upon Minneapolis. The Eagles have been Cinderellas all season and would love nothing more than to dethrone Brady and his Patriots. The weight of a city rests on the shoulders of Nick Sproles  sorry  Foles, who will be looking his cheese steak combo of Ertz, Jeffrey and Agholor. Nick can flat out run the ball, so can Brady for that matter. The game could very well be decided on the ground.    Brady comes into the Super Bowl with zero playoff chops and will be lucky if he can complete a pass downfield to Amendola or Cooks. Of course Brady also has half-man half-party machine Rob Gronkowski, but can Gronk shake off his latest concussion?    Will the white M.J. show everyone once again why he's the GOAT? Or can the Eagles pull off the upset of the ages?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 06:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539032/3539032_5B18D9E9B85A4645A2BDCF7521412EA6_180201_3539032_Patriots_ready_to_battle_Eagles_in_Super_Bowl_LI_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B80/D47/B80D4723CE9DCB26A3416DD283A0BD6F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Super Bowl, Super Bowl 52, Super Bowl LII, Super Bowl preview, Super Bowl Taiwanese Animation, Patriots vs Eagles, Brady v Foles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens if Earth's magnetic field flips?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE CORE OF THE PLANET  Earth's magnetic poles change position every few hundred thousand years.Earth's rotation around its core generates a magnetic field around the planet. This field creates two magnetic poles. Unlike the the geographical south and north poles which remain affixed, the magnetic poles are constantly shifting.Writing in The Conversation in January 2017, scientists from the University of Leeds said a reversal of the poles could happen in the next 2,000 years. They warn such events are difficult to predict, but speculate such an event could lead to multiple poles and a weakened magnetic field.This would allow more radiation to pass through onto the planet and could also impact the planet's electrical and electronic infrastructure.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 05:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/01/3539022/3539022_BE3BA9E579894EB7A77C0017CD67681E_180201_3539022_What_happens_if_Earth_s_magnetic_field_flips__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F5F/C67/F5FC671F742FEDA3F6917A054AB8065E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, magnetic pole flip, magnetic pole reversal, what happens when the Earth's magnetic field flips, NASA, Earth, Earth magnetic field, south pole, north pole]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New cancer 'vaccine' completely wipes out tumors in mice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA  Stanford University researchers used immune stimulators to target cancerous tumors, and it worked surprisingly well.T-cells that defend against cancer often end up overpowered by the disease, but scientists find they can be rejuvenated using CpG oligonucleotides and anti-OX40 antibodies, according to the Stanford University School of Medicine.When a microgram of the the immune-stimulating agents were injected directly into mouse tumors, the growths disappeared in about 10 days.CpG activates dendritic cells that help against tumor counterattacks, while anti-OX40 antibodies stimulate T-cells into attacking the cancer.Once a tumor is destroyed, the cells move through the body to find and eliminate other similar growths.The experiment eradicated lymphoma in 87 out of 90 mice, and also worked on breast, colon, and melanoma cancers.The team is looking to start clinical trials to see if the treatment will be as successful in humans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/02/3540386/3540386_68BCBECAB8A04AD8BAA35599E59A2EC7_180202_3540386_New_cancer__vaccine__completely_wipes_out_tumors_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/808/615/8086158FB5C50BBAB146DE3970B06933.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cancer treatment, cancer cure, cancer vaccine, immunotherapy, cure for cancer, cancer, cancer cells, tumor, immuno boosters, vaccine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl security: Minneapolis goes big brother for game day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS   Thousands of security cameras and police officers will be watching out for public safety at this weekend's Super Bowl in Minneapolis.Law enforcement will be watching fans through the lenses of some 2,000 fixed surveillance cameras, reports the Pioneer Press. Around 3,000 police officers will be deployed on the day, with 2,000 carrying smartphones. Those devices are equipped with a video application that'll let officers record and broadcast any suspicious activity to a command center. There, 80 staff from various law enforcement agencies will monitor public safety across Minneapolis. According to Pioneer Press, command center officials will watch the movements of officers in real-time by tracking blue and white badges on a map. Officials will also be able to monitor and deal with most incidents within the U.S. Bank Stadium via enhanced surveillance technology.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/02/3540376/3540376_0F16E82BA3F149CABF09A4FCC3D81BD1_180202_3540376_Super_Bowl_security__Minneapolis_goes_big_brothe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/95B/632/95B63252BF5E23875F8092EC86CC9B64.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Super Bowl 52 stadium, Super Bowl 52, Super Bowl security, surveillance operation, public safety operations, Super Bowl 2018, Super Bowl Sunday,  Superbowl LII]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Town might completely run out of water</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE TOWN, SOUTH AFRICA  Cape Town is running out of water and implemented new water restrictions on Thursday.Residents are being asked to reduce their daily water use to 50 liters down from an already restricted 87 liters, CNN reported.  Officials are predicting if reservoir levels continue to fall as expected, Cape Town will run dry by April 16, which is being called "Day Zero." With 50 liters, a person could use 18 liters for dishes & laundry, 15 liters for a 90 second shower, 9 liters for one toilet flush, 3 liters for hygiene, 2 liters for cooking, 2 liters for drinking water and 1 liter for pets. Several factors have contributed to the water crisis. The city has been experiencing a three year drought. Some residents have also not cut back on their water use. Only around 55 percent of Capetonians have been sticking to their water allowance, according to South African officials. The city is now working to improve its water infrastructure by rushing to construct desalination, aquifer and water-recycling projects. If the government declares Day Zero, water will be shut off for the city until it rains again. Residents will only be allowed 25 liters, to be collected from one of 200 stations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/02/3540281/3540281_CDE88D1686664C09B063EF538D88788C_180202_3540281_Cape_Town_might_completely_run_out_of_water_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1DA/392/1DA39274A44F201AFFD5CA95E2F45C9C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Cape Town, Cape Town water crisis, Cape Town drought, Cape Town Day Zero, Cape Town water allowance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck driver drives over Peru's 2,000-year-old Nazca Lines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NAZCA DESERT, PERU  Peruvian officials said a truck driver recently plowed over Peru's world renowned Nazca Lines, causing significant damage.The trucker, 40-year-old Jainer Jesus Flores[b], was arrested after he allegedly ignored warning signs and drove over the UNESCO World Heritage site. Peru's ministry of culture said Flores' truck left deep track marks across a 164-foot by 328-foot area of Nazca lines, affecting the surface and damaging three of the geoglyphs.Various sources reported that Flores said he didn't know the area because he had never traveled there before and that he left the road to change a damaged tire, however, Argentine newspaper Clarín speculated that Flores was perhaps trying to avoid paying a toll.According to UNESCO, Peru's Nazca Lines were etched into the ground by the region's ancient inhabitants approximately 2,000 years ago. The lines cover an area of about 280 square miles, depicting animals, plants, mythical creatures and geometrical figures, and was declared a World Heritage Site in 1994.Peruvian newspaper Peru21 reported that Peru's Public Ministry planned to punish Flores with nine months of preventive detention and a fine about $1,550, but a judge on Tuesday concluded there wasn't sufficient evidence to indicate the driver acted with intent.However, this is not the first time people have damaged the site. In 2014, Greenpeace activists planted a message on the site in advance of U.N. climate talks in Lima, leaving footprints all over the protected area.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 08:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/02/3539999/3539999_9340F153288A4A84B7B60F01E9A4EB46_180202_3539999_Truck_driver_drives_over_Peru_s_2_000_year_old_N_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/27C/353/27C35372F53933AB6BC7628573A6C8DB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, nazca lines truck, nazca lines damaged, nazca lines peru, truck nazca lines, nazca lines damaged, peru nazca lines damaged, unesco world heritage site]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese scientists grow new ears for children with deformities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Chinese researchers have successfully grown ears for five children with microtia, using a procedure that used the kids' own cells.According to the U.S. National Library of Medicine, microtia is a congenital deformity of the ear, the severity of which ranges from structural abnormalities to a complete absence of the external ear.The typical treatment for microtia is reconstructive surgery, often through rib cartilage ear reconstruction, or silicone prosthetic ears.CNN reports that according to a new study in China, scientists grew ears via a biodegradable scaffold that replicates the patient's normal ear. Cells from the microtia ear were seeded into the scaffold and cultured for three months.The new ears were then implanted to reconstruct ears in five patients, and monitored for up to two and a half years.While the idea itself is not novel, what's groundbreaking is that the scientists were able to carry out the procedure successfully in a series of patients, and had long-term results to boot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 07:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/02/3539923/3539923_79044F4A6CAE4D03A2C91C0552AC4EA6_180202_3539923_Chinese_scientists_grow_new_ears_for_children_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/711/F50/711F5062752F83450986A842F949A335.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, microtia, ear defect, deformed ears, growing ears, cultured ears, reconstructive surgery ear implants, prosthetic ears, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop pulls 240-lb teen DUI suspect from burning car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORION TOWNSHIP, MICHIGAN  Police dashcam footage shows the moment a hero cop rescued an 18 year-old suspect from his burning vehicle.The Detroit News reports the suspect crashed into some trees and flipped his vehicle. The car went on fire. The pursuing officer used his baton to smash the suspect's sunroof and then hauled him to safety. The officer, who remains unidentified, was praised for his actions. According to the Detroit News, the suspect was arrested for DUI and fleeing and eluding police.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/05/3542198/3542198_8EE8ED1FE8124DD8A21E4F34644455A2_180205_3542198_Cop_pulls_240_lb_teen_DUI_suspect_from_burning_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A04/9DC/A049DCA9BD7BDE6ABE7060E0B89F067F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cop rescues man from burning car, police rescue video, police dashcam, hero cops, cop saves man, shows moment cop saves]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch this grown man scream while getting a vaccine shot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUNAN, CHINA   Footage of a man facing what is clearly his worst fear has gone viral in China.In the video posted to China's viral video site, Pear Video, a 22-year-old man in a Chinese urban management officer uniform can be seen resisting a vaccination shot. Luckily, his colleagues were there to stabilize him so hospital staff could administer the injection without too much trouble.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 10:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/05/3541999/3541999_1BF5C71A39F94E598A7BA6B950EDFCF0_180205_3541999_Watch_this_grown_man_scream_while_getting_a_vacc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F43/BB7/F43BB76DDBE197EAB9ECF822F73D19FF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, grown man scared of needles, man scared of needles, fear of needles video, man afraid of vaccine shots, vaccine shots, vaccine shots are not scary, hunan, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two dead, 116 injured in South Carolina Amtrak crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAYCE, SOUTH CAROLINA  Two people are dead and dozens more injured after an Amtrak collided into a freight train early Sunday  the second deadly Amtrak crash in less than a week.The Washington Post reports that the accident occurred around 2:35 a.m. in Cayce, South Carolina, as Amtrak train 91 was travelling from New York to Miami with 139 passengers and 9 crew members onboard.Freight giant CSX managed tracks in the area, but had dispatchers manually routing trains since signal systems were down. Amtrak 91 was cleared to pass a railroad switch and continue straight down the main line, but the switch was set in the wrong position. Instead of heading straight, the train was diverted into a side track, where it crashed into a stationary freight train.The impact destroyed several freight cars and caused the Amtrak train to derail. Two crew members were killed and 116 passengers wounded in the collision.The National Transportation Safety Board is currently looking into the crash, and will focus its investigation on why the rail switch was lined and locked toward the siding.So far, officials have recovered the front-facing video camera from the Amtrak train, but have been unable to retrieve the event data recorders from either train due to the catastrophic damage.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 09:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/05/3541956/3541956_1E7D15EB5A224096B533E16653C5F6C0_180205_3541956_Two_dead__116_injured_in_South_Carolina_Amtrak_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/670/2C4/6702C46AEB4D7AD89D12A32F5BFACF74.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, amtrak crash, amtrak, amtrak freight crash, train crash, amtrak derailment, wrong track, railroad switch, csx, diverted train, side track, south carolina train crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela actually thinks people will by its petro cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARACAS, VENEZUELA  Venezuela announced that is will enter the cryptocurrency market with its launch of the "petro," backed by oil reserves. The petro will be backed by oil, gas, gold and diamond reserves, President Nicolas Maduro said on Sunday, Reuters reported. Maduro said the government will issue 100 million tokens, each valued at the price of one barrel of Venezuelan crude. That would value the petro issuance at just over $6 billion, according to CNBC. The government said the cryptocurrency will help the cash-strapped nation make financial transactions and overcome U.S. sanctions against the country. Venezuela's actual currency  the bolivar  is in a freefall, with the nation in need of things like food and medicine.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 08:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/05/3541897/3541897_6C7C19F4E20D4A7F9FACDBF6B9B34250_180205_3541897_Venezuela_actually_thinks_people_will_by_its_pet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6CF/6E5/6CF6E5E7431013C065DC9EBAE3666929.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Venezuela cryptocurrency, Venezuela petro cyptrocurrency, Venezuela petro issuance, digital currency]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United to get tough on passengers with comfort pets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  United Airlines is getting tougher on passengers travelling with comfort pets.From March 1, 2018 all passengers flying with a support animal will show documentation showing their pet has behavioral training and is vaccinated, reports the Chicago Tribune.Passengers currently travelling with comfort pets need to show they're in legit need of their animal.  They have to give United a letter from a mental health professional and 48-hours notice of their plans to travel with the animal.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 07:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/05/3541873/3541873_E0E0D15F7BD94075930C6CF5E45F3CF8_180205_3541873_United_to_get_tough_on_passengers_with_comfort_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/47B/EE5/47BEE547DF8470860799DD2014B1B21C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, emotional support animals, united airlines comfort pets, united airlines, emotional support animals in plane, comfort pets, comfort pets on plane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa launches single air transport market</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ADDIS ABABA, ETHIOPIA  Africa is finally taking a big step towards freeing their skies for air travel, nearly three decades after it was first proposed.CNN reports that 23 African countries have signed on to the Single African Air Transport Market initiative, or SAATM, which was launched by the African Union on January 28. 32 other AU member countries have yet to join.Africans make up 17% of the world population, but only 2-4 percent of global air travelers. Flights within the continent are often inconvenient and time-consuming.But with the single air market, more direct routes are expected to open up between African countries, with lower ticket prices.The increased service will result in more jobs, and a boost in intra-African trade and tourism could generate millions in additional spending.The aviation initiative is part of the Agenda 2063 project, which aims for a unified Africa.It successfully pushed for relaxed visa rules for citizens in several countries, and is now working to launch an African Union passport for all Africans by 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 06:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/05/3541814/3541814_B4AB4DEB8E594816A57BB636583F85A4_180205_3541814_Africa_launches_single_air_transport_market_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/905/19E/90519EF70090DA068DBEAA28ACE12A70.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News,  africa travel, african union, single african air transport market, SAATM, AU, africa open skies, african airlines, free skies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow suffers largest daily point decline in history with 1,175 drop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  The U.S. stock market went into a panic attack this week, sending the Dow spiraling down into its biggest point drop in history.The Washington Post reports that on Monday, the Dow Jones Industrial Average went negative after dropping 1,175 points or 4.6%.The sell-off began after the Department of Labor released its monthly report detailing the addition of 200,000 more jobs and a 2.9% increase in wages.The robust report likely worried investors into thinking inflation would rise quickly, stoking fears that the Federal Reserve would then keep it in check by raising interest rates up to 3%.Fortunately, at least for now, those fears are exactly that- fears.Experts say the U.S. economy is in good shape, and while stock prices probably won't be skyrocketing anytime soon, they probably won't be crashing either.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/06/3542913/3542913_0B4EF41A7EDF422EA6066506ECEFB8AC_180206_3542913_Dow_suffers_largest_daily_point_decline_in_histo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/084/B95/084B95C35A438E5B77E3AEA3BF1E021C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, dow jones drop, dow jones, dow jones industrial average, DJIA, stock market drop, Wall Street, inflation, federal reserve, interest rates, US economy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collision with large comet caused ice age on Earth 13,000 years ago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAWRENCE, KANSAS  Scientists have found evidence that a huge event may have caused a climate shift that affected the evolution of life on Earth.Newsweek reports that according to a new two-part study published in the Journal of Geology, fragments of a large, disintegrating comet struck Earth and triggered a massive firestorm some 12,800 years ago.The fires produced thick clouds of smoke and dust that covered the sky and cut off sunlight, causing the climate to cool rapidly and triggering a mini ice age.The cold climate lasted for a thousand years, killing off plants and many large animal species, and causing human populations to decline.Researchers came up with the impact theory after examining samples from 170 sites around the world, with chemical signatures indicating that 10% of the land surface was on fire.Analysis of pollen levels also suggests that pine forests had burned off and been replaced by poplar trees, a species that grows in barren ground.The theory is theorized to be the trigger event for the Younger Dryas period, a climate anomaly which saw gradual warming suddenly reverse.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 11:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/06/3542812/3542812_4FA160218E6E442C8E4F2B3ADF51A34E_180206_3542812_Collision_with_large_comet_caused_ice_age_on_Ear_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1F4/B56/1F4B56B257F6147E58A8B614027658F1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, comet, mini ice age, cosmic impact, impact hypothesis, ice age, firestorm, comet hits earth, younger dryas, impact theory, extinct animals, animal extinction, climate]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should you buy a prebuilt PC or build your own desktop?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  It has been a nightmare for PC master builders recent months. The cost of building a PC has gone skyrocketed due to the craze over cryptomining.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 07:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/06/3542604/3542604_49C3CAD5ACAD40DCA5065EE83C69FA2F_180206_3542604_Should_you_buy_a_prebuilt_PC_or_build_your_own_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FDC/1E2/FDC1E2AB535144C8854C307DB592B6C7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, PC master race, gaming pc, buying a gaming pc, desktop, build, guide, graphic card, GPU, prebuilt pc, premade pc, custom pc]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How eruptions cool the earth's climate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PLANET EARTH  Did you know a mega hot eruption can lead to a temporarily cooler planet?The New York Times reports NASA is developing plans to study how eruptions cool the planet.The plan involves sending high-altitude balloons into the air to observe a volcanic eruption event. When sulfur dioxide from an eruption mixes with airborne water vapor, the two create aerosols that reflect sunlight.In 1991, a volcanic eruption in the Philippines sent 20 million tons of sulfur dioxide planet's atmosphere. As a result, global temperatures cooled by one degrees centigrade.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 02:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/06/3542424/3542424_8B73AE4DF14F47F0AA8E7EC884E0ABFD_180206_3542424_How_eruptions_cool_the_earth_s_climate_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A1D/3EC/A1D3ECEFD0DA1AD045611033F9A8BBE7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, volcanoes and global warming, volcanoes, how volcanoes cool the climate, climate change and eruptions, volcanoes and climate change, nasa, volcano research]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman restrained with duct tape and zip ties after storming cockpit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHARLOTTE, NORTH CAROLINA  Federal authorities arrested a passenger last Wednesday after she charged the plane's cockpit and attacked crew members. The incident took place when an American Airlines flight from Dallas/Fort Worth was preparing to land in Charlotte. That is when 36-year-old Charlene Harriott suddenly bolted toward the cockpit and ignored flight attendants' instructions to sit down.The flight attendants chased after Harriot and then restrained her with duct tape and zip ties in the first-class section of the plane. While restrained, Harriot became even more violent and BIT one flight attendant in the arm and kicked another.Harriott was held in the Mecklenburg County Jail on three counts of assault and battery. On Thursday a federal judge reportedly ordered her to remain in custody until a detention hearing next week.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 11:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/07/3543853/3543853_FB561F05908F4419B077EC8C75AA6728_180207_3543853_Woman_restrained_with_duct_tape_and_zip_ties_aft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B94/2A7/B942A726D34E48F2B92C781518BF7104.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, american airlines passenger restrained, american airlines passenger video, american airlines passenger crazy, airlines passenger restrained, airlines passenger arrested, duct tape and zip lines, American Airlines video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PepsiCo backpedals after head honcho slammed for 'Lady Doritos'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PURCHASE, NEW YORK  PepsiCO's head honcho has suggested women needed a less fun version of Doritos  all the better to quietly snack in public with.CEO Indra Nooyi said during a Freaknomics podcast episode that unlike men, women don't like to crunch when they eat their chips, according to the Huffington Post.You'd be hard pressed to find women willing to stuff their faces with Doritos, dump the crumbs into their mouths, or even lick their fingers.But fret not, ladies, the snack you've been yearning for is finally here.Introducing Lady Doritos  they're like normal Dorito chips, except soggy and stale, for more ladylike munching. It even comes in a tiny bag to fit right in your purse.With chips to keep women silent, a female Colonel Sanders, and BIC pens designed for a lady's grip, who the heck needs equal rights...said no woman ever.Needless to say, people were pissed. The Lady Dorito backlash on Twitter alone was massive and pretty hilarious. And with Indra Nooyi probably number one on every feminist's hitlist, PepsiCo has now backpedaled to say Doritos for her was never a thing. Let's hope it stays that way.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 10:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/07/3543811/3543811_20FB4AE439854484AE9C3E92DBE0A817_180207_3543811_PepsiCo_backpedals_after_head_honcho_slammed_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1E7/B6D/1E7B6DCB404746B8AB7516E9AD310E12.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, lady doritos, doritos for her, doritos for women, lady friendly doritos, women friendly doritos, junk food, snacks, doritos, indra nooyi, pepsico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla to help South Australia build world's largest virtual power plant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH AUSTRALIA  After building the world's largest battery a year ago, Elon Musk is and the Aussies are now moving on to a virtual power plant.The South Australia government has announced plans to install rooftop solar panel systems and Tesla Powerwall-2 batteries in 50,000 residential homes over the next four years.The equipment generate power and provide electricity for each home, while collectively forming a virtual power plant with a 250-megawatt capacity.Any excess energy will feed into the main power grid, to be used to supply electricity to other homes, or during an emergency.Participants will still need to pay for any electricity they use, but will save 30% on their electric bill. Their homes will also be protected from blackouts.The first trial for the project is currently ongoing, with systems being installed at Housing Trust homes first, before being offered to other South Australian households.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 10:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/07/3543771/3543771_2D81CB75DE87463F9CC2D6EA43D68E9D_180207_3543771_Tesla_to_help_South_Australia_build_world_s_larg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DC1/4A4/DC14A414D9CA4111B969916587D41895.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, virtual power plant, solar power, power plant, power grid, world's largest, Tesla, South Australia, solar panels, powerwall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan 6.4-magnitude quake leaves at least 2 dead, 198 injured</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUALIEN, TAIWAN  A 6.4-magnitude earthquake off the eastern coast of Taiwan has left at least two people dead and more than 200 injured.  The quake struck at 11:50 local time 18.3 km off the coast from Hualien, at a depth of 10 kilometers, according to the Taiwan's Central Weather Bureau.  At least five buildings have collapsed, two bridges are closed and sections of two highways have been temporarily closed to traffic, the Taiwan News reported. Around 40,000 homes are without water. The basement and ground floor of the 10-story Marshal Hotel collapsed after the quake. One staff member was rescued, while two others are still trapped. Government agencies and the army have been called in for emergency rescues.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 09:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/07/3543751/3543751_2DF78D4D99C84D8FB7CBC3A097E327DD_180207_3543751_Taiwan_6_4_magnitude_quake_leaves_at_least_2_dea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CC7/8AC/CC78ACF3F71C4538A4F6968F26D15B25.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Taiwan earthquake, Hualien earthquake, building collapse, bridges closed, emergency responders]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers find Mayan mega city</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTHEASTERN GUATEMALA  A team of archaeologists have visualized an ancient Mayan mega city using laser scanning.National Geographic reports that researchers have uncovered an the 800 square mile settlement in northern Guatemala.Archaeologists used light detection and ranging technology, more commonly called LiDAR, to uncover the area. According to the National Ocean Service LiDAR is a remote sensing method use a combination of light, aircraft and pulse lasers to measure and visualize 3D structures.This let them remove the surrounding environment to show the scale of the interconnected area. Researcher found some 60,000 structures and said the area was home to millions of people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 08:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/07/3543646/3543646_9E72DEED19FC47C59F8872285C3F3B86_180207_3543646_Researchers_find_Mayan_mega_city_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/587/2BC/5872BCC562374353899B461EE5EDFC00.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, mayan city, guatemala, Ancient Mayan city found in jungle, mayan city found, liDAR technology, mayan civilization, mayan documentary, ancient civilization found, ancient cities]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed cops locked in 45-minute standoff with cuddly stuffed tiger</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PETERHEAD, SCOTLAND  Armed cops engaged in a standoff with what they thought was a wild animal, only to realize it was nothing more than a cuddly toy.According to the North East Police Division, the hullabaloo started last Saturday night in Peterhead, Scotland, when a farmer spotted what appeared to be a vicious tiger in his cowshed, and called the cops.Photos of the animal were shown to an expert sergeant, who confirmed that it was totally, definitely, a 100% real tiger. Several police units and a dog handler sent to the farm to tackle the wild beast even nervously reported that its ears were twitching and that it seemed well-fed.Let's just say that tiger was definitely stuffed  literally, as the cops and the farmer soon found out.Fortunately, everyone was a good sport about the whole incident. Though neither the cops nor the farmer have any clue as to who set up the prank.No one seems that concerned either, and netizens seem to be enjoying poking fun at the police for once.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 11:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544763/3544763_B7AE430F400146E492B47B8D761BCC15_180208_3544763_Armed_cops_locked_in_45_minute_standoff_with_cud_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1F8/E04/1F8E0466178A4DB3B4B89DD42785A374.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, tiger, stuffed tiger, tiger sighting, tiger on farm, cuddly toy tiger, false alarm, prank, joke, tiger prank]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Reports finds smart TVs are easily hackable</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YONKERS, NEW YORK  Smart TVs from Samsung and TCL were shown to be vulnerable to hacking exploits, according to an investigation by Consumer Reports.The publication says it tested sets from Sony, Samsung, LG, TCL Roku and Vizio against hacks. They discovered exploits in Samsung and TLC Roku Smart televisions. Consumer Reports found that the hackers could gain remote control of the television and play videos, adjust volume, install apps and disconnect it from the Wi-Fi network.  In a blog post, Roku said the publication "got it wrong" and said there was "no security risk." Samsung told Consumer Reports they were evaluating the issue.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 09:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544619/3544619_33E58476391640F3BF2CCBD94EF94625_180208_3544619_Consumer_Reports_finds_smart_TVs_are_easily_hack_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/571/74E/57174E437F0E4FE4847ECEB7ECD14DC8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, hacking into smart tv, smart tv hack, tv hack 2018, consumer reports tv hack, samsung tv hack, roku tv hack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food may influence cancer spread</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, ENGLAND  New research has found that breast tumors in mice struggled without the nutrient asparagine in their diets. The study, published in the journal Nature, looked at mice with an aggressive form of breast cancer. Asparagine is found in asparagus, poultry, seafood and many other foods, according to the BBC. It is an amino acid, a key building block of protein. Scientists from the Cancer Research UK Cambridge Institute found that when mice were given a low-asparagine diet or asparagine blocking drugs, tumor growth struggled in the mice. "In the future, by modifying a patient's diet or by using drugs that change the way that tumor cells can access these nutrients we hope to improve outcomes in therapy," said Prof. Greg Hannon, the BBC reported. Cancer tumors become deadly when the cancer spreads throughout the body (metastasises). Cancer cells need to go through considerable changes before they can spread throughout the body. Researchers believe it is this process for which asparagine is needed, however further studies are needed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 07:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544481/3544481_B7FE97FB88D94B3998EAFF385393E4E0_180208_3544481_Food_may_influence_cancer_spread_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4E4/BAE/4E4BAE1F565A4BE89949514DF7A42DC9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cancer, cancer growth, breast cancer, asparagine, cancer research, cancer tumors]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea may be behind Coincheck cryptocurrency heist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  Someone managed to pull off the world's biggest cryptocurrency heist last month, and surprise, surprise, the North Koreans might be involved.Reuters reports that on January 26, $530 million worth of virtual coins were stolen from Tokyo cryptocurrency exchange Coincheck, affecting 260,000 customers.South Korea's National Intelligence Agency told lawmakers on Monday that it's possible North Korean hackers are behind the theft.It probably isn't the reclusive regime's first crypto crime either, as they're believed to have masterminded quite a number of attacks in recent years, according to Bloomberg.UN Sanctions blocking the North's exports have led to a trade deficit, and experts believe the pariah state is turning to cryptocurrency to get cash.Pyongyang hackers had previously targeted the South's cryptocurrency exchanges in 2017, reportedly stealing 26 billion won through malicious codes in emails and bogus forms.South Korea currently has no evidence to prove the North's involvement, but is now working with international authorities to look into the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 06:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544445/3544445_1E2FD4FA486C4435A6006F401BC88EB2_180208_3544445_North_Korea_may_be_behind_Coincheck_cryptocurren_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/836/EC3/836EC35E339E4F7F878E13A584C7E9AA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency heist, coincheck, coincheck heist, virtual currency, north korea, japan cryptocurrency, XEM, NEM, hackers, north korean hackers, Kim jong un]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tests out land-based missile interceptor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China's Defence Ministry this week said that the country had conducted a successful test of a land-based anti-missile system.Missiles launched from land-based midcourse defense systems are designed to intercept incoming projectiles over Earth, reported the Asia Times. These are launched after the incoming projectile is tracked by satellite and radar systems. The Ministry of Defence said this week's land-based midcourse defense systems test wasn't directed at any country, reported Chinese state-run media outlet the Global Times.The U.S., along with the UK, France, Russia, India, North Korea and China are all reported to have intercontinental ballistic missiles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 06:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544414/3544414_1FA43FB0984E464C8076AB34090863C0_180208_3544414_China_tests_out_land_based_missile_interceptor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D05/59F/D0559FED2CBD43119FAC3990AC63A764.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, anti missile defence system, china icbm, icbm defense system, icbm defense system test, missile defense system china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese gamer left paralyzed after gaming for over 20 hours</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHEJIANG, CHINA  A Chinese gamer was recently left paralyzed from his waist down after playing games for 20 hours at a cyber café in China's Zhejiang province.According to China's viral news site, QQ, the gamer started the marathon session in the evening of January 27 till the afternoon the next day. He only realised he could not move his legs when he tried to get up from his chair to go to the toilet. Despite the condition he was in, the gamer begged his buddy to complete the unfinished game while being wheeled away, sigh.In a report conducted by South China Morning Post, China currently has about 565 million gamers, and in 2008 the country has officially declared 'internet addiction' a clinical disorder, which could result in addicts being confined to video game boot camps until the addiction is completely wiped out.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 06:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544408/3544408_0AE06FB85EF04FA7B6EFC6D60D0E2786_180208_3544408_Chinese_gamer_left_paralyzed_after_gaming_for_ov_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/13E/9B0/13E9B0C2CFBD400CB27ABBF664E6BAF3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, man paralysed from gaming, video addiction paralysed, video addiction, video addiction story, chinese gamer paralysed, gamer paralysed, cyber cafe, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon hair dryers are burning it up &#x2014; literally</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPARTANBURG, SOUTH CAROLINA  A woman says her new hair dryer turned into a blowtorch after it shot out flames when she turned it on. Erika Shoolbred posted video of the mini flamethrower to Facebook on Monday, mentioning she bought the hair dryer over Amazon. She wrote, "talk about a bad hair day! My new hair dryer (more like hair frier) from OraCorp on Amazon.com became a blow torch on its first use this morning." When she attempted to turn it off, the flame just got bigger.The too hot to handle dryer burned her hand when she went to pull the cord out, which gave her a nice little shock as a bonus. And it made the bathroom smell Amazon amazing. Erika has gotten a refund from Amazon, which has since pulled the OraCorp hair dryer off its website.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 04:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544338/3544338_8C8E83F088C94EBCA6F6B926F77B9063_180208_3544338_Amazon_hair_dryers_are_burning_it_up_____literal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0A8/DD7/0A8DD7EC164B4E898715593A3ED9EB55.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Amazon hair dryer, hair dryer malfunction, hair dryer hot, Amazon Oracorp hair dryer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists grow hair using Mickey D's french fries ingredient</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YOKOHAMA, JAPAN  Researchers at have successfully grown hair on bald a mouse using an additive found in McDonald's French Fries.The study used dimethylpolysiloxane, an anti-frothing additive. Scientists used the chemical to produce 5,000 hair follicle germs, or HFGs. These are reportedly critical in treating hair loss.Researchers used this as the base of a culture vessel full of other materials.  When applied to to a bald mouse via an HFG chip, they found that mouse had grown black hairs within days, Newsweek reported citing the research.Details of the Yokohama National University study were published in the journal, Biomaterials. The research could help spur new advances in for hair loss treatment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 02:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/08/3544276/3544276_C0CCA9B0226042F4B3DB07545B579590_180208_3544276_Scientists_grow_hair_using_Mickey_D_s_french_fri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/72D/7C5/72D7C5EC56B8491FB68C14295A499AE3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Hair loss treatments McDonalds, mcdonalds hair loss, baldness cure mcdonalds, hair loss, baldness, dimethylopolysiloxane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber criminals are attacking the 2018 Winter Olympics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYEONGCHANG, SOUTH KOREA  The Pyeongchang Olympics had been plagued by numerous cyber attacks well before the opening ceremony, and it seems the hackers are only just getting started.As millions tune in to see the 2018 Winter Olympics, security experts warn that malicious scams and cyber crimes may be on the rise, according to the New York Times.McAfee researchers told Wired that hackers believed to be from North Korea sent out phishing emails to Olympic-related organizations, with codes hidden in attached Word documents programmed to install spyware.Members of Russian cyber espionage group Fancy Bear have also accessed private emails from Olympic agencies and leaked them online, supposedly as evidence of doping in Western countries.According to experts, the worst case scenario would be if hackers tried to tamper with a venue's electronic system, or an event's results.Currently protecting the Olympics is a team of cyber security analysts, who are monitoring any potential threats. Whether or not this will be enough to deter cyber criminals, however, is still uncertain.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 10:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/09/3545599/3545599_29ADF4A3DBB046ABBDBBA9775F9FF480_180209_3545599_Cyber_criminals_are_attacking_the_2018_Winter_Ol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5A9/E4D/5A9E4DD7C55575D2DA176529F1168518.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, winter olympics, pyeongchang 2018, cyber attack, cyber security, hackers, russian hackers, north korean hackers, spyware, leaked emails, fancy bear, operation golddragon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee shop owner facing jail time for naked waitress stunt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHONBURI, THAILAND  A coffee shop owner in Thailand is now facing time behind the bars for hiring a model to serve customers wearing only a apron.Coffee On The Go opened recently in Thailand's Chonburi province, and the shop's 50-year-old owner wanted to boost its popularity, so he came up with a brilliant idea to attract customers to his shop.He hired 22-year-old model Arisa Suwannawong, who wore just a scanty apron and underwear that can barely covered her body while serving customers. The model also did a promo for the coffee shop. In the video she basically says 'the coffee is so good, they use plenty of milk', then glances down at the front of her body, cough cough.The video instantly went viral on Facebook with over 1.4 million views and has been shared over 7 thousand times since it was uploaded last Saturday. But the good times were short lived, and the wild stunt backfired with many Thai netizens are now pointing fingers at the owner. He is also facing issues with the law for uploading obscene content to the internet. The district's police commander said the owner admitted his wrongdoing, but didn't know he was breaking the law and said it was just a way to promote his coffee shop. The owner is now facing three to five years in the slammer and or a fine of 100,000 Thai baht[g].The girls who worked there said they felt sorry for the shop owner because the shop was struggling to attract customers since it's not located in the city, and all they wanted to do was help his business to grow.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 07:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/09/3545398/3545398_11219F936E9849F3B920F02B528E5494_180209_3545398_Coffee_shop_owner_facing_jail_time_for_naked_wai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EA9/38A/EA938A187E7E415D882ABEC7DF13F4D5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, coffee shop owner trouble, coffee shop in trouble, coffee shop apron, wearing apron, coffee shop marketing ideas, coffee shop in thailand, cafes in thailand, chonburi thailand]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese cops using high-tech sunglasses to nab suspects</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHENGZHOU, CHINA  Chinese authorities have begun donning high-tech glasses to spot suspects  the latest use of facial recognition technology in an increasingly all-seeing state.The South China Morning Post reports that police in Zhengzhou can now verify people's identities within minutes, using sunglasses with a camera attachment, which is connected to a database via a portable device.Officers who spot a suspicious person from as far as five meters away need only take a photo showing at least 70% of the face. The photo is run through the system, allowing officers access to information like name, ethnicity, gender, and address. It also details which hotel they are staying at, recent internet history, and whether they are wanted for any crime.Seven suspects involved in kidnapping and hit-and-run incidents have been arrested so far, with 26 others apprehended for using fake IDs.The use of facial scanners and other similar technology are widespread in China, where there are fewer privacy concerns.The government is in the process of amping up surveillance, starting with a database containing relevant information on its 1.3 billion citizens.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/09/3545329/3545329_C4F8711D4FF74F3FBB532CD011F52041_180209_3545329_Chinese_cops_using_high_tech_sunglasses_to_nab_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B57/BED/B57BED0842CE42BF98E571825940089D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, smart glasses, china surveillance, police surveillance, china facial recognition glasses, facial recognition, crime in china, police state, police database, chinese new year]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertilizers a huge contributor to Cali's smog problem</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DAVIS, CALIFORNIA  A new study finds that fertilized soils could be responsible for up to 40 percent of California's nitrogen oxides emissions.California has the poorest air quality in the U.S., according to a 2017 American Lung Association report, according to Mother Jones. Scientists from University of California, Davis published their findings in the journal Science Advances and found the state may be overlooking fertilizers as a major contributor to air pollution. According to the study, California's Air Resources Board currently estimates nitrogen oxides emissions at four percent from fertilizer. The team compared nitrogen oxides emissions over the Central Valley with fertilizer application rates, and discovered fertilized soils could be contributing up to 40 percent of the state's nitrogen oxides emissions. Hundreds of thousands of tons of nitrogen fertilizer are used on crops in the Central Valley each year. Excess fertilizer not used by crops is released into the atmosphere as nitrogen oxides and can create layers of smog that blanket towns and cities. Smog can lead to health complications like asthma and acute bronchitis, as well as cause missed school and work days.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 06:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/09/3545321/3545321_44CFE19925BF4E00AFF4D4029ECC4F1F_180209_3545321_Fertilizers_a_huge_contributor_to_Cali_s_smog_pr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/366/67D/36667D70ECD24EF4AE433117CB393C51.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, California smog, nitrogen fertilizers smog, nitrogen oxides emissions, California air pollution, air pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key iPhone source code for iBoot reportedly leaked to GitHub</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA  The iPhone's deepest, darkest secrets may have just been revealed in what some are calling the biggest leak in history, and Apple is not pleased.Motherboard reports that the source code for the iBoot, a core component of Apple's operating system, was posted on Github early this week.Despite being tied to the outdated iOS 9, the code could make it easier for hackers to find vulnerabilities that would allow them to decrypt an iPhone.Conversely, it could also be used by security researchers to develop protection against flaws that could compromise the device.With only 7% of devices currently running on iOS 9 or older, and several other safeguards in place, end users are not at risk. But keeping software up to date is still beneficial.Apple later confirmed that the leaked source code was genuine, but has since filed a DMCA notice to get GitHub to take it down.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 07:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/10/3546137/3546137_AAFDEBBB46054970817176CBCB743F32_180210_3546137_Key_iPhone_source_code_for_iBoot_reportedly_leak_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/015/7C6/0157C61532245CD6A10293DB00CA4505.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, iphone, iboot, source code, iphone leak, source code leak, iboot leak, github, apple source code, iOS 9, apple iOS, apple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian drone destroyed by Israeli Defence Forces</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIT SHEAN, ISRAEL  An Iranian drone was shot down on Saturday morning in northern Israel by the Israeli military.According to the Times of Israel, the drone was destroyed by an Israeli Apache helicopter that engaged it after it flew inside Israeli airspace.The aircraft is said to be a Iranian Saeqeh, drone, also known as Thunderbolt. This model is based on the American RQ-170 Sentinel spy drone, according to the Times of Israel. Both models bare resemblance to the B-2 stealth bomber .]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 10:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/12/3547518/3547518_B08060AF7DE94CA2880316EFCE9A240D_180212_3547518_Iranian_drone_destroyed_by_Israeli_Defence_Force_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/183/6B8/1836B8122AE346B697DD26F247CC363A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, iran v israel, drone gets shot down, iran drone, us drone, apache helicopter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>71 killed in deadly Saratov plane crash near Moscow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  A Russian plane crashed on Sunday, killing everyone onboard.The crash ended a 440-day streak without passenger airliner fatalities, which was the longest streak in modern aviation history, according to CNN.The Russian News Agency reports that Saratov Airlines flight 703 was set to fly from Moscow to Orsk with 65 passengers and six crew members.The Antonov AN-148 jet took off at 2:21 p.m. but reportedly disappeared from the radar about 5 minutes later.The BBC reports that according to flight-tracking site Flightradar24, the plane descended rapidly at a rate of 1,000 meters a minute. Eyewitnesses reported seeing it on fire as it fell from the sky and crashed near the village of Stepanovskoye, outside Moscow.Authorities searching through fragments of the wreckage have recovered the plane's black box, and confirmed the deaths of all 71 people onboard.Investigators have yet to determine what caused the crash, but say weather conditions or pilot error are possibilities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 09:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/12/3547505/3547505_87562784DF7049F7BBFF5281222D22F0_180212_3547505_71_killed_in_deadly_Saratov_plane_crash_near_Mos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6A7/3EB/6A73EB44A6D048DDBC5E9F32B2C2FE54.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, russian plane crash, russia plane crash, plane crash, saratov flight 203, deadly crash, saratov plane crash, saratov airlines, antonov AN-148, saratov AN-148, plane on fire, moscow, orsk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon patent hand-tracking wristbands for warehouse workers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  Internet mega company Amazon recently patented designs for a wireless wristbands to track warehouse workers' hands The patent describes system that steers employees hands to the correct box. So if you're hands go to the wrong place, that wristband is gonna buzz like a TomoNews sub with notifications turned on. Now the company told GeekWire, the plan with this is to free up workers wrists and eyes from scanners. So it's totally not for track those bathroom breaks but hey Amazon's already got that covered with reports of alleged timed toilet breaks.The Verge writes the technology "seems dystopian",  we reckon it seems more Bezo-nian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 08:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/12/3547419/3547419_CBC43C8030274B71ACF02CB6854C5C35_180212_3547419_Amazon_patent_hand_tracking_wristbands_for_wareh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/44E/D0F/44ED0F79BC314ACBB603BF03DC6C603C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, working at amazon warehouse, amazon fulfillment center, jeff bezos, amazon wristband for workers, amazon patents wristband, amazon, seattle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Airlines denies telling student to flush her hamster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE, MARYLAND  A college student is alleging that she flushed her emotional support hamster down a toilet after an Airlines staff disallowed her on board with the furry critter.Back in November, Belen Aldecosea[b], 21, said she asked Spirit Airlines twice about flying with her dwarf hamster, Pebbles, and the airlines gave her the green light.Pebbles was a doctor-approved emotional support animal that helped Aldecosea when she developed a growth in her neck while at school. The student said she bought Pebbles for some company.When Aldecosea arrived at Baltimore for a flight home to Fort-Lauderdale in late November, Spirit Airlines would not let her bring Pebbles on board.The student claimed a Spirit employee suggested she either let the animal free or FLUSH Pebbles down the toilet. Aldecosea considered letting Pebbles run free but thought it would be more humane to quickly end hamster's life, so down it went, see ya Pebbles.In regards to the incident, Aldecosea is considering filling a lawsuit against the airline company. The student's lawyer said the airline denies that an employee suggested she flush Pebbles the hamster.A Spirit representative told Aldecosea that they were sorry their agent was unable to provide her with the correct information regarding animals allowed on-board, and it is incredibly disheartening to hear she decided to end Pebbles' life.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 06:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/12/3547304/3547304_ABC5E08B1B6643FC8D07D2335E2A99E9_180212_3547304_Spirit_Airlines_denies_telling_student_to_flush__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7F7/BB0/7F7BB0049B9A4B78848A9CB221DAE759.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, emotional support hamster, travel with hamster, hamster flush, hamster flushed down toilet, hamster flushed, hamster flushed down toilet twitter, hamster spirit airlines, spirit airlines incident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poacher gets lesson in Darwinism from pride of lions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KRUGER NATIONAL PARK, SOUTH AFRICA  A suspected hunter lost everything but his head over the weekend after getting too close to a family of lions. Cops reckon he was poaching because a rifle and ammo near what was left of him, reports South African website Eyewitness News.The man was reportedly inside Kruger National Park on Friday. There, he reportedly got a little too close for comfort when the Pride decided to get Darwinian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 14:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/13/3548545/3548545_6226411132294BBFABFF1371C78640C2_180213_3548545_Poacher_gets_lesson_in_Darwinism_from_pride_of_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DDA/57E/DDA57EF1A46B7256D226E4C7C2823A07.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, hunting fails, lion v poacher, poacher fails, lions hunt poacher, lions attack poacher, kruger national park, hunting fails south africa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists have invented electronic skin that can heal itself</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO  Scientists have developed electronic skin that can heal itself and be recycled to be made anew.The electronic skin is made up of a polymer material named polymine and silver nanoparticles. The device can heal itself through a combination of heat and compounds found in ethanol, according to a University of Colorado news release.Healing agent is added to the electronic skin and it is then warmed on a heat press. This process sees the broken area heal itself with full sensory and mechanical ability, according to the researchers writing in Science Advances.When added to an ethanol solution, the device can be broken down and recycled to make more electronic skin. One of the researchers told Newsweek that, in the future, this recyclability concept could also be applied to other devices like smartphones and laptops.The electronic skin has sensors for airflow, temperature, humidity and pressure. According to Newsweek, if the device was used on a robotic or prosthetic hand, it could use these sensors to handle objects.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 11:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/13/3548423/3548423_B45628FAA98E4ABB8CD1E43076F24619_180213_3548423_Scientists_have_invented_electronic_skin_that_ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/308/F1B/308F1B7E33784EB50C21508D56A87477.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, self healing skin, electronic skin, smart skin, skin for robots, skin research, robot skin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to privatize the International Space Station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA  Heads up, investors! The International Space Station might soon be up for grabs.The Washington Post reports that Trump is planning to cut off funding to the ISS after 2024, and wants to instead turn it over to the private sector.In his vision of events, the space station would be a commercially run venture. NASA won't be managing, and will be just another client.Of course, at the moment, the president doesn't have anything specific in mind, but he will be requesting $150 million in funding to hammer out the plan.For all we know, it could be goodbye science experiments and hello space hotels. Or … not, because man that's an expensive commute.If the U.S. does give up its space outpost, there's no doubt Russia and China are going to swoop in to lead the space race.Apart from Trump and NASA's new administrator though, no one else seems onboard this privatization mission. The Republicans hate it; with Ted Cruz calling the idea extremely stupid.Here's hoping someone, everyone, can stop this madness.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 11:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/13/3548418/3548418_9C98BDE6A9334D908C080A8C3D5E5900_180213_3548418_Trump_wants_to_privatize_the_International_Space_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2CD/25C/2CD25C94C7021FD8D1190CA9FEA22F50.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ISS, International Space Station, funding, NASA, NASA funding, budget, privatization, commercialization, private companies, government funding, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran marks Islamic Revolution celebration with new weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN  Iran showcased its growing arsenal of weapons over the weekend, just weeks after deadly anti-government protests rocked the nation.The Washington Free Beacon reports that during rallies commemorating the 39th anniversary of the Islamic Revolution, Iranian leaders unveiled two new homemade missiles: the Ghadr and the Fajr-5.The Ghadr is a nuclear-capable, medium-range ballistic missile, which experts say bears striking similarities to North Korean technology.It can be launched from mobile platforms, and is equipped with a radar-evading system. It's also capable of striking Israel when fired from within Iran.The Fajr-5, meanwhile, is a long-range artillery rocket fuelled by solid propulsion, that is being used by Iran-backed anti-Israel groups like Hamas and Hezbollah.The Islamic nation currently holds the region's largest arsenal of ballistic missiles, and continues to develop them despite international criticism, most notably from U.S. President Donald Trump.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 10:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/13/3548326/3548326_102F3F7CC0B145AB9A7ADA9658271F8A_180213_3548326_Iran_marks_Islamic_Revolution_celebration_with_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C26/D37/C26D372568C7780DDA414B518362B2CC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, iran weapons, iran missiles, iran nuclear missiles, ballistic missiles, nuclear missiles, nuclear weapons, nuclear technology, ghadr, qadr, fajr-5, anti-Israel, anti-US, Iran vs. Israel, Islamic Revolution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study shows facial recognition biased towards certain skin tones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  A study conducted by MIT's media lab shows something shocking about facial recognition  the systems are better at identifying light-skinned males than darker-skinned females. MIT researcher Joy Buolamwini built a data set of 1,270 faces from different countries that included a large number of females in public office.The faces included three African nations with predominantly dark-skinned populations, and three Nordic countries with mainly light-skinned people.To see how well the systems are at identifying faces, three different facial recognition systems made by Microsoft, IBM, and Megvii of China were put into the trial. Each face was assigned with a rating for skin type based on the Fitzpatrick rating system, a six-point rating system which dermatologists use for classifying different shades of skin.The results showed the systems had an easy time with lighter-skinned men, only misidentifying the gender in about 1% of all photos, with about a 7% inaccuracy rate for lighter-skinned women. The systems struggled with darker-skinned men with 12% inaccuracy, while darker-skinned women had about a 35% inaccuracy rate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 09:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/13/3548305/3548305_621A5A8E94154F2E860A38CB044AE159_180213_3548305_Study_shows_facial_recognition_biased_towards_ce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ECB/B79/ECBB791FD480189839E4189214BAB145.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, facial recognition fail, facial recognition controversy, facial recognition mistake, facial recognition facial recognition error, facial recognition skin colors, facial recognition app, facial recognition algorithm, MIT, Joy Buolamwini]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to escape from the world's fastest predators</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOTSWANA  A years-long study has revealed how predators hunt in the African wild, and what tactics their prey use to outmaneuver them.BBC reports that researchers in Botswana fitted cheetahs, impalas, lions and zebras with custom radio collars to record each animal's location, speed, acceleration and deceleration, and how quickly they can turn.Muscle biopsies taken from each animal revealed that predators were 37% faster, and had muscles 20% more powerful that their prey, but were also less able to maneuver at lower speeds.Computer models suggest that running at full speed is not in the prey's best interest, since the predator can accelerate more quickly and take them down.Instead, prey should run at moderate speeds and turn sharply at the last minute in order to avoid capture.Lions and cheetahs were found to be successful in about a third of their hunts, generally when they are travelling just slightly faster than their prey.This is because the cats and their victims are co-evolving, in order to maintain balance between each group's numbers in the wild.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 07:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/13/3548121/3548121_B1CC3A53799947A5BB66436B8E85FB65_180213_3548121_How_to_escape_from_the_world_s_fastest_predators_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7EA/314/7EA3143F4A324232B0462A44C6069728.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, survival of the fittest, predators, how to escape from a lion, how to escape from a cheetah, how to escape from a predator, prey, lion, cheetah, zebra, impala, survival, savannah, africa, botswana]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman climbs into X-ray machine with her handbag to protect it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA  A woman in southern China she joined her handbag in an S-ray machine because she was afraid it would be stolen.The bizarre incident occurred on Sunday at Dongguan East Railway Station. After putting her luggage into the X-ray scanner, the woman became hesitant and refused to let her handbag go. The overly paranoid woman then decided to climb into the machine with her handbag. In a response to the incident, train station officials sent out a warning saying no matter how clever you think you are, do not climb into the X-ray machines as they are highly radioactive.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/14/3549100/3549100_527B2ADC85924D64A8ADAE0BD6FF9B3B_180214_3549100_Woman_climbs_into_X_ray_machine_with_her_handbag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AAE/545/AAE545689C5605CD9C7F5A80FAD61FEF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, chinese woman x-ray, chinese woman handbag, x ray machine, x ray machine airport, x ray machine train station, bizarre x ray photos, x ray photos, dongguan east railway station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salon mining Monera via ad-blockers' computers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  News website Salon.com has a hot new take on how to deal with revenue sucking users of ad-block.When ad-blockers visit the site, they're now asked to give over extra computing power to help Salon mine the cryptocurrency Monero via Coinhive. This can cause users' computers to heat up. So much so, Salon's FAQ on the opt-in process has a section labelled: "Why are my fans turning on?".Coinhive software is often associated with hackers, malware and cryptojacking. Cryptojacking is where your computer is used covertly to mine cryptocurrency, but with Salon it all looks above board.Salon says the process will only run while consenting ad-blockers are browsing the site and the site remains open.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 09:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/14/3549097/3549097_07D8692FABDC4A0DA53E8ACB5BDDE662_180214_3549097_Salon_mining_Monera_via_ad_blockers__computers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D50/94D/D5094DDAF2812BFAA9CC9BFC5799B082.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, salon adblock, salon adblock cryptocurrency, coinhive monero mining, ad-block cryptocurrency, cryptojacking virus, cryptojacking malware, new cryptocurrency news,cryptocurrency replacing advertising]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humongous boar 'PIGZILLA' caught rummaging through bins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  A giant wild boar was recently seen dumpster diving in a garbage bin close to a school in Hong Kong.Finding food can be a violent event in the animal kingdom, birds feed on fish, crabs feed on birds, and raccoons gorge on bread that they find in … well, trash. But nothing to compares to this. All ye peasants, behold the very hungry, very large boar king, Pigzilla and his mini or regular-sized wild boar minions.The hungry humongous boar king was seen rummaging through dumpsters near a local school. It is unknown if the beast successfully procured itself a good meal, but let's imagine it went something like what we showed you in our animation. The video was uploaded to a Facebook page called Tu Dongdong with a caption that loosely translated says "pig king", and it has been viewed 468k times already. Wild boars are actually common in the hills around Hong Kong. The beasts can weigh up to 450 pounds and are often forced into the city to find food due to Hong Kong's rapid urban development.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 05:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/14/3548870/3548870_4EF4876BA5E24411B6BD3D55ACB8C786_180214_3548870_Humongous_boar__PIGZILLA__caught_rummaging_throu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/67E/D49/67ED4998E453B7D165CE5389F59B67FF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, wild boars eating trash, wild boars trash bins, wild boars eat from a garbage bin near school, wild boars in hong kong, wild boars videos, pig eating trash, hong kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 worms pulled from Oregon woman's eye</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRANTS PASS, OREGON  A woman from Oregon got the shock of her life after discovering what was really irritating her eye: worms.CNN reports that thelazia gulosa are parasitic worms typically found in cattle. They live on the surface of the eyeball, and produce larvae that stay in the tears.Face flies that feed off the animal's eye secretions ingest the larvae, which develop into a more advanced stage while in the flies' digestive system.The worms can enter a human host when an infected fly lands close to or in a person's eye.So far, only 10 other cases of eye worms have been reported in the U.S., with none caused by thelazia gulosa until now.Eye worms can be killed with anti-parasitic medicine, but may cause scarring. As such, patients are advised to just monitor the eyes and remove any worms.The parasites have been known to cause vision loss and blindness in animals, but fortunately not in people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 05:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/14/3548857/3548857_EB18C1A8CCAF4039AD8E850E7E3E40D2_180214_3548857_14_worms_pulled_from_Oregon_woman_s_eye_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7A1/107/7A1107CE9C28458E300BAFA671C235C4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, eyeworms, eye worms, worms in eyes, parasite, worms, eye parasites, worm in eye, worm in woman's eye, cattle worms, eye infection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAE building Sustainable City that could be complete by this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES  The United Arab Emirates' Sustainable City is located just outside of Dubai.Work on the project started in 2013, and is slated to end at some point in 2018. It is home to 11 so-called greenhouse 'biodomes' that act in combination with garden farms to create food. The Sustainable City has 500 villas and 89 apartment buildings.  According to Tawahul Tech, the city agreed in January 2018 to allow testing of driverless electric vehicles inside it. That is reportedly part of the Dubai's plans to make a quarter of the public transport driverless by 2030. Cars are banned in most parts of the city, with residents getting around via electrical smart cars, golf carts, bicycles and horse-drawn carriages.According to Business Insider, 1,800 people have bought homes in the city and  900 are renting.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 09:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/15/3549882/3549882_A40ADBDBA26D4186BF662AA2309A31C8_180215_3549882_UAE_building_Sustainable_City_that_could_be_comp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D70/F23/D70F2371DC8037A76A46051904D005AB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, sustainable city in dubai, uae sustainable city, driverless vehicles, driverless, mega projects, dubai mega projects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities that could run out of water like Cape Town</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EARTH  As global fresh water supplies become scarce, several major cities across the world could run out of drinking water like Cape Town.  Only three percent of Earth's water is suitable for drinking. According to U.N. estimates, global demand for fresh water will exceed supply by 40 percent in 2030, due to climate change, human action and population growth, the BBC reported. Several major cities around the world may also face drinking water shortages in the future.São Paulo experienced a drinking water crisis in 2015 when its main reservoir fell below four percent capacity, and also had reservoir issues in January 2017.Bangalore's growing property market and tech industry have outpaced the city's ability to manage water and sewage systems. The city's water pipes also lose half its drinking water to waste. Beijing will increasingly struggle to meet its water needs. Figures from 2015, showed 40 percent of the city's surface water was so polluted it was not even suitable for agriculture or industrial use.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 09:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/15/3549866/3549866_0E339E1461104ACD8B09CB9B2C887BFC_180215_3549866_Cities_that_could_run_out_of_water_like_Cape_Tow_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/91F/E2B/91FE2BD9E3ECF9DBCC4FEE95C6466F24.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, water scarcity, fresh water shortage, drinking water shortage, water crisis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida high school shooting claims at least 17 lives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARKLAND, FLORIDA  More than a dozen are dead after a gunman went on a violent rampage at a South Florida school.The Washington Post reports that the incident began outside a Parkland, Florida high school, when a suspect armed with an AR-15, several magazines and a smoke grenade shot at least two people.The gunman reportedly pulled a fire alarm to draw students out of their classrooms, before then open firing on them, according to USA Today.Students hid in classrooms until SWAT teams arrived and ushered them out. Seventeen people have been confirmed dead so far.The gunman left the scene and was apprehended by police an hour later, roughly a mile from the high school.Authorities have identified the suspect as 19-year-old Nikolas Cruz, a former student who was expelled from the school.Investigators looking into his social media accounts say they contained disturbing material.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 08:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/15/3549837/3549837_878BC9756FBF48158DD2FA0CFC4115CC_180215_3549837_Florida_high_school_shooting_claims_at_least_17__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/50F/9ED/50F9ED8B0BB764A488F5D567FB5F2824.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, school shooting, florida school shooting, florida high school shooting, student shooting, florida shooting, gunman, AR-15, smoke grenade, marjory stoneman douglas high school]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers find new antibiotic in dirt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY Scientists have discovered a new group of antibiotics in soil, according to research published in the journal Nature Microbiology.Researchers examined some 2,000 soil samples from across the U.S., Nature reported. The new group of antibiotics are called malacidins.The team applied the new antibiotics to rats infected with MRSA and found it annihilated the infection, the BBC reported. Lead researcher Sean Brady told the BBC it's impossible to tell when or if the discovery would make it to clinics.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 07:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/15/3549760/3549760_615D17FF77CF4000A93CAF64E029A962_180215_3549760_Researchers_find_new_antibiotic_in_dirt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FB0/702/FB0702C4CCCC44DE0C37C75A91021AF8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, new antibiotic, malacidin, rockefeller university, new drug found, medicine discoveries, new discovery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman climbs into X-ray machine with her handbag to protect it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA  A woman in southern China she joined her handbag in an X-ray machine because she was afraid it would be stolen.The bizarre incident occurred on Sunday at Dongguan East Railway Station. After putting her luggage into the X-ray scanner, the woman became hesitant and refused to let her handbag go. The overly paranoid woman then decided to climb into the machine with her handbag. In a response to the incident, train station officials sent out a warning saying no matter how clever you think you are, do not climb into the X-ray machines as they are highly radioactive.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 06:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/15/3549695/3549695_5FECB947F8F7457C80ECFAF64530AC36_180215_3549695_Woman_climbs_into_X_ray_machine_with_her_handbag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9C7/72B/9C772BBC8E0FE05F9480985DA2C03F36.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, chinese woman x-ray, chinese woman handbag, x ray machine, x ray machine airport, x ray machine train station, bizarre x ray photos, x ray photos, dongguan east railway station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake surprises Miami maid with $10,000 shopping spree at Saks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  A Miami housekeeper got the best reward at the end of a long day's work, and it's all thanks to Drake.The Miami Herald reports that Odelie Paret got on Drizzy's radar after they ran a story on her crazy daily commute.Drake arranged for some much needed R&R for the Haitian native, starting with a spa massage and a steak dinner.Paret was then ferried to Saks Fifth Avenue, where Drake and football player Antonio Brown gave her 45 minutes to grab whatever she wanted. She ended up picking $10,000 worth of items, which included shoes, a Valentino handbag, perfumes, and an 18-karat diamond necklace.Santa Drake gave the rest of Miami a second helping of Christmas too, dropping tens of thousands of dollars worth of good deeds on the town.$25,000 went to Miami Senior High School, $50,000 to a University of Miami scholarship student, and another 50 grand to a homeless shelter.He also handed out Target gift cards and toys to women and children at the shelter, and foot the bill for shoppers at a local grocery store.In other news, Drake will also be releasing his new music video which will feature all these good deeds.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 07:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/16/3550376/3550376_D12CBB3E178442B0BABA8382011AF170_180216_3550376_Drake_surprises_Miami_maid_with__10_000_shopping_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EF0/306/EF03069760D3DF920E06A2A2194F48F5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, drake, god's plan, donation, charity, good deeds, shopping spree, miami donation, homeless shelter, antonio brown, miami senior high school, music video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engine on United Airlines flight falls apart mid air</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONOLULU  A United Airlines flight turned into an absolute nightmare for hundreds of people, after the plane's engine began falling apart mid air.ABC reports that the Boeing 777 plane was carrying 363 passengers and 10 crew members when it left San Francisco for Honolulu Tuesday morning.Passengers heard a loud boom 40 minutes before landing, and were shocked to see the engine cover falling off the plane.The aircraft began shaking hard, prompting the captain to warn of a possible rough landing, and leading some people to think they were legitimately doomed.Thankfully, the plane landed safely in Honolulu and passengers were able to deplane normally.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 06:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/16/3550319/3550319_2794906E861240CAB3E02C3F55F73CDA_180216_3550319_Engine_on_United_Airlines_flight_falls_apart_mid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/76A/BAE/76ABAE116AE5ECDE32735523958C80DD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, united airlines, plane trouble, plane turbulence, turbulence, engine failure, engine trouble, engine damage, ua1175, flight 1175, flight trauma, plane trauma, plane crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New research reckons genes can point to time of death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BARCELONA  Research from Spain has found that gene activity in dead bodies can point to the time of death.  Details of the study were published in the journal Nature Communication.According to Science, researchers found post death activity in the brain and spleen to showed little change. However, they also discovered post-mortem fluctuations across 600 muscle genes.According to Futurism, the research was done via an algorithm that looked at samples from 399 people. The program attempted to forecast the times of death for 129 people.In blood samples it found that DNA production, immune response and metabolism declined 6 hours after death. Most gene activity was found to occur between 7 and 14 hours after loss of life.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 05:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/16/3550300/3550300_2CC1BFC87CE44E4588C86EAC2340F045_180216_3550300_New_research_reckons_genes_can_point_to_time_of__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C81/812/C8181297269C4916AA8572912D87139B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, genes, time of death, forensic investigation, gene research, genes and investigation, genes as evidence, forensic genes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sun will get dimmer and cooler by 2050</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO, CALIFORNIA  Scientists are predicting the sun will be cooler and dimmer by 2050. According to a study published in Astrophysical Journal Letters, the sun will cool down because of the "grand minimum," a period when sunspots form less frequently, the Sun's magnetism is reduced and less ultraviolet radiation makes it to Earth, Tech Times reported. The phenomenon comes at irregular intervals and is believed to be triggered by random fluctuations in the sun's magnetic field. By analyzing nearly 20 years of data collected by the International Ultraviolet Explorer satellite mission, physicist Dan Lubin, from Scripps Institution of Oceanography, and his team predicted a grand minimum could occur within the next few decades. They also predicted the sun will be seven percent cooler than its usual minimum.  A dimmer sun will affect Earth by first thinning the stratospheric ozone layer, which will then impact wind and weather patterns.  However, the cooling effect will not be enough to stop global warming, according to Lubin.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 02:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/16/3550218/3550218_1D7BAAC2A30F4E90B58699BC3545E5AF_180216_3550218_The_sun_will_get_dimmer_and_cooler_by_2050_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5BC/25F/5BC25FB9147FBD4A741CB178AF1FBC7C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Sun dimmer, Sun dimmer 2050, Sun Grand Minimum, Solar Minimum]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence breaks out on South Pacific Carnival cruise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH PACIFIC  A relaxing vacation quickly devolved into the stuff of violent nightmares after a family of troublemakers wreaked havoc onboard a Carnival cruise from Melbourne to New Caledonia.According to 9News, one passenger claims the trouble began over some dude igniting a feud after getting his flip-flops stepped on.The large Italian family reportedly went around provoking fights and threatening other passengers, who complained to the captain, but to no avail.Scared families took to locking themselves inside their cabins to avoid being targeted by the aggressive bunch.The violence came to a head days into the trip, when a massive brawl broke out in the nightclub. Security personnel ended up jumping into the fray, and were seen kicking people brawling on the ground, and screaming at onlookers to stop filming.The guards supposedly locked the violent family in a cabin and have been accused of taking passengers' phones to delete evidence of the mayhem.Police removed 23 passengers from the ship when it docked at Eden, though none have been charged so far.Carnival, meanwhile, gave a half-assed apology for the actions of their security team, and offered traumatized passengers 25% off on their next cruise.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 11:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/19/3551846/3551846_33B4C09F20C649A6B948B49B4686EFDC_180219_3551846_Violence_breaks_out_on_South_Pacific_Carnival_cr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B81/988/B819880851E48742E76F9481D5A3E188.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Carnival cruise, cruise from hell, nightmare cruise, cruise violence, south pacific cruise, nightmare vacation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves new blood test that could help diagnose concussions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Food and Drug Administration approved a blood test last Wednesday to help detect concussions in adults. The Banyan Brain Trauma Indicator test looks for two biomarker proteins UCH-L1 and GFAP, which are released upon injury to the brain and pass through the blood-brain barrier, CNN reported.Elevated protein levels can be detected within 15 to 20 minutes of injury. The test can be administered within 12 hours of injury, and takes about three to four hours for results. Currently, patients are diagnosed with a concussion based on a combination of symptoms as well as imaging.CT scans can problematic in that they don't always detect concussion, have 200 times the radiation of a chest x-ray and are expensive. A CT scan can cost anywhere from $800 to $1,500 compared to the new test which would cost $150. The FDA estimates that by using the new blood test, imaging scans can be reduced by at least a third in patients who are suspected of having a concussion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 07:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/19/3551739/3551739_57E8C9644FBB4A7EAECCB10686808E47_180219_3551739_FDA_approves_new_blood_test_that_could_help_diag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AE4/49D/AE449DE26935937F2FA18664CC0D04DF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, concussion blood test, concussion, concussion diagnosis, Brain Trauma Indicator test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mountain plane crash kills 66 people in central Iran</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEMIROM, IRAN  Aseman Airlines flight EP3704 crashed in central Iran on Sunday morning, killing the 66 passengers and crew on board.The plane was travelling from Tehran to the city of Yasuj, but crashed in a mountain area near the town of Semirom, according to Reuters.Aljazeera reports, citing a deleted Instagram photo from Aseman Airlines, that the plane was grounded for seven years until October 26. The 25-year-old ATR-72 aircraft also reportedly performed an emergency landing in Tehran last month, where it was inspected and its problem was fixed. According to the Independent, Iran relies on old aircraft for old parts. This is reportedly due to sanctions in place against the country.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 07:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/19/3551727/3551727_CA24BDF88A764FFABF306610F267F2F9_180219_3551727_Mountain_plane_crash_kills_66_people_in_central__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F5B/DC0/F5BDC088E2EB96BE21C98F637BD00F18.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, mountain plane crash, aseman airlines, flight ep3704, aseman airlines crash, iran plane crash, plane accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McD's to remove cheeseburger, chocolate milk from Happy Meal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OAK BROOK, ILLINOIS  McDonald's is attempting to make their Happy Meals 'healthier' and it's making people unhappy.Bloomberg reports that cheeseburgers and chocolate milk are getting booted off the Happy Meal menu, in a bid to get meals down to 600 calories.Officially, the listed kids' meal choices are either nuggets or a hamburger. But the cheeseburger will still be available upon request, and the chocolate milk will eventually make a comeback after it's reformulated to have less sugar.Basically, McDonald's just wants to be able to advertise the Happy Meal as being 'healthy' even though it's just garbage.Still, some people are shookt. Angry parents are taking offense that McDonald's is trying to tell their kids what they can and can't eat. And then there's those folks who just don't think it's right to take away an iconic fast food offering.Meanwhile, child obesity rates are soaring in the U.S., but thank god eating and fatness have no correlation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 07:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/19/3551719/3551719_CE6A63EA3BF6407AB6A233390B3A894E_180219_3551719_McD_s_to_remove_cheeseburger__chocolate_milk_fro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3E5/6B6/3E56B6EF9F247645FBFA907BBD017A8A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, mcdonalds, mcdonald's, cheeseburger, happy meal, happy meal menu, kids meal, healthy kids meal, healthy meal, chocolate meal, fast food, child obesity, obese kids]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who went missing in NY somehow ended up in California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A 49-year-old Canadian firefighter who was skiing in New York went missing, only to be found six days later in Sacramento.Constantinos "Danny" Filippidis went missing on Feb. 7 while he was reportedly on an annual skiing trip at Whiteface Mountain with his colleagues. According to reports, his friends said Filippidis said he wanted to go one one last ski run that day, but he never returned.This prompted a frantic search for Filippidis that included a helicopter, K-9 units and up to 140 people trekking through the snowy mountains in hopes of finding him.Filippidis reportedly later bought and iPhone, which he used to call his wife, addressing her by her nickname. She recognized his voice and urged him to call the police.Authorities eventually found Filippidis at the Sacramento Airport, reportedly still in his ski clothes. Officials say Filippidis seemed to be confused and wasn't able to give them direct answers.He said he didn't remember much, but felt he may have suffered a head injury. He also mentioned that he had been riding in a big rig-style truck, and also spent a lot of time sleeping. At one point he also apparently got a haircut.Authorities have distributed a picture of Filippidis that was taken in California, in the hopes that people who recognize him can help them figure out what happened to him in the six days that he went missing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 09:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/20/3552351/3552351_68FF0BD7E7254FD0B48A399574BC6B1C_180220_3552351_Man_who_went_missing_in_NY_somehow_ended_up_in_C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/62E/FDA/62EFDA78E4514D5481911A20F7E158BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Constantinos Danny Filippidis, lost man found, Whiteface Mountain, ski trip gone wrong, mysterious disappearances, fugue state, lost time memory, man gets lost, confused man, lost memory, man goes missing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why heart attack symptoms are often misinterpreted in women</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW HAVEN, CONNECTICUT  A new Yale study indicates that women suffering from heart attack symptoms are less likely to have it diagnosed properly, leading to serious problems.Heart attacks occur when blood flow to the heart is cut off, often due to arterial blockage, which then results in tissue death or damage, according to the Cleveland Clinic.The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reports that in the U.S., heart disease is the leading cause of death for women, accounting for 1 in every 4 female deaths.The study led by the Yale School of Public Health analyzed data from 2,009 female and 976 male heart attack patients aged 18 to 55. Findings show that 53% of women who sought help prior to hospitalization were told their symptoms weren't heart-related, compared to only 37% of men.Ninety percent of men and women reported having chest pains, but women often had extra symptoms like indigestion, heart palpitations, and pain the jaw, neck, and arms.Instead of attributing their symptoms to muscle pain, the women were more likely to chalk it up to stress and anxiety.They also had multiple risk factors for heart disease, which suggests doctors should do more to rule out a heart attack when presented with such cases.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/20/3552315/3552315_6EE42DD449E944379E5C1B7BAC202DDE_180220_3552315_Why_heart_attack_symptoms_are_often_misinterpret_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E8D/972/E8D972D9BF94416C9F6392EA4619095F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, heart attack symptoms, heart attack, heart attack women, chest pain, chest tightness, chest discomfort, heart problems, having a heart attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on Moscow: Russia gets set for 2018 FIFA World Cup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  The world will be watching Russia this summer when the country hosts the 2018 World Cup.The tournament will be played between June 14 and July 15 at 12 venues in 11 cities western Russia. Two of the venues are in Moscow.To attend matches, fans will need a FIFA Fan ID badge along with a ticket. According to FIFA, over 4.9 million tickets were requested for the tournament so far.The month-long tournament will see 32 countries from around the world play a total of 64 matches, with the winning nation being awarded $38 million and the iconic World Cup trophy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 08:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/20/3552271/3552271_B8AEEC0AC01D4774BE357F4D4C3F7A8C_180220_3552271_All_eyes_on_Moscow__Russia_gets_set_for_2018_FIF_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D6B/C62/D6BC625A12B94E6A8708929CED41D820.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, 2018 world cup, 2018 world cup preview, russia, fifa fan id, fifa fans, the world cup explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Tesla might crash into Earth in the next million years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  A team from the University of Toronto made a simulation of the Tesla Roadster's trajectory in space, which indicates that there might be a slight chance it will hit Earth over the next million years.SpaceX's Falcon Heavy rocket recently launched a red Tesla Roadster into orbit toward Mars.According to a new study predicting the car's future path, the Roadster will be roughly one lunar distance away from the planet in 2091. Over the next million years, it then has a 2.5% chance of hitting Venus, and a 6% chance of crashing into Earth. However, if does come crashing into the planet, it will likely burn up in the earth's atmosphere before reaching the surface.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 08:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/20/3552256/3552256_D90846EAB6C24334ABFBC455A16C0E11_180220_3552256_Space_Tesla_might_crash_into_Earth_in_the_next_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F62/080/F620800624DF4476AD4E3518BF01F68C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, space tesla, tesla, tesla roadster, tesla crash, elon musk, starman, Tesla in space, Tesla crashes into Earth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers hijacked Tesla cloud to mine cryptocurrency</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA  Researchers at a cloud-monitoring firm discovered that Tesla's account was hacked and used to mine cryptocurrency.Fortune reports that unidentified hackers accessed an unprotected Kubernetes console owned by Tesla, and obtained login credentials to the company's Amazon Web Services cloud.They gained entry to the account using the login credentials, in the process exposing sensitive data stored inside about Tesla's test cars.The hackers than installed crypto mining software, which ran scripts that allowed them to mine cryptocurrency. In order to avoid detection, the intruders deliberately reduced CPU usage and masked their IP addresses.RedLock, the firm that discovered the breach, notified Tesla of the breach on January 30.Tesla has since resolved the issue, and reportedly found no indication that customer privacy or vehicle safety and security were compromised.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 11:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3553035/3553035_C418B38F402F4E17843FB15EE42E10D3_180221_3553035_Hackers_hijacked_Tesla_cloud_to_mine_cryptocurre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/99E/C14/99EC142D1C6E4551A980927504132CA9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cryptocurrency, crypto jacking, crypto mining, monero, tesla, cryptocurrency mining, tesla hacked, hackers, cyber criminals, crypto crime, crypto criminals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How U.S. federal gun background checks work</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  How do federal gun background checks work? When a person wants to buy a gun from a federal firearms licensed dealer (FFL), he or she must provide identification and pass a federal background check, according to Fox News. Buyers must fill out the Bureau of Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives' 4473 form. The form asks basic information with a Social Security Number suggested, but not required. The form also asks questions about criminal background, mental health and immigration status. After form 4473 is filled out, the dealer submits it to the National Instant Criminal Background Check System (NICS) online or over the phone. If the NICS indicates the purchase can proceed, the gun sale can continue. If the NICS cancels or denies the form, the seller cannot legally sell the gun to the buyer. If the NICS marks the form as delayed, the sale cannot be completed for three business days. Unless a denied designation is issued, the firearms purchase can proceed after the three days.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 10:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3552964/3552964_4762FD0AE0414ADA9796795CD45E6249_180221_3552964_How_U_S__federal_gun_background_checks_work_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7BC/CC0/7BCCC0A2B671495B93F9C1326CE7E34B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, gun background checks, federal gun background checks, NICS, background checks, Form 4473]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan building world's tallest wooden skyscraper</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Japan's Sumitomo Forestry Company has unveiled plans to construct a 350-meter-tall wooden skyscraper in Tokyo.The 70-storey building would consist of 10% metal and 90% percent wood, with balconies that span all sides. Sumitomo says the interior of building will be made of pure wood, and will contain 8,000 homes.The building would use a brace tube structure system made from timber and steel. This comprises a column and beam framework, with steel braces inserted diagonally. This is meant to protect against deformation from forces such as wind and earthquakes. Sumitomo hopes to complete the building come 2041 to mark their 350th anniversary.The estimated cost of the project is 600 billion yen, or 5.6 billion dollars.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3552919/3552919_DCEDBFD1BE104CA894DD137D8BB52D04_180221_3552919_Japan_building_world_s_tallest_wooden_skyscraper_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/074/E7D/074E7DABA7704B9A868EF94D54364907.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, tallest wooden skyscraper, sumitomo forest company, worlds tallest building, mega projects, skyscraper construction, wood skyscraper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Sinabung blows in Indonesia, creating flight chaos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH SUMATRA, INDONESIA  Indonesia's Mount Sinabung started spewing ash earlier this week, prompting the country to issue flight warnings.According to the Guardian, volcanic ash had been sent to heights of 7km. If ash comes into contact with aircraft engine, glass inside it can melt inside the combustion chamber, reports Wired. That can cause the plane's blades to stick together and stall the engine.Ash particles can also become lodged inside the pitot tubes, a plane's airspeed sensors. If blocked, they may provide pilots with false readings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3552897/3552897_C980088F6DE64F0F91CEC79D23DE754E_180221_3552897_Mount_Sinabung_blows_in_Indonesia__creating_flig_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/247/035/247035FD25E842799FDD02ABFF06E866.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, mt sinabung, mount sinabung eruption, flights, mount sinabung volcano, indonesia eruption 2018, indonesia volcano, eruptions, planes and volcanoes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-sheep hybrids could grow human organs someday</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA  Researchers in California are working on reducing organ transplant rejections by using sheep and pig embryos with human cells.The team introduced adult stem cells into early-stage sheep embryos, and then returned them to the sheep to grow for three more weeks, Newsweek reported.The scientists say they achieved sheep embryos where one in every 10,000 cells was human. The findings were presented by Hiro Nakauchi from Stanford University and Pablo Ross from the University of California at the American Association for the Advancement of Science's annual meeting in Austin, Texas, UPI reported. In the U.S. alone last year, 34,770 organ transplants were performed, while 115,035 people are currently waiting for a transplant. Around 20 people die daily waiting for transplants.The research is still in its preliminary stages, but Nakauchi is optimistic that humans will one day receive organs grown in animals.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 07:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3552838/3552838_784D0C8ED06C47C48060BD0929245E16_180221_3552838_Human_sheep_hybrids_could_grow_human_organs_some_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DA1/5DA/DA15DA7FE4BC4E1DBEE8E2014D9BA462.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, organ transplant, sheep embryos, pig embryos, human stem cell, human-sheep hybrid, human organs grown animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump proposes ban on bump stocks after school shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  President Donald Trump has announced that he has directed his attorney general to propose changes to put a ban on bump fire stocks.White House Press Secretary Sarah Sanders said during a press conference, "The president supports not having the use of bump stocks, and that we expect further action on that in the coming days."Regular semi-automatic rifles require the user to pull the trigger to fire a shot. Bump stock modifications essentially eliminate the need for this.The modification absorbs recoil from the firing rifle, and uses it to bump the trigger into the shooter's stationary finger. This combined with forward positional pressure from the shooter, allows the gun to fire at a rate closer to that of a fully automatic weapon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 04:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3552721/3552721_604147AF9C124838B918B10B6E28B065_180221_3552721_Trump_proposes_ban_on_bump_stocks_after_school_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BDC/F45/BDCF456E16CC4EF290806A4EB6866470.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bump stock how they work, bump stocks explained, bump stock demo, bump stock shooting, bump stock animation, bump stock ban, Donald Trump, bump stock ar 15, gun ban]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KFC forced to close shop in the UK due to chicken shortage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  Chaos is breaking out all over the U.K. as hundreds of KFC stores shut down over a lack of chickens.According to the Guardian, the brouhaha started when the fried chicken giant dropped its old distributed partner Bidvest and shacked up with DHL, which then proceeded to fail its job miserably.The distribution mess-up meant more than half the outlets in the country were left with empty buckets, and no chickens for frying.Thousands of hangry fast food customers have had to turn elsewhere for their fried chicken needs, which sucks for Colonel Sanders.The good ole Colonel is currently working on a solution, but unless he can mass produce birds, doesn't look like anyone will be getting their 11 herbs and spices fix anytime soon.There are some KFC joints that remain open, but they have a limited menu, and the company can't say for sure when everything will be sorted out.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 04:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3552714/3552714_CBAA2767DAD84231A1080005887CB948_180221_3552714_KFC_forced_to_close_shop_in_the_UK_due_to_chicke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5BB/8AC/5BB8AC643873434DBBA482254336E1DC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, kfc, chicken shortage, kfc chicken shortage, fried chicken, fast food, kfc uk, DHL, Bidvest, chaos, chicken chaos, chickensad]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new World Cup 'Smart Ball' is not actually very intelligent</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  The official World Cup match ball has a built-in chip that links up with users' smartphones.According to FIFA, the Adidas Telstar 18 features a near-field communication (NFC) chip. When the ball is tapped by a smartphone, it'll show users personalized content. This feature is designed for consumer use and not World Cup matches. The Telstar 18 is also made up of six thermally bonded panels, each layered with a 3D-textured surface. This is said to provide players with greater control in different weather conditions. The ball's design is based on the iconic black and white Telstar ball from the 1970 World Cup ball.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 03:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/21/3552671/3552671_7546463B29754FCF9A4B3FF36DD3C86A_180221_3552671_The_new_World_Cup__Smart_Ball__is_not_actually_v_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FDA/D70/FDAD70BE74BF400DAA76B583AB3F32DB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, world cup 2018, world cup smart ball, telstar 18, world cup 1970, nfc adidas ball, adidas world cup ball]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is building a giant solar power plant near Chernobyl</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PRIPYAT, UKRAINE  Once the site of the world's worst nuclear disaster, Chernobyl is getting a makeover to turn it into a source of renewable energy.Reuters reports that Ukraine's Chernobyl power plant contaminated the region with radiation when it exploded in 1986, but is now being covered by a steel arch that will be completed in 2018.Surrounding the plant is an exclusion zone of forest and marshland, which the government allowed to be developed once the radiation was under control.Two Chinese firms plan to revive the the area by building a 1-gigawatt solar photovoltaic plant within the exclusion zone.The Chinese have previously converted damaged and contaminated land in its own territory into solar and wind farms, and hope to undertake the same endeavor globally.Aside from the Chinese project, a Ukrainian-German company has also begun installing solar panels just a hundred meters from the decommissioned nuclear plant, reports AFP.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 13:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/22/3553777/3553777_A498A3591CEC4238B04A24BCD38121CE_180222_3553777_China_is_building_a_giant_solar_power_plant_near_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DAF/B7E/DAFB7EE20AEE4E909BBE41F57604FE99.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, chernobyl, nuclear, nuclear reactor, radiation, chernobyl power plant, china, solar power plant, solar power, solar energy, renewable energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Fat&#x2019;s sis is probably carrying, S. Korea is captivated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KOREAS  The sister of Kim Jong Fatty told South Korean officials during the Winter Olympics she’s expecting her second child  yay!According to unnamed government sources, Kim Yo-jong told Seoul officials she was carrying during her visit to Pyeongchang between Feb. 9 - 11, the Korea Herald reported. Kim looked to be a bit under the weather during her visit, leading to baby bump speculations.  South Korea knows almost nothing about their dictator cousins up north. They weren’t even sure Kim Yo-jong had had a first child.Things obviously aren’t going too well in Pyongyang if Fatty needs to send out his pregnant sister to handle foreign relations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/22/3553635/3553635_F08AEFEF254D4106B5550021C69CDB74_180222_3553635_Kim_Jong_Fat___s_sis_is_probably_carrying__S__Ko_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/723/A34/723A34F14C2348C08A9925297A62895C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Kim Yo-jong pregnant,Kim Yo-jong pregnancy,Kim Jong Un,North South Korea,Pyeongchang Winter Olympics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waitresses fired for thinking they're Taiwanese</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  Two Taiwanese waitresses got their employment nullified after failing to satisfy their Chinese bosses' belief that Taiwan is part of China.According to the New York Times, Man-Tzu Tuan was asked by her boss if Taiwan was part of China. She said no and was later fired.Yating Ying also crushed her boss's national spirit when she told a customer she was Taiwanese. Ying too was fired.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 09:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/22/3553631/3553631_317880332C0D4265AD3004438D4DFE41_180222_3553631_Waitresses_fired_for_thinking_they_re_Taiwanese_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CA6/8C1/CA68C1C3CF634713928AE8C125551CE6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, china australia relations, china v australia, china v taiwan, are taiwanese considered chinese, are taiwanese chinese, chinese boss employee drama]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese 'baby factory' dad wins custody of 13 surrogate kids</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BANGKOK  A Thai court has awarded a Japanese man custody of his 13 kids after a years-long legal battle famously known as the 'baby factory' scandal.The Bangkok Post reports that the bizarre case made headlines in 2014, when cops raided a Bangkok apartment and found a whole bunch of babies, each with their own nannies.Eccentric Japanese millionaire Mitsutoki Shigeta had fathered the babies, and then some, using surrogacy. His semen and an egg from an unnamed donor were planted into nine Thai women, which resulted in the births of 13 children. Apparently, he wanted a really big family, which is apparently one way to be a 'Super Dad'.Unfortunately, because of the baby factory case and other controversial incidents, the government cracked down on commercial surrogacy for foreigners, effectively closing off the womb of Asia to wealthy would-be parents.Thai authorities ended up putting Shigeta's kids in an orphanage after the raid, while he fled to Japan and started the fight for custody.The court granted paternity rights after realizing the 28-year-old was a pretty stand-up dad, and is filthy rich enough to take care of his spawn.Shigeta plans to take his now 4-year-old kids back to Tokyo, where they'll get an international school education and be taken care of by nurses and nannies.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/22/3553513/3553513_7372B341CC0740D1BF70B6C41CC87F34_180222_3553513_Japanese__baby_factory__dad_wins_custody_of_13_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7AF/C28/7AFC28FAEE354D2D8A447A489AD8BA98.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, baby factory, surrogacy, surrogates, thai baby factory, japanese baby factory, foreign surrogates, commercial surrogacy, baby daddy, baby mama, mitsutoki shigeta]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vows to crackdown on rural tradition of funeral strippers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  The Chinese government has launched a crackdown on funeral strippers and rewards tipsters for revealing information on such performances.It has been a long tradition for rural folks in China to use local opera performers for funerals to get people to attend and show respect to the deceased. However, since the 1990s, a "funeral strippers" phenomenon has emerged in some areas of China.The latest crackdown is focused on 19 cities across Henan, Anhui, Jiangsu and Hebei province. The new campaign offers tipsters cash incentives when they report "funeral misdeeds" via a special "hotline".In 2015, China's Xinhua news agency commented that the performances highlight "the trappings of modern life in China, whereby vanity and snobbery prevail over traditions."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 05:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/22/3553430/3553430_7D965722DFB84BA78A57AC29BD2B09DC_180222_3553430_China_vows_to_crackdown_on_rural_tradition_of_fu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D62/C4F/D62C4F0DC20642FDAB2CF310616530BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, china funeral strippers, china funeral culture, china funeral tradition, funeral strippers in china, china funeral rituals, funeral strippers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss air travel concept could change how we fly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAUSANNE, SWITZERLAND  Researchers at Switzerland's Federal Polytechnic Institute have conceptualized a new to ferry cargo and passengers.The pod plane concept could one day allow passengers to borad at rail stations. These pods each measure 30 meters in length. After being ferried to the airport, the pod would join others under a giant 60-meter wing.This modular concept aircraft is one of several developed by Swiss researchers called Clip-Air. According to CNN, its speed and range would be around the same as most mid-sized commercial aircraft.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 04:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/22/3553410/3553410_2BAB5AAECB53439695C8947502B6FEC5_180222_3553410_Swiss_air_travel_concept_could_change_how_we_fly_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/57E/A91/57EA91CA550A4C23A99FC259A05D364C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, future aircraft, aviation technology clip air, pod planes, epfl, planes, future planes, aircraft documentary, new technology, circular runways, son of concorde, future air travel, aviation technology, space plane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kylie Jenner tweet causes Snapchat stocks to plummet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  Snapchat is definitely not keeping up with the Kardashians, and it's costing them more than a billion bucks.Bloomberg reports that the company recently redesigned the app to make it more user friendly, and ended up doing the exact opposite.People found the update annoying, so much so they petitioned to get rid of it on Change.org.Queen Snapchat Kylie Jenner didn't seem to like it either and called it quits Her shady tweet on Wednesday pretty much summed it up: "sooo does anyone else not open Snapchat anymore? Or is it just me...ugh this is so sad."With the Queen out of Snap, it was only a matter of time before the millenials noticed and decided to say "Bye, Felicia."The Kylie tweet dominoed all the way to Wall Street, where Snap's market value took a dive, to the tune of $1.3 billion dollars.That's gotta hurt. Guess you might want to keep up a little bit with the Kardashians.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 15:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/23/3554558/3554558_AB4272F1A88B4F4C8F096AD775AFA71C_180223_3554558_Kylie_Jenner_tweet_causes_Snapchat_stocks_to_plu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6F6/03C/6F603C09C0385B8ACAC043DC9EEE1A45.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, snapchat, snap, kylie jenner, snapchat update, snapchat redesign, kardashian, keeping up with the kardashians, snap stock market, market value, twitter, tweet, evan spiegel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA study confirms Antarctica is losing ice fast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA  A NASA study provided the sharpest focus yet on how fast the Antarctic ice sheets are melting.NASA reports that the research, published in the journal Cryosphere, used new software and computer vision techniques to look at data compiled over seven years. They found that in 2015, Antarctica lost roughly 1,929 gigatons of ice, 89% of which was from the western part of the continent.The study confirms that the West Antarctic ice sheets are melting more rapidly than those in the east, with glacier flows increasing in response to warming oceans.The area has also experienced major iceberg calving incidents in recent years, which renders the larger region of ice left behind more prone to melting.If the entire Western Antarctic ice sheet were to melt, a study from PNAS estimated it could cause a 3-meter rise in global sea levels.Scientists say the loss of the ice sheet might be inevitable unless the world can manage to decarbonize in the near future and keep emissions low.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 14:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/23/3554545/3554545_D321CD1204E14C0E8FF9AA73844AA91A_180223_3554545_NASA_study_confirms_Antarctica_is_losing_ice_fas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/13B/342/13B342A90F27C642F8FE68521AECD035.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, antarctica, ice melting, west antarctic ice sheet, antarctica losing ice, antarctic ice loss, global warming, climate change, NASA, glacier flow, glacial melt, sea level rise]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troopers buy distraught woman plane ticket to friend's funeral</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  Two New York State Troopers went above and beyond the call of duty when they paid for a woman to attend a friend's funeral.NBC reports that Jordana Judson had rushed to the airport sobbing after finding out her friend had been a victim in the Parkland, Florida tragedy, and was noticed by two concerned officers.Troopers Robert Troy and Thomas Karasinski escorted her to the JetBlue ticket counter, but the distraught 23-year-old could not afford the $700 one-way ticket.Thankfully, Troy and Karasinski stepped in with their credit cards to pay for her flight, despite her insisting they didn't have to do it.The good deed meant Judson made it back home in time for the funeral, and was able to grieve and support heartbroken family members.Many were moved by the troopers' act of generosity, including JetBlue, who said Tuesday that they would be refunding the cost of Judson's ticket.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 08:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/23/3554225/3554225_BC3AFA7B76D545AC8EEC56EFFE7B12FF_180223_3554225_Troopers_buy_distraught_woman_plane_ticket_to_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/676/57B/67657B218B884AA299820602A0E38064.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, good cop, acts of kindness, cops helping people, ny state troopers, florida school tragedy, parkland florida tragedy, marjory stoneman douglas high school]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym fanatic paralysed from neck down after sit-up accident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SÃO JOSÉ DO RIO PRETO, BRAZIL  A woman in southern Brazil was left paralysed from the neck down when she fell from an exercise equipment while doing sit-ups at the gym. In January 2016, 23-year-old law student and self-proclaimed gym fanatic Marcelle Mancuso was doing a simple inverted sit-up at the gym when the accident took place.The strap that tied Mancuso to the equipment reportedly broke and her trainer wasn't able to catch her time, resulting in her head hitting the floor.  The impact left Mancuso instantly unable to move.The injury broke Mancuso's fifth vertebra in the neck, another vertebra was knocked out of place and a third was squashed. The injury compressed Mancuso's spinal cord, which led to the paralysis. Lucky for her, after several months of therapy, Mancuso managed to start walking again, and eventually recovered fully from the horrific injury. Mancuso said the injury was like a nightmare she was glad to be woken from. She's says she's thankful to God that her life is back to normal, and has learned to value the simple things in life.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 07:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/23/3554186/3554186_E031091D32974D4BAACFF5623CC2D2C3_180223_3554186_Gym_fanatic_paralysed_from_neck_down_after_sit_u_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9CF/196/9CF196D168454C9FBEFF779392370E9B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, workout injury, workout fails women, workout fails girls, gym workout girls fails, workout injury neck, neck injury workout, gym workout accident, gym workout accidents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese woman had two surgical sponges left inside her for 6 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHIBA, JAPAN  Two surgical sponges were left inside a Japanese woman's abdomen for at least six years. The unidentified 42-year-old woman went to the doctors saying she had felt bloated for the past three years, according to a report in the New England Journal of Medicine, CNN reported.A CT scan revealed two masses with strings attached to them. A surgical exam confirmed the presence of two gauze sponges that had become attached to the woman's omentum and colon. Researchers think the sponges were left there after a C-section. The woman had received two C-sections from the same clinic.After the woman informed the clinic, the doctor still wouldn't admit his mistake, citing a lack of clear proof.  The woman had the sponges removed, her symptoms clear up and she was discharged five days later.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 07:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/23/3554175/3554175_8334FD57F78D482F9788BA39BB2BEB8F_180223_3554175_Japanese_woman_had_two_surgical_sponges_left_ins_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/816/705/8167056647274E8CB427CFC6083B07A7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, surgical sponge left inside, surgical sponge left inside patient, surgery fails, surgery mishaps]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors remove massive tumor from man's brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MUMBAI, INDIA  A blind Indian man may regain his sight after having a 1.8kg brain tumor from the back of his skull.Shopkeeper Santlal Pal had been living with the massive tumor on his head for three years before it was removed this month.Surgeons at Nair Hospital in Mumbai removed it on February 14. According to Live Science, the brain tumor might be one of the biggest in the world.They say only 10% of the tumor grew within Pal's skull, but that was enough to make him blind. He may regain his sight through recovery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 01:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/24/3554729/3554729_2025231D846741DC83D240315AE66D75_180224_3554729_Doctors_remove_massive_tumor_from_man_s_brain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/682/18F/68218F50D679A814579462D12F40EE8A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, worlds largest brain tumor, nair hospital, santlal pal, biggest ever tumor, worlds larrgest tumor, mumbai]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying taxi drone takes off in first flight test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SILICON VALLEY, CALIFORNIA  The flying car concept is a step closer to reality after Airbus successfully flew their drone taxi prototype last month.At the end of January, Airbus silicon valley carried out their first successful test of their autonomous aircraft. The all-electric drone flew at a height of 16 feet for 53 seconds by itself.According to Engadget, Airbus hopes to create a network of autonomous flying drones. The company aims to create a production-ready drone by 2020, the Verge reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 11:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/26/3556256/3556256_7261570FC6344071ADB40A4AB7FB7048_180226_3556256_Flying_taxi_drone_takes_off_in_first_flight_test_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/935/F8B/935F8BEFB5AC43F5A194F1AFA9BBE52D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, flying car reality, airbus, flying taxi drone, flying taxi drones, flying car, airbus, a3, a3 taxi drone, drone network]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy fears as Apple shifting iCloud data and keys to China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China-based iCloud users' data will be stored in servers based in the People's Republic of China from the end of February.Apple will move China-based iCloud users' data and keys from its servers in the U.S. to China. The company told Reuters this to comply with Chinese law.If a user's Apple device is connected to an iCloud account, it typically backs up such as photos, emails, messages, contacts and other information. From the end of February, Chinese authorities will be able to issue Apple with a warrant to access this data. According to Reuters, this only applies to users who set their home as China. Users in Hong Kong and Macau are not affected.The data will be stored on servers of state-controlled firm Guizhou-Cloud Big Data. Many are concerned how this will impact Chinese users' privacy, reported Reuters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 11:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-video/F58/A1C/F58A1CC3B3F6444F9C5E159AA5A9AD76" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/935/F8B/935F8BEFB5AC43F5A194F1AFA9BBE52D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, privacy in china, china privacy, apple icloud china, apple moves icloud to china, china data centers, apple, apple in china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists uncover ancient necropolis in Egypt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINYA, EGYPT  An Egyptian mission has found an ancient necropolis south of Cairo containing several tombs, artifacts, and a fully preserved mummy.Reuters reports that archaeologists at the Tuna Al-Gabal site near Minya, Egypt uncovered a large number of burial shafts believed to be more than 2,000 years old.The mummified remains of a high priest of the Egyptian god Thoth were unearthed in the tombs, along with 1,000 figurines and four canopic jars made of alabaster.The team also found 40 limestone sarcophagi of various shapes and sizes, which may have belonged to the priest's family members.Excavation on the site began in late 2017 and is expected to continue on for at least five years.Egypt is planning to use the recent discoveries to revive tourism in the area, which was a popular destination for antiquities sightseeing until the political turmoil in 2011.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 08:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/26/3556125/3556125_53F9995DFB1C417CBE3DE8DD6C089A5C_180226_3556125_Archaeologists_uncover_ancient_necropolis_in_Egy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2B1/0C5/2B10C58126A041ADB5FA6659907C01F9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, necropolis, egypt necropolis, ancient necropolis, ancient burial, egyptian tomb, tomb, cemetery, archaeologists, thoth, mummy, sarcophagus, egypt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient archaeological site facing pollution threat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YUCATAN PENINSULA, MEXICO The world's largest underwater archaeological site could be under threat from pollution.Speaking to British newspaper The Telegraph, archaeologist Guillermo de Anda said that the Sac Actun cave system in the Yucatan Peninsula maybe under threat from pollution and development. Many tourists use sinkholes the caves for snorkeling, The Telegraph reported.Reuters reports researchers recently found a network of 248 sinkholes throughout the 216 mile system. They also discovered 9,000 year-old human remains, as well bones of a giant sloth and ancient elephant.The discovery could help provide new information on the ancient Mayan civilization.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 08:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/26/3556102/3556102_7268C3A78A3E43C08FA458F4301CA68F_180226_3556102_Ancient_archaeological_site_facing_pollution_thr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D68/46E/D6846E4580334675B33442D303FD7D06.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, great mayan quifer project, underwater archaeological site, mayan civilization, yucatan peninsula, guillermo de anda]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets himself stuck in socket wrench</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWPORT, WALES  Not really sure how people in the UK use socket wrenches, but this tool from Wales actually got his nuts and bolts stuck in one.  This do-it-yourselfer from Newport, Wales really did it to himself. Once he and his tool became attached, the tool started to get a bit too clingy, so the handyman was forced to call 911. After emergency crews arrived, they went to work freeing the man's tool from his little boxes. Firefighters even sent out a warning over Twitter afterwards. Naturally Twitter responded the way you would expect Twitter to respond.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 07:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/26/3556020/3556020_B46F51B8699D41C184A16C4478E3703D_180226_3556020_Man_gets_himself_stuck_in_socket_wrench_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/863/5FB/8635FB4C7EE54880AB6DC043D99A3722.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, man stuck on wrench, stuck on wrenches, trapped by tool, wrenches and ratchets, what not to do with wrenches, socket wrench, socket wrench how to use]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spends 10 years tattooing himself black</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRIGHTON, UK  A body modification artist has spent the last ten-years transforming himself and now sports almost entirely black skin, dyed eyeballs and implant stretchers in his nose and lip.Eli Ink is a 27-year-old tattoo artist from Brighton England who became obsessed with body mods at a young age after seeing his uncle's tribal tattoo.Inspired by Picasso and abstract painting, the body modification artist wanted to look like an abstract character in one of Picasso's paintings, so he covered most of the outside of his body with layers of black ink, and he has also tattooed the inside of his mouth and his eyeballs.Besides the ink, the tattoo artist has A LOT of piercings and massive stretchers in either side of his nose and bottom lip. However, the artist's girlfriend said that the artist's body is still a work in progress that he is gonna spend his whole life to 'perfecting his work'.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 08:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/27/3556816/3556816_8B429D1DD2494368851AABA6F032C234_180227_3556816_Man_spends_10_years_tattooing_himself_black_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B59/B01/B59B01598ABC4D01BADFDC16AA42E181.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, body modification, body modification artist, body modification enthusiast, body modifications extreme, body modification piercings, body modification tag, body modifications video, body modification implants, Eli Ink]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Japanese drug can kill flu virus in one day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OSAKA, JAPAN  The Japanese health ministry has approved a groundbreaking new drug that can get rid of the flu in just one day.Nikkei reports that Osaka-based pharmaceutical company Shionogi has been cleared to manufacture and market its new drug Xofluza, which could rival Tamiflu, made by Swiss drugmaker Roche. The influenza virus causes an infection in the respiratory tract when it is transmitted. The virus hijacks the cells to make copies of itself, which then burst forth and infect other cells.Antivirals like Tamiflu are taken in multiple doses over several days, and stop the virus by binding to a coating on its surface to inhibit its ability to escape an infected cell.The new drug Xofluza requires a single pill, and suppresses virus replication by targeting an enzyme.During trials, the drug was shown to eliminate the flu virus in 24 hours, compared to three days using Tamiflu.Xofluza was approved in just four months under Japan's fast-track drug review system, and is set to go on sale once a price is determined by the government.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 07:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/27/3556790/3556790_EB2BC272233D4D92B2DDA7F731A53F84_180227_3556790_New_Japanese_drug_can_kill_flu_virus_in_one_day_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E71/755/E717558ACF294F23ADC45BF9700BDA53.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, flu, flu outbreak, flu epidemic, flu medicine, cure for flu, flu cure, tamiflu, xofluza, flu pill, japan, shionogi, medicine, medical]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX competitor aiming for 70% cheaper rocket launches</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CENTENNIAL, COLORADO  SpaceX rival United Launch Alliance has plans to drop rocket launch costs to below $100m, according to Business Insider.The company, formed by Lockheed Martin and Boeing, aims to launch their Vulcan rocket by the mid 2020s at a rate 70 percent cheaper of the current cost. That's around $400m, according to Time.The rocket's detachable boosters are autonomous and use an inflatable aeroshell to re-enter Earth's atmosphere. After deploying a parachute, the booster is caught in mid-air by a helicopter and taken back for re-use. The upper stage of the Vulcan rocket is fueled by cryogenic hydrogen and oxygen. These are more adaptable to the elements of space than rocket-grade RP-1 kerosene, according to Business Insider.  This can be left in orbit where it can be refueled and used for other space-based missions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 07:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/27/3556754/3556754_DCC416803B324EDF85EF714DC4ED5805_180227_3556754_SpaceX_competitor_aiming_for_70__cheaper_rocket__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D66/E0E/D66E0E7BB32C4AE59C242633FE4CD01A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, spacex v ula, elon musk, boeing v spacex, lockheed martin spacex, united launch alliance, cheaper space travel, reusable rockets]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX fires two broadband 'Starlink' satellites into orbit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANDENBERG AIR BASE, CALIFORNIA  SpaceX last week launched two demonstration broadband internet satellites.On  Feb. 22 2018, the company launched the PAZ radar imaging satellite for a Spanish government satellite operator. Also onboard the rocket manifest for that launch was 2 of their demo satellites, dubbed Microsat-2a and Microsat-2b. Those are part of the SpaceX's planned Starlink broadband satellite network that will reportedly comprise a mesh of around 12,000 satellites orbiting the Earth.According to the BBC, this network would provide internet to regions needing it the most. However it could also put SpaceX in competition with the telecom companies.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/02/27/3556748/3556748_0E6782F71F4A4E8EA3A45D09809152B6_180227_3556748_SpaceX_fires_two_broadband__Starlink__satellites_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/885/AF8/885AF8B773E74F559ACF39AA033AB634.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, SpaceX internet plan, spacex launch, spacex starlink, starlinks, space based internet, elon musk internet, elon musk internet plans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
