<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Beachfront</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 19:30:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers have discovered a 'monster black hole'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Researchers have discovered a massive black hole 15,000 light years from Earth in the Milky Way Galaxy.Professor Liu Jinfeng at the Chinese Academy of Sciences said in a press release that the stellar black hole named LB-1 is so large that "it should not even exist in our galaxy."According to the international research team, the "monster black hole" has a mass that is 70 times greater than the mass of the sun.The discovery comes as a surprise as scientists had previously estimated the mass of most stellar black holes in our galaxy at less than 20 times the sun's mass.Scientists spotted LB-1 by looking for stars that circle a black hole. LB-1's companion has eight times the mass of the sun and circles the black hole every 79 days.The international team credits China's Large Sky Area Multi-Object Fiber Spectroscopic Telescope for making the discovery.The Gran Telescopio Canarias in Spain and the Keck I telescope in the U.S. then determined the physical parameters of LB-1 and its companion star.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929614/3929614_97D4AE8E39A34F3894261E91CECCD29F_191202_3929614_Researchers_have_discovered_a__monster_black_hol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EB9/241/EB924193826C79F6B8AA5D55ABADEC77.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Black hole, monster black hole, stellar black hole, LB-1, LB1, milky way galaxy, galaxy, Chinese Academy of Sciences, LAMOST, China, space, astronomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine man shot dead by his own home booby trap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VAN BUREN, MAINE  A man in Maine lost his life after getting shot by his own home booby trap.According to the Van Buren Police Department, Ronald Cyr called 911 on Thanksgiving night saying he'd been shot.The cops who arrived at his home to provide medical assistance discovered that the front door had been rigged with a homemade booby trap.65-year-old Cyr had apparently designed it so a handgun would fire should anyone try and enter the door, which a friend later said was because he had been "robbed too many times."Problem is, Cyr then unintentionally triggered the device and ended up getting shot himself, according to the police investigation.He was taken to the hospital, but ended up succumbing to his injuries.Police later found other unknown devices inside the home, which prompted them to contact the state bomb squad.The Washington Post reports that although Maine law allows the use of deadly force against home intruders in certain cases, it's illegal to use booby traps to defend property.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929608/3929608_A99A06B48C7D497E80011508E2CF8A33_191202_3929608_Maine_man_shot_dead_by_his_own_home_booby_trap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BC0/21D/BC021DD60DA699DF079572EE20713898.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Booby trap, rigged handgun, booby trap fail, man dies from own booby trap, home intruder device, home protection device, handmade device, ronald cyr, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman hit by train after falling onto tracks talking on her phone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  A 28-year-old woman had an up close and personal meet and greet with a train in the Windy City after she ended up on the tracks. ABC News reports that according to a Chicago police spokesperson, the really intelligent woman, who was not identified, was talking on her cellphone when she fell onto the tracks.  The Chicago Sun Times reports that the boneheaded incident happened at 9:25 a.m. at the 328 S. Dearborn St. station.   Police initially said the woman accidentally fell backward onto the tracks, but after reviewing surveillance video footage said it looked like she appeared to step forward onto them. Authorities say initial eyewitness statements did not match the footage captured at the station. Luckily for the absent-minded woman, the Blue Line train was able to stop in time, but not before giving her a bit of a love tap.Windy City boys in blue say she was found partially under the lead car of the train.  Officials say the woman was then transported to Northwestern Memorial Hospital in critical condition.  According to the Chicago Transit Authority, Blue Line service was partially suspended for about an hour after the incident. Service was back to normal by midafternoon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 12:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929528/3929528_9A194F8DA1F943E1B36FE0BBFC04EFB0_191202_3929528_Woman_hit_by_train_after_falling_onto_tracks_tal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/490/368/490368B06296AC703F696766040918B3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Woman on phone, woman falls on train tracks, woman hit by train, woman survives hit by train, Chicago woman falls on train tracks, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA unveils lunar lander for future missions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA has unveiled designs for a medium-sized lunar lander that would be able to carry payloads that weigh up to 300 kilograms to the moon's polar regions.Payloads may include scientific instruments, a robotic rover and even a ramp for the rover.The lander will include a thermal control system, an electrical power subsystem and a navigation system with Terrain-Relative Navigation.Its metal structure will house a solid rocket motor to allow the lander to brake on arrival to the moon and a liquid propulsion system to facilitate landing on the moon's surface.The lander will take three to six days to reach the moon and will be sent via a commercial launch vehicle.As the lander makes its way to the moon, solar panels on its surface will supply power to batteries on the lander. This will help power the rover once the lander has descended to the moon's surface, and allow it to explore the lunar environment for up to six hours. The mission is part of NASA's plan to establish a permanent base on the moon.The ultimate goal is to prepare humans to make their way from the moon to the red planet in order to make human exploration of Mars a reality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 12:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929517/3929517_62906788F4A24774A52900620F9808A0_191202_3929517_NASA_unveils_lunar_lander_for_future_missions_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/933/3BA/9333BA6633F02F0B68E3B500260BF9E3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Space exploration, nasa space exploration, nasa lunar lander concept, nasa Commercial Lunar Payload Services, robotic lunar lander, nasa robotic lunar lander, NASA moon mission, nasa lunar mission, NASA missions, NASA mission preparation,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon forest fires could make glaciers melt faster in the Andes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH AMERICA  The fires burning in the Amazon rainforests are accelerating the melting of Andean glaciers, according to a study Nature published on November 28.Brazilian scientists at the Rio de Janeiro State University report that smoke from the fires are carrying black carbon as far as the Zongo Glacier in Bolivia.The study focused on the Zongo Glacier between 2007 and 2010, when more fires occurred in the rainforests than normally seen.The researchers said satellite LiDAR imagery confirm black carbon particles are carried to and deposited on the Zongo, or at an altitude between three and five kilometers.Lead researcher Dr. de Magalhães Neto talking to the BBC said that the black carbon then darkens glacial ice and snow.The research team said that tropical glaciers supply water to millions of people in South America.According to the paper, snow and ice infused with black carbon is less able to deflect sunlight, resulting in a significantly higher rate of melting.Dr. Magalhães Neto tells the BBC that forest fires in Bolivia, Peru and Brazil may have vast social implications for the continent, as glacier loss could lead to a water crisis.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929442/3929442_4E884F3BB1FC47688CE9DEC999AEC6F4_191202_3929442_Amazon_forest_fires_could_make_glaciers_melt_fas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F9/7D1/1F97D1C5FAA88BA3583573D9FC7560C4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Amazon fires, rainforest, deforestation, deforestation fires, black carbon, glaciers, tropical glaciers, andes, andean glaciers, Rio de Janeiro State University, Zongo Glacier, Brazil, Bolivia, Peru, environment, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handyman fired after ceiling full of rats falls on him</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A New York handyman whose bosses skimped on safety gear had a ceiling full of rats collapse on him, only to get a hospital stay and termination for his trouble.According to a lawsuit obtained by the New York Post, Robert Petersen had been tasked with installing a new wall at a West 147th Street building. Since it involved dealing with rat droppings, he asked his boss for safety gear, but was shot down and told not to be a baby about it.The 45-year-old said his boss, Crystal Fernandez, made it sound like he'd get axed if he didn't do the work, so he did, even without the proper gear.Petersen claims he was cleaning rat droppings and urine on soaked pieces of insulation, and was surrounded by rodents  both dead and alive  while he was working.After 16 hours of working that filthy job, he was then called to repair a leaking hole in a ceiling  again without any gear on him.This time, the poor man had to stick his head in the hole and deal with all the rats running around his head.While pulling down a board from the ceiling, the whole thing collapsed on him, raining down rats, droppings, and all things nasty and disgusting.Peterson got itchy welts on his face and arms and began vomiting. He had to check into the hospital for a week, during which his lovely boss threatened to give him the boot.According to court documents, Petersen filed a complaint with OSHA over his filthy work conditions. He was fired 10 days after returning from work, but only told it was "not going to work out."The lawsuit alleges that the handyman's termination was in direct retaliation for his OSHA complaint.Here's hoping Peterson's crappy boss and company get what's coming to them.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 03:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929271/3929271_67857040438B4B4399F993EE43146903_191202_3929271_Handyman_fired_after_ceiling_full_of_rats_falls__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/002/D0E/002D0EC834D46B77BE3560D141E4504B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Rats, rats in ceiling, ceiling collapse, ceiling falls, unhygienic work conditions, labor complaint, OSHA, crappy boss, NY handyman, New York handyman, Robert Petersen, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia uses smart cameras to spot texting drivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA  The Australian government has rolled out a smart traffic camera system to catch drivers who use cell phones on the road.Transport for New South Wales officially activated the mobile phone detection system on Monday after the testing the technology from January to June this year.According to NSW Transport, the system features high definition cameras with infrared flash. The cameras are linked to an artificial intelligence program.The optics allow the system to see into the front cabinet of road vehicles and capture clear images during day or night and in all weather conditions. The system's software then analyzes the images to spot drivers who are using mobile phones.The algorithm excludes images of legal phone use but passes the suspicious ones to authorized reviewers, who checks the images before issuing penalties and fines.NSW Transport says it expects to install 45 cameras across its jurisdiction by 2023.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 14:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3930149/3930149_DB64F5E49DBE4F89BEBA381EAC10DB49_191203_3930149_Australia_uses_smart_cameras_to_spot_texting_dri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/411/0E7/4110E7687EDC613119198572E6888494.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mobile phone detection, detection system, smart cameras, AI, artificial intelligence, driving while texting, Australia, New South Wales, New South Wales Transport, NSW Transport, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA &amp; ESA plan to crash into an asteroid and explore its properties</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  NASA and the European Space Agency are joining hands for a planetary defense mission in order to learn how to protect Earth from a possible asteroid collision.The ESA is preparing for the Hera mission that will gather data from Didymoon, the accompanying moonlet of a binary asteroid system called Didymos, years after NASA crashes a spacecraft into it through its Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART.According to NASA, the binary asteroid system is located roughly 11 million kilometers from Earth. NASA's DART spacecraft will be guided by an onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system as it makes its way to the binary asteroid. By 2022, NASA aims to crash onto the surface of Didymoon at a speed of roughly 6 kilometers per second in order to change the speed and direction of the asteroid.Didymoon is 160 meters in width. This is roughly the width of the Great Pyramid of Giza, according to the American space agency. The Hera spacecraft will then research the crater formed by the DART experiment in 2026.According to an ESA news release, the spacecraft will collect surface samples, as well as data about the shape and dimensions of the crater.Hera will also use thermal imaging technology to examine the asteroid's structure. The European Space Agency says the experiment will provide "valuable insights" into the history and origins of our solar system.The agency explained in a news release that the study would provide information on whether or not this technique would work to deflect an asteroid if one ever heads our way.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 13:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3930122/3930122_958940575C314A399604567469E46B11_191203_3930122_NASA___ESA_plan_to_crash_into_an_asteroid_and_ex_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A5B/F67/A5BF67A2FE9FFDA55404343A7EAAE87E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Double Asteroid Redirection Test,hera mission NASA, DART, planetary defense mission, asteroid, NASA protects Earth from asteroids, NASA DART, Didymos, planetary defense system, esa, asteroid, didymos, binary asteroid system, didymoon, asteroid impact, meteor impact, Hera mission esa,  Didymos asteroid, Didymoon, didymoon 2022, asteroid impact mission, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida woman fakes medical issue to get bigger plane seat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENSACOLA, FLORIDA  A Florida woman is in custody after she hatched the perfect plan to fake a medical issue on an hour and forty minute-long flight in order to get a bigger seat. Okaymaybe her plan had a few tiny holes before lift off.NBC News reports the incident occurred on an American Airlines flight from Pensacola to Miami last Friday morning.  According to an American Airlines statement to NBC News, American Eagle 3508 took off at 5:43 a.m. After the plane was in the air, the woman, who has not been identified, started pretending she had trouble breathing as part of her scheme to get a free upgrade. She reportedly told flight attendants, who then told the pilot, who then turned the entire plane aroundand aroundand around some more before finally landing back at Pensacola at 6:26 a.m. According to NBC News, flight crews then called the police to Pensacola International Airport, where the woman admitted she had made up the problem to get a bigger seat on the plane. At first, Little Miss Sunshine refused to get off the plane, which then prompted a complete evacuation of the plane. She finally got her behind off the plane and was then taken into custody by the police. The flight finally got on its way at 7:41 a.m. Criminal charges have not been filed yet against the woman, but she still may get charged. Imagine what she would have come up with if this had actually been a long haul flight.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 12:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3930100/3930100_49BD3DF1FCDB410593BDE272745BD6C1_191203_3930100_Florida_woman_fakes_medical_issue_to_get_bigger__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C31/B30/C31B305D33981B73B8496F04E7472C65.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Woman wants bigger seat, woman fakes medical issue, woman fakes breathing issue, woman free upgrade, woman wanted bigger seat, woman wanted free bigger seat, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spoilt man-child keys BMW so daddy has to buy it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGXI, CHINA  Surveillance footage from inside a BMW showroom caught a 22-year-old man key a dark blue BMW because he wanted his dad to buy it for him.  Pear Video reports that when local police arrived, the man explained that his dad had promised to buy him a new car as a gift for passing his driving test, however, he had yet to make good on his word, prompting his son to force his hand by keying the BMW.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929989/3929989_890E271F37B240FE9BA7606C38F8E47F_191203_3929989_Spoilt_man_child_keys_BMW_so_daddy_has_to_buy_it_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/882/7D9/8827D95AF2943C820786B8871E727A72.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese spoilt, spoilt children, crazy spoilt asians, rich asians, spoilt chinese kids, spoilt son keys car, scratching cars, keying cars, man-child, China's little emperor crisis, people doing dumb stuff, people doing stupid stuff, stupid things, stupid caught on tape, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India tiger searches for prey, mate in longest walk ever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALL OVER INDIA  A tiger in India has gone on the longest walk ever, logging in over 1,300 kilometers in just five months.According to the BBC, the two-and-a-half-year-old male was fitted with a radio collar, and has been on the move since it left its home in a wildlife sanctuary in June.The tiger, called C1, travelled around the western state of Maharashtra, walking back and forth over farms, waterways, and highways. At one point, it even popped into the neighboring state.It hides during the day and comes out at night, and has been surviving on wild pigs and cattle. Experts believe it's likely on the lookout for territory, food, and a mate. But since most of the potential tiger areas have no vacancy, it's had to explore a heckuva lot more.Most humans in the area are oblivious that a big striped cat has been schlepping around. And except for accidentally injuring one man who came across it, there's been no serious conflict.Still, wildlife officials say C1 needs to be recaptured and relocated to the forest to avoid any other accidents. There's also a chance they'll lose contact soon, since the battery on the collar is down to 20%.So really, who knows until when we'll all be privy to the giant cat's journey?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 09:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929964/3929964_F6C1228E615C4D22B6B47AF8F684C74E_191203_3929964_India_tiger_searches_for_prey__mate_in_longest_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA1/132/BA11321E1420EE6C80590170D85C92DC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tiger, India tiger, Tiger walk, longest walk ever, tiger tracker, tiger prey, tiger mate, tiger radio collar, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banana stumps turned into biodegradable plastics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENSINGTON, AUSTRALIA According to researchers at Australia's University of South Wales, banana growing can be a highly wasteful process with 88 percent of the plant being discarded after fruit harvesting.The scientists have designed a new method that reduces this waste by reusing the pseudostem, or the banana's trunk, and turning it into biodegradable packaging.According to the university's press release, the team cut the pseudostem, then dry heated the pieces at low temperatures to remove water.The process extracts cellulose from banana plant cells in powdered form, which is then chemically treated to become the packaging material.According to the researchers, the finished product is a baking paper like polymer that may replace plastic bags and single use commercial containers for meat and fruit.They claimed that tests conducted at the university found the material to be nontoxic and can be recycled up to three times.According to one of the professors involved in the study, bananas are annual plants and could potentially provide a round the year supply of sustainable packaging material.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929931/3929931_0F5C7957FA544BFAB29B3D0BCD80F831_191203_3929931_Banana_stumps_turned_into_biodegradable_plastics_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6F0/241/6F0241BF0E00A8CE6AC4CA5AA52685E3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Banana, cellulose, plastic alternative, plastic, polymer, biodegradable, recyclable, environment, science and technology, UNSW, University University of South Wales Sydney]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater loudspeakers could help boost coral reef recovery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EXETER, UNITED KINGDOM  New research has found that deploying underwater loudspeakers to play the sounds of healthy coral reef could help restore damaged reefs.In a joint study by two British universities and two Australian universities, scientists recorded sounds of healthy reefs and then played these sounds via a loudspeaker for 40 days on Australia's northern Great Barrier Reef.One of the authors of the study explained that healthy coral reefs are noisy, with shrimp and fish living in the area creating noise. Once coral reefs start to degrade or are damaged, reefs turn eerily quiet. This results in fish in the reefs leaving to find a new home. At the end of the experiment, scientists found that the degraded coral reefs had a 50 percent increase in the number of juvenile fish.Lead author of the study, Tim Gordon, explained in a news release that the growth of fish population choosing to stay in the damaged reefs could help to kick-start the natural recovery process for the coral reefs.Co-author of the study, Andy Radford, from the University of Bristol, said that this technique could be combined with other coral restoration techniques to help accelerate ecosystem recovery.Though Radford added that we need to combat other threats such as climate change, water pollution and overfishing in order to better protect these ecosystems in the first place.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 07:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929897/3929897_BF9827165BAD49128BF19E59928222FE_191203_3929897_Underwater_loudspeakers_could_help_boost_coral_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C12/932/C12932F2C0E66B2690E258E8F2B4F5B7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Great barrier reef new coral, coral restoration, spawning new coral, Great barrier coral,  great barrier reef dying coral, damaged coral, damaged coral underwater loudspeakers, coral reef restoration, coral reef loudspeakers, Great barrier reef loudspeakers, using loudspeakers to restore coral, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>104-Year-Old Grandma VS Buck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHILLIPS, WISCONSIN  Retirement isn't for everyone and 104-year-old Florence Teeters is the perfect example.Born in 1915, Florence may just be the oldest person to have taken down a deer in Wisconsin, after her son helped her to obtain her hunting license just days before. Speaking to NBC15, her youngest of five children Bill said that he took his mother to a hunting blind recently when a buck showed up around 30 yards away. He told reporters that he tapped her on her knee and pointed out to the unsuspecting buck; she nodded, grinned and then took her shot. The Wisconsin Department of Natural Resources is currently looking into the claim that Teeters may be the oldest registered hunter in the state.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 02:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929748/3929748_7AF10E5BD8EB469082E72218C1B810CA_191203_3929748_104_Year_Old_Grandma_VS_Buck_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/22E/016/22E0161D1FC976E6901361F3BC825E97.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[104-year-old hunts deer, old woman hunting, hunting, hunting fails, funny hunting, deer hunting, hunting deer, oldest hunter, old woman hunter, Wisconsin old woman hunter, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA's astronaut dummies will test new vests around the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA will send astronaut dummies around the moon in the Orion spacecraft for the uncrewed Artemis I mission scheduled for next year, Space.com reports.  According to the outlet, NASA says the goal of the mission is to test a new piece of equipment designed to protect female astronauts from space radiation called the AstroRed. According to the European Space Agency, the pair of phantom dummies named Zohar and Helga are fitted with over 5,600 radiation sensors.Zohar will wear the AstroRad protective vest and Helgo will not, which will help researchers evaluate the effectiveness of the vest. Makers of the radiation vest, a company called StemRad, say the vest protects the breasts, bone marrow, stomach, ovaries and other vulnerable organs that contain stem cells via its variable thickness shielding.According to the Tel-Aviv based contractor, the contoured shields are solid polymer shielding elements that are arrayed in a scale like structure. According to the German Aerospace Center's Thomas Berger, though the vest is designed for women, the garment could be adjusted for males.StemRad claims its vest could allow astronauts to leave the Orioin's solar storm shelters to perform important tasks during a solar storm.According to the company, the vest significantly reduces cancer and other fatal radiation exposure risks for astronauts.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 10:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/04/3930537/3930537_B4833DD56D7A45F7B7B56CC63DFF4103_191204_3930537_NASA_s_astronaut_dummies_will_test_new_vests_aro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/349/504/349504D61FA4932646F5AB4ABB56ED69.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA, StemRad, AstroRad, dummies, vest, vests, Lockheed-Martin, Artemis I, Orion, moon, space exploration, radiation, solar storm, astronaut]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Smart TV could spying on you: FBI</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON  The FBI warned consumers this week that their smart TVs may be collecting extensive data about them.In a message to Christmas shoppers, the agency warned that smart TVs are vulnerable to cyberattacks. This is because they are connected to the internet and include features such as microphones and cameras.The FBI said that if a device is hacked, hackers could use these features to cyberstalk someone. The bureau urged owners of smart TVs to take preventive actions against this by learning their devices' privacy settings and how to turn off its microphones and cameras.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 07:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/04/3930401/3930401_7F62A0FB7FC946939C139DF0919E33E8_191204_3930401_Your_Smart_TV_could_spying_on_you__FBI_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8D7/FB3/8D7FB34C29884E7AF6BA7840F73BC137.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Smart TV, smart TV spying on you, smart TV warning, smart tv spying, smart tv cameras, smart tv cameras watching you, technology, smart technology, smart tv technology, smart technology 2019, smart tech spying, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog nearly burns the house down after turning on microwave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ESSEX, UNITED KINGDOM  A dog in England inadvertently started a house fire after he turned on the microwave.According to the BBC, the husky had been left alone inside a house in Essex when he switched on the appliance, which was on a kitchen counter.This wouldn't be a problem if there was nothing in it, but a packet of bread rolls just happened to be inside, and they began to burn and start a small fire. The homeowner wasn't home at the time, but got alerted to the blaze by an app on his phone.Checking the live feed from a camera inside the house, he saw smoke coming from the kitchen and quickly called fire services.Firefighters got to the house and found the kitchen filled with smoke, but contained the fire so it didn't spread to the rest of the house.Essex Fire Services says the dog wasn't hurt, and that his human got very lucky. Just imagine how serious it would have been if the blaze wasn't caught in time!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 15:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3931166/3931166_5F8C2DAF87B34D86B54900D560108B8B_191205_3931166_Dog_nearly_burns_the_house_down_after_turning_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5FA/359/5FA359A58533CEAB01955625E30ADFCB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dog starts fire, dog starts house fire, husky, siberian husky, microwave fire, microwave house fire, house fire, dogs getting in trouble, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McDonald's is testing a new chicken sandwich</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  Everyday Americans have been going absolutely bonkers over chicken sandwiches as of late with no signs of slowing down.  As the Chicken Sandwich Wars have been raging, Popeyes and Chick-fil-A have been slugging it out, while Mickey D's has been left out in the cold watching from the sidelines. That could all change soon as CNBC reports McDonald's is testing out two new Southern-style chicken sandwiches at locations in Houston, Texas and Knoxville, Tennessee. Pictures of the new crispy chicken sandwich show a fried chicken fillet topped with butter and pickles. If you're having trouble picturing what that looks like, just think of a Chick-fil-A or Popeyes chicken sandwich with a Mickey D's wrapper around itVOILÀ!!   The deluxe crispy chicken sandwich comes with tomatoes, lettuce and mayo on top of the chicken fillet. According to Business Insider, the test will run from December 2 through January 26, 2020. According to CNBC, McDonald's has apparently been trying to get a decent tasting chicken sandwich together for quite a few months now. With Chick-fil-A catching up in the rearview and Popeyes dominating recently, can McDonald's McCopied chicken sandwich save the day?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 12:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3931112/3931112_E5C29A3B47A44591BE589B96033576AE_191205_3931112_McDonald_s_is_testing_a_new_chicken_sandwich_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F42/BBC/F42BBCC5351E2DBB29C1AB6C281D2F79.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[McDonald's, McDonalds testing new chicken sandwich, McDonald's crispy chicken sandwich, McDonald's v Chick-fil-A, Popeyes chicken sandwich, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing employs 'influencers' to spread communism</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China's United Front Work Department aims to enlist online 'influencers' to spread the core values of the communist party. Officials from China's cyber administration along with propaganda specialists from across the country met to discuss ways to adopt influencers such as makeup teachers and stunt performers into their arsenal.You Quan, the department head of the United Front, said, "We need to build an online personnel team, to guide them to play an active role in leading public opinion and other areas."He added, "We will work hard to surround them by the Communist Party's side, to concentrate the wisdom and power for achieving the rejuvenation of the Chinese people and the Chinese dream."From last year, China's United Front Work Department has since expanded, with it now getting a say in areas such as ethnic policies and religious affairs. The term "online personnel" was defined as those who command influence among their followers, either by shaping public opinion or by encouraging the public to react to an event in a certain way. Author and political commentator, Sonny Lo Shiu-Hing said that it wasn't at all surprising Beijing wanted to "woo" online influencers, because the communist party wants to control all media.The United Front set out three recruitment tasks, train the influencers, encouraging them to produce "healthy content" and most worryingly make them actively engage in major online propaganda.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3931070/3931070_033E1E8E6F1B4704B79C33E1FD84435F_191205_3931070_Beijing_employs__influencers__to_spread_communis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B77/1E0/B771E0D1ADD939249E866690A45D92E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Police state, Beijing employs influencers, social media spies, social media influencers, communism, communist influencers, TomoNews, satire, Beijing employs influencers to spread communism, Chinese girl streamer, Chinese streamers, Chinese BJ dance, BJ dance, Chinese vlogger]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to attach 'robot hotel' to International Space Station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION  NASA plans to launch a storage space for robotic tools called the Robotic Tool Stowage, or RiTS, to the International Space Station.In a news release, NASA explained that the robot hotel will be launched aboard a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket, during its 19th commercial resupply mission, on December 4.Two robotic tools called Robotic External Leak Locators, or RELL, that are currently onboard the International Space Station, will be the first residents of the storage space. These robotic tools are capable of detecting gases such as ammonia and are used to find leaks in the station.NASA says the storage unit will protect the tools from space radiation, tiny meteoroids, or other high-speed objects traveling through space.The Robotic Tool Stowage's thermal system will be able to maintain a constant temperature to help the space station's robotic equipment stay functional. The location of the storage space will also make it easily accessible for the International Space Station's robotic arm called Dextre to get a hold of these tools.Once the robot hotel makes its way to the space station, astronauts will perform a spacewalk to install the storage space to the station's exterior.NASA says this type of technology could potentially be used in future space missions to the Moon, Mars, or beyond.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 07:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3930938/3930938_58C29F7D59584856B2C9E21AC32E0163_191205_3930938_NASA_to_attach__robot_hotel__to_International_Sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/57B/733/57B733767E03D880F94A3E7D65778C4F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Robot hotel, robot hotel NASA, International Space Station, International Space Station robot hotel, Robotic Tool Stowage, RiTS, RiTS NASA, Robotic Tool Stowage NASA, space exploration, robot hotel ISS, NASA to launch robot hotel, Robotic External Leak Locators,   TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may implement mandatory facial scans across airports</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. Department of Homeland Security has proposed a new regulation that would require all travelers  including U.S. citizens and green card holders  to undergo mandatory facial scans when entering and leaving the country.Facial recognition technology typically matches an image of a person from a photo or video with a still image of them in a database. It has become increasingly used in airports throughout the world, according to CNN. The proposed regulation would be part of a broader system to track travelers as they enter and exit the United States.According to Reuters, the Trump Administration contends the face scan requirement will combat the fraudulent use of U.S. travel documents and aid the identification of criminals and suspected terrorists.The U.S. Customs and Border Protection has already conducted pilot programs that collect photographs and fingerprints from foreign travelers, but until now, U.S. citizens had been exempt, Reuters reports.   In 2017, President Trump signed an executive order to accelerate a full roll out of airport biometrics for all domestic and international travelers.According to a statement by a senior policy analyst from American Liberties Union Jay Stanley, travelers shouldn't have to submit to "invasive biometric scans" just because they want to travel.The U.S. government has been using facial recognition technology for the past 20 years, though the government has only recently started pushing for use of this technology across U.S. airports, CNN reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3930855/3930855_03FAB6B904BE4671808EA0559C87D870_191205_3930855_U_S__may_implement_mandatory_facial_scans_across_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/750/38D/75038D531BC45BE8E8FFE880F02093AE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Facial recognition, Face scans, US face scans, facial recognition surveillance, US facial recognition technology, US homeland security face scans, facial recognition US citizens, facial recognition usa, US airports face scans, US airports facial recognition tech, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three missing in Chinese sinkhole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TIANHE, GUANGZHOU, CHINA  Three people have been missing since Sunday morning after falling into a massive sinkhole in the southern Chinese city of Guangzhou.The road in the city's Tianhe district suddenly caved in around 9:30 a.m local time, just as a street-cleaning vehicle and a scooter were driving over it. Chinese outlet, The National Business Daily report that the area below the road was, in fact, a subway line that was undergoing construction; the estimated depth of the collapse is thought to be around 38 meters. In an effort to find the missing three people, more than 1,100 rescue workers, and 192 rescue vehicles have taken to the hazardous area, however, search and rescue efforts have been delayed as the collapse continues to expand outwards.Workers tried to fill the expanding hole to reinforce its slopes to avoid further collapses.The individuals of the street cleaning vehicle were identified as a 51-year father and his 26-year-old son. The rider of the scooter has yet to be identified.Construction workers in the metro tunnel below were evacuated. The cause of the incident, however, is still under investigation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 02:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3930788/3930788_14383A975EF74083906B80A7D1AE8F23_191205_3930788_Three_missing_in_Chinese_sinkhole_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B67/548/B67548E8B258AEDDC65562F20ACE0CB1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sinkholes, massive sinkholes, big sinkhole, Chinese sinkhole, Guangzhou sinkhole, Tianhe sinkhole, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China turns 'Great Cannon' on Hong Kong webforum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  A Chinese cyberweapon dubbed the Great Cannon is launching DDoS attacks on a Hong Kong webform after years of silence, AT&T Cybersecurity reported on Wednesday.The internet security developer says analysis indicates that the Cannon begin attacking the webforum named LIHKG in August.According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Hong Kong activists have been using the forum to coordinate protests.The Citizen Lab at the University of Toronto reported previously that the Great Cannon represents a "significant escalation in state-level information control."AT&T Cybersecurity states that the Cannon inserts malicious Javascript code into browsers when users access servers within China's Great Firewall.The Great Cannon then uses the code to send numerous requests to overwhelm the targeted domain's resources and to make it unavailable.According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Great Cannon caused global disruption in 2015, when it was deployed against Github and the online freedom group GreatFire.org.The security firm says that the Chinese-language news website Mingjingnews.com was attacked from two years ago and that it expects more attacks against LIHKG.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 14:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931729/3931729_E0E215EAD1904BA98067CC299A724FD6_191206_3931729_China_turns__Great_Cannon__on_Hong_Kong_webforum_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C49/7F7/C497F7567B896512094313D9E0BCD83D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Great Cannon, China's great cannon, Hong Kong, LIHKG, Great Firewall, China's Great Firewall, censorship, cyberweapon, internet censorship]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese kid gets stuck in claw machine trying to get prize</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHONGSHAN, CHINA  A little dude in China is really into claw machine games, so much so that he actually got stuck in one. According to video posted to Miaopai, the boy was apparently out for a day at the mall with his mom in the Guangdong city of Zhongshan. While little man's mom was doing some shopping, a claw machine named "Come on baby" GRABBED the boy's attention. Staring back at the boy from inside the machine were plush toys galore, so he came up with an ingenious plan to get his hands on them.Using his Jack Ma-esque build, he was able to wiggle his way into the prize chute. But unfortunately, getting in proved to be a tad bit easier than extricating himself out of the grabber machine. At some point, people realized that the boy probably wasn't supposed to be there, so they called for help. Video shows firefighters using a crowbar to gently pry the machine open and get the boy out. In the end, little guy made it out in one piece. Hopefully this will be a lesson learned. Next time look for one with a bigger prize chute.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931715/3931715_DEC965816EE2407E81ADD1CCE882CA21_191206_3931715_Chinese_kid_gets_stuck_in_claw_machine_trying_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/618/8ED/6188ED64B2AC07F3E144748DF8D71785.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China claw machine, claw machine game, grabber machine game, stuck inside claw machine, inside claw machine game, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhengzhou subway in China using face recognition at all stations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHENGZHOU, CHINA  As cities across China continue to testing face recognition payment systems for subways, Zhengzhou has become the first to roll out the tech at all their stations. Forget to bring your wallet, metro card or mobile phone with your QR code? No worries, just use your face.  According to the Henan Daily, starting this week all commuters can pay at any Zhengzhou subway station using an optional face scan. The SCMP reported that according to the Henan Daily, since trials began in September, almost 200,000 commuters in Zhengzhou have given up their biometric data in order to use the metro face-scan payment app. All people have to do after they register is to show up at a subway turnstile scanner to scan their beautiful mugs. They get in right away while the fare is deducted through a pre-set payment plan. While Zhengzhou is the first city to roll out the face scanners at all stations, subways in other Chinese cities like Guangzhou, Nanjing and Shenzhen have also been testing out the tech. And as for privacy concerns? Hold on, what's privacy?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 07:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931424/3931424_2746A6D0984D454EA73B950CDD2AF298_191206_3931424_Zhengzhou_subway_in_China_using_face_recognition_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FAC/B6F/FACB6FF7BF8F00504B35705DD4777775.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China facial recognition, China subway facial recognition payment, Zhengzhou subway facial recognition payment, Zhengzhou facial payment, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors successfully 'reanimate' heart from deceased donor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA  For the first time in the U.S, doctors have successfully "reanimated" a heart from a deceased donor, prior to the heart being transplanted to an adult recipient.This procedure is known as donation after circulatory death or DCD.Donor hearts usually come from those who have been declared as brain dead but still have a beating heart. The beating heart is then transplanted into a recipient, CNN reports. Jacob Schroder, one of the doctors involved in the heart transplant procedure, told CNN that the donor heart was doused with a cold solution and removed five minutes after the person's death was announced and after heartbeat and circulation had stopped.Physicians from Duke University Medical Center then placed the heart in the TransMedics Organ Care System. The system pumps warm blood and allows the non-beating heart to be preserved and resuscitated for a transplant.Once the heart and the heart recipient is ready, the donor heart is then transplanted into the recipient via standard heart transplant procedure.Schroder explained that the procedure could increase the donor pool and the number of transplants performed by 30 percent. This would decrease wait time and the number of deaths of those waiting for a transplant.The procedure has previously been performed in medical centers in the United Kingdom and Australia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931317/3931317_22B827FD7AB74E188390A49A52F35C36_191206_3931317_Doctors_successfully__reanimate__heart_from_dece_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0C7/FCA/0C7FCABA14697A685E2EC9E65A1ECAE7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Heart transplant, reanimating a heart, doctors reanimate heart, doctors bring heart back to life, heart transplant stories, donor heart preservation, organ donor heart, heart donor, reanimate donor heart, TransMedics Organ Care System, Duke University Medical Center, Duke University Medical Center reanimate heart, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar bear spray painted with graffiti in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHUKOTKA, RUSSIA  Video shared on social media of a polar bear spray-painted with graffiti is causing outrage after experts say it poses an extra threat to an already endangered animal.World Wildlife Fund employee Sergey Kavry told the BBC that the video was shared on a WhatsApp group for indigenous people in Russia's Chukotka region, but that he didn't know where exactly it was filmed.The polar bear had been spray painted on one side with "T-34", the name of a Soviet-era tank. It could take weeks to wash off, and would seriously screw up the animal's ability to camouflage while hunting. After Kavry posted the video to Facebook on December 1, it went on to spark outrage among experts and en.Anatoly Kochnev, a scientist at the Institute of Biological Problems of the North, says the bear was probably sedated or at the very least immobile when the letters were painted. So either it was done for science, or as a sick joke.Kochnev says polar bears have been foraging closer to residential areas due to the lack of food, so it's possible the locals may have stepped up to stop them.Local Russian media claims though, that it was an expedition of scientists in Novaya Zemlya that marked the bear after it scavenged through rubbish bins of a human settlement, to see if it would return.Either way, poor bear.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 02:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931302/3931302_1B2B02ABDC664719B2AA4DF2C2081B17_191206_3931302_Polar_bear_spray_painted_with_graffiti_in_Russia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/828/333/828333CD1B6AF83B2627F1C32840FD6A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Polar bear graffiti, polar bear, russia polar bear, polar bear t-34, spray painted polar bear, russian wildlife, endangered wildlife, polar bear survival, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taipei ranked best city for expats to live and work...China numba 43</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Taiwan is numba one for expats!For the second year in a row, Taipei has been ranked the best city for expats to live and work in, while Shanghai and Beijing eat dust in 43rd and 60th place.The survey by Internations asked about 25 different aspects of life, divided into: Quality of Urban Living, Getting Settled, Urban Work Life, and Finance and Housing.Taipei reigned supreme as far as quality of life, transportation, healthcare, friendliness, and cost of living.Shanghai was okay in the transportation, safety, and disposable income department, but people weren't crazy about air pollution and the Chinese intranet.As for Beijing – how are they not lower on the list?? No doubt China is going to get its panties in a twist about this ranking – not that anyone cares, because we all know Taiwan numba one, China numba forty three[b]!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 09:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/07/3931976/3931976_813C1CC65DE141B38F26C0B3AFC175E3_191207_3931976_Taipei_ranked_best_city_for_expats_to_live_and_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/194/A92/194A92AF7452081B5B4D6D2D3A02152C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taipei expat, taipei, taiwan numba one, taipei numba one, best expat cities, best cities for expats, best cities, best city, Shanghai, China intranet, Great firewall, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North American birds are shrinking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANN ARBOR, MICHIGAN  New research has found that tens of thousands of North American birds have become smaller in size since 1978.Scientists examined 70, 716 dead birds  52 bird species in total  that crashed into skyscrapers in Chicago.The study, published in the journal Ecology Letters, found that 49 of these bird species had a reduction in the length of their lower leg bone by 2.4 percent.Meanwhile, the average wing length of birds saw an increase of roughly 1.3 percent.The authors of the study suggested that a change in the birds' size may be a response to rising temperatures caused by climate change.They added that the birds may have evolved to have a wider wingspan to compensate for their smaller bodies and to help them migrate long distances.Scientists said that animal species tend to be smaller in warmer regions and larger in colder regions. This is to help animals carry less heat in hot areas while those in colder areas need a larger body size to conserve warmth.The researchers plan to use the data to look at the mechanics of how a birds' body changes in shape and size, according to CNN. They also plan to examine whether the change is a result of developmental plasticity  an animal's ability to change its own development as a response to the changing environment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 08:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/07/3931961/3931961_9F36CDFD1F3C4D7EB538F3DF35B20D0F_191207_3931961_North_American_birds_are_shrinking_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0C4/01F/0C401F212847610EC910EF95848BAD03.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bird population, bird population north america, north american birds shrinking, north american birds getting smaller, climate change birds, smaller north american birds, climate change birds affected, birds and climate change, global warming bird population shrinking, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China makes propaganda game that lets you hit HK protesters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China is hitting back against the "Liberate Hong Kong" game by coming up with a version that lets you beat the protesters instead.The anti-protest propaganda video game, called "Everyone Hit the Traitors," tells you right off the in big bold letters that "Hong Kong is part of China" and "can't be meddled with by outside powers."When you click to play, it starts by saying there's a bunch of traitors colluding with Western powers and instigating protests in Hong Kong.These traitors include activist Joshua Wong, media tycoon Jimmy Lai, and former Hong Kong chief secretary Anson Chan  who are all depicted as caricatures.Once you've chosen a traitor to target, it's time to beat him and his horde of young protesters, or "useless youths," by tapping them with a hand, flip-flop, or baseball bat. You can choose!If any of the protesters make it across the screen, you lose  but that's highly unlikely because they're lumbering so slowly.The traitor needs a bit more tapping to be defeated and then arrested, but it's still not rocket science  really, the only way to fail is if you do it on purpose.In case you're interested in playing this Chinese propaganda game, it's free on dalaoshu.net, dalaoshu being the Chinese for "big rat." Wow, subtle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932870/3932870_1B03122A073C447BBF4E2D1A81D4034F_191209_3932870_China_makes_propaganda_game_that_lets_you_hit_HK_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/000/44C/00044C9DED0C3179D142CA26B6B6944F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong activists, Hong Kong protesters, HK protest, HK protesters, Chinese video game, Chinese propaganda, propaganda video game, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$120,000 banana art taken down after idiotic crowds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  A slippery piece of artwork that was nothing more than a banana duct taped to the wall, which actually sold for $120,000 last week, had to be taken down because too many idiotssorry, peoplewanted to see it. According to the New York Post, Maurizio Cattelan's controversial banana piece titled "Comedian" had to be taken down on Sunday morning at the request of the art fair's organizers.This was just one day after a New York-based performance artist showed up at the Art Basel in Miami and ate the banana. Cattelan's gallery Perrotin announced, "Art Basel collaboratively worked with us to station guards and create uniform lines."Hold on...COLLABORATIVELY worked with us? So they just mean, "WORKED with us." Anyways, the statement went on, "however, the installation caused several uncontrollable crowd movements and the placement of the work on our booth compromised the safety of the artwork around us, including that of our neighbors. In the end, I would like to warmly thank all those who participated in this memorable adventure."Art Basel also confirmed that the $120,000 banana was no longer on display. But not to worry, if you really want to see the FART-work for yourself...just get a wall, a banana and some tape. And don't forget to call yourself an artist too.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 12:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932823/3932823_B14D447602474F1BBC4A3A340CE86FC2_191209_3932823__120_000_banana_art_taken_down_after_idiotic_cro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/647/9A0/6479A07FB1F04BAEDC86AAABCCA36EBF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[$120,000 banana artwork, $120,000 banana art, Miami Art Basel banana, Maurizio Cattelan Comedian, Comedian banana piece, Banana art piece, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two piglets containing monkey DNA born in Chinese laboratory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  These little piggies had some crazy scientists genetically engineer them with a bunch of monkey DNA in China.According to New Scientist, pig-primate chimeras were created by a team in China. The two piglets resembled normal pigs on the outside, but they also had a proportion of their cells derived from cynomolgus monkeys. According to Tang Hai at the State Key Laboratory of Stem Cell and Reproductive Biology in Beijing, "this is the first report of full-term pig-monkey chimeras." The goal of the mad scientists is to grow human organs in animals for transplantation.Unfortunately, the research has a long way to go as both little piggies died within a week. The Chinese researchers genetically modified cynomolgus monkey cells growing in culture so they made a fluorescent protein called GFP, allowing them to track the cells and their descendents. The team then derived embryonic stem cells from the modified cells and jammed them into pig embryos five days after fertilization. Over 4000 embryos were implanted into sows with ten piglets born as a result of which two where chimeras. All became bacon within a week. The Chinese scientists now say they are trying to engineer healthier animals with a higher proportion of monkey cells. But in the meantime, might as well just continue harvesting organs from the totally unwilling.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932768/3932768_918B0D49DBB34EAB81F72F93DC300BAA_191209_3932768_Two_piglets_containing_monkey_DNA_born_in_Chines_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7D1/152/7D1152D55AE1921F9BE5C44EFD9D11B6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Piglets with monkey DNA, piglets born with monkey DNA, piglets monkey DNA, China genetic engineering, China piglets monkey DNA, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded sperm whale had 100 kg of garbage in it stomach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARRIS, SCOTLAND  A sperm whale that became stranded and died on a Scottish beach had 100kg of garbage in its stomach, according to the Scottish Marine Animal Strandings Scheme (SMASS).According to an SMASS Facebook post on December 1, the animal had been dead for two days by the time workers examined the carcass.  According to SMASS, the juvenile whale measured 14 meters long. Approximately 100 kilograms of garbage was found in its stomach, including nets, ropes, plastic cups and bags, gloves and packaging.SMASS said that debris in the whale originated from both fishing and land sectors and that the animal had been eating litter for quite some time.The whale could have swallowed the debris between the Azores to Norway and efforts to explain why this whale ingested so much garbage is still ongoing.While the garbage did not appear to block the whale's intestines, SMASS said the debris caused indigestion and may have played a role in the stranding that resulted in the whale's demise.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932750/3932750_97116C9179694875A875D186540C0E99_191209_3932750_Stranded_sperm_whale_had_100_kg_of_garbage_in_it_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sperm whale, whale, stranding, stranded, marine debris, trash, ocean, pollution, plastic pollution, Harris Island, Isle of Harris, Scotland, environment, SMASS, Scottish Marine Animal Strandings Scheme]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 500k crabs TRAPPED by plastic waste on remote islands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOBART, AUSTRALIA  A new study led by the University of Tasmania has found that more than 560,000 hermit crabs have died from being trapped in plastic waste on the remote Cocos Keeling and Henderson Islands.Scientists surveyed sites on both the islands for plastic debris and found open plastic containers across the islands. The study also accounted for the number of trapped crabs, both dead and alive, found inside the plastic containers.Researchers said that the piles of plastic waste present on the island beaches create physical obstacles as well as traps for the hermit crabs.The problem is exacerbated as hermit crabs don't have shells of their own, which means that they need to track down other dead crabs via their odor in order to acquire them.In one example, researchers found that this led to 526 crabs being trapped in a single plastic container.In a University of Tasmania news release scientists said that these hermit crabs are important as they help disperse seeds, fertilize the soil in tropical environments and form an integral part of the marine ecosystem.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 04:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932528/3932528_231D509177414C25ADD55E02DE6EE57E_191209_3932528_Over_500k_crabs_TRAPPED_by_plastic_waste_on_remo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/166/2EF/1662EFD4B921FB919ACBD47AC6816C3E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plastic pollution, hermit crabs, hermit crabs trapped in plastic, hermit crabs plastic waste, plastic waste, plastic waste in oceans, ocean plastic pollution, plastic waste in the ocean, plastic polluting the oceans, plastic debris crabs,  Cocos Island hermit crabs, Henderson Island hermit crabs, hermit crabs stuck in plastic debris, marine pollution, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman stung by scorpion on United Airlines flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO / ATLANTA  A woman on a United Airlines plane got a nasty stowaway that turned what should've been a relatively uneventful flight into a painful one.According to TMZ, the lady was on a flight from San Francisco to Atlanta Thursday morning when she felt a stinging sensation on her leg. She went to the lavatory when it intensified, and that's when a very much alive scorpion fell out of her pants leg and scurried away.As if snakes on a plane wasn't bad enough, now we gotta worry about these venomous little buggers?!Flight attendants  bless them  eventually caught the scorpion.According to a United Airlines statement, medics treated the passenger as soon as the plane landed in Atlanta. She was taken to the hospital, and is going to be just fine.No word on how the scorpion ended up on the plane, but we've got a few ideas.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933445/3933445_43D7339C7BB6486886E23B3873E9C833_191211_3933445_Woman_stung_by_scorpion_on_United_Airlines_fligh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/551/2C5/5512C5AA651849AC1676CF4DC92ECF7B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Scorpion on a plane, scorpions on a plane, united airlines, woman stung by scorpion, scorpion sting, scorpion on flight, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Island volcanic eruption explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WHITE ISLAND / NEW ZEALANDThe sudden eruption of New Zealand's White Island volcano has left 5 people dead and injured dozens of others, reports CNN.According to the University of Otago, White Island straddles the Australian and Pacific tectonic plates.Magma is created beneath the island when the Pacific plate pushes against the Australian plate and sinks beneath it.The Guardian reports that White Island magma is shallow and heats groundwater to form pockets of extremely hot steam. This causes high pressure in surrounding rocks.The expansion of water into steam can be supersonic and its energy can shatter the rockbed, resulting in a steam-driven eruption, also known as hydrothermal eruption.The Guardian reports that White Island's steam-driven eruption blasted hot volcanic rocks, ash and coarse particles that can inflict impact trauma, burns and respiratory injuries.Authorities fear as many as 13 people could be dead.CNN reports that five tourists on the island have been killed, while 27 have suffered serious burns and eight are still missing as of Tuesday.The Guardian reports that steam-driven eruptions can happen quickly and without warning because their triggers are not well understood.Volcanologists at GeoNet says the White Island volcano erupted with enough force that its plumes rose to a height of three kilometers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933391/3933391_19CEF64E3B9F487C8A4437865C12B756_191211_3933391_White_Island_volcanic_eruption_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/44C/564/44C56472EF8ED9663BAC2B099799AE6D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Volcano, volcanic eruption, volcano eruption steam, hypothermal eruption, hypothermal volcanic eruption, disaster, White Island, New Zealand, geology, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oceans are running out of oxygen because of climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRID  The International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN), warns that climate change and nutrient pollution are depleting the oceans of oxygen in a report published in December. The report states that nitrogen and phosphorus runoffs from sewage, agricultural waste and industrial pollution are the main cause of oxygen deletion, especially in coastal seas.According to the BBC, the study also found that climate change is heating the oceans and reducing the amount of oxygen they can hold. The study found the oxygen dissolved in the ocean has dropped two percent globally and as much as 40 percent in parts of the tropics.The study warns that the combined effects of warmer oceans and run offs could affect the top 1,000 meter of the water column, which is richest in biodiversity.The IUCN states that deoxygenation harms bigger fish that are oxygen sensitive, such as tuna, marlin and sharks, but favors microbes and jellyfish that are not.The report suggests that the lack of oxygen would force the fish to live closer to the surface, where they are vulnerable to overfishing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 09:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933196/3933196_EDFE5F674416485E9A18A39ABA2F4006_191210_3933196_Oceans_are_running_out_of_oxygen_because_of_clim_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC7/64B/DC764B7F10CECF6C1336F79396CA76A3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ocean, oceans, oxygen, deoxygenation, nutrient pollution, runoff, climate change, global warming, fisheries, IUCN, fisheries, International Union for Conservation of Nature, environment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Seahorse hotels' planned for endangered species in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  New artificial habitats could help save the endangered White's seahorse species in Australia.SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium is working with the University of Technology Sydney and the New South Wales Department of Primary Industries Fisheries on a new breeding and conservation project for Australia's White's seahorse, one of only two endangered seahorse species worldwide.The Department of Primary Industries Fisheries states on its website that the main cause for the decline of White's seahorse, also known as the Sydney seahorse, is the loss of its natural habitats.In the project's first phase, researchers collected breeding pairs of White's seahorses from Sydney Harbor. Their offspring are being kept at a custom built facility at SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium and will eventually be released into the wild.For the second phase of the project, the team will begin constructing "seahorse hotels," or artificial habitats for seahorses, in Sydney Harbor this month.Researchers say the seahorse hotels will provide a habitat for the project's seahorses when they are released into the wild. Monitoring of the seahorses will continue after their release.These artificial habitats will be transformed into natural habitats for White's seahorses as they are grown over by sponges, algae and other marine creatures.Researchers say the artificial habitats were previously trialled in Port Stephens in New South Wales, Australia in 2018 and earlier this year.Trials were found to be extremely successful as they attracted seahorses, leading to mating and breeding.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 08:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933159/3933159_A78C359848AE443C92B00FE77CA9494F_191210_3933159__Seahorse_hotels__planned_for_endangered_species_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/114/F49/114F490C1D5DE5DBA154D1085B19943E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Seahorse hotels, seahorse hotels australia, sydney seahorse, seahorse hotels White's seahorses, endangered australian species, Australia's only threatened seahorse, White's seahorses, australia White's seahorse, endangered White's seahorses, seahorse breeding project, artificial habitats for seahorses, artificial habitats White's seahorses, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Orca: Luxury superyacht inspired by killer whales</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RAVENNA, ITALY  Italian shipyard Rosetti Superyachts has unveiled its new luxury yacht that is designed to look like an orca.Project Orca will be 65 meters long and consist of four decks, SuperYacht Times reports. The ship will have a range of 5,000 miles and will be able to travel at a cruising speed of 12 knots.The yacht itself comes with several deck configurations. In its standard configuration, the vessel will have an open deck, a touch-and-go helipad, and snow sledges.The superyacht may also be modified to include an infinity pool, or a raised helipad with a pool and spa area in its interior.Project Orca's interior includes six cabins, which can accommodate up to 12 people along with a crew of 12. The lower deck will also be equipped with a garage to store equipment like jet skis.Fulvio Dodich, CEO and chairman of Rosetti Superyachts, said that the yacht will take approximately 36 months to be built.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 07:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933112/3933112_292EBA6009B74C1B81C309732A97E02C_191210_3933112_Project_Orca__Luxury_superyacht_inspired_by_kill_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/207/983/207983CD95F24E8EC06E3A8BE92E94AD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Superyacht, italy superyacht, Project Orca, Orca superyacht, Project Orca yacht, orca yacht, superyacht designed as orca, killer whale superyacht, luxury superyacht, luxury orca superyacht, Rosetti Superyachts, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FBI is investigating Pensacola base shooting as a terrorist attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENSACOLA, FLORIDA  A Saudi trainee at the US Navy Pensacola Air Station carried out a shooting early morning on Friday that the FBI is assuming to be a terrorist attack.The New York Times reports that federal investigators identified the shooter as Saudi air force Second Lieutenant Mohammed Alshamrani in a press event on Sunday.The commanding officer of the base told the New York Times that three sailors tried to tackle the shooter in order to save others and were killed in the attack.Deputies responding to the emergency fatally shot Alshamrani. The incident left three sailors dead and eight injured, including two deputies who were shot in the limbs.The Times reports that one Saudi national was on the scene and videoed the shooting. The FBI has detained this individual alongside with two other Saudis on base for questioning.According to the FBI, Alshamrani was carrying a 9 millimeter Glock 45 pistol with a 33 round magazine and several spare magazines when deputies shot him.FBI special agent in charge Rachel Rojas, who identified the weapon, said the shooter "purchased the weapon legally and lawfully."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 07:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933087/3933087_4426A639CD574C7F9259C0A567005C0A_191210_3933087_The_FBI_is_investigating_Pensacola_base_shooting_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DA4/410/DA44103F07E157D73892A4D430F152B2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Main keyword or keyword phrase you are targeting, a few variations of your main keyword, two to three tags that describe video's overall category, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese woman swallows a massive tube</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGZHOU, CHINA  22-year-old Ms. Lu went to the hospital complaining about some nagging pains after she swallowed a straw, but not all is as it seems.She said she was drinking a bubble tea when she suddenly swallowed the straw, however, on examination, the medical team discovered it was definitely not a straw. The woman was immediately taken for scans at the Third Affiliated Hospital of South Medical University in Guangzhou, where doctors found a long plastic tube measuring 30 centimeters in length and 1.9 centimeters thick, deep in her esophagus and stomach. Fortunately, Doctor Yue Hui removed the mysterious tube from her esophagus, pulling it out through her mouth.The doctor explained that the woman suffered from stomach ulcers as a result of the tube, however, she is expected to make a full recovery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 06:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933067/3933067_20B7853A68F3461CA1C342834819ED90_191210_3933067_Chinese_woman_swallows_a_massive_tube_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61E/E37/61EE37696EFFF620CFCE6B8D2DBDABF8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese woman swallows tube, people doing dumb things, fails, funny fails, Chinese woman swallows 12-inch tube, woman swallows plastic tube, doctor removes tube from Chinese woman, woman swallows straw TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architects propose 'vertical city' of the future</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ITALY  The Italian firm, Luca Curci Architects have proposed 'Vertical City', a project involving a self-sustaining, zero energy building that intends to house 25,000 people. The futuristic city proposes to be settled into the sea bed close to the mainland, accessible by land, sea, and air.The cylindrical residential building would be clad in photovoltaic glazing, a technology that produces electricity from sunlight. Natural light and ventilation will be promoted through hexagonal openings in the building.The 'Vertical City' targets low poverty, no noise, no pollution, desalinization of seawater and producing 1,144,500 KWh of daily solar energy.According to the Italian firm, this new interpretation of urban development would allow its residents to be apart of a "healthier lifestyle" through the connection with the surrounding natural elements; it would also allow residents to re-think the traditional concept of community and society.According to Luca Curci Architects, the 750-meter-tall residential skyscraper would consist of 10 modular layers, each layer consisting of 18 floors, including a mixture of homes, offices, stores and other facilities. The building would also offer more than 200,000 square meters of green space, which includes the public garden at the top of the building.In addition to the 25,000 people housed within the central residential tower, the Vertical City as a whole, including the three adjacent towers that house offices, government departments, healthcare facilities, and educational institutions, would service over 100,000 people who would travel to the city for work, school and medical care."Luca Curci described the plans as a "new way of living." He said the proposal would be more sustainable, more interconnected and most importantly reduce poverty.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 03:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3932995/3932995_9C50FAFD4956490DB41AAA3DBC14A8D4_191210_3932995_Architects_propose__vertical_city__of_the_future_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F1C/6C1/F1C6C16DD904BC4C9E434AA846A97BCD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Luca Curci Architects, Vertical City, Vertical City of the future, Buildings of tomorrow, futuristic buildings, cool architecture, cool buildings, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery stripes on Saturn's ice moon Enceladus finally explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Scientists may have finally solved the mystery of the 'tiger stripes' on Saturn's moon Enceladus.According to a study published in Nature Astronomy, the Cassini probe first detected the four strange fractures on the moon's north pole when the spacecraft orbited around Saturn 15 years ago.According to the researchers, the 'tiger stripes' are about 130 kilometers long, with fracture lines running parallel to one another, spaced at 35 kilometers apart.Lead author Doug Hemingway at the Carnegie Institute for Science says that the fissures constantly blow out water and ice, unlike any other formation known to exist on icy moons.According to the research team, the tiger stripes and the formation's strange behavior is caused by the moon's 'eccentric' orbit around Saturn.Because Enceladus' distance to Saturn fluctuates, planetary gravity stretches and flexes the moon. This effect generates the heat that keeps Enceladus from freezing solid.The gravitational force is so powerful that it changes the shape of the moon, with the resulting stress creating the first tiger stripe on Enceladus.As the moon's surface ocean erupts through the fissure, the jets of water then freeze and fall back on the moon." The weight of the accumulated ice and snow puts pressure on the nearby ice sheet and breaks the crust on parallel lines. Those fractures become the moon's stripes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 10:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933742/3933742_BA23F72CF92C48C2A37E666EEEDEB0FD_191211_3933742_Mystery_stripes_on_Saturn_s_ice_moon_Enceladus_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/27F/4AB/27F4AB6DA2C3DBD1C9F90B8A6C684500.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Enceladus, Saturn, tiger stripes, stripes, icy moon, Carnegie, Carnegie Institute for Science, Cassini, astronomy, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LED fishing nets save turtles and dolphins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM / PERU  Researchers at the University of Exeter and Peruvian NGO ProDelphinus have found that by putting LED lights on top of floating commercial fishing nets, the number of critically endangered species caught in them, can be reduced by 70 percent or moreThe research published in the journal Biological Conservation looked at small-scale vessels departing from three Peruvian ports between 2015 and 2018. LEDs were placed every 30 feet along the float line of 864 illuminated gillnets.Lead author Alessandra Bielli explained that gillnet fisheries often have high bycatch rates of threatened marine species such as sea turtles, whales, dolphins, and seabirds.Saying, "Sensory cues – in this case, LED lights – are one way we might alert such species to the presence of fishing gear in the water."Each gillnet was paired with an unlit gillnet to compare the results. Eighty-six percent of the turtles caught in the unlit nets were green turtles, however, loggerhead and olive ridley turtles were also found in the nets.Among the small cetaceans captured, 47 percent were long-beaked common dolphins, 26 percent were dusky dolphins and 24 percent were Burmeister's porpoises.The findings also support previous research which suggested LED lights reduce bycatch of seabirds in gillnets by about 85 percent.Just as warning lights warn us of danger, the intelligent animals were able to see the illuminated nets, furthermore, the light modification made no change to the amount of commercial catch fisherman caught.Researchers hope the cost-effective nets are promptly adopted by fishermen as more than one-third of the marine mammals and nearly one-third of sharks and fish are currently threatened with extinction due to the consequences of fishing and other human activity.University of Exeter Professor Brendan Godley said, "this work has further shown the usefulness of lights on nets to save wildlife. We now need lights that are ever more robust and affordable."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 06:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933589/3933589_E4EB52C8A48041DB8972ACC014F32595_191211_3933589_LED_fishing_nets_save_turtles_and_dolphins_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/119/D32/119D3281DB09F0A33B98F422136CC2B4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[LED fishing nets, fishing nets, turtles, dolphins, LED nets save turtles, gillnets, gill fishing nets, fishing nets with lights, conservation, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dentist rode hoverboard while pulling patient's tooth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANCHORAGE, ALASKA  A dentist all the way up in Alaska is currently on trial after allegedly yanking out a tooth from a sedated patientall while riding a hoverboard. NBC News reports that according to court records, prosecutors say 34-year-old Seth Lookhart engaged in an "unlawful dental act" that "does not conform to minimum professional standards of dentistry." According to NBC News, the fantastic dentist supposedly performed the tooth extraction on Veronica Wilhelm in July 2016 while he was riding a hoverboard in his office. And how does the world even know about this? Because like a true dumb dumb, Lookhart filmed himself doing it and then had the good sense to send the video to at least eight friends.Investigators say that according to phone records, Lookhart boasted in his text messages that his actions were a "new standard of care." In the video, hovermaster is then seen raising his arms in victory like a true douchebag as he rolls down the hallway. What's worse is that the woman whose tooth that was pulled didn't even know what had happened until investigators contacted her.   Wilhelm said in court that she had to be sedated for the yanking because she is allergic to medicines used for local anesthetics. Unfortunately for Lookhart, he's also facing charges for allegedly engaging in a scam to defraud Medicaid of at least $1.8 million in fraudulent billing and stealing $250,000 from business partners. His own lawyer even apologized to Wilhelm in court, but denied his client was guilty of the other charges he's facing.      Clearly the only practical solution would be to let Wilhelm do all of Lookhart's dental work going forwardon hoverboard, naturally.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 03:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933512/3933512_A170350B38CB4F23A96CCA406E400C53_191211_3933512_Dentist_rode_hoverboard_while_pulling_patient_s__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/982/213/9822133D28A764DCD7754FD3073E0BF4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dentist on hoverboard, dentist hoverboard removing tooth, dentist hoverboard pulling tooth, hoverboard dentist, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian dancer shot for pausing during wedding performance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TIKRA, INDIA  An Indian dancer actually took one in the chin for stopping in the middle of a wedding performance in northern India.   According to the Press Trust of India, the incident occurred on November 30 in Tikra village in the district of Chitrakoot in Uttar Pradesh. Video footage shows the woman dancing for the wedding celebration when the music system develops a bit of a glitch. And what do you do when you're dancing to music and the music stops? You pause and catch a breather. Unfortunately, the 22-year-old dancer, identified only as Hina, caught a bullet to the face instead. Two others in the audience were also lucky enough to sustain minor gunshot wounds as well.According to police, Hina was taken to the hospital where she was treated for her injuries and was said to be out of danger.  Authorities say two men have been arrested for the boneheaded incident and are now facing attempted murder charges.  Hopefully the courts order these two knuckleheads to become dancers at weddings where everyone attending is strapped. That seems fair.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 03:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933509/3933509_CA71CD7114BC4893AA8B13BBFA7C094E_191211_3933509_Indian_dancer_shot_for_pausing_during_wedding_pe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D0F/416/D0F416823ACF5A276DCD0AE474865651.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[India wedding celebration, India wedding dancer, India wedding dancer pauses, wedding dancer takes one in chin, Tikra wedding celebration, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with mosquito-killing farts hired to create insect repellant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAMPALA, UGANDA  Who needs bug spray when you can just toot to make the mosquitoes go away?A Ugandan man called Joe Rwamirama is claiming he lets out farts that can kill mosquitoes.The toxic toots are supposedly lethal only to bugs, not people. Best not to take chances though.The 48-year-old told the Talk of Naija that he doesn't eat anything special, bathes daily and doesn't stink. But for some reason, the mosquitoes can't stand to even lay a foot on him.Must be nice to not know what a mosquito bite feels like.His unusual attribute is pretty famous in his village, where he says no one has ever gotten malaria. Why? Because his gas is so potent and far reaching, it apparently knocks out flying insects over a six-mile radius. What?! Larger than the Hiroshima bomb fallout?!Joe further claims he's been signed on by two companies who want to study his intestinal gas and harness its bug-repelling properties. He won't say which companies, though, only that they're paying him 'millions' according to the Daily Mirror.We're a little skeptical, but who knows, we could be seeing bug spray bottles with Joe's face on them in the not too distant future.Toot on, Joe, toot on.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 17:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934493/3934493_B0165E46B85F441FA36EF33666BE449D_191213_3934493_Man_with_mosquito_killing_farts_hired_to_create__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/60E/041/60E0419DFD5B3BD9B1BB70A1B523EDE3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mosquito killing fart, mosquito fart, toxic fart, deadly fart, mosquito repelling fart, mosquito repelling gas, mosquito repellant, insect repellant, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Jersey City shooting unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JERSEY CITY, NEW JERSEY  Investigators are not sure why two shooters launched a deadly attack at a New Jersey kosher grocery store, federal and state officials said on Wednesday. Reuters reports that six people, including two shooters, three civilians and a police officer, died in a series of events that ended in a police shootout on Tuesday in Jersey City. According to NBC News, New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy, Attorney General Gurbir Grewal and other law enforcement leaders at the state and federal level held a press conference Wednesday to detail what took place during the incident. According to Grewal, it is believed at some point Tuesday, 47-year-old David Anderson and 50-year-old Francine Graham encountered and killed Jersey City police Det. Joseph Seals in the Bayview Cemetery in Jersey City.At roughly 12:21 p.m., a white U-Haul van driven by Anderson parked directly across the street from the JC Kosher Supermarket. Seconds later, Anderson exited the driver side door armed with a rifle as he walked toward the supermarket and immediately began shooting. Graham, who was sitting in the passenger's side of the van, then followed Anderson into the store. Inside the supermarket, the suspects encountered four civilians. Three of these civilians were killed and one survived a gunshot wound. Around 12:38 p.m., a bystander called 911 to report Seals' body in the cemetery. Grewal said that at approximately 12:43 p.m. Jersey City Police Department personnel arrived on scene and engaged the two suspects in an hours-long shootout. At approximately 3:25 p.m., an armored police vehicle broke through the front of the supermarket. Around 3:47 p.m., law enforcement discovered Anderson and Graham's bodies inside the supermarket. According to NBC News, authorities are currently in the process of identifying all available video footage from the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934397/3934397_849D04F3BD2C4862BBDC34704B965134_191212_3934397_How_the_Jersey_City_shooting_unfolded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/009/163/009163B53153766D988A083F9C93DAA2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Jersey City shooting, Jersey City attack, Jersey City shooters, David Anderson shooter, Francine Graham shooter, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESA's spacecraft will take out orbital debris in 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  The European Space Agency has commissioned the world's first mission to capture a piece of space debris from Earth's orbit in 2025.The ESA says that the Swiss startup ClearSpace was awarded with the contract for ClearSpace-1, a spacecraft that will sport four robotic arms for grabbing debris.ClearSpace CEO Luc Piguet says the spacecraft will be a "tow truck" that clears space debris to make room for satellites.According to the ESA, ClearSpace-1 will recover the VESPA, a secondary payload adapter that has been left adrift since it helped deliver the Proba-V satellite to space in 2013.The VESPA is close in size to a small satellite, and its simple shape and sturdy construction makes the adaptor a prime candidate for the experiment.ClearSpace-1 will be launched into a 500-kilometer orbit to undergo testing before it moves up to VESPA's higher orbit, which sits at an altitude of 660 by 800 kilometers.Once in position, ClearSpace-1 will utilize its quartet of arms to catch Vespa under the ESA's supervision.After ClearSpace-1 captures the target, it will return to the Earth's atmosphere and burn up with the VESPA.The ESA says it will refine the chaser's capabilities with the goal of launching follow up missions in the future, including capturing multiple objects.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 12:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934375/3934375_90D4A5532BF84119A1B4621C471D4ABF_191212_3934375_ESA_s_spacecraft_will_take_out_orbital_debris_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E4E/4E0/E4E4E0B15F74AC69FF77392F86ED35A1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[ClearSpace, Clear Space, ClearSpace-1, ClearSpace 1, space debris, VESPA, space junk, satellite, European Space Agency, ESA, space, payload adaptor, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers can access personal data via smart home devices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON  The FBI issued a statement earlier this month warning consumers about smart home devices that could be vulnerable to hacks.This includes smart digital assistants, smart watches, smart refrigerators, home security devices, and gaming systems.FBI officials explained in the statement that these Internet of Things devices are continuously sending and receiving data, but users are typically unaware of how the data is being collected or where exactly it is being transmitted.The agency warned that hackers may be able to conduct a "virtual drive-by" of users' digital lives if they gain access via unsecured devices. This, in turn, gives them access to a user's router and everything connected to their home network.The bureau urged users to change the default password and set unique passwords for every smart home device, as well as store sensitive and private data on a network system separate from the IoT devices.The FBI also recommended updating smart home devices regularly, and checking permissions on mobile apps linked to the smart devices.The agency further encouraged users to turn on automatic updates for software, hardware and operating systems on their smart devices for the latest updates.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 07:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934155/3934155_6377439C71A44ECA8F67C91071435A1E_191212_3934155_Hackers_can_access_personal_data_via_smart_home__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/66D/D7E/66DD7E62F95B621586AE74C84B8D25D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Technology, smart technology, smart home devices, smart technology 2019, smart tech spying, Internet of Things, smart devices spying, smart home devices warning, smart home devices spying, smart devices cameras, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese driver stuck waiting as thousands of geese cross road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANHUI PROVINCE  Why did the goose cross the road? Apparently to join the thousands and thousands of fellow geese on the other side.Hilarious video footage posted to Weibo shows probably the most unlucky driver in the world on some random road in China's Anhui province stuck behind a mini army of geese. The driver, surnamed Yin, filmed his feathery roadblock consisting of a single-file line of geese about the length of the Great Wall.As the geese slowly and surely move in front of Yin, the massively long line can be seen extending off into the horizon. According to Yin, he waited for a good 15 minutes before the owner of the geese showed up to clear a path for him.   Yin then got on his way, while the geese did the same.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 05:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934063/3934063_204F0756ABB442038A3D6EAA4EA7B077_191212_3934063_Chinese_driver_stuck_waiting_as_thousands_of_gee_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/005/476/005476DDD1BCB8A1BEF1AFB38B882A3F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Geese crossing road, thousands of geese cross road, thousands of geese road, driver waits for thousands of geese, China geese crossing, China driving, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozone layer recovery has slowed climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  A new study from the University of New South Wales has found that in addition to allowing the ozone layer to recover, the Montreal Protocol has also slowed the rate of climate change by up to 25 percent.The Montreal Protocol is an international agreement signed by countries around the world in 1987 to stop the import and production of chemicals such as chlorofluorocarbons that are harmful to the earth's ozone layer, after an "ozone hole" was found over Antarctica.The ozone layer protects our planet by deflecting harmful radiation from the sun.Researchers tested out two different scenarios: one in which the Montreal Protocol was brought into effect and another in which the agreement wasn't.Using an estimated 3 percent increase of CFC emissions per year starting from 1987, scientists estimate the Montreal Protocol has likely already helped our planet avoid 0.5 degrees Celsius to 1 degree Celsius of temperature rise over some land areas and 3 degrees Celsius to 4 degrees Celsius of temperature rise across much of the Arctic, as of 2019.The study, published in the journal Environmental Research Letters, estimates that our planet will be at least 1°C cooler by 2050 than it would have been had the agreement not been enacted.Researchers also found that the Arctic summer sea ice extent is roughly 25 percent higher today than it would have been otherwise.The study also suggests that Greenland's melting ice sheet and subsequent sea level rise is happening at a slower speed. Lead author of the paper, Rishav Goyal, said in a University of New South Wales news release that the agreement saved the ozone layer as well as reduced a "substantial fraction" of global warming as CFCs are a thousand times more potent than carbon dioxide.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 04:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934038/3934038_69DB59CE68D44CC5AC0765C41BB6C6E5_191212_3934038_Ozone_layer_recovery_has_slowed_climate_change_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EEC/7A4/EEC7A4F765A4BF137916CD2D49003BB8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Climate change, global warming, Montreal Protocol, montreal protocol 1987, Montreal Protocol success, Montreal Protocol reduced climate change effects, ozone layer, saving the ozone layer, global warming slowed, slowing global warming, global warming ozone layer, climate change ozone layer, montreal protocol ozone depletion, ozone depletion, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell phones to blame for mom's eye disorder</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WAKE FOREST, NORTH CAROLINA  "I'm blind in the morning, basically," said Gretta Nance, a mom from Wake Forest, who can blame her mobile device habits for her eye disorder. Gretta Nance is a brand manager and she spends hours every day switching between her iPhone, Macbook, and television. She, like so many, had perfect vision her entire life, but now, unsurprisingly, is part of a troubling trend that optometrists are seeing.Nance told ABC11 that she essentially wakes up blind, she also stated that by the evenings she can't even watch television because her eyes just want to close. She said that she now keeps bottles of eye drops and several pairs of glasses distributed about her home. She was recently diagnosed with, Meibomian Gland Dysfunction, more commonly known as MGD. Doctors said the condition is common among the older generation, but they are starting to see more cases and younger patients. Optometrists think it's because of our dependence on mobile devices.According to EMarketer.com, people are spending more time staring at their smartphones than watching TV. They say the average American is spending more than three hours every day on their mobile devices, and doctors believe when we're using these devices, our eyes are alert and glued.Dr. Amorette Hanna of Stonehenge Vision Source explained that when we're using digital devices, we blink about 60 percent less. The blink is what triggers the eyelid to secrete oils. Those oils coat the eye and allow us to see clearly without irritation.If you don't blink, the oils are not being replenished and the glands dry out, resulting in permanent damage.Hanna said, "When those glands are lost, unfortunately, there's no way to get them back."X-rays of Wake Forest mum Nance's eyelid, show that her oils have evaporated.So, what're the symptoms of MGD?Dryness. A sandy or gritty feeling. Burning sensation. Eye and lid irritation. Contact lens intolerance. Eyelids sticking together in the morning and or blurry vision.How can you prevent getting MGD?Doctors recommend the 20-20-20 rule. For every 20 minutes you spend on the phone, look away for 20 seconds to something 20 feet away.Nance is now visiting her doctor every six weeks, she said, "This is something I'll have to deal with for the rest of my life. That was probably one of the most shocking things of it: learning I can't get those glands back."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 03:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934023/3934023_9F1934A0512B497BAB4238DFF3812F49_191212_3934023_Cell_phones_to_blame_for_mom_s_eye_disorder_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/447/A4C/447A4C3EC8D5E5D08470B2C1A2194195.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mobile phones and eyes problems, Cell phones cause eye problems, Wake Forest mom eye problems, Meibomian Gland Dysfunction, MGD eye, eye exercise, how to look after eyes, how to keep eyes healthy, eye health videos, eye exercise videos, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bus full of kids evacuated because of too much Axe body spray</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARRISH, FLORIDA  Someone in Florida thought it would be a good idea to prank an entire school bus of kids with a ridiculous amount of Axe deodorant, and it ended just about how you'd expect  BADLY. WFTS reports that on Monday, the bus was on the way to Buffalo Creek Middle School with 30 students on board, when one or a couple of 'em decided to release the kraken. The kraken, in this case, was a crap ton of Axe body spray. Oh, those poor children.Everyone who's caught a whiff of Axe knows that stuff is potent, so just imagine being hotboxed with all of that man deodorant. It was BAD. So bad, it triggered an evacuation. According to Fox News, a second deodorant-free bus had to be called to the scene to take the students to a nearby high school, where parents could then pick them up.No one was seriously injured, but at least 15 middle schoolers were treated for "mild respiratory irritation." Yep, that's the Axe effect.Officials are now reviewing the bus cameras to figure out the mastermind behind the crop-dusting.Dunno about you, but our money's on a coordinated Murder-on-the-Orient-Express-style ploy to get out of school.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 03:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934012/3934012_9E2929FAABDD40A4A5A558C8AADEFCDC_191212_3934012_Bus_full_of_kids_evacuated_because_of_too_much_A_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F5/951/1F5951E7DBF90BD5E5E8B3ECF83F3CB2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Axe prank, axe deodorant, axe body spray, axe bus, axe effect, axe body spray prank, bus evacuation, school bus evacuation, florida school bus, too much axe body spray, too much body spray, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport official axed for making ambulance pick up friends</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  Getting to and from airports these days is annoying enough to make any person want to give up traveling all together. That is unless you have friends in high places. Chinese netizens were outraged yet again over the weekend after a video of an ambulance picking up a group of douchey travelers outside the Shanghai Pudong International Airport went viral.According to a report by Shanghai's airport authority, a manager surnamed Yu called an airport ambulance and demanded the driver race over to Terminal 1 to pick up his wife, kid, and three friends, who had just arrived back from vacation. Oh yeah, they also had a small army of duty-free shopping bags with them. Video shows the ambulance with its lights on parked in a no parking zone as the people load their booty into the emergency vehicle. The ambulance apparently then drove the shopaholics to an airport parking lot.  Nothing like a good old abuse of power to start the day. Unfortunately for Yu, he was given the axe and will also receive a nasty Communist Party finger wagging. As for the ambulance guys, one driver was given the boot while another was given some demerits. And if you're wondering how all the duty-free shopping bags are doing, after being transported to the hospital for a thorough examination, they were released and are doing okay.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 01:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3933980/3933980_4981F56E8E444ABB8B2D26A3BDFE59C1_191212_3933980_Airport_official_axed_for_making_ambulance_pick__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/58F/137/58F1375651AE4E1CB8AC42F84279C32A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China airport ambulance, airport ambulance picks up friends, airport official ambulance friends, ambulance picks up airport passengers, ambulance airport shuttle, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa teen uses Siri to call for help after car plunges into icy river</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MASON CITY, IOWA  An Iowa man was saved from an icy demise after using Siri to call for help.According to KIMT, Gael Salcedo was driving to class when his Jeep hit a frozen patch on the road. He turned right, and ended up plunging into the freezing Winnebago River.When the 18-year-old realized his car was in the river, he quickly rolled the windows down for fear that the vehicle would sink.He also couldn't find his iPhone, but thank god for voice assistants.Salcedo only had to call out "Hey Siri, call 911" for Siri to come through and call for help...and help him find his phone.Mason City firefighters arrived soon after, approaching from the passenger's side because the strong river current was pinning the driver's door shut. They had not so great news for Gael though: he'd have to walk out.So walk out he did  in the freezing cold of the river, while struggling against the current. It was an ordeal, for sure, but with the help of the firefighters, he made it back to land and into an ambulance.Salcedo was treated for shock at the hospital but was released just three hours later.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/14/3935134/3935134_4489B9DA266E4806BAC19E6A90CF1C93_191214_3935134_Iowa_teen_uses_Siri_to_call_for_help_after_car_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/162/67C/16267C2C77EAFFEF339C3240A5578C45.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Siri, voice assistant, iphone voice assistant, siri iphone, iphone siri, siri help, siri call 911, siri call for help, car accident, car drives into river, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch now on sale in China with only one game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  The wait for Chinese video game aficionados is finally over as the Nintendo Switch is now officially on sale.The console, which first hit markets in 2017, can be hooked up to the TV or played on the go. And with over 1900 gamesaccording to Wikipediagamers have no shortage of selection. Only one problem though. In China, video games have to be approved by the super fun-loving government before they can be sold to the public. So remember the 1900 plus games we mentioned earlier? Just subtract all but one from that. That's rightSuper Smash Bros is the only official Nintendo game you can buy in China if you drop $298 for the Switch console. According to BBC, in order to do business in China, Nintendo was forced to partner with Chinese firm Tencent. Nintendo is hoping Mario Kart 8 Deluxe and Mario Odyssey will also be added to their amazing China selection, but have yet to be given the old Panda nod. They said they hope to have between 10 and 20 games for the China Switch by the end of 2020. Ten to 20?? Let's be real, they may not be able to even get that many. But with a power packed selection like that, Chinese gamers will no doubt SWITCH in no time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3935011/3935011_14BE1B7C52F044B1B784DB0C0CEA6F69_191213_3935011_Nintendo_Switch_now_on_sale_in_China_with_only_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/795/A98/795A986B3B9057067F048F86830D6BCA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch, Nintendo Switch China, Nintendo Switch China one game, Nintendo Switch console on sale in China, China Nintendo, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bald eagle seconds away from becoming dinner for octopus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER ISLAND, CANADA  A bald eagle who almost became the main course for a hungry octopus off the coast of Vancouver Island will luckily live to fly another day after the intervention of some Canadian salmon fishermen. According to CNN, the group was on the way back to their float house when they heard screeching and splashing sounds last Monday.According to salmon farmer John Ilett, the guys found "a full-sized eagle submerged in the water with a big giant octopus in the water trying to drag it down."The fishermen had a front row seat to mother nature for about five minutes as they went back and forth on whether or not they should intervene. Ilett said, "we weren't sure if we should interfere because it is mother nature, survival of the fittest. But it was heart wrenching  to see this octopus was trying to drown this eagle."The salmon fishermen maneuvered their boat closer, so Ilett could reach out with a pole. He was able to use the pole to latch onto the octopus and give it a bit of a tug, which then caused it to release its death grip on the eagle. The eagle then hightailed it over to the shore as quickly as possible, while the octopus disappeared back down into the water.  The men didn't see how the eagle got all wrapped up, but Ilett guesses our feathery friend tried to grab the octopus out of the water, but then became prey himself. Guess that's what you call biting off more than you can chew.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3935005/3935005_F1EAA3DAC8BC46DA91E1BBCA4FBC8BE7_191213_3935005_Bald_eagle_seconds_away_from_becoming_dinner_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/42D/D89/42DD890B6E68504B19B61F7767BA8F93.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bald eagle attacked by octopus, Bald eagle v octopus, fishermen rescue eagle octopus, fishermen rescue eagle from octopus, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinkhole swallows road, cars in Xiamen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIAMEN, CHINA  A massive sinkhole swallowed up several cars and part of a busy road intersection in Xiamen, China at 9:50 pm on Thursday, Chinese officials told China News.The state-run media reports that 500 square meters of the road had collapsed near Xiamen Metro's Lucuo Station. Social media footage on China News shows at least two cars that had fallen into the pit. Chinese officials told the outlet that all personnel trapped in the sinkhole had been rescued and that no one was injured in the incident.According to China News, an underground pipe or pipes was damaged during the incident and caused flooding to the area.Citing Chinese netizens on Weibo, Taiwan's Liberty Times speculated that the water main might have been damaged prior to the incident and had caused the collapse to occur.The incident went viral on Chinese social media and netizens posted videos of brown water inundating Lucuo station up to ankle depth.Chinese officials say that the subway system will resume normal operations by 8:30pm on Friday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 11:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934950/3934950_07EE9FBD2B564C1B83AE27722BBCB06A_191213_3934950_Sinkhole_swallows_road__cars_in_Xiamen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2F8/930/2F8930713E755202E05C2E86DACCA924.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sinkhole, collapse, cars, car, flooding, subway, Xiamen, China, Xiamen metro, amtr]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New recluse spider species discovered in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY  Biologists at the National Autonomous University of Mexico said they have discovered a new species of recluse spiders named Loxosceles tenochtitlan in Mexico Valley.Quoting a researcher, El Universal reports that the spider has a distinctive dark brown coloring and a clear violin pattern on its dorsal section.According to the university's press release, the spider is set apart from other recluse spiders by its sensing appendages and sexual organs of its females.The spider also possesses a venomous bite that it utilizes as a defense mechanism.The bite causes a blue-purple ulcer on the victim that could be hard to identify clinically because it is not painful and symptoms could be confused with a common rash or infection.Biologist Valdez-Mondragon told El Universal that the spider lives in urban homes because the environment provides suitable humidity, heat and prey.The spider favors hiding in tight spots and eats cockroaches, so they could be encountered in trash cans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934818/3934818_3C2B73D101E64B9C9ECF5A0197894768_191213_3934818_New_recluse_spider_species_discovered_in_Mexico_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E3E/FA9/E3EFA988B81E84EED873FD71F3881523.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Loxosceles tenochtitlan, spider, recluse spiders, violin spiders, venom, science, biology, Mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiamen subway collapses in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIAMEN, CHINA  A subway in Xiamen, China has collapsed.At around 9:52 last night, a sinkhole suddenly opened up. The collapse damaged underground water pipes, leading to a burst of sewage flooding the station and railroad tracks. The underground soil was washed away, causing the road surface to sink and form a 500 square meter hole. Two cars fell into the hole created by the collapse, the two drivers were able to evacuate safely.Xiamen Metro Line 2 just passed examination 2 weeks ago with officials claiming the construction as good. It is unclear if people have been trapped or injured due to the collapse.As of 8:30 (GMT+8) this morning, all subway lines have resumed operation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 03:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934589/3934589_2CAF566CAA274661A1299B76FA96F851_191213_3934589_Xiamen_subway_collapses_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/003/D46/003D4658C713124D5758F0276FD102AD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Xiamen collapse, Xiamen sinkhole,  Xiamen subway collapse, Chinese sinkholes, Chines subway station accident, sinkhole accident, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as 'hundreds' of birds found dead in the road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANGLESEY, U.K.  Hundreds of starlings have been found lifeless on a lane in Anglesey, North Wales. The 200 plus birds were spotted by Hannah Stevens on Tuesday afternoon when she was on her way to an appointment; she saw the flock flying in the sky, however, about an hour later she found the birds dead in the road with blood on their bodies. She got on the phone and called her partner, Dafydd Edwards.41-year-old Edwards told Sky News that when his partner first saw the birds, "they took off to the fieldsand she thought, 'Oh, that was a large number of birds', and then on her way back she found them all dead in the road."Mr. Edwards said, "It was very distressingmy gut instinct is that they have been poisoned, but we don't know." His partner, Ms. Stevens reported seeing the birds eating something in the road.The couple has since contacted the police and the Animal and Plant Health Agency who they say are looking into the incident. RSPB Wales told Sky News: "We are concerned with what we have seen."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 01:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934556/3934556_F101116D95334C60814E4D4B24882C50_191213_3934556_Mystery_as__hundreds__of_birds_found_dead_in_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D22/C00/D22C00A9645A18D2E2F0956B1FF17FB6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Birds fall from the sky, mysterious birds fall from sky, mystery murder, UK birds found dead in road, hundreds of birds found dead, birds falling from the sky, M=mystery as hundreds of birds found dead in the dead, RSPB Wales, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland's glaciers are melting at worst-case scenario rates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GREENLAND  A new study using satellite images finds that Greenland's glacier melt is accelerating, the study's authors wrote in an article published in the journal Nature. The study says the pace of melting matches the worse climate warming and sea-level scenarios predicted by the U.N.The Guardian reports that according to the data, Greenland has lost 3.8 trillion tonnes of ice since 1992 and that the current rate of melting is seven times faster than compared to the nineties. Study co-author Andrew Shepard says that Greenland has raised the sea level by one centimeter since the 1990s, enough to bring annual and seasonal floods to six million people.He tells the Washington Post that the U.N.'s worst-case scenarios predict that  Greenland will contribute another 16 centimeters of sea-level rise by 2100.While seawater normally erodes the glaciers, the study finds that rising summer temperatures are turning exposed ice to meltwater, which makes the shelf melt faster.The study additionally finds that glaciers are flowing faster into the deep waters of Greenland's fjords and that this makes the ice shelf break into pieces in the ocean.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 08:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/14/3935281/3935281_48186F235F00457A92E5FFBDC3887E72_191214_3935281_Greenland_s_glaciers_are_melting_at_worst_case_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Greenland, glaciers, melting glaciers, ice sheet, ice loss, glacier retreat, climate change, climate warming, global warming, sea-level, sea-levels, environment, science, IMBE, Ice Sheet Mass Balance Inter-comparison Exercise]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using sunlight to convert plastic into green fuel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE   Researchers at the Nanyang Technological University this week said they have found a way to use sunlight to turn consumer plastic into a valuable chemical that could generate clean power. They reported their findings in the journal Advanced Science.Speaking in a university news release, the team said dissolved polyethylene in a solution that contained a vanadium-based catalyst.Vanadium is a metal commonly used in steel and aluminum alloys for vehicles and aircraft.The researchers exposed the solution to artificial sunlight, which breaks the carbon bonds in polyethylene and transforms the substance into formic acid.While other conversion methods exist, the scientists said their process does not use high heat or toxic substances to produce formic acid from plastics.They explained that formic acid is utilized for power generation in hydrogen fuel cells which could be a low-emissions source of clean energy.The researchers say they are working to scale up the technology to help Singapore to turn its plastic waste into energy resources without harming the environment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 08:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/14/3935269/3935269_9CA41691B3DE4AEFA2F8BA7CEBB6B2FB_191214_3935269_Using_sunlight_to_convert_plastic_into_green_fue_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4D3/A9C/4D3A9C8D429C192E78D54942B9A65369.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plastics, plastic, formic acid, conversion, sunlight, recycling, carbon emissions, alternative energy, green energy, hydrogen fuel cells, fuel cells, hydrogen fuel cell, fuel cell, Singapore, Nanyang Technological University, NTU Singapore]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian girls go gaga over bizarre wavy lip trend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUSSIA  Talk about next-level lip contouring.The New York Post reports that ladies in Russia are going gaga over devil or octopus lips  a bizarre new beauty trend where the lip line is wavy or scalloped. Essentially, it's the lip filler's edgier cousin.No one's entirely sure when, where, and WHY it started, but Russian plastic surgeon Emelian Braude claims we have him to thank for it. Thanks but no thanks, Doc.As with most weird trends, opinions on the devil lip range from "What fresh hell did you rise out of??!" to "Ohmygod take my money!" A lot of folks don't believe it's a real thing that exists either, claiming that it's nothing but a Photoshop job.To settle the score, Dazed Digital consulted dental surgeon and facial aesthetician Dr. Krystyna Wilczyński, who says they're unnatural, and can't be legit.She claims that to achieve this, you'd have to be injecting filler inappropriately, and basically letting it block the blood vessels around the lips, which is definitely not safe.Thing is, the images going around the interwebs is so convincing some ladies might actually go out to get fillers to achieve the look.Beauty influencer Nilam Holmes warns that that kind of lip job isn't easily reversible, and is going to distort the lip border. When it wears off, it won't do so evenly, so best be prepared for frilly octopus puckers for years to come. If this wavy devil lip is really your jam, maybe try hacking it through makeup instead of messing up your pouters.Just get yourself a drag queen and learn to paint face the non-permanent way.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936278/3936278_B8BE9764965944DEA52AA1C260457986_191216_3936278_Russian_girls_go_gaga_over_bizarre_wavy_lip_tren_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BEF/E0D/BEFE0DEAABA0D746EBB534D71C89F43D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Devil lips, octopus lips, wavy lips, lip fillers, wavy lip trend, russian lip trend, bizarre beauty trend, scalloped lips, photoshopped lips, lip contouring, lip surgery, plastic surgery, botched, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker steals $88,000 from bank, arrested after social media posts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO  An ex-employee was busted by the FBI on Dec. 4 for allegedly stealing over $88,000 in cash from a Wells Fargo vault in North Carolina. He might have gotten away with it tooprobably notif only it weren't for his damn social media posts.  According to an unsealed indictment released last Friday by the United States Attorney's Office for the Western District of North Carolina, 29-year-old Arlando Henderson had access to the Wells Fargo vault in Charlotte where he worked. According to the indictment, on at least 18 occasions in 2019 he stole money from cash deposits made by the bank's customers to the vault, and then deposited some of it at a nearby ATM. The indictment alleges that Henderson then destroyed certain documents and madeor caused others to makefalse entries in the bank's books and records to cover his tracks.   He is accused of using the cash to pay for personal expenses, including a $20,000 down payment on a 2019 Mercedes-Benz. Why do we know any of this? Because between July and August 2019, Henderson had the genius to hop on Facebook and Instagram to post a boatload of pictures with him holding huge stacks of cash. Henderson is now facing a ton of charges, including two counts of financial institution fraud and 19 counts of theft. Guess it's time for a new Facebook update.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936218/3936218_F80BF7B310B64A26B6190B8294172CE3_191216_3936218_Worker_steals__88_000_from_bank__arrested_after__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/49B/868/49B868656654217162E8F4967745332A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dumb criminals, stupid criminals, man poses with stolen money, man poses with stolen cash, worker steals $88,000 from vault, bank worker steals, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muscular kangaroo is harassing people and tearing up gardens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA  A six-foot and ripped kangaroo has been wreaking havoc Down Under, attacking three people in recent months.According to LadBible, the kangaroo from Queensland has already had run ins with a tourist from New Zealand, the wife of a bar owner and an elderly woman. According to Stuff, the unnamed Kiwi was in town for a wedding when he got up close and personal with the towering kangaroo. The massive marsupial put its paws on the man's shoulders and was about to kick him, before it was scared off.  The next unlucky victim was the wife of bar owner Shane Toy, who was outside of the pub when she was attacked by the kangaroo a few months ago.   Luckily, a customer armed with a bar stool came to his wife's rescue. They all then locked themselves in the pub until the kangaroo bounced. Then last week, according to 7 News, a 72-year-old woman was out walking her dog when she got jumpedliterally.   Apparently, the roo snuck up from behind and shoved the woman down to the ground and scratched up her shoulders, legs and torso.  But like a true soldier, the woman declined an offer by paramedics to be transported to the hospital. The local police have since been notified and are now tracking the kangaroo.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936212/3936212_F80CB7BB9D1F48B5ACE8A148F765D315_191216_3936212_Muscular_kangaroo_is_harassing_people_and_tearin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8AA/DF4/8AADF477BFBB6D9868F27EDB6216E4E9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Kangaroo, muscular kangaroo, kangaroo attacks, muscular kangaroo attacks, muscular kangaroo bad attitude, Australia kangaroos, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Monster black hole' might not be so monster after all</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Two new studies have called into question the size of the "impossibly big" black hole named LB-1, according to the papers published independently to the arXiv database.A team led by Chinese astronomer Liu Jinfeng claimed that LB-1 is 70 times the mass of the sun, bigger than the 20-solar-mass models predicted for black holes in our galaxy.'The papers found the same basic problem with the Chinese researchers claim: it relied on evidence that the unseen black hole was wiggling very slightly as its heavy companion star wheeled around it." The new studies claim that the initial team misinterpreted what they were seeing in the light from the distant system.Movements from LB-1 create spectral light via doppler effect called H alpha line emissions."The Chinese team used China's powerful LAMOST telescope to detect H alpha line emissions, then used the black hole's movements to infer its mass."The authors of the new studies argue that the original team did not properly adjust for the emissions from LB1's star, which also emits H alpha, according to Live Science.Astrophysicists El-Badry and Quataert write in their paper that after factoring in the star, the data suggests LB1 is far more likely to be a sun-sized black hole.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936201/3936201_E03E02B6E4E84F6197F8DDE0C06754FB_191216_3936201__Monster_black_hole__might_not_be_so_monster_aft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/906/FE8/906FE83E3CBF92ABB37CBA1DADA015CA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Black hole, monster black hole, stellar black hole, LB-1, LB1, milky way galaxy, galaxy, Chinese Academy of Sciences, LAMOST, h alpha line, h alpha emission, space, astronomy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How plants make noise when stressed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEL AVIV, ISRAEL  New research from Tel Aviv University has found that plants make noise when stressed.For the study, scientists focused on tomato and tobacco plants.They placed plants into three groups. These were drought-stressed plants, plants cut at the stem and control plants. These were placed in an acoustic box for an hour.Each plant was recorded with two microphones placed 10 centimeters away.On average, drought-stressed tomato plants emitted roughly 35 ultrasonic sounds per hour, while tobacco plants produced 11 per hour. Cut tomato plants created roughly 25 sounds per hour, while tobacco plants generated 15.The study found that all control plants produced, on average, less than one sound per hour.The scientists explained in the study that these sounds could potentially be heard by other organisms up to several meters away.The tomato plants were also placed in a greenhouse setting to test whether or not sounds emitted by plants would be identified outdoors. The results matched researchers' findings from the plants in the acoustic box in that plants produce more sounds as they become dehydrated.Machine learning classifiers were able to distinguish distinct noises produced by the different plants in both the acoustic box and the greenhouse setting.Researchers suggested that in the future, farmers may be able to use this type of technology to listen out for drought-stressed crops to better assess their crops.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 02:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3935825/3935825_D0CF564CEDF14532A890B604BBA9B699_191216_3935825_How_plants_make_noise_when_stressed_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ACF/09C/ACF09C60D771D9428EF68569AD6EE48F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plants, plants under stress, plant stress, plant stress sounds, plant sounds, tobacco plants, airborne sounds plants, plant stress reaction, tomato plants, plants can talk, plants make sounds, plants make ultrasonic noises, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA hones in on asteroid sample site</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANSICO, CALIFORNIA  NASA has selected a target site for the spacecraft  OSIRIS[i]-REx[j] to gather samples on the asteroid Bennu, according to the mission's principal investigator.In a statement made at the American Geophysical Union annual conference last week, principal investigator Dante Lauretta said the spacecraft has been orbiting Bennu since December 2018.Lauretta says that Nightingale lies far to the asteroid's north, with cooler temperatures than other possible sites.This means Nightingale's surface would preserve more materials dated back to Bennu's formation for the probe to collect.Citing Lauretta, Science News reports that Nightingale is a 20-meter wide crater contained in a larger crater and that parking the six-meter wide spacecraft could be a 'tight fit'." The New York Times reports that Bennu is one of the oldest rocks in the solar system and that the asteroid is rich in carbon and organic substances like hydrated minerals."The spacecraft will touch down on Bennu for only a split-second next year and deploy its robotic arm to gather a sample.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936794/3936794_8BC5064CC29E47E7B361B2AC46212C1C_191217_3936794_NASA_hones_in_on_asteroid_sample_site_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/029/561/0295613F3F44136DCDCC9ACB4916CA21.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Osiris-rex, Osiris, spacecraft, space probe, probe, asteroid, asteroid Bennu, Bennu, nightingale,  NASA, US, space, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA wants to put antennas on the far side of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Space researchers have proposed building a network of radio antennas on the far side of the moon, according to a NASA funded report.NASA says that the arraynamed the Farside antennaswill allow the agency to monitor the closest stellar systems more easily.The paper's lead authors professors Jack Burns and Gregg Hallinan suggest deploying 128 antennas by using a lunar rover.The antennas will be tethered to a base station that supplies central data processing, power and communications across the array's 10 kilometer span.The Farside base then will use NASA's proposed Gateway Station to transmit signals back to Earth.Habitable exoplanets closest to the solar system would possess magnetospheres that the antennas will be able to detect from the moon's far side, where there is limited sky noise.The study states that the antennas could also sound the moon's subsurface.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936777/3936777_0646EB5DB72B4CB69BCDE25E5E237BD7_191217_3936777_NASA_wants_to_put_antennas_on_the_far_side_of_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/64E/660/64E66091625E65979106B1755CA1ED90.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Farside antennas, low frequency antennas, farside project, far side of the moon, exoplanets, exoplanet, deep space, space, space exploration, Blue Origins, US, NASA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man folded in half for 28 years finally stands straight up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA   A Chinese man is looking at the world from a whole new perspective now that he's finally able to stand straight after suffering from an aggressive form of arthritis that left his face jammed up against his thighs for almost three decades. According to Chinese media, 46-year-old Li Hua was diagnosed with ankylosing spondylitis in 1991 when he was only 18. The intense pain in his joints forced him to become more and more hunchbacked over time. His family from the Hunan city of Yongzhou didn't have the money to get medical treatment so his entire upper body eventually folded onto his lower limbs in a permanent bending pose. According to Li, his condition got a lot worse over the past five years to the point where he couldn't sit up straight or lie down flat, and was having trouble eating and drinking.Surgeons from the Shenzhen University General Hospital broke and rebuilt Li's entire spine in a series of four operations this year.During the four-phase surgery, Li was able to first sit up, then lift his head, then lie flat. Li is now able to stand tall after 28 year long years. He is now able to get around with the help of a walker, and should regain normal mobility with a couple of months of physical therapy. Guess things really are looking up for Li.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936752/3936752_F8EDCD33645E4483BF574DF02D0D85A8_191217_3936752_Man_folded_in_half_for_28_years_finally_stands_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A9A/691/A9A691791F61F67AB36FDB440583C140.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man folded in half, man folded in half 28 years, Chinese man folded in half, man folded in half stands, man folded in half stands straight, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guy rescues dog after leash gets caught in elevator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON  A Pomeranian from H-town is probably wishing for a new owner after being rescued by a 27-year-old man when its leash got caught in an elevator door.Security camera footage captured the heart-pounding moment Johnny Mathis saved the little pooch from becoming elevator dinner. Mathis told NBC News that he was coming home late from work last Monday night and exited the lift on the floor to his apartment. That's when a new tenant walked into the elevator dragging her dog on a leash behind her.Most pet owners would probably check if their animals made it in before shutting the doors. This woman doesn't appear to be one of those. Video Mathis filmed from his building's security camera shows the elevator doors shut on the dog's leash. Mathis is seen running over to the Pomeranian and struggling to free the dog from its leash as the elevator was heading up to the top floor. He told NBC News, "I tried to break it at first. I tried to lean down on it with all my weight but it wouldn't snap. Luckily Mathis was able to get the collar off and save the doggo just in the nick of time.Pay attention to your pets people...or just don't have any. Have some kids instead. Those are much easier to handle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 10:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936694/3936694_A754410A04314B3A9806FA1EC9D20A5D_191217_3936694_Guy_rescues_dog_after_leash_gets_caught_in_eleva_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6A1/7C9/6A17C94D86F2BF1F39CE8110FC38923F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man rescues dog, dog rescued by man, dog leash caught in elevator, leash caught in elevator, man saves dog, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobras are invading home toilets in Jakarta</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST JAKARTA, INDONESIA  Imagine going to your bathroom and coming face to face with a cobra rearing its flared head.That's the kind of terror residents in West Jakarta, Indonesia faced on Sunday after tens of the venomous snakes invaded their crappers.All in all, there were 18 cobras averaging a length of 20 centimeters, which took four firemen 30 minutes to round up. They will eventually be handed over to the Indonesia Sioux Snake Foundation.The Jakarta Post reports that according to a homeowner named Hera, the snakes crept inside through the drainage system, which is connected to a warehouse.Workers there had previously encountered snakes too, likely because of its proximity to a cemetery and plot of land where bamboo trees grow and where the cobras breed.The cemetery was just renovated, so the slippery serpents were probably scouting for a new pad when residents spotted them in the toilets and slithering into bedroom. According to reptile observer Arbi Krisna, the snake invasion isn't surprising, since we're in the middle of snake hatching season. So peep before you pee, and make sure to clean the moist, dark, and quiet places where snakes lay their eggs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936685/3936685_0C63B99F1FA14ABFB1D3112631772765_191217_3936685_Cobras_are_invading_home_toilets_in_Jakarta_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/285/F7E/285F7EF33215AFB18C0A02CBD2A60EFA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cobra in the toilet, cobras in toilet, snakes in toilet, cobras terrorizing Jakarta, cobras terrorizing Indonesians, cobra invasion, snake invasion, cobra hatching season, snake hatching season, cobra eggs TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the brain sees the world</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANNOVER / NEW HAMPSHIRE  Researchers say that the visual world humans perceive is produced by parts of the brain lying outside of the visual cortex, according to a new study published in Current Biology.Dartmouth College says that the findings have significant implications for the debate about what human consciousness is and where it occurs in the brain, in a press release dated to December 13.The study used MRI technology to scan test subjects who observed a screen displaying a visual illusion created by the so-called Gabor patch.As the patch moves in one direction, the flickering shape tricks the brain into seeing that it is moving in a perceived path that is different from its actual path.According to the study, the brain scans then allowed researchers to identify the visual cortex as the area of the brain that senses the patch’s actual physical path.Further, the scans showed that seeing the illusion directly corresponds to activity in the frontal lobes. This suggests that the frontal lobes also process visual information. According to co-author Patrick Cavanagh, the study establishes that the frontal lobes are not only responsible for decision making and thinking, but also provides the end step for perceiving where objects are.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936698/3936698_D80E2A7698284D75AD29BA1DB5E075C1_191217_3936698_How_the_brain_sees_the_world_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Brain,frontal lobes,visual cortex,visual processing,cognition,consciousness,visual perception,optical illusion,Dartmouth College,Hannover,US,neuroscience,psychology,science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are a million times more microplastics in the ocean: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO  A new study from the Scripps Institution of Oceanography at the University of California San Diego suggests that the ocean could potentially contain a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought.Researchers say that past methods used for collecting microplastic samples, such as net tows, were inadequate as smaller plastic particles are able to escape through the holes of the net.For the study, the team developed a new technique to gather microplastics from the ocean surface.Researchers took three different cruises during three different time periods between 2009 to 2015 to gather surface seawater samples in metal buckets from the open ocean and near the shore. The samples were promptly filtered with polycarbonate filters and then frozen.Scientists also gathered 100 salp samples from the sea in 2009, 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2017 using mesh bongo nets. Salps are gelatinous creatures that suck in seawater for food as well as to propel themselves in the ocean.The study found that nearshore samples of seawater had a higher concentration of plastic than samples obtained from the open sea. Researchers then analysed the salps via epifluorescence microscopy and found that every single salp sample contained tiny microplastic pieces in their gut.Scientists estimated that the sea is contaminated by roughly 8.3 million pieces of "mini-microplastics," or the smallest microplastics, per cubic meter of water.Lead author of the study, Jennifer Brandon, explained in a news release from the university that even though salps are low in the ocean's food chain, these microplastic particles could eventually make their way up the food chain and one day end up in the human body.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 09:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936609/3936609_6DFF4D46AA5D436E909E8952D3A784E3_191217_3936609_There_are_a_million_times_more_microplastics_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/638/382/6383823863CE87603582987CCCDFBFE3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Microplastics, microplastic contamination, microplastics in the ocean, microplastics ocean pollution, plastic fiber, microscopic plastic, mini-microplastics, plastic pollution, plastic contamination, plastic particles, plastic particles in the ocean, ocean plastic, microplastic particles in the ocean, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook serves ads based on your offline shopping habits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook is able to gather data about user shopping habits, both online and offline, in order to serve targeted ads on its platform, according to a new report by Business Insider.The report says that Facebook acquires information about user purchases via its partnerships with retailers.It explains that when a consumer buys a product from a physical or online store, the retailer can retain purchase details and user information such as name, email, or phone number.This could be sent to Facebook if they want to display targeted ads to the consumer.Facebook then matches the information to a user's profile and starts displaying ads from the retail stores directly to the consumer.The company says this allows them to create a custom audience from the acquired information, allowing them to show targeted ads to Facebook users that have shopped at the store.According to Business Insider, retailers such as Macy's and Dick's Sporting Goods are using these advertising techniques to increase sales.The report mentioned that Facebook users have the option of opting out of targeted ads, by clicking the 'Not allowed' option on their Facebook ad setting page.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 02:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936387/3936387_1DA9C3940E1742F5B944A8C4A2A5A713_191217_3936387_Facebook_serves_ads_based_on_your_offline_shoppi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/803/834/80383414BAB39853B7CB3C423125C29E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Facebook, Facebook ads 2019, facebook controversies, facebook scandals, facebook hidden codes,  facebook privacy, facebook user data scandal, facebook privacy concerns, Facebook tracking, facebook tracking you at physical stores, facebook physical stores, facebook ads privacy, facebook tracks users offline, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China blocks football game over player's Uyghur tweet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Arsenal's German midfielder, Mesut Ozil took to social media to condemn China's treatment of Uyghur Muslims. China retaliated by removing Arsenal's English Premier League fixture from state TV.In his social media post, Ozil, who is a Muslim, called Uighurs, "warriors who resist persecution" and criticized both China and the silence of Muslims in response. China, however, denies the mistreatment of Muslims and always has, standing by the fact they are instead being "educated" in "vocational training centers" to combat violent religious extremism. The Global Times, a Chinese state-run paper, described Ozil's comments as "false" and claimed he had "disappointed" football authorities. The Chinese Football Association said Ozil's comments were "unacceptable" and had "hurt the feelings" of Chinese fans. The BBC reported that CCTV instead showed Sunday's game between Tottenham and Wolves.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936369/3936369_EDC9588BDDF04A698925ADBE4DEA4F34_191217_3936369_China_blocks_football_game_over_player_s_Uyghur__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AA/76F/1AA76F153A522885B06542FB46250A83.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Arsenal, Man City, Mesut Ozil, China bans Mesut Ozil, Mesut Ozil China, Mesut Ozil Muslim, Uyghur, Uyghur coverup, Chinese censorship, Chinese censor, English premiere league news, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company to impose smell check for bathroom time over 10 mins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOME STINKIN' COMPANY  A crappy company is raising eyebrows and middle fingers after it put up a sign threatening smell checks for employees who are in the bathroom for too long.Fox News reports that the sign was posted on a workplace bathroom at an unidentified business, and first appeared on Reddit. The text reads: "If in bathroom for more than 10 minutes, a smell check will be completed to ensure employee not on phone." Presumably, the new measure is an attempt to reclaim company time and prevent workers from slacking off on the toilet.The sign goes on to say that if no stink is sniffed, then the employee in question would then be "reported to office."It's such a ridiculous scenario, many are wondering if it's a joke, or who the stinkin' manager is that came up with such a crappy idea.Everyone agrees though, that there's only one loser here: the poor schmuck who has to be on sniff duty.Because honestly, if that's how management wants to play this game, it's easy enough to comply.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/18/3937368/3937368_8821666D3F114E86A4A2EC06E533A24A_191218_3937368_Company_to_impose_smell_check_for_bathroom_time__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E89/3B8/E893B8A6B2EADF2ABBDA1100ECB84AD8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Smell check, bathroom time limit, restroom time limit, work restroom, work bathroom, toilet phone, restroom sign, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA, Lockheed Martin to build 'quiet' jet for supersonic air travel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA has cleared the final assembly of Lockheed Martin's quiet supersonic jet prototype, the agency says in a news release on Tuesday.Lockheed Martin says that X-59 aircraft will be a model for quiet, faster-than-sound passenger jets.Lockheed Martin states that the X-59 will be able to cruise at an altitude of 55,000 feet and achieve an airspeed of 940 miles per hour.The corporation claims technology derived from the jet will cut air travel time by half.According to NASA, the X-59's shape is specially designed to mitigate sonic boom by reducing the noise that reaches the ground.Lockheed Martin says that the airplane makes 75 Perceived Level decibels, or about as loud as a closing car door.According to NASA, the jet will feature cameras and sensors that allow safe flying without a forward-facing window.NASA says the finished jet will fly over select US communities to create instrument readings and to measure the public's opinion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/18/3937359/3937359_62FD4AA1ADC04ED8A4FD60671E4CC744_191218_3937359_NASA__Lockheed_Martin_to_build__quiet__jet_for_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/85A/964/85A9645A7955438A4B670FB281DC3049.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[X-59, X59, prototype, quiet jet, supersonic jet, jet prototype, supersonic, Lockheed Martin, Lockheed, US, NASA, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jacks $500 of shrimp by shoving it in his pants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIVERSIDE, CALIFORNIA  California cops are looking for a small-time crook who apparently is really into frozen shrimp. You could say he thinks they're SHRIMPRY the best.According to KTLA, police are on the hunt for a man who jammed 30 bags of shrimp down his pants and lifted them from a Riverside grocery store.Riverside police said in a press release that the "Shrimp Bandit" stuffed the frozen shellfish down his trousers in the frozen-food section of a Vons supermarket. The incident occurred around 12:30 p.m. on Dec. 4. Investigators say the super shrimp fan had to make three separate trips over 15 minutes with his trousers packed full of frozen goodies to complete the heist. KTLA reports that the man was caught on surveillance camera leaving the store. Police say he is a white dude in his 50s, about 5-foot-10 and between 150 and 180 pounds, plus or minus the 30 bags of shrimp on his person.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 12:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937847/3937847_10499315310544EA9E1C16034FDE0B5F_191219_3937847_Man_jacks__500_of_shrimp_by_shoving_it_in_his_pa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/320/1C0/3201C0775A9836990F14EA5D866F718B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man steals shrimp, man steals frozen shrimp, man steals shrimp in pants, man shoves shrimp in pants, Shrimp Bandit, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter Island Moai statues may have helped ancient farmers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EASTER ISLAND / CHILE  Easter Island's Moai[e] stone monoliths might have been created out of the belief they would make crops more fertile, according to new research by the University of California, Los Angeles.According to a UCLA press release, ancient Easter Islanders built over 1,000 Moai statues under the direction of the ruling elite in a remarkable feat of human engineering.According to the study, published in the Journal of Archeological Sciences, Rano Raraku quarry is the origin point for over 95 percent of all Moai statues.Researchers studied two monoliths found in the quarry and took extensive soil samples from the surrounding areas.Analysis by the researchers found that quarrying would have helped in releasing clay soil that is rich in phosphorus and calcium.Those elements would have helped the growth of bananas, sweet potatoes and taro that Easter Islanders grew extensively near the quarry.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937705/3937705_4ADB29922DF045E7AACF7C48855A6048_191219_3937705_Easter_Island_Moai_statues_may_have_helped_ancie_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D70/F6F/D70F6F82D92A07483509A5014DC4AD90.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Moai, statues, statue, monoliths, monolith, Easter Island, Chile, archeology, UCLA, agriculture, Rano Rakaru, quarry, quarrying, crops, archeology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company unveils new slanted toilets to reduce bathroom breaks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STAFFORD, UNITED KINGDOM  British company StandardToilet has unveiled a new design in which the toilet is tilted downwards at a 13 degree angle in a bid to reduce the amount of time spent in the bathroom.The design has been approved by the British Toilet Association, an organization that advocates for better toilet facilities across the United Kingdom.Founder of the StandardToilet, Mahabir Gill, explained to Wired that the toilet is designed to cause strain on the legs, like squat thrusts, and make you want to get up after about five minutes of use.The company says the toilet provides health benefits such as reducing haemorrhoids, musculoskeletal disorder and improving a person's posture.The company's website states that the toilet uses a water saving dual-flush system and includes specially designed slots in the toilet's rim that would allow for a quieter, more uniform flush.In a press release from the British Toilet Association, StandardToilet explains that the toilet would reduce long lines for public bathrooms in shopping malls, train stations and other public spaces.The company also says the toilet's new design would minimize the amount of time employees spend in the restroom during bathroom breaks. In the press release, StandardToilet noted that the workplace bathroom has become a space for texting and using social media.The company's founder told Wired that the toilet would mainly benefit employers not employees, with a primary focus on reducing the amount of time spent by employees on their phone while working.The toilet is currently being sold for £150 to £500, or roughly US$196 to US$655.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937672/3937672_489EE64169A34DE3B7A46B777C152BF0_191219_3937672_Company_unveils_new_slanted_toilets_to_reduce_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC2/28B/DC228B876411AB652C81876EC0344C35.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Toilets, weird toilets, futuristic toilets, downward-tilting toilets, StandardToilet, StandardToilet UK, toilet technology, tilting toilet, tilting toilet seat, new toilet design, new toilet design 2019, reinvented toilets, new technology toilet seats, new design toilet seats, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog keeps eating everything in site, including his own muzzle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEDDINGTON, U.K.  A cute little puppy from the other side of the pond really likes to chew on things, so much so that he's already had four trips to the surgeons to have foreign objects removed from his stomach. According to the Metro, Dexter quite enjoys chewing on things that he probably shouldn't be chomping on like fishnet tights, chocolate and duct tape. His owners Andrew and Teri Gumpert from Teddington have already had to take the 18-month-old doggo to the vet more than seven times already because of his unusual eating habits. Other things that have strangely found their way into Dexter's tummy include a tennis ball, wood chippings, a hair scrunchie, a plastic bag and one of his play toys. So the Gumperts decided to get Dexter a muzzle. Problem solved. Wellmaybe not. He ate that too. It appears that Dexter enlisted the help of another dog in the household to help him loosen the muzzle a bit first. Then it was down the old hatch. Owner Andrew said, "we hope it's just a playful puppy thing and he'll eventually grow out of it as at the moment we can't take our eyes off him for a minute." Where's the dog whisperer when you need him?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 05:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937576/3937576_46CBC8F03B244B3C830C774616300CFA_191219_3937576_Dog_keeps_eating_everything_in_site__including_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/476/370/4763703DED0546C797EA712BE891D341.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dog chews on everything, puppy chews everything, dog eats own muzzle, dog eats own mouth guard, puppy eats own muzzle, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car blows up after driver used 'excessive' aerosol</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HALIFAX, YORKSHIRE, U.K  A car in Halifax exploded after the driver used "excessive" aerosol before sparking up. The so-far unnamed motorist was caught in traffic around three in the afternoon on Saturday.According to the BBC, the blast blew out the windscreen and windows and also buckled the doors; it was so forceful it caused damage to windows at nearby businesses.Police said the incident "could've been worse" and fortunately the man escaped with only minor injuries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937469/3937469_1A08B89712E74E8EB4222167A7916990_191219_3937469_Car_blows_up_after_driver_used__excessive__aeros_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/248/37C/24837C6730C3A04BC29DB5CED0D1D84A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Car blows up, car explosion, aerosol accidents, aerosol explosion, aerosol fails, driver blows up car,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple's photo session burns down forest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGYUAN, GUANGDONG, CHINA  A couple have been detained after triggering a huge forest fire during a photoshoot atop a mountain. The couple began setting off fireworks which resulted in the trees below catching ablaze, sending flames roaring up the mountainside.The pair were since detained for 15 days, however, as it stands it's unknown if they will face further charges.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 01:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937463/3937463_DB1B63A37E054063B0C7C959D3A09D24_191219_3937463_Couple_s_photo_session_burns_down_forest_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/99D/06C/99D06CED3A147A8C96C25C6084428105.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Selfie fails, selfie causes forest fire, forest fires, Chinese forest fire, photoshoot went wrong, photoshoot gone wrong, couple burn down forest, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$66 million in jewelry stolen from F1 heiress Tamara Ecclestone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Some Ocean's Eleven-esque robbers reportedly jacked around $66 million in jewelry from F1 heiress Tamara Ecclestone. Reuters reports that a spokesman said the daughter of ex Formula 1 boss Bernie Ecclestone was left "shaken and angry" after the Pink Panther prowlers evaded both the 24-hour security teams that patrol the street known as "Billionaire Row" and Tamara's own internal crack squad security. The Sun reports that Ecclestone had just left her 57-room mansion with her hubbie and 5-year-old daughter to go on Christmas holiday when three men got in by climbing over the back fence and going through the garden. They then carried out a 50-minute Thomas Crown Affair, clearing out every single piece of jewelry from hidden bedroom safes.  According to the Sun, rings, earrings and a Cartier bangle worth $105,000 were all taken in the heist. The Italian Job was then interrupted by one of Tamara's security guards.The thieves then Fast & Furious-ed it out of there and were long gone by the time cops showed up with some dogs.  Police say no arrests have been made yet, but that it was on the hunt for the three suspects.Our thoughts and prayers are with Tamara at this difficult time as one can only imagine the pain and anguish she must feel over all her bling bling that went bye bye. Naturally a GoFundMe campaign has been started to help Tamara get back on her feet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 01:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937460/3937460_D5A10DDC67774C3F910531AC32D53C80_191219_3937460__66_million_in_jewelry_stolen_from_F1_heiress_Ta_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE8/555/FE855544FB0B008A143C18310DB254FB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[F1 heiress robbed, Tamara Ecclestone robbed, Ecclestone robbed, F1 Tamara Ecclestone, jewelry heist, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump impeached by House in historic vote. Now what?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON   Donald Trump has now been officially impeached, making him the third U.S. president after Andrew Johnson and Bill Clinton to face removal from office.According to CNN, the House of Representatives on Wednesday voted to impeach President Trump on two articles of impeachment: abuse of power and obstruction of Congress.The article on abuse of power accused Trump of withholding aid to pressure Ukraine into investigating his political rival Joe Biden. It passed 230 votes to 197, with only two Democrats opposing.The second article, which passed 229 to 198, charged Trump over his refusal to cooperate with the impeachment inquiry and his urging of witnesses and government agencies to do the same.No House Republicans supported impeachment.CBS reports that the next steps would be for Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi to name the impeachment managers that will argue to case to senators, and transmit the impeachment articles to Senate.A trial will then be held in the Senate, presided over by the Supreme Court Chief Justice, with senators acting as jury.A two-thirds majority vote is needed to remove Trump from office. But with the Republicans controlling the Senate with at least a 51-seat majority, and Senate leader Mitch McConnell claiming he's working with the White House, the president will likely be exonerated.According to the New York Times, Pelosi has suggested that the House might delay sending the articles to the Senate, in order to negotiate the terms of the proceedings.The BBC reports that this could put off the trial for an indefinite amount of time, effectively denying Trump the acquittal he expects.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938454/3938454_77C34D48A6C7491FA7AB312B11016499_191220_3938454_Trump_impeached_by_House_in_historic_vote__Now_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C75/DBE/C75DBE29468F67735AD7704F2E8CFE93.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Trump impeachment, Trump impeached, Donald Trump, Trump, impeachment, presidential impeachment, impeachment inquiry, Nancy Pelosi, us president, us impeachment, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese woman left with 4 melons after botched boob job</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA  Bigger is always better and the more the merrierokay, maybe not in this case. A Chinese woman who intelligently spent $32,500 for a new rack was left with a bit more than she bargained for. Where there were two, now there are four. Huh!?According to a report on Bilibili, a mother of one from Shenzhen felt unsatisfied with mother nature's plans for her figure after childbirth, so she decided to put work in to get it all back. Actually, she just went under the knife instead. Unfortunately for the lady, the plastic surgeons from IF Aesthetic Surgery in Guangzhou slightly miscalculated the number of implants needed and went with four.  The woman said she was told by the plastic doctors that she should buy two pairs of implants. No alarm bells went off at this point?Despite getting knocked out, the woman said she also woke up during the surgery. And after it was over, she also found a large scar on her arm, which doctors say was a burn mark. Talking to a local reporter about her botched surgery, the woman said, "the upper parts are bigger, the lower parts are smaller; the upper parts are hard, the lower parts are soft."Apparently the Barbie doll doctors offered the woman a refund as well as an extra $4,300 for pain and suffering. Well, maybe next time she should go for six.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938443/3938443_3E5F55D1D59D45D698F87F3C5CB9D523_191220_3938443_Chinese_woman_left_with_4_melons_after_botched_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE8/8F4/EE88F448A8CCD6532F7B99F6ABBBEF1D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plastic surgery, China plastic surgery, China botched plastic surgery, woman botched plastic surgery, China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Older Japanese workers powering up in exoskeleton suits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN  Older people in Japan are suiting up in exoskeletons to help them get through the daily grind and to stay in the workforce longer. According to New Scientist, The Land of the Rising Sun isn't getting any younger, with a whopping 28 percent of the population 65 or older. The problem is, the country now has fewer and fewer young people which has led to a shortage of workers, especially in manual labor industries like construction, manufacturing and farming. To help them stay in the game, Japan has no choice but to have its aging workforce remain working as long as possible. That's not depressing at all.  Enter good OLD Japanese technology. Several tech firms in Japan are developing exoskeleton suits to give workers added support so they can keep on working. One of these firms is Innophys, which has designed several exosuits that you wear like a backpack. By squeezing the hand pump 30 times, you pump air into the air-powered 'muscles' which then allows the person to lift up to 55 pounds. They ain't cheap though. Just one suit costs 1300 bones. At this rate, it should only be a matter of time before Japan goes real Gundam style.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938438/3938438_8A46FCF173C7423BBA736A883371A32F_191220_3938438_Older_Japanese_workers_powering_up_in_exoskeleto_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E10/664/E10664A30997E3820AA46F2686CB75C5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Japan exosuits, Japan older worker exoskeletons, exoskeleton suits, Japan exoskeleton suits, elderly workers exoskeletons, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA's Mars 2020 rover conducts its first test drive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA  As part of NASA's preparation for next year's Mars mission, the Mars 2020 rover took its first driving test at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory in California on December 17.The rover was able to roll forward, backward and perform a pirouette in the laboratory over a period of 10 hours, according to NASA. The Mars 2020 rover was also able to drive over small ramps in the lab.The rover is equipped with an autonomous navigation system, which uses high-resolution navigation cameras and image processing software. Its wheels have been redesigned for added durability.NASA says the technology will allow to rover to drive roughly 200 meters per Martian day. The Mars 2020 rover will also carry a radar imager to gather data about Mars' surface.The rover will be launched in July or August of 2020. It is scheduled to land on Mars' Jerozo Crater on February of 2021.The Mars mission is part of a larger project that includes lunar missions to prepare humans to eventually explore the red planet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 09:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938221/3938221_AE51DB2129F34B808B1712F206B00902_191220_3938221_NASA_s_Mars_2020_rover_conducts_its_first_test_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6C2/F38/6C2F38E7F4E3DD1E5FF90104242CFA09.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mars 2020, Mars 2020 rover,mars rover, nasa mars rover 2020, nasa mars rover Mars rover, Mars mission, nasa Mars mission, Mars, nasa Mars mission 2020, space exploration, Mars 2020 rover, Mars 2020 rover completes first drive, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcanic climate change may have contributed to dinosaur extinction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANN ARBOR, MICHIGAN  Massive volcanic eruptions in India may have contributed to the extinction of the dinosaurs, which has long been believed to be the result of a massive asteroid impact.According to a timeline assembled by University of Texas at Austin researchers, the Chicxulub asteroid struck a shallow ocean some 66 million years ago, hitting it with the force of 10 billion atomic bombs. The blast set the land ablaze, igniting trees and plants up to thousands of miles away.Although the asteroid caused destruction at the regional level when it hit, the impact itself was not what killed off the dinosaurs.Instead, scientists say sulfur-bearing rocks were vaporized at the site, releasing an estimated 325 million metric tons of sulfur  into the atmosphere, where it reflected sunlight away from the planet and caused global cooling.Researchers believe the global climate change that followed was responsible for the mass extinction of the dinosaurs.Global cooling disrupted photosynthesis, which killed the plants and caused the food chain to collapse.Now, a new study published in Nature Communications has found evidence that another event may have contributed to the extinction.The University of Michigan-led research collected and analyzed ancient fossilized shells from around the world, finding evidence of both ocean warming and high mercury concentrations when they were formed 66 million years ago.These measurements are both symptoms of volcanic eruptions. They align with the onset of a series of violent eruptions that created India's Deccan Traps formations, starting before the extinction, and lasting on and off for about a million years.Mercury is toxic to humans, fish, and wildlife. The levels researchers found in the ancient shells were found to be roughly equivalent to those in modern shells from mercury-polluted industrial sites. Scientists believe that such a level of global mercury contamination indicates a volcanic climate change was already present before the extinction, and may have merely been accelerated by the impact event.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3937999/3937999_0E80629A83AA4DD1BF63071F809DE5CC_191220_3937999_Volcanic_climate_change_may_have_contributed_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dinosaur extinction, dino extinction, dinosaur mass extinction, dino mass extinction, Deccan traps, volcanic climate change, volcanic eruptions, dinosaur extinction theory, dinosaur extinction cause, mercury poisoning, global mercury poisoning, global warming, fossilized shells, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey vs Greece: Fighter jets spar in Greek airspace row</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TURKEY / GREECE  Turkish and Greek fighter jets engaged in 16 mock dogfights after Greece's airspace was violated by Turkish jets on December 17 over territorial claims in the Aegean Sea, according to Stars and Stripes.Greek air force pilots rushed to intercept the Turkish jets as they entered the country's airspace a total of 40 times on Tuesday, Stars and Stripes reports. The two nations are at odds over issues including the delimitation of territorial waters, airspace, exclusion zones and Turkey's claims over small islands in the Aegean Sea.Turkey said it could send in military forces into the eastern Mediterranean and add armed drones to northern Cyprus over the two countries' territorial disputes, Stars and Stripes reports, citing Turkish Vice President Fuat Oktay.Greek Defense Minister Nikos Panagiotopoulos had previously said that the disputed area is controlled by the Greek military.According to Greek City Times, the country plans to purchase drones from the U.S. and Israel. The technology could be used to surveil Turkey's military moves in the Mediterranean.The move comes amid growing tensions between Greece and Turkey as the U.S. has increased its military ties with Greece while the U.S. could move ahead to sanction Turkey over its military invasion in northern Syria.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3937992/3937992_74CEAAAF20C04EE7BC06289CE6F4E5E1_191220_3937992_Turkey_vs_Greece__Fighter_jets_spar_in_Greek_air_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/879/E51/879E51366D83D07596A0F7E2C312AC4C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Turkey fighter jets, Greek fighter jets, turkey violates Greek airspace, greek airspace, turkey greece, Aegean Sea, Turkey Greece territorial dispute, Mock Dogfights, turkey greece mock dogfights, turkish jets intercepted, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500-year-old anchors believed to be from Conquistador ships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO  Archaeologists believe that they may have just discovered ship anchors from Hernán Cortés, the conqueror of the Aztec empire. Mexico's National Institute of Anthropology and History have announced that two 500-year-old iron ship anchors have been discovered on Mexico's Gulf Coast. These anchors could belong to the ships of Spanish conquistador, Hernán Cortés, thus potentially offering an insight into the Spanish invasion.Divers discovered the anchors 10 to 15 meters below the sea, under a thick layer of sediment. In 2018, just 1,000 feet away from the site, another anchor was found and dated back to the 15th century via its wood. The date is significant as it would fit with that of Hernán Cortés as records show he landed in Veracruz, Mexico in April 1519.All three anchors were found on the coast just north of the port city of Veracruz.Head of the Underwater Archeology Office, Dr. Roberto Junco details the most voluminous of the three anchors as 3.68 meters long and 1.55 meters wide between its tips.Both anchors are well preserved as a result of being protected beneath the sediment of the ocean. For this reason, after documentation and measurement, they will be returned to adhere to the archaeological protocols of conservation.Marine archaeologist Frederick Hanselmann explains why this is so important, "The Conquest of Mexico was a seminal event in human history, and these shipwrecks, if we can find them, will be symbols of the cultural collision that led to what is now the West."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 01:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3937978/3937978_00450419BA5E4B74B27B6BDF184A0F97_191220_3937978_500_year_old_anchors_believed_to_be_from_Conquis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CD2/DDB/CD2DDBD470D8132041AF1CC60EB74EC7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[500 year old anchor found, Hernán Cortés, Aztec empire, underwater archeology, TomoNews, satire, Conquistador, Mexico Gulf Coast, anchors, anchors found]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Master thief tries to steal money from ATM, gets trapped by door</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGYING, CHINA  A master thief who tried to boost some cash from an ATM almost made a clean getaway if only it weren't forthe door. According to a Pear Video, CCTV footage from a bank ATM in the Shandong city of Dongying captured a play by play of the finely planned heist on December 17. In the video, the man is seen walking up to the ATM, as the door closes behind him, which activates an automatic voice welcoming him. This clearly freaks the man out, which causes him to try and open the door to get out. Let's just say doors aren't this guy's forte. He fiddles with the pesky lock, but gets nowhere. It must have been made in China.The man then grabs the lid to the trash can and proceeds to smash it into the door with Hulk-like strength. When that doesn't work, he turns his focus to the ATM screen and starts to pound on it with the metal lid. He wasn't able to get the door open, or any money out of the machine, but he did succeed in setting off an alarm. Genius eventually got the door, but by that time, the cops had already shown up and promptly arrested himDOH.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 13:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939555/3939555_78FD2A2BD9FA40F5B559B596A575B966_191223_3939555_Master_thief_tries_to_steal_money_from_ATM__gets_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE5/7A1/EE57A172B9475AB6829CF98BFFA7731F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[ATM thief, ATM robbery, ATM robbery fail, ATM robber can't open door, robber has trouble opening door, man can't open door, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesco stops production at Chinese factory over alleged 'forced' labor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  Tesco has halted production of Christmas cards at a factory in China after a British girl found a message from workers inside one of them. The BBC reports that Florence Widdicombe found a note inside the card allegedly written by prisoners in Shanghai saying they were "forced to work against our will."The message also said to, "please help us and notify rights organizations." Tesco naturally said they were "shocked" and added, "we would never allow prison labor in our supply chain." Well, then why are you guys having things made in Chinathe home of forced labor?According to BBC, Florence was writing cards for her classmates when she found one that had already been written in. In all capitals, the message said, "We are foreign prisoners in Shanghai Qingpu prison China. Forced to work against our will. Please help us and notify human rights organizations."The message also asked anyone who found the message to contact British journalist Peter Humphrey who himself had also wasted time in Chinese prisons four years ago. Tesco claims that it has a "comprehensive auditing system" to ensure suppliers are not using prison labor. Clearly it's not that comprehensive. According to Tesco, the factory in question, Zhejiang Yunguang Printing, apparently was checked last month with no signs of prison labor. AKAthey didn't have the prisoners working on the day the Tesco people were COMPREHENSIVELY doing their checks. Unfortunately for the prisoners, things will now probably just get worse for them as China clearly isn't going to stop using forced labor. Merry Christmas everyone!!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 13:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939550/3939550_FBB0CC8A01194166AF83861C34120F87_191223_3939550_Tesco_stops_production_at_Chinese_factory_over_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD7/277/FD7277385B6F2A1F0C625A493E450C72.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tesco halts China factory production, China forced labor, China prison labor, China forced prison labor, Shanghai forced prison labor, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea has expanded its ballistic missile launcher factory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGSONG, NORTH KOREA  Civilian satellite imagery by Planet Labs has revealed an expansion to the March 16 factory in North Korea's Pyongsong, NBC News reports.Citing expert analysis given to the channel, NBC reports that these activities could mean North Korea will soon resume the testing of intercontinental ballistic missiles.Analysis Jeffrey Lewis told the channel that a temporary structure has been erected at the March 16 factory.Lewis, director of the East Asia Nonproliferation Program at the Middlebury Institute of International Studies, speculated that the structure is built to accommodate efforts to raise a missile launcher arm.Lewis told CNN the March 16 factory is involved in manufacturing civilian vehicles and missile launchers.Citing Lewis, CNN reported that the heavy-duty trucks built at the factory are powerful enough to transport large missiles.Lewis told NBC the facility's expansion occurred after North Korea's leader Kim Jong-un visited the factory in June.NBC speculates that the revelation could mean North Korea will test launch a missile designed to be capable of reaching the U.S.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939499/3939499_8941932864424CDE9B3B6600F6FEED7F_191223_3939499_North_Korea_has_expanded_its_ballistic_missile_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E03/73B/E0373BE8FBBB4E6E17AB2EB580CBA58E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sattelite, satellites, satellite images, satellite imagery, satellite photos, factory 16, missiles, missile, ICBM, intercontinental ballistic missile, missile test, missile tests,  Pyongsong, North Korea, US, defense, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Navy's submarine drones may be getting offensive weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANNAPOLIS, MARYLAND   A retired commander has proposed using the U.S. Navy's Boeing Orca underwater drone offensively in future conflicts. According to Forbes, the Orca autonomous drone is a diesel-electric submarine with a payload baythat could carry minesand a control unit located in the forward section."In a post on the US Naval Institute blog, Commander Brian Dulla says the "moorpedo" is a smart weapon that is both a torpedo and a moored or bottom mine.The design includes an antenna, electric power propulsion, a temporary anchor, and a shaped explosive warhead with contact and proximity triggers.The Orca drone or other platforms could lay inactive moorpedos in international waters during peacetime, which is legal under international law.The underwater offensive drone would use its anchor to lay in wait and its antenna for receiving commands.If the autonomous weapon receives the command to actuate, it would engage the propulsion system to redeploy against an enemy port.The drone would also be able to attack enemy warships entering or leaving port as a mine or strike at moored ships as a slow-moving torpedo.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939482/3939482_63601DAC612A4BF297EBA08BCBC8E03A_191223_3939482_U_S__Navy_s_submarine_drones_may_be_getting_offe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4F4/050/4F4050F090ECFE92DD620575FA9E2AFF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Orca, extra large unmanned underwater vehicle, xluuv, Boeing, USN, US Navy, minelayer, naval mines, autonomous, unmanned, unmanned vehicle, drone, morpedo, mine, torpedo, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin skyscrapers proposed for Brooklyn waterfront development</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  Danish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group and New York-based landscape architecture firm James Corner Field Operations have unveiled plans for a mixed-use development on the waterfront in Brooklyn, New York.The River Street Waterfront Master Plan would consist of two sandy beaches to improve coastal resiliency as sea levels continue to rise.The project plans to transform the area into a waterfront park with a circular walkway raised on stilts where visitors can stroll or take part in outdoor activities such as boating, Dezeen reports. To protect against heavy flooding, the seabed underneath the park will be stepped, so it can fill up with water in an emergency.The redesigned waterfront site would also include nature trails and bird watching sites for the public.The two companies also want to construct two skyscrapers beside the park. These towers would include residential units and office space as well as retail stores. The buildings would also include a YMCA gym and a swimming pool.The structures would make use of sustainable design elements such as passive solar shading.Lead designer Lisa Switkin from James Corner Field Operations explained to Dezeen that the project would provide a better wildlife environment and allow the public to live in harmony with the surrounding water.The project is currently waiting for approval from New York's City Hall, the Department of City Planning and other relevant authorities such as the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers. This process is expected to take two years. If approved, construction of the new waterfront could take up to five years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 03:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939251/3939251_0286A7B0D7CB4A96A53D75C18D4CEF69_191223_3939251_Twin_skyscrapers_proposed_for_Brooklyn_waterfron_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E5B/4EE/E5B4EEF89A5143A1F3815E0FFD736941.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Williamsburg's waterfront, River Street Waterfront Master Plan New York, new coastal brooklyn park, new brooklyn waterfront, New York city waterfront redesigned, brooklyn waterfront walkway, James Corner Field Operations, Bjarke Ingels Group, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple gets hit in same spot 10 minutes apart for not looking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YICHANG, CHINA  A couple in China were clearly meant to be after being struck trying to cross an insanely busy street in the exact same spot only 10 minutes apart for totally ignoring traffic rules.According to The Paper, police released CCTV footage of the hilarious incident which took place in the Hubei city of Yichang on December 17.The wife is seen attempting to cut through traffic riding an electric bike when she totally doesn't look to see if, you know, a car might be coming, and gets up close and personal with the front end of a car in the right turn lane.  She gets pretty good airtime and falls off her bike, losing a shoe in the process. As the woman gets up, police come over and get her to the side of the road. End of story. Well, maybe not quite yet because about 10 minutes later, her dear hubby seeing all the commotion comes running over, choosing the exact same route his wife took. Guess we can all see where this wreck is headed. The guy makes his way successfully through the rows of cars until he was no longer successful. He then manages to get hit in the exact same spot as his wife. The match made in heaven didn't quite get to heaven, but they did get taken to the hospital. Lucky for them, neither have life-threatening injuries. Guess there really is someone for everyone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3940034/3940034_6D9FA2B25F2E444E9589B6378CA4FFE8_191224_3940034_Couple_gets_hit_in_same_spot_10_minutes_apart_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EA7/EA1/EA7EA13115036263ABE3D91C94377B00.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China traffic, China busy traffic, husband and wife hit same spot, couple ignore traffic rules, couple cuts through traffic, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan's Taipei City will test driverless night shuttles in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI, TAIWAN  Taiwan's capital city of Taipei will test driverless shuttles in the second quarter next year, the Taipei Times reports.According to the shuttle's designer and operator Turing Drive Inc, the vehicle features an NVIDIA DRIVE PX2 processor, a top-mounted LIDAR and front and rear cameras.The shuttle is controlled by an AI that uses a deep learning algorithm to drive and has lower carbon emissions.Citing the city's transportation director Chen Hsueh-tai, the Liberty Times reports that sensors will be installed at intersections to help the shuttle recognize traffic signs.The Taipei Times reports that the pilot program will run on the part of the city's Xinyi road between the East Gate and the Keelung Road intersection at 30 kilometers per hour.Officials told the Liberty Times that a safety operator will be present on the shuttle to intervene if necessary.The shuttle line is to run during the closed hours of the city's mass transit system, or between midnight and 5:00 a.m.Chen told the paper while the technology is not yet ready for daytime, running the shuttle at night will help residents commuting at late hours.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3940003/3940003_4EE1F1F0D21D4983B48FE6F879B17FF5_191224_3940003_Taiwan_s_Taipei_City_will_test_driverless_night__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C18/F24/C18F2467779FFA4A23C82D3249739AFB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Driverless bus, driverless shuttle, autonomous, AI, artificial intelligence, self-driving, Turing Drive Inc, Taipei, Taiwan, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jams 18-cm long bottle into his behind to scratch an itch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA  No one likes an itchy backside, but sometimes finding the right tool to help scratch that itch can be easier said than done. Just ask this man from China.According to a report over Weibo, a real do-it-yourself kind of guy from the Guangdong city of Dongguan had a serious case of the itchy itchies, but had nothing to scratch with. The 60-year-old man then enlisted the help of a 18-cm long glass bottle to do the dirty work. Unfortunately for the man, the bottle decided to get a bit cheeky and went it for a deeper lookand then got stuck. The man then got himself over to the hospital and told doctors he was having trouble passing gas and dropping the kids off at the pool. It didn't take long for physicians to get to the BOTTOM of the discomfort after some all to clear x-rays. The doctor who treated the lucky man told local media that he could feel the bottle when touching the man's stomach. In the rear end, doctors were able to successfully extricate the man's bottle back scratcher via surgery. All's well that ends well.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 09:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939971/3939971_7C0E43A6E798425185AE98D54BF0F387_191224_3939971_Man_jams_18_cm_long_bottle_into_his_behind_to_sc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D42/817/D4281744AB1BC932AEF033C1D3B64CF7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China glass bottle gets stuck, man scratches itch, man tries to scratch itch, itching, scratching an itch, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing bans medium and large dog breeds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Beijing has hit a new low as far as animal rights, banning medium to large dogs and threatening to sick the cops on them if the owners don't comply.According to a legal notice reposted by Taiwan's Green Party, Beijing's southeast district of Tongzhou is banning residents from raising dogs taller than 35 centimeters.Pet owners are given a three-day grace period after receiving the notice to "dispose" of their fur babies. If they don't comply, police officers will come and impound the animal, which in China basically means beating them to death in public.Rather than risk such a brutal end for their beloved pets, many owners have chosen the lesser evil of having their fur babies euthanized at the vet.CTS reports that some folks on Weibo can't afford to properly euthanize their pets, and have had to suffocate or kill the poor pups themselves.Beijing animal rescue group CaliPaw has also been looking for volunteers with travel plans to San Francisco or L.A. to help rescue the dogs.Tongzhou police say the Draconian ban is actually part of a list of dog management regulations that took effect in 2003, and justified its enforcement by saying there have been complaints since November about misbehaving dogs.Yeah, no one's buying that. Congratulations, China, for reaching a whole 'nother level of cruel.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939943/3939943_A45232DCC5E0412EAE64DF076D0A3607_191224_3939943_Beijing_bans_medium_and_large_dog_breeds_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/294/954/294954609C1125ED3D855CF1364F2A99.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Beijing dog ban, dog ban, Beijing war on dogs, Beijing dog limit, China dog ban, medium and large dog ban, Beijing medium and large dog ban, dog height limit, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen beef patties recalled over possible plastic contamination</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CINCINNATI  There's another recall of food that was sent to schools, and Tyson Foods Inc is involved again.The U.S. Department of Agriculture announced that Tyson Foods subsidiary AdvancePierre Foods is recalling 15,738 pounds of its beef patty products as they may be "contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically small, green soft plastic."The USDA is classifying this as a Class II Recall. This means there is a remote probability that use of the product may result in adverse health consequences.In a statement, the company said that it is voluntarily recalling the product CN Fully Cooked Flamebroiled Beef Patties as a precaution after receiving complaints from a foodservice establishment.AdvancePierre Foods says only two of the patties were found to be contaminated.The company is recalling 1,043 cases, or roughly half a truckload of product, that were produced in September 2019.According to the USDA, the product was shipped to a warehouse in Iowa, then distributed to institutions including schools as part of a commercial sale. The product was not sold in retail stores.AdvancePierre Foods says it has not received any reports of injuries or illnesses due to consumption of the beef patties. The USDA urged institutions that have purchased the product to either discard it or return it to the place of purchase.In April of this year, AdvancePierre Foods recalled over 20,000 pounds of beef patties after consumers found pieces of soft, purple plastic in the product.AdvancePierre Foods' parent company, Tyson Foods, which has been involved in a series of food scandals, voluntarily recalled more than 5,000 cases of its crispy chicken fritters after plastic was found in the product in June 2019.The company said that the product was not sold at stores, though it was distributed to schools across the country.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 07:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939848/3939848_954AF9B0314D4248B5D9AD548004B5F3_191224_3939848_Frozen_beef_patties_recalled_over_possible_plast_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/987/9F3/9879F335E428B5AC8182AB099FD75C59.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Frozen beef patties recall, beef patties recall, Plastic contamination, beef patties plastic contamination, plastic in beef, plastic in beef patties, Advance Pierre Foods, AdvancePierre Foods beef patties, food recall, beef recall, contamination in beef patties, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla may soon unveil a secret new vehicle from its 'Master Plan'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA  Tesla has yet to unveil one of its vehicles, a high passenger-density urban transport vehicle, according to the second part of the company's Master Plan. Tesla recently unveiled a new vehicle, the Tesla Semi, which was also mentioned in the plan.In the Master Plan, the automotive company stated that the new electric vehicle would include self-driving technology.The plan mentions that center aisles inside the vehicle would be eliminated in order to increase passenger area density. Seats would instead be added to the vehicle's current entryways.Tesla explains that the vehicle would be able to take passengers all the way to their destination and would improve overall traffic congestion.The plan was released in 2016, in which the automotive company explained that the vehicle is currently at its early stages of development and should soon be ready for unveiling.Tesla had previously released its first Master Plan over a decade ago, in 2006, and has since launched the Model S, Model 3 and the Roadster as part of the plan.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 04:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939764/3939764_B99F1B21BD7D4E9E9639CFB68BB07A37_191224_3939764_Tesla_may_soon_unveil_a_secret_new_vehicle_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/853/971/8539717CA340622628C2A55D984F17FC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tesla, new tesla vehicle, Tesla Master plan, Tesla Master Plan Part 2, tesla elon musk,  Tesla Semi, high passenger-density urban transport, tesla high passenger-density urban transport, tesla news, tesla vehicles 2020, tesla new car, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China removes Mesut Ozil from video game after Uyghur tweets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  In response to Mesut Ozil's tweets condemning China for its treatment of Uyghurs, the country has removed the Arsenal midfielder entierly from the Chinese version of the popular video game franchise, Pro Evolution Soccer.NetEase, the publisher of PES, said Ozil had also been deleted from three existing titles too.In a statement on Weibo, they said, "The German player Ozil posted an extreme statement about China on social media. The speech hurt the feelings of Chinese fans and violated the sports spirit of love and peace. We do not understand, accept or forgive this!"Ozil's club, Arsenal has since distanced themselves from Ozil's comments and branded themselves as "apolitical."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 03:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939717/3939717_0B4B9A54DB9D4C8E94817C0AE3ED18D9_191224_3939717_China_removes_Mesut_Ozil_from_video_game_after_U_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/542/5A6/5425A6622DF5D14AD909A9C0D2147547.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[PES, Winning eleven, winning 11, pro evolution soccer, Mesut Ozil banned from PES, PES 2020, PES news, China bans PES, China bans Ozil, Arsenal, PES Arsenal, China gaming ban, Uyghurs, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin city to allow snowball fights after 50-year ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WAUSAU, WISCONSIN  After a more than 50-year ban on snowball fights, residents of Wausau, Wisconsin could soon freely pelt each other with balls of ice.Wisconsin Public Radio reports that the city had a rarely-enforced ordinance banning projectiles on city property, which included hurling rocks, shooting arrows, and yes, throwing snowballs.It's only been used to issue tickets 10 times in the past 15 years, with only two instances involving snowballs being thrown, both at passing cars. In early December, the city got called out by several news outlets for the snowball ban, which was inaccurately reported as new. One even dubbed Wausau "the worst town in America" for stamping out winter fun. Well, officials weren't having that, and put out a video to set the record straight, featuring cops having a snowball fight and the Deputy Chief of Police hitting a bullseye on the mayor's head.The city council also voted last week to remove "snowball" from the local law banning projectiles. But while snowball fights between friends or enemies are fine, chucking a fast one at a moving vehicle on the highway is still going to land you in hot water with the cops.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 10:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940406/3940406_1181D2B0CE9C4AB0AEB8FDB1CC4F886C_191225_3940406_Wisconsin_city_to_allow_snowball_fights_after_50_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E62/B62/E62B6207EDA1369A86C56B26783C2A4D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Snowball fights, snowball, wausau, wausau wisconsin, snowball fight ban, illegal snowball fight, launching projectiles, worst town in America, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese man caught smuggling 90 iPhones taped to his body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHUHAI, CHINA  A Chinese man was caught trying to cross the border from Macau to mainland China on Monday with a whole boatload of iPhones wrapped around his person. According to China News, the man was at the Gongbei border crossing in beautiful Zhuhai when he was stopped by customs officials. Apparently the guy was looking a bit on the "bloated" side with strange bulges protruding from his waist and legs, so he was stopped for a search. After dropping trow, customs officers were shocked to find 90 iPhones strapped to the man's body. The Apple phones were wrapped in plastic wrap and a whole bunch of tape around his waist, lets, thighs and ankles. China News reports that the case has now been transferred to the anti-smuggling department for further investigation. Uh ohit looks like someone's social credit score is going to take a big hit this holiday season.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940374/3940374_C74C717392D04057B8B76D5E81C36D41_191225_3940374_Chinese_man_caught_smuggling_90_iPhones_taped_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/269/72C/26972CF3758C6BC1BE3828041684027E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[iPhone, man iPhones taped to body, Chinese man iPhones taped to body, man 90 iPhones taped to body, smuggling iPhones, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marathon leader runs off course 200 meters from finish, loses race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA  A North Korean marathon runner steps away from certain victory blew it right before the finish line when he unfortunately veered off course. According to World Athletics, Ri Kang Bom of the super Democratic People's Republic of Korea was out front at the Asian Marathon Championships in Dongguan on December 22. Ri had a real comfortable lead over second-place Japanese runner Daichi Kamino with only 200 meters left and was cruising along nicely as he headed into the final corner.  That's when a TV broadcast motorcycle pulled in front of Ri and then exited the course right ahead of the finish line. Unfortunately for the North Korean Usain Bolt, he followed.WIth only half a minute left in the race and the end in sight, Kamino turned on the afterburners for the last leg of the race. By the time Ri figured out that he was going the wrong way and returned back to the course, his lead had evaporated. Kamino then dramatically overtook Ri in the last 40 meters and finished with a time of 2:12.18. Ri took second only 3 seconds behind at 2:12.21.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940371/3940371_7C15E0B7501A4BA59EFA20621ABDA817_191225_3940371_Marathon_leader_runs_off_course_200_meters_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/93A/9EF/93A9EF232CA87555452FCE108772E589.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Marathon leader runs off course, marathon leader loses, China marathon leader runs off course, Dongguan marathon blunder, marathon mistake, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supergiant red star Betelgeuse is becoming dimmer and dimmer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VILLANOVA, PENNSYLVANIA  Astronomers from Villanova University recently published an article noting that Betelgeuse in the constellation Orion has been significantly dimmer in recent months, leading some to speculate it could go supernova.According to CNet, one possible explanation for the dimming is that Betelgeuse is out of fuel and has begun to collapse on itself resulting in a supernova explosion. Once the star explodes, the explosion would be visible during daylight and could even be brighter than the moon at night for a few weeks or even months.However, astronomers say this is unlikely.The other likely explanation is that because Betelgeuse is a variable star that has been dimming and brightening for a millennia, the dimming could just be the most significant dip in the past 50 years or so, which is a very short amount of time in the star's lifespan.  NASA's website states that Betelgeuse is over 1,000 times larger than our sun.The star's radius is also big enough to encompass Jupiter and all four planets in our inner solar system: Mercury, Venus, Earth and Mars, CNet reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 05:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940272/3940272_A84E09711ABA4FBE87DCFB1F3D84184A_191225_3940272_Supergiant_red_star_Betelgeuse_is_becoming_dimme_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/893/F5F/893F5F9F9358A85FE77CC0221D37F4F2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Betelgeuse, red supergiant star Betelgeuse, Betelgeuse supernova, Betelgeuse explosion, Betelgeuse explained, betelgeuse dimming, betelgeuse fainting, supernova, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan seals the deal for advanced F-16 fighters with U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI, TAIWAN  Taipei has signed a U.S. arms deal for 66 F-16V fighters while upgrading older models to F-16V standard earlier in December, Taiwan's state run Central News Agency reports on Saturday.According to Lockheed Martin, the F-16V is the latest variant of the F-16, a multirole fighter that features advanced weaponry, targeting systems, electronics, and radar. Citing an unnamed military source, CNA reports that the F-16Vs have better weapons than the older generation J-11 fighters used by China's People's Liberation Army.According to the source, the F-16V may not be a match for the PLA's J-20 stealth fighter, but Taiwanese jets could utilize friendly early warning aircraft to contain the threat.Jane's Information Group reports that Lockheed Martin will establish an F-16 maintenance center in Taiwan with the locally owned Aerospace Industrial Development Corporation.According to Jane's, the facility will provide maintenance and logistical support to Taiwan's F-16 fleet, in addition to refurbishing 140 F-16A/Bs[e] to F-16Vs.The PLA deploys about 700 fighters in China's southeastern coast, which is double the size of Taiwan's tactical air arm.CNA cites the source as saying that the combination of F-16Vs and air defense systems give Taiwan's military a needed boost to combat the PLA's superior numbers.Citing associate professor Lin Ying- yu[f] at the National Chung Cheng University, the CNA reports that China's carriers are now a threat to Taiwan's eastern defensive perimeter.CNA cites Lin as saying that the F-16Vs and anti-ship missiles will serve as a deterrent to Chinese carriers and aircraft operating in the seas east of Taiwan.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 03:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940231/3940231_0AF97BE188CF4E44B8684E41BC6F62A2_191225_3940231_Taiwan_seals_the_deal_for_advanced_F_16_fighters_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/927/470/9274704727127A01D512B9D2FC7FDC3D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[F-16V, F-16, F16V, arms sale, F-16C/D, F-16A/B, Block 70, Taiwan, U.S., China, Chinese carriers, People's Liberation Army, People's Liberation Army Navy, PLA, PLAN, defense, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dog caught on cam stealing toys from charity bin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FRANKLIN, MASSACHUSETTS  A police therapy dog may have landed himself on Santa's naughty list after being caught stealing from the charity bin.According to the BBC, the Franklin Police Department had been collecting toys for the Santa Foundation, which donates presents to needy families on Christmas. For some reason though, the toys kept disappearing, so the cops started to look into it.It didn't take long to figure out that the Christmas toy thief was one of their own – a furry four-legged pup named Ben Franklin.Officers caught the adorable golden retriever red-handed, carrying a toy baby in a carrier through the station.Turns out Ben had thought the toys were his, and had been hoarding them in his secret lair beneath a desk.Franklin Police Deputy Chief James Mil says Ben has since been banned from the collection room. All the toys he took were also replaced after he got slobber all over them.We're just kidding about the naughty list, Ben. You're still a good boy!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 02:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940219/3940219_5577F1AC830A4343A9BC5D918E29657C_191225_3940219_Police_dog_caught_on_cam_stealing_toys_from_char_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/97D/BE0/97DBE01C1643F9FF12125C2BB839CAD2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Police dog, toy thief, police toy theft, ben franklin, police therapy dog, golden retriever, cute dog videos, santa foundation, christmas toy theft, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium's upgraded APCs can only be driven by small people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS  It looks like the Belgian army's latest tank upgrade forgot to take into account that people would need to fit inside them. According to the BBC, drivers or gunners of the new and maybe not-so-improved Pandur must be shorter than 5'7'' to fit in the armored vehicle. This is great because Belgium is one of the tallest countries in the world.The upgrade program for the Pandurs has a budget of $34 million, but all is well since the Belgium Ministry of Defense says it only spent $1.9 million of it so far.Citing Belgium's broadcaster VRT, the BBC reports that Belgium bought the Pandurs from Austria in 1966.Belgium has been trying to modernize the aging Pandurs for military operations, including a planned deployment to Mali in 2021.The Brussels Times reports the upgrades included extra armor, air conditioning and raised floors to protect troops from IEDs.The upgrades might have made the Pandur safer, but apparently, you have to be Tom Cruise size to actually drive them.Citing VRT, the BBC says the upgrades make steering and braking a "nuisance, and that the tall floor makes it hard to get in or out of the Pandur."That is a very bad thing for when your ride is on fire.According to BBC, Admiral Yves Dupont told the local press that the upgrades weren't finished. He also said it's not unusual for armor crew to be restricted to being 5'7" tall, which is technically true if you are in a Russian antique.However, Belgium's MP Wouter de Vriendt isn't buying any of this and tweeted that the Pandur upgrade was a "fiasco" and that the Pandur "could not be used."In the meantime...Belgium is now looking for a few good menshort ones though.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940511/3940511_BA41E7BFE3AA471489B4BE7579F7F70E_191225_3940511_Belgium_s_upgraded_APCs_can_only_be_driven_by_sm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/47F/A11/47FA11628B2F5769AA66922B41D6BE25.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Pandur,Pandur I,Pandur 1 6X6,Pandur,upgrade,upgrades,Belgium,short,cramped,defense,short,TomoNews,satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man throws money into the air after robbing bank on Christmas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLORADO SPRINGS  A man with a striking resemblance to Santa Claus was feeling the spirit of the holidays when he decided to rob a bank two days before Christmas and then redistributed the cash by throwing it out into the streets.According to Colorado 11 News, police say 65-year-old David Oliver entered the Academy Bank in Colorado Springs around lunchtime on Monday afternoon. Authorities say he entered the bank, claimed to have a weapon in his pocket and then made off with the loot. According to eyewitness Dion Pascale talking to Colorado 11, Oliver "robbed the bank, came out, threw the money all over the place.""He started throwing money out of the bag and then said, 'Merry Christmas!'"And what do you do after robbing a bank? You get a coffee of course. Witnesses said Oliver then casually made his way over to a Starbucks, sat down in front of the coffee shop, and waited for the cops to arrive. Colorado 11 News reported that bystanders were reported to have picked up all the cash from the street and then returned it back to the back.   Oliver was eventually taken into custody and is currently being held on $10,000 bond.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/26/3940934/3940934_F56745E5B0C74115B18F7D43458A7D05_191226_3940934_Man_throws_money_into_the_air_after_robbing_bank_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3ED/783/3ED78329995C542AF268FD6E7215D0EF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man robs bank, man robs bank throws cash in air, man robs bank throws cash in streets, man throws money away, man gives bank money away, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman with cold gets $28,395.50 bill for a throat swab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A New York woman with a case of the sniffles who visited the doctor was hit with a $28,395.50 bill, most of which her insurance coughed up. According to NPR, Alexa Kasdan popped into see Dr Roya Fathollahi, a primary care physician at Manhattan Specialty Care, back in November because of a lingering sore throat.  Kasdan told NPR she was going to go on vacation so she wanted to make sure she wasn't hit with strep while on break. NPR reports that she popped in for a quick visit and had her throat swabbed and some blood drawn and was sent on her way with some antibiotics. Her vacay went fine, but then the sickness came. Dr. Fathollahi's office had left messages and an email saying her insurance company was sending her family a check for MORE THAN 25 grand to cover some out-of-network lab tests. Tests that would have cost only $653 had the throat swab been sent to Kasdan's in-network provider. They told Kasdan that these tests were normal and that actual bill was an insane $28,395.50. The doctor's office also said it would waive her portion of the bill, which came out to $2,530.26.Another possible reason for such an astronomically expensive bill is there could be a connection between the out-of-network lab and Dr. Fathollahi. According to NPR, Kasdan's bill shows the tests were done by Manhattan Gastroenterology, which conveniently has the same phone number and locations as her doctor's office. Damn, that's COLD.   In the end Kasdan paid her usual $25 copay and a $9.61 fee for some separate lab testsSo what's the lesson of the day? American healthcare is a total sham.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/26/3940930/3940930_24D2159EF0604113800127D219045D99_191226_3940930_Woman_with_cold_gets__28_395_50_bill_for_a_throa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ACB/D00/ACBD001C37E84A977AA349A10D72E97F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Woman sent bill, woman sent huge bill, woman sent massive doctor bill, woman throat swab, huge doctor bill, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah bro implants Tesla key and other chips into his hands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPRINGVILLE, UTAH  Carrying keys, wallets or purses are increasingly becoming things of the past as more and more people embrace mobile technology. But would you go so far as to have cybernetic implants shoved under your skin all for the sake of some marginal convenience? According to ABC 7, that's exactly what Ben Workman did. The self-described "cybernetics enthusiast" studies human and machine interaction. He's had four different chips jammed inside him so he can unlock doors at work, log on and off of his computer and share contact information. You need to have implants for those things?According to Workman, it was hard to find people in the beginning to turn him into Tony Stark Beta. He eventually recruited a family member for his first try. And then came Ben's Tesla Model 3. Who can be bothered carrying around car keys anymore? Workman had to enlist the help of a piercing studio to get the larger Tesla key implant into his hand.   Ben apparently also had a magnet implanted into his left hand, that he uses for "magic tricks" and "fun stuff." Hopefully he doesn't get a new caror carjacked.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 15:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941530/3941530_A0A9F9D70D92461B9101FF887351B66F_191227_3941530_Utah_bro_implants_Tesla_key_and_other_chips_into_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0D9/A59/0D9A591EB4B9388FB9D9AEAC71ADD17E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Guy embeds Tesla key hand, man implants Tesla key, man implants Tesla Model 3 key, key in hand, cybernetics, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China builds airport in Cambodia, raising fears about its ambitions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DARA SAKOR, CAMBODIA  China's construction of an airstrip in Cambodia is raising alarms about its military ambitions, according to the New York Times.Bloomberg reports that Beijing now controls 20 percent of Cambodia's coastline via the lease of Dara Sakor, where a contractor is building an airport, a deep water port, medical facilities and a resort.According to the New York Times, the Chinese claim the Dara Sakor airport  which will feature the longest runway in Cambodia  is a civilian facility.However, the newspaper reports that the construction's scale and its tight turning bays which accommodate fighter jets point to a military purpose.China-based Union Development Group holds the 99 year lease to the Dara Sakor investment zone.Citing political scientist Sophal Ear at Occidental College, the New York Times reports that China's construction of the airport is to project power in the region. According to the New York Times, the construction in Cambodia is likely a move to further Beijing's military strategy known as the "string of pearls."This strategy involves establishing infrastructure and military bases that stretch from the South China Sea to the Indian Ocean and beyond.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 11:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941422/3941422_46F2B6345B5E442F974248F5BF769F81_191227_3941422_China_builds_airport_in_Cambodia__raising_fears__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/733/337/733337E08441637D6718EE08AA9A630C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[DaraSakor International Airport, airfield, airbase, lease, Dara Sakor investment zone, Dara Sakor, string of pearls, belt and road, Cambodia, China, US, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man fires gunshots out of a moving car, gets arrested</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EL PASO, TEXAS  A man in Texas was arrested on Monday after a video surfaced online of the guy randomly firing gunshots through an open window of a moving car.In the video, the man is seen smiling in the backseat as he starts firing while cars pass by on El Paso's Patriot Freeway.The video was initially posted on to social media after which it was picked up by a local gossip site Fit Fam El Paso, according to ABC News. This caught the attention of the El Paso police. Authorities posted a tweet on December 21 saying that they are looking into the incident.The next day, the police called for the unidentified man to turn himself in and "make it a lesson learned."On December 23, Jonathan Jay Oneal, turned himself in. The cops said that he was arrested on charges of discharging a firearm in certain municipalities.In a news release, the police said that Oneal was booked into the El Paso County Detention Facility on a US$50,000 bond.The police said no one was injured in the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941394/3941394_2120886A038748BABB8DF0C873590C19_191227_3941394_Man_fires_gunshots_out_of_a_moving_car__gets_arr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/788/22F/78822FE7ABA56AAED20C5AE96C52C576.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Smiling suspects, man fires out of car window, texas, viral videos, texas police, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser telescope can now spot small space debris from Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China-based scientists have developed a way to use laser telescopes and neural network analysis to locate space debris.According to a study in the Journal of Laser Applications, the team tested the method at the Beijing Fangshen laser range telescope station.Citing the team leader Ma Tianming, the American Institute of Physics says the technology allows laser scopes to detect reflected laser light from small space debris with greater accuracy than before.It can detect space junk with a cross-section of one square meter and a distance of 1,500 kilometers from earth.According to the news release, neural networks are algorithms based on the human brain's sensory inputs, processing and outputs.Using the neural network to fine-tune telescope readings, the team says their technology is the first to have significantly augmented laser ranging accuracy.Researchers say refining the technology will enable telescopes to pinpoint orbital debris.The paper states that locating the debris would then allow spacecraft to chart a safer course to avoid space junk.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941391/3941391_B51625600A474D0A88B287A9BBDBAB46_191227_3941391_Laser_telescope_can_now_spot_small_space_debris__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/288/BE8/288BE880E23522969C86FA1F2B4DF5BE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Laser telescope, laser telescopes, space junk, space debris, neural network, neural networks, algorithm, algorithms, Chinese Academy of Surveying and Mapping, China, US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest 3D-printed building completed in Dubai</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES  Apis Cor, an American construction firm that specializes in 3D printing, completed the world's largest 3D-printed building in Dubai at the end of October.The building stands at 9.5 meters and covers an area of 640 square meters, according to the company's project website. The structure was built using a mobile 3D printer onsite. It was moved around by a crane at the construction site. The 3D printer used a gypsum-based mixture developed by the company.Apis Cor said the printer was able to withstand Dubai's harsh weather conditions as the entire process took place outdoors, without temperature or humidity control.According to design magazine Dwell, the building was completed in three weeks.Traditional construction methods were used to lay the building's foundation and install the structure's roof, windows and insulation. Manual labor was used to fill the building's columns with heavy concrete and rebar.The building will provide offices for a government agency in Dubai, according to Dwell. Apis Cor said on their website that they plan to improve their 3D printing technology and develop a new version of the printer that would be twice as fast.The company plans to build affordable 3D-printed houses in the states of California and Louisiana.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941366/3941366_18DC3748CB744127ABFB70137133C948_191227_3941366_World_s_largest_3D_printed_building_completed_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7DA/F67/7DAF67E13E316F368255F3F96963ABD2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[3D printing, 3D printed buildings, Dubai Municipality, Dubai 3D printed building, world's largest 3D printed building, 3D printing technology, 3d printing building construction, 3d printing building construction dubai, 3D building design, Apis Cor, apis cor dubai, apis cor 3D printed building, Apis Cor 3D printing, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AA back to squeezing in tighter seats on Boeing 737s</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FORT WORTH, TEXAS  American Airlines is back to retrofitting their fleet of Boeing 737-800 planes with a newer, tighter, and much less comfy interior. According to View From the Wing, the retrofit program was paused back in March after 737 Max planes were grounded following the fatal Lion Air and Ethiopian crashes.At the time, American didn't want to take any more planes out of service and risk cancelling even more flights. But now, they're back at it again, squeezing in 12 more seats per plane at the expense of passengers' ever-shrinking legroom. The seats are harder, with less padding and less recline ability.  The divider between first and economy is gone, and there's no seatback video screen, either!The only thing that did get bigger are the overhead storage bins, but that's so the airline won't have to keep gate-checking bulky bags, which can cause delays.If you think that's a tight fit, wait til you see the bathroom, described by one AA pilot as "the most miserable experience in the world."There's no way anyone will be happy flying in this sardine can, so we're not sure where AA President Robert Isom heard the nice responses customers supposedly gave.Hate to break it to ya, Bobby boy, but your Project Oasis is really more of a mirage, and definitely not a "real success."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 03:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941102/3941102_31B7043263544E40BA71B66466049CA7_191227_3941102_AA_back_to_squeezing_in_tighter_seats_on_Boeing__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/86A/6D9/86A6D9967CAD2BCA3BAEB917035E09A4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[American Airlines, Boeing 737, cramped airline seats, cramped plane, cramped plane seats, Oasis configuration, Project Oasis, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super thirsty koala grabs a drink from cyclist's water bottle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA  A woman out biking with her friends was shocked when an extremely parched koala walked up and drank from her water bottle. According to 7 News, Anna Heusler was biking with a group of cyclists toward Adelaide last Friday when the thirsty little fella hailed them down. It approached the riders, so Heusler started giving it water. That's when her furry new friend climbed up onto her bike so it was easier to have a sipokay, more like a massive gulp. In a series of several Instagram posts, Heusler said the koala was suffering from severe thirst due to recent the heatwave and fires.   Heusler told 7 News that it wasn't unusual to see koalas while biking, but seeing one approach them like that was surprising. Talking to the station, she said, "we've seen literally hundreds of koalas over the years, we have never seen a koala do this."Unfortunately, they didn't have more water to give the little guy. They eventually put the furry fellow back into some nearby trees. Australia's koalas have been seriously struggling after massive bushfires in the region this year have destroyed habitats, leaving them without food or water.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 13:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942593/3942593_0753B6238F154D67B153389A16A748CC_191230_3942593_Super_thirsty_koala_grabs_a_drink_from_cyclist_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0CF/860/0CF860FCD0892D118351D8670A7EC6BF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Koala, thirsty koala, thirsty koala drinks cyclists water, thirsty koala drinks water, Australia fires, Australia koala fires, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New leaked OPCW documents reveal Douma inconsistencies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DOUMA, SYRIA  Wikileaks has posted several documents that further exposes the coverup within the OPCW of what really happened during the alleged Douma gas attacks.On the night of April 7, 2018, Syrian military helicopters allegedly dropped chlorine bombs on the town of Douma, killing dozens of civilians.The Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons sent a fact-finding mission to investigate two sites where gas cylinders were found: a rooftop balcony and a bedroom. According to the official OPCW report, the rooftop bomb first struck a corner of the balcony wall.This initial impact decreased the cylinder's velocity and changed its trajectory, causing it to hit the concrete floor hard enough to make a hole and fracture the valve, but without sufficient energy to fall through.At the bedroom location, the official report maintains that the chlorine-filled cylinder fell parallel to the roof of a building and crashed through the concrete.""It fell through and briefly impacted the floor, then continued forward on an altered trajectory that landed it on the bed. The harness and valve remained intact, and its contents were not discharged.In a newly-leaked memo on Wikileaks, a scientist who was part of the Douma fact-finding mission told OPCW Director-General Fernando Arias that over 20 inspectors have expressed concern over inconsistencies in the official findings.The memo's author claims that  except for one FFM member who was a paramedic, all others on the ground in Douma were excluded in the production of the final report.Instead, OPCW gathered a separate "core" group that operated from "Country X", believed to be Turkey, to create said report.Wikileaks had also released the first draft of the report, in which investigators say they were unable to explain "the relatively moderate damage to the cylinder...compared to the destruction caused to the rebar-reinforced concrete roof."Blood and other samples taken from alleged victims who fled to Turkey found no trace of any nerve agent – a finding left out in the final report. No trace was detected in surrounding buildings or vegetation in Douma, either.Another crucial finding involves the symptoms of the victims in the alleged chemical attack as being inconsistent with exposure to chlorine-containing choking or blood agents like chlorine gas, phosgene, or cyanogen chloride.These directly contradict the final report, which states the investigation found "reasonable grounds that the use of a toxic chemical as a weapon took place."In a report on CounterPunch, OPCW whistleblower 'Alex' said chlorinated organic chemicals are present in the natural environment, so to serve as an indicator of a chemical attack, chlorine levels should be significantly higher than what is already present.In an email exchange with FFM leader Sami Barrek from July 2018, an investigator raised concern that the final report mentioned the presence of chlorinated organic chemicals at the scene, but excluded the fact that only very low levels were recovered.Earlier in May, a leaked OPCW engineering assessment by ballistics expert Ian Henderson had found that the characteristics of the cylinders and surrounding scene were inconsistent with being dropped from an aircraft. It concluded that there is a higher probability they were manually placed at the two sites.In CounterPunch, Alex mention an incident that could explain why the OPCW was ignoring so many dissenting voices.In July 2018,  Alex claims the OPCW was visited by US officials from an unknown US agency, who told them emphatically that "the Syrian regime had conducted a gas attack, and that the two cylinders found on the roof and upper floor of the building contained 170 kilograms of chlorine.The Americans, along with the British and the French, had launched retaliatory airstrikes against Syria for the chemical attack on Douma.If it turns out that the attack was in fact a false flag operation masterminded by the rebels, it would be a massive blow to the narrative already established by the Western powers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942553/3942553_6BC39F27271749A3AAC436507877A3F4_191230_3942553_New_leaked_OPCW_documents_reveal_Douma_inconsist_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A20/4FA/A204FAE3C335FC3B4DA85AA3D185ECEB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Douma gas attack, douma chemical attack, OPCW, OPCW report, sarin gas, chlorine gas, wikileaks, leaked OPCW documents, leaked documents, OPCW whistleblower, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's floating nuclear power plant now produces electricity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PEVEK, RUSSIA   The floating nuclear power plant Akademik Lomonosov has been connected to the electricity grid and successfully produced power for the first time in the Russian town of Pevek.Back in August, the vessel had set out on a three-week journey from the port of Murmansk, as reported by the Associated Press.As it is not self-propelled, the floating power unit was towed by a fleet of tugboats to the Russian town when it arrived on September 14.The vessel is 144 meters long and 30 meters wide, according to a news release from Rosatom, the company that designed the floating plant.The Akademik Lomonosov is equipped with two reactor systems, each with a 35-megawatt capacity. The reactors produce steam for a turbine that will then generate electricity.The vessel is designed to provide energy to port cities and offshore gas and oil-extracting platforms.It is capable of producing enough to power a city of 100,000 inhabitants.Rosatom claims that the floating nuclear plant is designed with a great margin of safety that exceeds all possible threats, which makes nuclear reactors "invincible" against tsunamis and other natural disasters.The Associated Press points out environmentalists have criticized the floating nuclear plant as "inherently dangerous" adding that it threatens the clean Arctic region.But Russia has dismissed these concerns, insisting that a floating nuclear power plant is completely safe.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 10:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942498/3942498_F4A513A87BE84EE8A9C05C7351CE2E80_191230_3942498_Russia_s_floating_nuclear_power_plant_now_produc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5C3/F4A/5C3F4A50135848F24F2643E798C0D24F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Floating nuclear plant, floating nuclear power plant, russian floating nuclear plant, first floating nuclear plant, russia nuclear plant, floating power plant, russia's first floating nuclear power plant, akademik lomonosov nuclear, akademik lomonosov floating nuclear power plant, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster halo could unravel the Earth's antimatter mystery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA's Fermi telescope discovered a vast halo around a neutron star that could explain why there is so much antimatter near Earth.According to NASA, there is higher than expected amount of antimatter near Earth, a phenomenon which scientists have struggled to find an explanation for. NASA published its study in Physical Review D Tuesday last week.According to NASA's news release, when a giant star dies and explodes into a supernova, its remaining core sometimes becomes a neutron star. The neutron star named Geminga is a pulsar, which constantly discharges electrons and their antimatter counterpart known as positrons into space.As charged positrons and electrons collide with photons from starlight, the added energy charge the light into gamma rays.Since the path of gamma rays are scrambled by the magnetic fields they encounter, scientists have been unable to trace the positrons back to their origins until now. Using the Fermi data, a NASA affiliated team removed background gamma radiation from the readings and determined that Geminga is in fact the source of the extra positrons.According to the study's co-author Silvia Manconi at Aachen University, the pulsar contributed about 20 percent of positrons detected near Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 08:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942431/3942431_7F0FC4D5CE0D4BDDA75A6F9B29276DBE_191230_3942431_Monster_halo_could_unravel_the_Earth_s_antimatte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1A4/DCB/1A4DCB11DEC5E525DC6608CAE916FED1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fermi, telescope, gamma rays, gamma radiation, halo, Geminga, positrons, positron, antimatter, anti-matter, NASA, Aachen University, space, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
