<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <source>RSS feed for Topbuzz</source>
  <item>
    <title>Toys R Us bankruptcy lawyers get $56M while laid-off workers $2M</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/toys-r-us-bankruptcy-lawyers-get-56m-while-laid-off-workers-2m-3853318</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/01/3853318/3853318_0170C0BC60B946148E55D6F6334BF956_190701_3853318_Toys_R_Us_bankruptcy_lawyers_get__56M_while_laid_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[VIRGINIA  A year after Toys "R" Us closed, tens of thousands of laid-off workers will get some of the estate's remaining cash to make up for severance they were denied during the court case. Bloomberg reported Judge Keith L. Philips of the Eastern District of Virginia awarded $2 million to the workers, who were promised severance at the start of bankruptcy as part of a benefits plan that was later canceled as the restructuring went haywire. According to Bloomberg, former workers led by 30-year Toys "R" Us employee Ann Marie Reinhart Smith filed a class action claim in 2018 to the bankruptcy court to ask that severance claims get the same priority as administrative claims.   The retailer's bankruptcy is in its final stages and is now focusing on distributing cash set aside for administrative fees. According to Bloomberg, these expenses usually include fees for advisers, lawyers and other parties involved in winding down the company. They're given high priority by the court for repayment in fullof course.The $2 million settlement means 33,000 axed employees will get about $60 bucks a person. To put that into perspective, the law firm of Kirkland & Ellis LLP, which represented Toys "R" US in the bankruptcy was awarded $56 million in fees. So that's what it feels like to be a Toys "R" US kid.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B24/027/B240278FFF95B5A49C21647FC8CE8055.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>76</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Toys R Us</Tag>
          <Tag>Toys R Us bankruptcy</Tag>
          <Tag>Toys R Us severance lawsuit</Tag>
          <Tag>Toys R Us class action lawsuit</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 14:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>James Harden gets called for traveling on Shanghai scooter</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/james-harden-gets-called-for-traveling-on-shanghai-scooter-3853297</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/01/3853297/3853297_676723D85E6D439E8801FA59AC5C5750_190701_3853297_James_Harden_gets_called_for_traveling_on_Shangh_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SHANGHAI, CHINA  Houston Rockets guard James Harden is a big fan of travelinghe also likes going to see other countries which is why he was in Shanghai. According to the SCMP, Harden was stopped by traffic police on Saturday for zipping around on an electric scooter with some friends.  In photos and videos uploaded to Weibo, the step back king was apparently pulled over for breaking some local road rules. The SCMP reported the Beard was traveling from Shangri-La Hotel to Cao Yang Road around 3 p.m. in the afternoon. It's unknown if Harden was given a ticket, but cops probably had no idea who he was. The Houston guard did get his electric scooter confiscated thoughthat's what you get for traveling everywhere.According to the SCMP, Harden was in China on an Adidas promotional tour. After his little scooter situation, he jumped on China's Twitter knockoff Weibo to issue an apology."China, thank you  for your hospitality. I would like to apologize for violating traffic rules during my scooter ride today," he said. "Not a good example obviously but I was just trying to enjoy the city as much as possible. Thank you for your understanding and I'll make sure to abide by the rules next time here."]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/48F/D22/48FD2231E316A6019645C2D5DE924DE3.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>92</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>James Harden</Tag>
          <Tag>James Harden China</Tag>
          <Tag>James Harden scooter Shanghai</Tag>
          <Tag>Harden pulled over China</Tag>
          <Tag>James Harden pulled over Shanghai</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 13:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Woman with unforgettable mugshot arrested for 3rd time</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-with-unforgettable-mugshot-arrested-for-3rd-time-3853212</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/01/3853212/3853212_68BAA9FCE6C5466AA43C5F33E171D202_190701_3853212_Woman_with_unforgettable_mugshot_arrested_for_3r_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[DAYTON, OHIO  An Ohio woman whose mean mug went viral last year is making headlines once again, after being jailed for the third time in the last six months.WKYC reports that 27-year-old Alyssa Zebrasky's inked face made its criminal debut in November 2018 for an obstructing justice arrest. She and boyfriend Logan Daugherty had been in possession of weapons and tried to run from the cops.Zebrasky's distinct facial tattoos consist of a spider web and a full skeleton face, which quickly got attention online.A month later, Miss Dia de los Muertos got nabbed once again after stealing a bag from Walmart. The guys in blue also busted her for possession of meth, and for failing to appear in court for her first crime.Her tattooed mug made its latest appearance in April, after the police booked her into Montgomery County Jail on a charge stemming out of Mahoning County. There's no telling what gnarliness she got into this time, but given her track record, that's probably not the last we'll see of it.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CD3/4B5/CD34B5C68C10E29643391712A9B69048.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>69</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>viral mugshot</Tag>
          <Tag>viral mug</Tag>
          <Tag>facial tattoo</Tag>
          <Tag>mugshot</Tag>
          <Tag>unique mugshot</Tag>
          <Tag>full face tattoo</Tag>
          <Tag>full face skeleton tattoo</Tag>
          <Tag>full face skull tattoo</Tag>
          <Tag>unforgettable mugshot</Tag>
          <Tag>dia de los muertos</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 10:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Japan to resume commercial whaling despite global outcry</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/japan-to-resume-commercial-whaling-despite-global-outcry-3853197</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/01/3853197/3853197_66668D0C1CB84324B6787A7966B999BF_190701_3853197_Japan_to_resume_commercial_whaling_despite_globa_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[JAPAN  Despite international scrutiny, the Japanese government is about to resume profitable whale hunting.According to the BBC, Japan has now withdrawn from the International Whaling Commission, or 'IWC'.The IWC's site states that it was set up in 1946 with the purpose of proper conservation of whale stocks and the management of whaling.Kyodo News reported that Japanese whaling fleets will set sail Monday morning, a day after Tokyo formally left the IWC, with a target of catching 227 whales for the year.Although Japan has not technically practiced commercial whaling for 31 years, it has been hunting whales in the Antarctic Ocean for 'scientific research' under the exception of an IWC rule.Since 1987, Japan has caught between 200 and 1,200 whales annually, under the ostensible purpose of observing stocks to establish sustainable quotas.Japan opened itself up to accusations of a cover-up from critics when whale meat from the 'research' usually went on sale.Hideki Moronuki of the Japanese fishing ministry told the BBC that whaling "will be conducted within Japan's territorial waters and Exclusive Economic Zone."But why is Japan restarting whaling now? According to the AFP, in a 2016 IWC gathering, Japan asked IWC members to allow for small hunts around coastal communities, arguing that whale meat is part of its history and culture.And what impact will Japan's whaling have?Japan plans to hunt three species of whale: minke, Bryde's and sei whales. According to the IUCN Red List of Threatened Species, Minke and Bryde's are not endangered and Sei whales numbers are improving.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C02/73B/C0273B599C8CF9D54E5845C0606713CB.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>108</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>whaling</Tag>
          <Tag>conservation</Tag>
          <Tag>Japan to resume commercial whaling</Tag>
          <Tag>Japan resumes commercial whaling</Tag>
          <Tag>japan whaling industry</Tag>
          <Tag>Japan</Tag>
          <Tag>whales</Tag>
          <Tag>whale</Tag>
          <Tag>laws</Tag>
          <Tag>illegal</Tag>
          <Tag>poaching</Tag>
          <Tag>caught</Tag>
          <Tag>regulations</Tag>
          <Tag>commercial</Tag>
          <Tag>species</Tag>
          <Tag>populations</Tag>
          <Tag>environment</Tag>
          <Tag>ecosystem</Tag>
          <Tag>whaling in Japan</Tag>
          <Tag>whaling regulation.</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 09:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Nipsey Hussle murdered for calling Holder a snitch</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nipsey-hussle-murdered-for-calling-holder-a-snitch-3853089</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/01/3853089/3853089_8601753DA8B04EED98BE2CF2B1F1E2E5_190701_3853089_Nipsey_Hussle_murdered_for_calling_Holder_a_snit_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  According to NBC News, an unsealed grand jury transcript said that rapper Nipsey Hussle was shot on March 31 after making a comment about someone being an informant.Hussle was murdered outside of his clothing store in Los Angeles during a personal dispute with alleged killer Eric Holder.According to witness testimony from Herman Douglas, Hussle allegedly said, "man, you know, they got some paperwork on you."Deputy District Attorney John McKinney said the remarks led Holder to leave, return and then fire shots from two weapons, a semi-automatic handgun, and a revolver.Douglas testified that "paperwork" meant police or court documents recording Holder as a snitch. Holder was driven to the scene by a woman he was dating. The woman testified in court saying that she was amazed to see the rapper and got out of the car to ask for a picture, it was at this point she heard Holder turn the accusation onto Hussle.After the heated exchange, the woman said that she and Holder drove off and that's when Holder pulled out a gun and demanded she stop and wait at a certain location. She said that Holder got out of the car, didn't explain himself and then after a short while jumped back into the vehicle. She continued saying that she was confused but that Holder threatened to slap her if she did not drive off quickly.Holder has pleaded not guilty.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3E4/534/3E453442CCFC360872653D52AD28A0C0.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>84</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Nipsey Hussle</Tag>
          <Tag>Nipsey Hussle shooting</Tag>
          <Tag>Eric Holder</Tag>
          <Tag>Nipsey Hussle rapper</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 07:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>NASA to send Dragonfly rotorcraft to explore Titan</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-to-send-dragonfly-rotorcraft-to-explore-titan-3852983</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/01/3852983/3852983_17D14C985CC248F3B682030644308061_190701_3852983_NASA_to_send_Dragonfly_rotorcraft_to_explore_Tit_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA is sending a nuclear-powered drone to explore the unique and richly organic world of Titan.NASA announced on Thursday that it will be sending a multi-rotor vehicle called Dragonfly on a mission to Titan, Saturn's largest moon.Dragonfly will launch in 2026 and land on the satellite eight years later, in 2034.The rotorcraft, which has eight rotors and flies like a drone, will spend at least two and a half years making two dozen short flights to explore Titan.According to the New York Times, it will be equipped with a nuclear battery that is charged in between flights.Part of the mission is to study whether Titan is or once was host to life. Its nitrogen-based atmosphere is similar to Earth's, albeit four times denser. Instead of water, lakes, rivers, and seas are filled with liquid methane.While the surface is composed of rock-hard water ice, a liquid water reservoir exists beneath the crust.Dragonfly will have cameras on board to stream images taken during flight. It will also carry scientific instruments including spectrometers to study the moon's composition, meteorology sensors, and seismometers.Drills in the landing skids will take surface samples to be analyzed onboard.Dragonfly is not the first spacecraft to touch down on Saturn's largest moon. Europe's Huygens probe landed on Titan in 2005, after travelling to the Saturn system with NASA's Cassini spacecraft.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E0C/10C/E0C10C4AF0475026FBB13E99275BE644.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>95</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>dragonfly</Tag>
          <Tag>nasa dragonfly</Tag>
          <Tag>dragonfly mission</Tag>
          <Tag>titan</Tag>
          <Tag>titan moon</Tag>
          <Tag>saturn moon</Tag>
          <Tag>saturn system</Tag>
          <Tag>life on titan</Tag>
          <Tag>nasa mission</Tag>
          <Tag>nasa new frontiers</Tag>
          <Tag>new frontiers</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 03:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How to view next week's South American eclipse safely</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-to-view-next-week-s-south-american-eclipse-safely-3852966</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/01/3852966/3852966_2FEB31C57B1D434698D6705480B1FAC3_190701_3852966_How_to_view_next_week_s_South_American_eclipse_s_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SOUTH AMERICA  Ahead of next week's total eclipse across South America, astronomers from the American Astronomical Society are warning the public that staring directly at an eclipse can cause permanent damage to the eyes.The American Astronomical Society's website says eclipse glasses or handheld solar filters that compliant with ISO 12312-2 international safety standards must be used when looking at a partially eclipsed sun.This is because the concentrated solar rays from the sun are strong enough to cause significant damage to the retina and could even lead to blindness.Unfiltered cameras, telescopes or regular sunglasses must be not be used when viewing an eclipse. Old solar filters must be discarded if they are scratched, punctured, torn or damaged in any way.The solar filter can only be removed when the moon has completely covered the sun in a total eclipse.Alternate viewing methods include viewing the eclipse via a pinhole projection. This is when you cut a pinhole onto a piece of paper or cardboard and use it to project light onto another piece of paper to view the eclipse.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6BF/71E/6BF71E90FACBCC5830C6C229627EC7C5.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>88</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>south america</Tag>
          <Tag>solar eclipse</Tag>
          <Tag>solar eclipse in south america</Tag>
          <Tag>solar eclipse explained</Tag>
          <Tag>south america eclipse</Tag>
          <Tag>july solar eclipse</Tag>
          <Tag>look at the sun during eclipse</Tag>
          <Tag>how to look at the sun during a solar eclipse</Tag>
          <Tag>looking at a solar eclipse</Tag>
          <Tag>solar eclipse eyewear</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 02:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Thai teacher goes viral for cool class welcomes</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/thai-teacher-goes-viral-for-cool-class-welcomes-3853776</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/02/3853776/3853776_AE9F1901E68F44E1AFBD106E2E56927D_190702_3853776_Thai_teacher_goes_viral_for_cool_class_welcomes_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[CHACHOENGSAO, THAILAND  An elementary school teacher in Thailand has gone viral for her creative and heartwarming way she welcomes her class in the morning. In a video posted to Facebook, 25-year-old Nattaya Nat is seen giving her students a kindhearted morning hello. Nat teaches at the Banpruewai School in Chachoengsao province and gives her students a choice of four different greetings: 1. hug, 2. handshake, 3. fist-bump and 4. High-five.The pupils are scene lining up to enter the classroom and picking their personalized what's up.Her video has already racked up more that 3.8 million views, with over 37,000 shares and a boatload of comments.  Nat has also shared other videos of her and her students learning and having fun together in class. Wellshe definitely gets an A for effort.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE0/F75/FE0F751D557C4B392AE4FF397FD08606.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>57</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Thai teacher</Tag>
          <Tag>Thai teacher class welcomes</Tag>
          <Tag>Thai teacher class greetings</Tag>
          <Tag>Thai teacher Nattaya Nat</Tag>
          <Tag>Facebook Natayya Nat</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 11:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>62 infected in U.S. salmonella outbreak linked to papayas</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/62-infected-in-u-s-salmonella-outbreak-linked-to-papayas-3853739</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/02/3853739/3853739_09E3714502BA45F9909F42F9FEEE14FA_190702_3853739_62_infected_in_U_S__salmonella_outbreak_linked_t_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[ATLANTA  More than 60 people have gotten sick in the U.S. this year after eating salmonella-contaminated papayas.The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has warned that 62 people in eight states have become infected with the uganda serotype of the salmonella bacteria. 23 of those who got sick were hospitalized.The outbreak has been linked to the consumption of fresh papayas imported from Mexico.According to the Mayo Clinic, salmonella bacteria typically live in the intestinal tracts of humans and animals, and are shed through feces. Humans become infected mostly through contaminated water or food.The CDC reports that symptoms typically show 12 to 72 hours after infection, and may include abdominal cramps, high fever, and diarrhea.It usually lasts from 4 to 7 days, with patients recovering without treatment. But complications arise when the infection leaves the intestinal tract and enters the bloodstream.The Mayo Clinic reports that in such cases, it can infect tissues in the body, including those surrounding the brain and spinal cord, the lining of the heart, valves, or blood vessels, and bones or bone marrow.According to the CDC, an estimated 450 people in the U.S. die from acute salmonellosis each year.The elderly, children younger than five, and those with weakened immune systems are more vulnerable to severe infections.Methods to prevent the spread of salmonella include hand washing after using the toilet, changing diapers, or handling raw meat.Raw meat, poultry, and seafood should also be kept separate from cooked food, fruits, and vegetables to avoid cross-contamination.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/635/FCA/635FCA18E5320130831C22A0096A8AD8.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>102</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>salmonella</Tag>
          <Tag>salmonella infection</Tag>
          <Tag>salmonella outbreak</Tag>
          <Tag>salmonellosis</Tag>
          <Tag>contaminated papaya</Tag>
          <Tag>tainted papaya</Tag>
          <Tag>salmonella papaya</Tag>
          <Tag>salmonella bacteria</Tag>
          <Tag>bacterial infection</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Beijing's new mega-airport is nearly complete</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/beijing-s-new-mega-airport-is-nearly-complete-3853721</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/02/3853721/3853721_28756A1E17BD438F8DE9371C1ACC623C_190702_3853721_Beijing_s_new_mega_airport_is_nearly_complete_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BEIJING   According to Business Insider, China's construction of the world's largest-airport project is coming to an end after three years of work.The 6-pier, radial-shaped airport project, which covers a reported distance of 700,000 square meters, or 7.5 million square ft, has so far cost just shy of $12 billion.The South China Morning Post reported that the overall decoration work is expected to be finished by late April, with the airport set to officially open on September 30, 2019.The airport is located in an area that overlaps the Daxing district in Beijing and Guangyang district of Langfang, Hebei province. The airport will serve Beijing, Tianjin, and Hebei.The airport could shift the balance of power in the country's airline industry with three state-owned airlines lobbying for landing slots. Flag carrier Air China dominates the current Beijing airport. Its regional competitors China Eastern Airlines control Shanghai, while China Southern Airlines hold Guangzhou.The new airport will allow China Eastern and China Southern a 40 percent share of passengers each, which may encourage the two provincial airlines to open new North American routes.It's estimated that the current Beijing Capital International Airport and the new airport will handle a combined annual total of 170 million passengers with their seven runways by 2025.However, experts worry that because only about 20 percent of the airspace of China is open to civilian flights, the expansion will result in extremely heavy air traffic.China is not only a world leader in airport size but also in flight delays. Business Traveller reported that in 2017, bad air pollution, i.e smog, resulted in poor visibility and made up for 50 percent of its delays.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9A4/57B/9A457B8C0EBB5D23DC6C6BFA6AFF8476.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>124</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>beijing new airport</Tag>
          <Tag>beijing daxing airport</Tag>
          <Tag>beijing international airport</Tag>
          <Tag>beijing mega airport</Tag>
          <Tag>beijing mega infrastructures</Tag>
          <Tag>world's biggest airport beijing</Tag>
          <Tag>china megaprojects</Tag>
          <Tag>zaha hadid architects</Tag>
          <Tag>flight delays</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Texas plane crash leaves 10 dead</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-plane-crash-leaves-10-dead-3853456</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/02/3853456/3853456_F79E07D2D95642789626E6F601FF5FFC_190702_3853456_Texas_plane_crash_leaves_10_dead_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[ADDISON, TEXAS  A private plane crashed into an airport hanger in Texas on Sunday, leaving behind no survivors.The aircraft was a twin-engine Beechcraft BE-350 King Air, NBC News reports.Federal Aviation Administration spokesman Lynn Lunsford told the Dallas News that the plane crashed into the hanger at 9.10 a.m. during takeoff from Addison Airport in Texas.No one was inside the hanger during the time of the accident.Citing a statement from the FAA, NBC 5 Dallas-Fort Worth reports, the aircraft was completely destroyed by flames killing all 10 onboard. Officials have yet to release the names of the victims.The plane was headed from Addison, Texas to St. Petersburg, Florida, reports CNN.Both the National Transportation Safety Board and the Federal Aviation Association will send a team to investigate the cause of the accident, according to CNN.Judge Clay Jenkins, a Dallas County judge, tweeted, "Please pray for the families who lost loved ones in this tragedy. Team in process of notifying them."Airport operations resumed around 45 minutes after the crash, as reported by The Dallas News.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EDE/9E0/EDE9E0DD362810346A82C62888DAFFC7.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>67</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>texas</Tag>
          <Tag>plane crash</Tag>
          <Tag>airport hanger</Tag>
          <Tag>addison municipal airport</Tag>
          <Tag>addison municipal texas</Tag>
          <Tag>Beechcraft BE-350 King Air</Tag>
          <Tag>texas plane crash</Tag>
          <Tag>texas plane crash 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>texas plane crash addison municipal airport</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 02:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mysterious space radio waves
finally pinpointed by scientists</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mysterious-space-radio-waves%0Afinally-pinpointed-by-scientists-3853438</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/02/3853438/3853438_8E4017E834C64DD7998A745D987D4FBD_190702_3853438_Mysterious_space_radio_waves_finally_pinpointed__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MURCHISON / AUSTRALIA    Australian scientists have for the first time pinpointed the precise location of a mysterious burst of radio waves that originated in another galaxy.According to a release by the Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization or CSIRO, researchers in a world's first have identified the exact location of a great one-off rupture of cosmic radio waves.New Atlas reported that fast radio bursts are one of the most perplexing mysteries of the space age. So what in the galaxy are they and why haven't their origins been located before?Fast radio bursts, or FRBs, are millisecond-long signals which are known to repeat. However, most are single bursts, making them extremely challenging to localize. They come from all corners of the universe and were discovered in 2007, with 85 of them since detected. Nobody has been able to understand where they're coming from or what's causing them, until now.An Australian led team of astronomers have now located the galaxy from where one of these FRB waves originated, some 3.6 billion light-years away. The discovery was made using CSIRO's new Australian Square Kilometre Array Pathfinder, a radio telescope in Western Australia.The galaxy was then pictured using the three largest optical telescopes on the planet, Keck, Gemini South, and the European Southern Observatory's Very Large Telescope.CSIRO lead author Keith Bannister said, "This is the big breakthrough that the field has been waiting for since astronomers discovered fast radio bursts in 2007."So, how has this new technology allowed them to localize the radio signal?The Australian Square Kilometre Array Pathfinder is a design of multiple dish antennas. The burst had to travel a different distance to contact each dish, thus reaching them all at a somewhat different time, allowing for pinpoint accuracy.Adam Deller of Swinburne University of Technology said, "From these tiny time differences  just a fraction of a billionth of a second  we identified the burst's home galaxy and even its exact starting point, 13,000 light years out from the galaxy's center in the galactic suburbs."The cause of the burst remains unknown.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4C2/BF2/4C2BF28D8CFB7500947EC70205A509B3.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>116</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>space</Tag>
          <Tag>Australia</Tag>
          <Tag>CSIRO</Tag>
          <Tag>ASKAP</Tag>
          <Tag>astronomers have determined the precise location of a powerful one-off burst of cosmic radio waves</Tag>
          <Tag>FRBs</Tag>
          <Tag>fast radio bursts</Tag>
          <Tag>radio waves</Tag>
          <Tag>galaxy</Tag>
          <Tag>galaxies</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Hong Kong protests turn violent on anniversary of 1997 handover</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hong-kong-protests-turn-violent-on-anniversary-of-1997-handover-3854363</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/03/3854363/3854363_05572336D6F9420F9E54B15E7337637C_190703_3854363_Hong_Kong_protests_turn_violent_on_anniversary_o_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Beijing has condemned the protests in Hong Kong as violent, calling it an "undisguised challenge" to its rule.The BBC reports that during the anniversary of the Hong Kong handover on Monday, protesters blocked streets around the venue where Chief Executive Carrie Lam was attending the annual flag-raising ceremony.Demonstrators wearing hard hats and masks broke off from the main protest around midday, and made their way to the Legislative Council.They surrounded the building, eventually smashing through the glass facade.Inside the central chamber, protesters defaced the Hong Kong emblem and raised the old British colonial flag. They also spray-painted messages across the walls and shattered furniture.At midnight, police charged toward the building after several warnings earlier in the evening to clear it, firing tear gas at the rest of the crowd outside as they advanced.The streets were cleared within an hour, with only media and police remaining.The violent display came after a peaceful weeks-long demonstration, in which hundreds of thousands of Hong Kongers flocked to the streets to protest a controversial China extradition law.Like the Chinese government, Lam  likewise condemned the "extreme use of violence," adding that Hong Kong authorities will "pursue any illegal acts" carried out by demonstrators.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2B7/A43/2B7A4370A029C0F54C2A5CE9334F72A1.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>71</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong protest</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong protests</Tag>
          <Tag>extradition protest</Tag>
          <Tag>hk protest</Tag>
          <Tag>hk extradition bill</Tag>
          <Tag>carrie lam</Tag>
          <Tag>china extradition bill</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 11:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Arctic fox travels 3000km from Norway to Canada in 76 days</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/arctic-fox-travels-3000km-from-norway-to-canada-in-76-days-3854357</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/03/3854357/3854357_EEE7246B07C644BBAB55720E31E54B15_190703_3854357_Arctic_fox_travels_3000km_from_Norway_to_Canada__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[ELLESMERE ISLAND, CANADA  Scientists couldn't believe one arctic fox's epic 76-day, 3,000-kilometer trek from Norway to Canada  the longest and fastest ever recorded for this species.The BBC reports that researchers from the Norwegian Polar Institute fitted a young female arctic fox with a GPS tracking device, before freeing her into the wild in March 2018.From Spitsbergen on Norway's Svalbard archipelago, the animal set off west, reaching Greenland in 21 days and then continuing on to Canada's Ellesmere Island. The fox travelled 3,506 kilometers in just 76 days.Researchers say the fox covered an average of 46.3 kilometers a day, sometimes reaching 155 kilometers.She slowed down on only two occasions. Scientists think she may have either sat out bad weather, or found a source of food.The Polar Institute reports that the transmitter collar stopped working in February 2019, so the fox's current whereabouts are unknown.They do say she will likely need to change her eating habits, because while Svalbard foxes subsist on a mainly marine diet, those in Ellesmere Island live largely on lemmings.According to CNN, the Arctic is heating up twice as fast and causing a massive melting of sea ice, which is having an impact on arctic foxes.The BBC reports that in time, the population on Svalbard might become completely isolated.But researcher Eva Fuglei says there's hope, as higher temps mean more Svalbard reindeer, whose carcasses the foxes scavenge off.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/102/E89/102E891EA222AB7933CA2E989E55DDE4.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>106</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic fox</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic fox trek</Tag>
          <Tag>epic trek</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic fox epic trek</Tag>
          <Tag>Norway to Canada</Tag>
          <Tag>Svalbard</Tag>
          <Tag>Ellesmere Island</Tag>
          <Tag>Canada</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic fox diet</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 11:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Hong Kong 1997 handover: How the UK returned HK to China</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hong-kong-1997-handover-how-the-uk-returned-hk-to-china-3854226</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/03/3854226/3854226_BED6E46EC6B2445AAFFB718FA34C0054_190703_3854226_Hong_Kong_1997_handover__How_the_UK_returned_HK__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[HONG KONG  July 1, 2019 marks the 22nd anniversary of Hong Kong's return to Chinese rule. Here's everything you need to know about the handover.The South China Morning Post reports that China ceded Hong Kong Island to Britain in 1842, and Kowloon in 1860, ending the First and Second Opium Wars, respectively.In 1898, Britain leased the New Territories for a period of 99 years to better enforce control on the area.Over the course of those years, Hong Kong became a major financial and business hub, different both politically and economically from China, which came under Communist rule in 1949.June 30, 1997 marked the end of British colonial rule in Hong Kong, as the Chinese sovereignty resumed sovereignty at midnight on July 1.Beijing agreed to rule the city under the 'one country, two systems' principle for the next 50 years, turning Hong Kong into a Special Administrative Region with its own legal and political system, rights, and a constitution known as the Basic Law.Hong Kong's leader, the Chief Executive, is elected by a 1,200-member election committee. In the Legislative Council, half the representatives are elected, while half are chosen by professional or special interest groups.According to the BBC, many felt that the election process gave China the ability to screen out candidates it disapproves of. Dissatisfaction intensified in August 2014 after Beijing rejected calls for open nominations of the next Chief Executive, ultimately culminating in the Umbrella protests. China's 50-year-deal with Hong Kong will end in 2047, and while some have called for full independence, Beijing has said this is not an option.There are three likely scenarios: first, China extends the deal allowing Hong Kong its autonomy and Basic Law; second, China allows some of the current privileges, but not all, and third, Hong Kong loses its special status, and becomes just like any other Chinese province.But unlike its older residents, Hong Kong's increasingly politicized younger generation aren't ones to kowtow to China. So an intense political struggle is likely in the city's future. And if the recent extradition bill protests tells us anything, it's that Hong Kongers won't go down without a fight.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3F8/C65/3F8C65E0D2DC5005B2A54007B442A977.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>156</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong handover</Tag>
          <Tag>1997 handover</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong 1997 handover</Tag>
          <Tag>hk handover</Tag>
          <Tag>hk 1997</Tag>
          <Tag>hk protests</Tag>
          <Tag>hk extradition protest</Tag>
          <Tag>hk extradition bill</Tag>
          <Tag>hk history</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong history</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 08:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Man opens emergency exit on plane, says he didn't know any better</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-opens-emergency-exit-on-plane-says-he-didn-t-know-any-better-3854078</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/03/3854078/3854078_586A7FFAB53B4E6CB0F0F6332B5BB288_190703_3854078_Man_opens_emergency_exit_on_plane__says_he_didn__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BANGKOK  A Chinese man was escorted off a plane by Thai cops last Wednesday after opening the aircraft's emergency exit, reports the South China Morning Post.Lion Air flight SL940 was preparing to fly from Bangkok to Wuhan when the passenger decided to open the emergency exit door, according to Chinese broadcasting company, Phoenix Television. Citing the Chutian Metropolis Daily, the South China Morning Post reports that a witness saw the man reaching for the handle then pulling the emergency exit downwards, while the plane was on the ground.Terrified passengers began yelling at him, while a crew member rushed to see what was happening. The passenger that he didn't know that the emergency exit was not meant to be opened. He was apparently nervous and kept apologizing to the flight attendant, according to Phoenix Television.Not long after, the Thai police appeared and took the man off the plane with his luggage. It's unclear what happened next.  The airline declined to comment on the incident, The South China Morning Post reports.The 6:55 p.m. flight ended up being delayed for around two hours, before eventually departing Thailand at 8:47 p.m.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A28/2AD/A282ADB2CCFD564727B61B8047A8A328.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>86</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese passenger</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese tourists</Tag>
          <Tag>emergency exit plane</Tag>
          <Tag>thai cops</Tag>
          <Tag>thailand</Tag>
          <Tag>china</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese man removed from plane</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese man opens plane's emergency exit door</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese man opens plane door</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese man opens emergency exit door</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese tourists behaving badly 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese tourists on airplane</Tag>
          <Tag>thai lion air</Tag>
          <Tag>lion air chinese tourists</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 04:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>South Korea scrambles jets after 'unidentified object' over DMZ</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/south-korea-scrambles-jets-after-unidentified-object-over-dmz-3854880</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>https://fl4e4kle4v6fhmr5ypjtqhz6oc.gcdn.anvato.net/up-video/66F/73B/66F73B702554466C9836DC1C30EC6B1C?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1656845409&amp;Signature=he5A34%2BV7IXjutF501R2dUp%2FnsCKx1MZMPwDOA4ePwdWe3%2BF4bXIjbsy1nq7lIB9Q5WsONewKPcuf5f3zsLy7ywapvbosznsTHGx03pre3QNGRP29%2BFDl6jTqqahrDoMjgRKjiFXPieyBCLxSxO5N3mpUqsvLrD%2BiLOokQdlWRHUNy16jCA5HjPMQBJvFjMuKt3%2FikElI%2B%2B22hie3hirrXW0cIgHAMjhi4CzMVPCC4b%2Bi3jDhgUpLPhVudPOVPkmL6QIQdX7NTgu17GMqcOEzwktLP5AmA3Hiw6qmygzfhnw%2BBVN%2B9edbmVChRXRB42SzPtpQ2XYrYzzEXuy%2FtroEw%3D%3D&amp;Expires=1656962942&amp;KeyName=mcpkey1&amp;Signature=KZP76Pnps_ZDMdSpitrlA1XY-hQ</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SEOUL  South Korea's elite military detected an "unidentified object" flying near the border with North Korea on Monday.The K-Pop nation immediately bounced into action launching some fighters, and then ingeniously alerting the press.  ABC News reported the South's Joint Chiefs of Staff had said earlier on Monday that its radar found "the traces of flight by an unidentified object" over the central portion of the DMZ. The South Korean media feeding frenzy immediately began making stuff upsorry, SPECULATINGthat it was most likely a North Korean helicopter flying across the border. Turns out the mysterious object was actually a UFOYOU KNOWunidentified feathery object.According to a South Korean military official who wasn't supposed to chirp about the incident, turns out it was a flock of about 20 birds.    South Korea sent the funner Korea a message about its fighter jets to avoid unnecessary tensions. It's unknown how the flock of birds felt being buzzed by a bunch of flyboys. The incident came a day after a meeting between BFFs located inside the DMZ between Trump and Kim. During the meeting Donald briefly stepped into North Korea with Kim for some historic selfies before the odd couple headed back over to the south for some more quality time. Could this lead to further diplomacy between the U.S. and North Korea? In the meantime...watch out for those UFOs.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/421/484/421484534CBCD1DB76777FA08A63932F.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>105</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>South Korea scrambles jets</Tag>
          <Tag>South Korea unidentified object</Tag>
          <Tag>unidentified object DMZ</Tag>
          <Tag>Trump Kim</Tag>
          <Tag>Trump in NK</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 10:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Frozen body falls from
airplane in London</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/frozen-body-falls-from%0Aairplane-in-london-3854776</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/04/3854776/3854776_D1116C97D50041B5BCED4072F96FD5A0_190704_3854776_Frozen_body_falls_from_airplane_in_London_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[LONDON  The frozen body of a man was found in a garden in Clapham, south London on Sunday, June 30.The man had concealed himself inside the aircraft while the plane was at Nairobi airport, The Guardian reports.Authorities believe the man was a stowaway in the landing gear compartment of the plane. The plane was headed from Nairobi Airport to London's Heathrow Airport.According to the Guardian, the frozen body of the man had fallen from the landing gear compartment while the aircraft was still in the air.The authorities were called at 3:39 p.m. In a statement the Metropolitan Police said a post-mortem examination will be carried out. The police are still trying to determine the man's identity.The death is not being treated as suspicious, CNN reports.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/448/27F/44827FD737F8487DDC07E6544E02EA3E.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>69</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>stowaway</Tag>
          <Tag>London</Tag>
          <Tag>UK</Tag>
          <Tag>London garden</Tag>
          <Tag>heathrow airport</Tag>
          <Tag>stowaway falling from plane</Tag>
          <Tag>plane ride</Tag>
          <Tag>airport</Tag>
          <Tag>airport security</Tag>
          <Tag>stowaway body found</Tag>
          <Tag>body fell from plane</Tag>
          <Tag>body fell from plane london</Tag>
          <Tag>body fell from plane clapham</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 08:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>'Alien' Oumuamua likely to be of natural origin, says scientists</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-alien-oumuamua-likely-to-be-of-natural-origin-says-scientists-3854764</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/04/3854764/3854764_4763332D525A427AB1E801928C6C2818_190704_3854764__Alien__Oumuamua_likely_to_be_of_natural_origin__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[COLLEGE PARK, MARYLAND  According to the Guardian, Oumuamua is a reddish interstellar object that was first seen using the Pan-STARRS telescope at Haleakala Observatory, Hawaii in October 2017, as it passed by Earth at 156,428 kilometers per hour.Its unique shape and unusual level of acceleration have made it an object of mass speculation among the astronomy community.Oumuamua, whose name comes from a Hawaiian word meaning 'scout' or 'messenger sent from the distant past to reach out to us', is 400 meters long and roughly 40 meters wide.Scientists are still debating whether or not the object has extraterrestrial creations, but current research suggests that it has natural origins.According to the Independent, Matthew Knight, an associate research scientist at the University of Maryland Department of Astronomy, has considered the possibility that the object was thrown out of a giant gas plant that was orbiting another star.Sean Raymond, the co-author of 'The Natural History of Oumuamua', a new paper published to Nature Astronomy, said in his blog that even a cigar shape could have a natural explanation. Oumuamua could be a fragment of a much larger object shredded before it was ousted, a process that elongated it.Raymond explained in his blog how the orbit of Oumuamua isn't even special.'The odds of running into a Japanese person in Paris are pretty low. They are in a small minority. But they are no longer a small minority if you are at the airport, by the gate for a flight to Tokyo. It all depends on the context. In the right context, Oumuamua's orbit is nothing special. No need for aliens.'However, according to Raymond, there is no universally accepted answer as to what the mysterious object is and despite there being theories, he says, none of them are 'mic-drop compelling'. The scientists who suggested that the object could be an alien spacecraft also argued that the dearth of similar natural objects in space suggests that Oumuamua should never have been found, and may, therefore, have been intentionally aimed at Earth.Here's to hoping these scientists are wrong, and an intelligent civilization did indeed just take a sneaky-peek at life on earth.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FB7/140/FB7140FB9E0C1F9436D6108921D783F2.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>146</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>explainer</Tag>
          <Tag>Oumuamua</Tag>
          <Tag>Harvard</Tag>
          <Tag>alien spacecraft</Tag>
          <Tag>oumuamua trajectory</Tag>
          <Tag>solar system</Tag>
          <Tag>interstellar object</Tag>
          <Tag>oumuamua interstellar object</Tag>
          <Tag>Space</Tag>
          <Tag>Sean Raymond</Tag>
          <Tag>Matthew Knight</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 07:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>China separates Uyghur kids from their parents in Xinjiang</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-separates-uyghur-kids-from-their-parents-in-xinjiang-3855616</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/06/3855616/3855616_B6B0C4F83E2B4F82B06A0E6BF8B67FF1_190706_3855616_China_separates_Uyghur_kids_from_their_parents_i_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA  A new report has found that Muslim children in China's Xinjiang region are being deliberately separated from their families, faith, and culture.According to a report in the Journal of Political Risk, Uyghur children in Xinjiang whose parents have both been detained in reeducation camps are being placed in state care.The BBC reports that the children are being kept in local schools, which provide them with accommodation, food, and clothes.Report author Adrian Zenz found that the number of Uyghur children enrolled in Xinjiang schools went up by more than half a million in just one year, and now has the highest preschool enrollment level in the whole country.Chinese authorities have been undergoing a massive school expansion in the region, spending over $1.2 billion on building and upgrading kindergartens in southern Xinjiang alone.According to Zenz, the construction includes the addition of large amounts of dormitory space.Research shows that many of the schools are equipped with full surveillance systems, perimeter alarms, and electric fences as part of "hard isolation closed management measures."The use of Uyghur and other local languages are being eliminated from the schools, which enforce full Chinese language teaching. The children are also being cut off from religious and cultural beliefs as a result of being in the schools.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ED5/487/ED5487AA3751C5608928B4CA41E9E397.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>93</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>parent child separation</Tag>
          <Tag>xinjiang</Tag>
          <Tag>uyghurs</Tag>
          <Tag>uighurs</Tag>
          <Tag>xinjiang reeducation</Tag>
          <Tag>uyghur reeducation</Tag>
          <Tag>china reeducation camps</Tag>
          <Tag>xinjiang schools</Tag>
          <Tag>china police state</Tag>
          <Tag>china surveillance</Tag>
          <Tag>xinjiang boarding schools</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 16:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>U.S. Army to deploy pocket-sized drones to Afghanistan</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-army-to-deploy-pocket-sized-drones-to-afghanistan-3855485</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/05/3855485/3855485_5CE87179786847929BF43805B7E575EC_190705_3855485_U_S__Army_to_deploy_pocket_sized_drones_to_Afgha_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[KABUL  The Black Hornet nano-unmanned aerial system will be deployed to troops in the 82nd Airborne Division in Afghanistan this month on a trial basis, Stars and Stripes reports.The unmanned aerial drone is 6.6 inches in length and weigh less than 33 grams, Army Technology reports.The device features two electro-optic cameras and a fused thermal LED light night imager.According to Army Technology, this allows the aerial vehicle to transmit HD videos using night vision to allow soldiers to survey their surroundings while in combat.The drone can be launched in 30 to 120 seconds with a flight endurance of up to 25 minutes. The device is capable of flying at speeds of up to 24.49 kilometers per hour with a range of 2 kilometers.The U.S. Department of Defense plans to extend the use of the hand-held drones to most of its ground force if the trial proves successful, according to Army Technology.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CC4/74D/CC474D67551BFB8569532699F5067AEE.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>69</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>military drone</Tag>
          <Tag>us military</Tag>
          <Tag>afghanistan</Tag>
          <Tag>pocket-sized drone</Tag>
          <Tag>mini drone afghanistan</Tag>
          <Tag>Black Hornet Personal Reconnaissance System</Tag>
          <Tag>hand-held military drone</Tag>
          <Tag>military technology</Tag>
          <Tag>us afghanistan drone</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 11:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Denver to kill wild geese, donate meat to the needy</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/denver-to-kill-wild-geese-donate-meat-to-the-needy-3855407</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/05/3855407/3855407_C6AF2537E20D4D6883F0ECA47455D888_190705_3855407_Denver_to_kill_wild_geese__donate_meat_to_the_ne_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[DENVER  Wild geese are getting to be too much of a pain the butt for Denver Parks and Rec, so they're teaming up with the Department of Agriculture to round 'em up and turn them into chow.According to the Denver Channel, the city has about 5,000 full-time geese residents, which means doodoo everywhere.It's not only annoying, but also a health hazard, with geese poop FOWL-ing up the waterways and aggravating algae blooms and E. coli.Attempts to control the goose population over the years have all failed miserably. The city has tried scare tactics and hazing methods, but not even a Goosinator could chase 'em away.This latest goose management plan is pretty simple: round up the feathered fiends and just straight up kill 'em- humanely, of course.Wild Canada geese are protected under the U.S. Migratory Bird Act, but the government has ok-ed the culling of as may as 2,200 birds.Once the geese are "processed", their meat will be donated to needy families, so it's a win-win situation.Goose meat is perfectly safe for human consumption, and very tasty. Just ask Hong Kong.But not everyone is onboard with the new plan, with some saying it seems "kind of intense." Guess that means no roast goose for you.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9AE/437/9AE4374E927B2702E3554314062368F2.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>81</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Canada geese</Tag>
          <Tag>geese culling</Tag>
          <Tag>Denver geese</Tag>
          <Tag>roast goose</Tag>
          <Tag>geese for the needy</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 10:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Street Fighter ads to recruit
cyber police in Japan</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/street-fighter-ads-to-recruit%0Acyber-police-in-japan-3855213</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/05/3855213/3855213_F46BF5B03D3146EE947884C0F1D4915E_190705_3855213_Street_Fighter_ads_to_recruit_cyber_police_in_Ja_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[OSAKA / JAPAN  In a surprising move, police in Japan will be using Street Fighter adverts to recruit cybercrime officers.Green Gaming Man reported that Capcom, the Japanese game developer and publisher has been working with police on 'crime prevention awareness campaigns' for some time, but it's the first time Street Fighter characters have been approved for recruitment.Capcom received the request from Osaka police to use characters from the game, which has sold 42 million units as of March 2019 because of its palpable influence.According to Capcom's own site, 3,000 flyers and 1,000 posters of Capcom's Street Fighter will be distributed in Osaka prefecture police stations, police boxes, and train stations.The move comes at a time when cybercrime has seen a noticeable rise in recent years. According to Statista, in 2018, Japan fell victim to 58,477 cases of online illegal businesses.Camcom said on its site the game was selected for the brand's powerful image, popularity among a wide range of age groups, and the affinity that esports has with cyberspace. The characters will be featured in hiring campaigns with the aim of raising the number of officers specializing in cybercrime.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9C5/B16/9C5B16C961FE394024C6104D07EE49AF.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>86</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>CAPCOM</Tag>
          <Tag>Street Fighter</Tag>
          <Tag>Japan</Tag>
          <Tag>Osaka</Tag>
          <Tag>Japan to use Street Fighter as part of recruitment campaign</Tag>
          <Tag>hackers</Tag>
          <Tag>cybercrime</Tag>
          <Tag>Cyber police</Tag>
          <Tag>online crime</Tag>
          <Tag>online</Tag>
          <Tag>egaming</Tag>
          <Tag>games</Tag>
          <Tag>cyber world</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 05:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Superdelegates could override voters' choice for DNC nominee</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/superdelegates-could-override-voters-choice-for-dnc-nominee-3855171</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/05/3855171/3855171_79BE95622B9A43F6A5DAC2422978FC13_190705_3855171_Superdelegates_could_override_voters__choice_for_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  The 2020 Democratic Primaries could end up a god-awful mess, with the possibility of a brokered convention, and superdelegates hijacking the nomination process. Here's what you need to know.According to The Intercept, the Democratic Party currently has more than 25 presidential candidates. With four to five garnering significant support in the polls, there may not be a clear frontrunner by next July's Democratic National Convention in Milwaukee."In order to get the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination, candidates need to win a 51% majority, or at least 2,026 of the 4,051 delegates during the first ballot  the initial vote of the convention.Otherwise, the nomination goes to a brokered convention, where delegates vote until a majority is achieved, and a nominee secured.Also participating in these subsequent ballots are superdelegates, a group of elected officials, party leaders, and other party insiders that are unpledged. This means they are free to support any candidate in the party primary. For the 2020 Democratic National Convention, there will be 764 superdelegates.In 2016, Bernie Sanders supporters accused the party of tipping the scales in favor of Hillary Clinton, who received 571 superdelegates, compared to only 45 for Sanders.The Democratic Party has since changed the rules, allowing superdelegates to vote only in the case of a brokered convention.Many are worried that if a brokered convention were to occur, powerful party insiders and superdelegates could override the voters' choice and in effect decide who becomes the next Democratic presidential nominee.It's a very real and pretty scary possibility, so I guess we can all agree with California Democratic Rep Ro Khanna when she says: "I wish we had just eliminated the superdelegates."]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/312/14C/31214C5FE7442AF9FF4C345AF7C1EE6D.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>158</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>superdelegates</Tag>
          <Tag>presidential election 2020</Tag>
          <Tag>us election 2020</Tag>
          <Tag>democratic primary</Tag>
          <Tag>democratic primaries</Tag>
          <Tag>brokered convention</Tag>
          <Tag>DNC</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 04:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Using bra clasps to treat injured turtles</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/using-bra-clasps-to-treat-injured-turtles-3855119</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/05/3855119/3855119_6D8115F8547D421C9E9A8D4110354E5D_190705_3855119_Using_bra_clasps_to_treat_injured_turtles_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[INDEPENDENCE, IOWA  A wildlife rehabilitation center in Iowa has come up with the idea of using old bras to treat injured turtles.Trace Belle, founder and director of an animal rehab center in Independence, Iowa, told local KWWL news that she came up with the idea to use old bra closures with epoxy small zip ties to save turtles with injuries to their shells.In a Facebook post, her non-profit, Wildlife and Animal Rehabilitation and Sanctuary, called on women to donate old bra clasps that can be used to repair turtle shells.The bra clasps are glued to opposite sides of the turtle shells, while the zip ties are used to fasten the crack in the shell, according to a Facebook post by the organization.This allows the turtle's cracked shell to heal.Another non-profit organization, Carolina Waterfowl Rescue, is using a similar method but with a wire instead of zip ties to fix cracked turtle shells, WBTV reports.The bra clasps are removed once the turtle shells have healed, and the turtles are then released into the wild.Wildlife and Animal Rehabilitation and Sanctuary's Facebook post since gone viral, with thousands sharing the post and, the non-profit says, donating to the cause.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/979/F99/979F99FE03913512E5A8C9F22219A72B.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>89</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>animals</Tag>
          <Tag>animal rehab center</Tag>
          <Tag>turtles</Tag>
          <Tag>bra clasps</Tag>
          <Tag>turtles bra clasps</Tag>
          <Tag>broken turtle shells</Tag>
          <Tag>cracked turtle shells</Tag>
          <Tag>saving turtles</Tag>
          <Tag>old bras</Tag>
          <Tag>helping turtles</Tag>
          <Tag>helping turtles heal</Tag>
          <Tag>Animal rehab center turtles</Tag>
          <Tag>repairing turtle shells</Tag>
          <Tag>using old bras to fix turtle shells</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 02:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Carnegie Mellon &amp; Astrobotic to build MoonRanger rovers for NASA</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/carnegie-mellon--astrobotic-to-build-moonranger-rovers-for-nasa-3856785</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/08/3856785/3856785_B581AB6E0BC74BB1A0B076CE8DB21231_190708_3856785_Carnegie_Mellon___Astrobotic_to_build_MoonRanger_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Carnegie Mellon University and Astrobotic, a space robotics company, have been awarded a $5.6 million contract by NASA to build a small, speedy lunar rover called MoonRanger.According to Astrobotic, the autonomous rover will weigh only 13 kilograms and could land on the moon by 2021 or 2022.MoonRanger will be the size of a suitcase. It will be taken to the moon via Astrobotics' lunar lander Peregrine. The robot will operate autonomously on weeklong missions within 1 kilometer of its lander while on the moon, according to press releases by NASA and Carnegie Mellon.It could search the moon's polar regions for ice or lunar pits and produce detailed 3D maps of the moon's terrain.Data gathered by MoonRanger will be relayed back to our planet via a radio once the rover returns to its lander. This is because the rover is too small and is unable to carry a radio powerful enough to communicate with earth.MoonRanger is one of 12 proposals selected by NASA as part of its Lunar Surface and Instrumentation and Technology Payload program. It is scheduled to head to the moon via NASA's Commercial Lunar Payload Services project.NASA says these projects would allow the U.S. space agency to get a better understanding of the moon and explore more of its surface as NASA prepares for its Artemis moon mission in 2024.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/87B/6AF/87B6AF78B091EF771F0E5D414F72DFCE.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>91</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>NASA</Tag>
          <Tag>moon mission</Tag>
          <Tag>lunar mission</Tag>
          <Tag>space</Tag>
          <Tag>astronauts</Tag>
          <Tag>moon</Tag>
          <Tag>space mission</Tag>
          <Tag>moon mission</Tag>
          <Tag>mission to the moon</Tag>
          <Tag>NASA lunar mission</Tag>
          <Tag>Astrobotic</Tag>
          <Tag>autonomous moon rover</Tag>
          <Tag>lunar rover</Tag>
          <Tag>nasa lunar rover</Tag>
          <Tag>MoonRanger lunar rover</Tag>
          <Tag>robotic lunar rover</Tag>
          <Tag>NASA Lunar Surface and Instrumentation and Technology Payload program</Tag>
          <Tag>Moonranger rover</Tag>
          <Tag>Moon Ranger Carnegie Mellon University</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>China is installing spyware on tourists' phones</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-is-installing-spyware-on-tourists-phones-3856623</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/08/3856623/3856623_EC990599886843188456D1A2761CDC35_190708_3856623_China_is_installing_spyware_on_tourists__phones_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA   An investigative report by the New York Times, the Guardian, Motherboard, Sddeutsche Zeitung and German public broadcaster NDR has uncovered a systematic program to harvest data from the phones of tourists entering Xinjiang.Tourists entering Xinjiang by land from Kyrgyzstan are forced to unlock their phones at border checkpoints and give their pin codes to border officials, according to a report in the Guardian. The phones are taken away by Chinese authorities to a separate room. iPhones are plugged into a reader that scans them while Android phones have a spyware app called "fengcai" installed on them.The malware downloads emails, text messages, phone contacts, calls logs and scans the device for more than 73,000 different items, including images and videos related to Islamic terrorism or the Quran. In most cases the Android app is uninstalled by authorities before the phone is returned to the tourist. However, some tourists have still found the app installed on their phones.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6BE/CAF/6BECAF9FC5AE150FEE5191298D027D2E.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>81</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>china surveillance</Tag>
          <Tag>China</Tag>
          <Tag>surveillance app</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese surveillance</Tag>
          <Tag>uyghur</Tag>
          <Tag>uighur</Tag>
          <Tag>xinjiang</Tag>
          <Tag>uyghur crackdown</Tag>
          <Tag>china surveillance</Tag>
          <Tag>minorities</Tag>
          <Tag>Muslim minorities</Tag>
          <Tag>ethnic minorities</Tag>
          <Tag>China</Tag>
          <Tag>China human rights</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese surveillance</Tag>
          <Tag>apps</Tag>
          <Tag>China Muslims</Tag>
          <Tag>China Uighur</Tag>
          <Tag>Muslim Uighurs</Tag>
          <Tag>china surveillance xinjiang</Tag>
          <Tag>china mass surveillance</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 08:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Woman who licks ice cream
faces up to 20 years in prison</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-who-licks-ice-cream%0Afaces-up-to-20-years-in-prison-3856561</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/08/3856561/3856561_C2E3ACF8C1A84575AF11DE6E00BDDC03_190708_3856561_Woman_who_licks_ice_cream_faces_up_to_20_years_i_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[TEXAS, LUFKIN    In what seems to be a trend of filming yourself doing derpy, trashy things in public that, let's be honest, lowers the expectations of society and further reinstates how underwhelming social media can be  a woman licked a tub of ice cream inside a Lufkin Walmart, and then put it back.NBC News reported on the incident saying that after licking the ice cream and putting it back, she now faces up to 20 years behind bars.According to the Texas state penal code, tampering with consumer products is a second-degree felony that carries a punishment of a two to 20 years prison sentence and up to $10,000 in fines.The attention-seeking video which was posted on June 28th went viral and has received more than 11 million views. According to Lufkin Police's Facebook, social media commentators earlier in the week stated that the woman was from San Antonio. Detectives believe that they have identified the woman in question-based on the surveillance footage. They're also wanting to find the man who filmed the attention-craving act where he can be heard offering some breathless voyeuristic commentary, "Lick it, lick it. Oh, you foul. Put it back, put it back." Blue Bell, who produced the now-infected ice cream, put out a statement confirming the tub in question was never sold. According to the company, "based on security footage, the location, and the inspection of the carton, we believe we may have recovered the half-gallon that was tampered with. Out of an abundance of caution, we have also removed all Tin Roof half gallons from that location."]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8D3/B9C/8D3B9CC91E3FE834D00AA01A1E61845A.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>138</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream</Tag>
          <Tag>woman faces 20 years in prison for licking ice cream and putting it back</Tag>
          <Tag>social media</Tag>
          <Tag>texas</Tag>
          <Tag>crime</Tag>
          <Tag>Blue Bell</Tag>
          <Tag>tin roof ice cream</Tag>
          <Tag>viral videos</Tag>
          <Tag>twitter</Tag>
          <Tag>lick it</Tag>
          <Tag>selfies</Tag>
          <Tag>woman licks ice cream</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 06:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>An explainer on African swine fever</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/an-explainer-on-african-swine-fever-3856540</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/08/3856540/3856540_B4096B6128A440EBADCC39FBE884FA6F_190708_3856540_An_explainer_on_African_swine_fever_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BEIJING  African swine fever continues to affect pigs in China and other Asian nations even as authorities try to halt the spread of the disease.African swine fever is typically spread through bites by infectious ticks, contact through infected animals, contact with objects containing the virus, or by ingesting the meat of infected animals, according to the European Food Safety Authority.The disease is spread by the DNA virus of the Asfarviridae family, according to the World Organization for Animal Health.African swine fever affects only porcine species. Warthogs are naturally resistant to the virus but can expose wild boars to infection.Domestic pigs can contract the disease through exposure to infected wild boars, to which the disease is endemic.Symptoms include high fever, redness on the ears, abdomen, legs as well as diarrhea, as stated by the World Organisation for Animal Health.There currently is no approved vaccine to prevent the spread of the disease among pigs.Asian countries such as Mongolia, China, North Korea, Laos and Cambodia have all been hit by the virus.Vietnam has been hit particularly hard, with 10 percent of its herd  some 2.8 million animals  having been culled.The disease is fatal for pigs. It, however, isn't transmissible to humans.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/74C/A80/74CA80CF015EEB94539E5DD400B67AEE.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>82</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>African swine fever</Tag>
          <Tag>pork</Tag>
          <Tag>pigs</Tag>
          <Tag>pork products</Tag>
          <Tag>african swine fever china</Tag>
          <Tag>african swine flu china</Tag>
          <Tag>african swine fever outbreak in china</Tag>
          <Tag>african swine fever 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>african swine fever symptoms</Tag>
          <Tag>what is african swine fever</Tag>
          <Tag>how african swine fever spreads</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 06:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>British Marines seize Iranian oil tanker allegedly on its way to Syria</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/british-marines-seize-iranian-oil-tanker-allegedly-on-its-way-to-syria-3856506</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/08/3856506/3856506_325AB769FBBC4A3A8019B6A4847C3F15_190708_3856506_British_Marines_seize_Iranian_oil_tanker_alleged_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[PORT OF GIBRALTAR  British Royal Marines seized a Iranian tanker on its way to Syria through Gibraltar on Thursday for violating EU sanctions, Reuters reports.Gibraltar authorities said they had reason to believe the Grace 1 tanker was carrying crude oil to the Baniyas refinery in Syria.According to the Guardian, Britain said troops seized the ship early morning on July 4 to enforce EU sanctions against Syria. Royal Marines from 42 Commando landed on the ship by descending from a Wildcat helicopter. Images from the UK's Ministry of Defence show other British troops reaching the vessel via a speedboat.Gibraltar authorities said in a tweet the vessel departed Iran in mid-April for what they believed to be Syria by sailing around Africa. It was seized when it entered British territorial waters.Iranian state news agency IRNA cited an official from the Foreign Ministry as saying that the tanker was sailing in international waters and was seized illegally by the United Kingdom.Tehran has since summoned the UK's ambassador to Iran over what it is referring to as the "illegal seizure" of its oil tanker.The Syrian government has yet to respond to the incident.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/641/A7C/641A7C078B6A1AB52315D2FF90F9A4E9.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>63</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>british marines</Tag>
          <Tag>iran</Tag>
          <Tag>syria</Tag>
          <Tag>iranian oil tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>gibraltar</Tag>
          <Tag>british royal marines</Tag>
          <Tag>port of gibraltar</Tag>
          <Tag>tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>oil tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>crude oil</Tag>
          <Tag>Grace 1 super tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>Baniyas Refinery</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 04:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Fire breaks out on Russian nuclear submarine</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/fire-breaks-out-on-russian-nuclear-submarine-3857157</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/09/3857157/3857157_7073937972834E7C9CA4D1CFCD28F1A2_190709_3857157_Fire_breaks_out_on_Russian_nuclear_submarine_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Russia's Ministry of Defense says 14 sailors were killed when a nuclear-powered submarine caught fire while it was underwater last week.The vessel was a AS-12 Losharik submarine, Russian media outlet RBC reports, citing anonymous sources. The AS-12 can reach depths of up to 6,000 meters. Its nuclear reactor is isolated and operates autonomously.The vessel is carried beneath the hull of the nuclear-powered submarine Orenburg to avoid detection, according to Russian newspaper Novaya Gazeta. Russian News Agency TASS cited a statement by the Russian Ministry of Defense as saying that the submarine was in Russian territorial waters and was studying the seafloor. The statement added that the sailors died as a result of inhaling combustion products on the vessel.The exact cause of the fire is unknown.Russia's President Vladimir Putin cancelled a planned visit and extended condolences to the family members of the victims, RBC reports. According to TASS, President Putin ordered a thorough investigation to determine the cause of the submarine fire.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CD4/C7F/CD4C7F65F679C899C1F12A2015C5F9C5.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>76</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>russia</Tag>
          <Tag>russian submarine</Tag>
          <Tag>undersea cables</Tag>
          <Tag>russia surveying undersea cables</Tag>
          <Tag>underwater cables</Tag>
          <Tag>submarine</Tag>
          <Tag>AS-12</Tag>
          <Tag>nuclear-powered submarine</Tag>
          <Tag>russia cutting undersea cables</Tag>
          <Tag>russian military submarine</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 08:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Thieving flower tourists force park to shut down for the year</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/thieving-flower-tourists-force-park-to-shut-down-for-the-year-3857007</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/09/3857007/3857007_C2B0B5CDEF464A9A92B854FF60250B3B_190709_3857007_Thieving_flower_tourists_force_park_to_shut_down_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[LU COUNTY / CHINA  A park in southwest China has closed for the rest of 2019 after tourists plucked its famed lotus flowers, reports the South China Morning Post.The sprawling fields of flowers at Longqiao Cultural and Ecological Park cover around 250,000 square metres or 62 acres  an area about the size of New York's Grand Central Terminal. Since late March, the park has been closed and fenced off for construction and was due to reopen soon.        But since the start of summer suspected visiting tourists are breaking into the park and ripping the flowers from their roots.Pictures from Red Star News show individuals trudging into the muddy waters and coming out stocking bunches of the long-stemmed, and now pillaged flowers. A member of staff surnamed Zhou told Red Star News, "We cannot control the tourists - We've put notes on the park gate and near the flower field and we have security personnel on patrol as well."Zhou continued, saying that the construction work in the park was near complete but that there was little point in reopening because there were virtually no flowers left to see.It is estimated that between 200 to 300 people may still be breaking into the park on a daily basis. Zhou said, "We've already repaired the fencing five times this year."The park's management said it has stepped up its number of security personnel in response to the threat.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/23F/F86/23FF867C925DD99BD21EEA9A9A21F1DC.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>120</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>China</Tag>
          <Tag>Chinese tourists</Tag>
          <Tag>Chinese tourists destroy park by picking lotus flowers</Tag>
          <Tag>flowers</Tag>
          <Tag>lotus flowers</Tag>
          <Tag>park forced to shut after Chinese tourists destroy it by picking all the flowers</Tag>
          <Tag>Sichuan province's Lu county</Tag>
          <Tag>Longqiao Cultural and Ecological Park</Tag>
          <Tag>Chinese park shut down after thieving tourists wreck its main attraction</Tag>
          <Tag>An ecological park in southwest China has been forced to close after tourists pick most its famed lotus flowers</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>East Asians were stretching their skulls 12,000 years ago</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/east-asians-were-stretching-their-skulls-12-000-years-ago-3856997</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/09/3856997/3856997_CABE3872D8704E6591A2150FE50C5AE6_190709_3856997_East_Asians_were_stretching_their_skulls_12_000__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[JILIN, CHINA  Elongated xenomorph-shaped skulls have been discovered in an ancient tomb in China.According to research published in the American Journal of Physical Anthropology, scientists unearthed 25 skeletons at the Houtaomuga site in northeastern China.11 of the skulls had been intentionally modified: the braincases were elongated, and flattened bones were found at the front and back of the head.The 11 modified skulls date back to between 12,000 to 5,000 years ago. They belonged to five adults  four men and one woman  and six children.The practice of artificial cranial deformation is typically done in infancy, when the baby's skull is still soft and malleable. The head can either be compressed using hands, wrapped tightly with cloth, or shaped using boards. According to Science alert, it has no negative impact on cognitive function.Researchers say the practice of skull reshaping was a marker of social status, and may have been reserved for high-status individuals.In one tomb, a three-year-old with an elongated skull was found buried with large amounts of pottery and artifacts, suggesting the child was from a rich family.Intentionally reshaped skulls have previously been found in other parts of the world, in southeastern Australia and western Asia.To know more about the ancient practice, scientists say more research will need to be conducted to compare Houtaomuga with other Neolithic sites around the world.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F13/ED6/F13ED6C29FB314D54A3E04E3AF23373F.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>84</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>skull modification</Tag>
          <Tag>skull reshaping</Tag>
          <Tag>skull stretching</Tag>
          <Tag>xenomorph</Tag>
          <Tag>xenomorph skull</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient humans</Tag>
          <Tag>houtaomuga</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient practices</Tag>
          <Tag>weird ancient practices</Tag>
          <Tag>bizarre ritual</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient ritual</Tag>
          <Tag>coneheads</Tag>
          <Tag>real coneheads</Tag>
          <Tag>real xenomorphs</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Louisiana man arrested in copycat Blue Bell ice cream licking video</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/louisiana-man-arrested-in-copycat-blue-bell-ice-cream-licking-video-3857932</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/11/3857932/3857932_13D78E0CF5374AADA2430A119A42B94B_190711_3857932_Louisiana_man_arrested_in_copycat_Blue_Bell_ice__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#icecreamlicker #BlueBell #LouisianaASSUMPTION PARISH, LOUISIANA  For one Louisiana copycat attempting the depravity that is the gross ice cream challenge, it was 15 minutes of fame and straight on til prison. According to CNN, Lenise Lloyd Martin III had been inspired by the viral video of the ice cream-licking teen from Texas, and wanted internet infamy for himself too.Clearly missing the part about how it landed the teenager in a whole sludge of trouble, Martin high-tailed it to his local supermarket and pulled the exact same stunt. He got a friend to record him swiping a Blue Bell ice cream carton from the freezer, licking it, poking it with his fingers, and then licking it again. Ew.The 36-year-old, who really should've known better, proudly put the video up on Facebook, where it got hundreds of thousands of views, reports the New York Times.It caught the attention of a concerned customer, who then alerted the supermarket's manager. Martin later went back to the store with a receipt, claiming he'd bought the licked carton. But the manager said they couldn't be sure which one he'd contaminated, and so had to clear everything out and notify Blue Bell.The copycat ice cream licker was nabbed by the cops and thrown in jail for criminal mischief for tampering with a product, and unlawful posting of criminal activity for notoriety and publicity.In the end, dude kind of got what he wanted. Smile for the camera Lenise  ya famous!]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/351/CF5/351CF55CF3B420AFFE1DEF54B071404C.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>90</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>ice cream licker blue bell</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker copycat</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker</Tag>
          <Tag>copycat ice cream licker</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licking</Tag>
          <Tag>viral video</Tag>
          <Tag>blue bell licking</Tag>
          <Tag>blue bell ice cream</Tag>
          <Tag>louisiana blue bell licker</Tag>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Lenise Lloyd Martin III</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker identified</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker found</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker news</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker jailed</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker trend</Tag>
          <Tag>ice cream licker charged</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 16:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Taiwan is buying $2 billion worth
of American-made armor</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-is-buying-2-billion-worth%0Aof-american-made-armor-3857684</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/10/3857684/3857684_6E6D48EF470A463F93331DF99558386C_190710_3857684_Taiwan_is_buying__2_billion_worth_of_American_ma_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[WASHINGTON    The U.S State Department has approved an arms sale worth of over $2 billion to Taiwan, according to a Defense Security Cooperation Agency news release.The package includes M1A2 Abram tanks and surface-to-air Stinger missiles. Reuters reports that Taiwan has been interested in updating its current U.S-built tank inventory. This includes M60 Patton tanks.According to Military.com, the M1A2 Abrams are equipped with a 120mm XM256 Smooth Bore Cannon and can travel at a maximum speed of 42 mph.  With a range of 265 miles, the tank can also carry four people.Global Security.org lists Stinger missiles or the FIM-92 Stinger as a man-portable, shoulder-launched air-defense system.  It is a "fire-and-forget" weapon, employing a passive infrared seeker which locks onto, or seeks, the heat from an aircraft engine.34 ScanEagle drones are being sold by the Pentagon to Malaysia, Indonesia, the Philippines, and Vietnam in a deal worth $47 million.According to Reuters, these may limit Chinese activity in the region as the technology allows for more comprehensive intelligence-gathering.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7D5/18A/7D518A398623B4EDB5B72194E95FB0E4.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>117</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>Taiwan us military</Tag>
          <Tag>us taiwan military relations</Tag>
          <Tag>us taiwan army</Tag>
          <Tag>taiwan tanks</Tag>
          <Tag>china taiwan military</Tag>
          <Tag>taiwan relations act</Tag>
          <Tag>South China sea</Tag>
          <Tag>Pentagon</Tag>
          <Tag>US China trade war</Tag>
          <Tag>trade</Tag>
          <Tag>war</Tag>
          <Tag>M1A2 Abram tanks</Tag>
          <Tag>Stinger missiles</Tag>
          <Tag>Washington</Tag>
          <Tag>U.S</Tag>
          <Tag>Taiwan</Tag>
          <Tag>China</Tag>
          <Tag>Tanks</Tag>
          <Tag>deal</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 08:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Using waste plastic to build roads</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/using-waste-plastic-to-build-roads-3857504</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/10/3857504/3857504_F917053465F546F09025F62515E13686_190710_3857504_Using_waste_plastic_to_build_roads_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[ELGIN, SCOTLAND  Springfield Properties, a housing development company, and MacRebur, a company that uses plastic waste to surface roads, have teamed up to build a road out of plastic waste in Scotland, according to a report in the BBC.MacRebur has patented a process in which plastic waste is turned into granules and then mixed with a special "activator" that allows the granules to bind together.Asphalt producers can use the resulting product as a substitute for a portion of the bitumen in an asphalt mix.Springfield Properties says that for every tonne of bitumen, a form of petroleum, that is replaced, the carbon footprint of the road surfacing is reduced by a tonne of carbon dioxide.The company said in a news release that these "plastic" roads are up to 60 percent stronger than roads that are currently in use, which will reduce road maintenance costs.The company claims it is the first house builder in the UK to use waste plastic to build a road on a housing development. The company plans to surface more roads with plastic waste across Scotland.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/136/3CB/1363CBE94BF786A88F51BC978A74E2E1.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>67</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic</Tag>
          <Tag>recycling plastic</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic bottles</Tag>
          <Tag>turning plastic bottles into roads</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic roads</Tag>
          <Tag>scotland</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic waste</Tag>
          <Tag>scotland</Tag>
          <Tag>turning plastic waste into roads</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic roads uk</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic roads scotland</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic bottles recycling</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic bottles into roads</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic bottles recycled into roads</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 02:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Farting suspect gives himself away to police</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/farting-suspect-gives-himself-away-to-police-3858589</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858589/3858589_31068A5E65394649BA5960D5D1BF5601_190712_3858589_Farting_suspect_gives_himself_away_to_police_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[CLAY COUNTY, MISSOURI / U.S   A wanted man in Missouri got himself caught by the law by farting loudly.USA Today reported that the man, wanted for possession of a controlled substance, hid from police before farting so tremendously that he gave himself away.Clay County Sheriff's department took to Twitter to share the story with #ItHappenend.Jumping in on the fun, the official Twitter account of the City of Liberty said, "The Liberty Police Department was surprised to see this incident slip out, which stinks for the arrestee."And for those of holding your breath, don't worry, no one was injured in his capture.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/430/517/430517DC8E8974176FBE311770B43976.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>66</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>missouri man fart</Tag>
          <Tag>missouri man arrested</Tag>
          <Tag>Missouri man farted</Tag>
          <Tag>Missouri suspect fart</Tag>
          <Tag>loud fart gives away suspects hiding place</Tag>
          <Tag>suspect arrested for farting loudly</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 23:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Thousands of Android apps harvest data without permission</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/thousands-of-android-apps-harvest-data-without-permission-3858206</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/11/3858206/3858206_57A82047178D4F20906CA8F1A6E0882C_190711_3858206_Thousands_of_Android_apps_harvest_data_without_p_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA  A joint report from the International Computer Science Institute and AppCensus, a company that examines how much data an app is collecting from a user, has found that 1,325 Android apps are able to gather location data and unique device identifiers  such as the IMEI of a device  even if users haven't given the apps permission to do so.Their findings were presented at the Federal Trade Commissions' PrivacyCon at the end of last month.A total of 70 apps including Shutterfly, a photo-editing app, were found gathering geolocation data through images taken by users and sending the data to their own servers. The apps were able to bypass Android permissions and gather user data through Wi-Fi connection and by accessing the metadata stored in photos.Thirteen other Android apps, including Baidu's Hong Kong Disneyland park app, were found looking through hidden files stored in the SD card folder. The apps were able to access data they didn't have permission for because it was stored in the files.Researchers added that 153 additional apps, including Samsung's Health and Browser apps, also have this ability.The report noted that three smart remote control apps were harvesting location data by connecting to a user's Wi-Fi network and by accessing the router's MAC address.Google told CNet it will be addressing these issues in its software update,  Android Q.Serge Egelman, research director of Usable Security & Privacy at the Institute, said at the FTC conference that consumers have few tools they can use to control and make decisions about their privacy.He said, "If app developers can just circumvent the system, then asking consumers for permission is relatively meaningless."The study looked at more than 88,000 Android apps from the Google Play store.According to CNet, Egelman will be releasing details and a list of the 1,325 Android apps  in August, when he presents the study at the Usenix Security conference.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E7F/12F/E7F12F2B5AD5F33C515E3DEA5433E4FC.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>114</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>android phones</Tag>
          <Tag>permissions on android apps</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps privacy</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps privacy issues</Tag>
          <Tag>android permissions systems</Tag>
          <Tag>android's broken permission system</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps permissions explained</Tag>
          <Tag>international computer science institute</Tag>
          <Tag>app permissions</Tag>
          <Tag>Google play store</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Man Tire Spins Himself into 
a Fiery Mess and a Driving Ban</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-tire-spins-himself-into-%0Aa-fiery-mess-and-a-driving-ban-3858983</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858983/3858983_B25175EBAAC842ECB708613B5B359A37_190712_3858983_Man_Tire_Spins_Himself_into__a_Fiery_Mess_and_a__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND / AUSTRALIA   According to the Washington Post, a 29-year-old man from the town of Nerang, Australia was convicted after his vehicle exploded into a fiery blue mess during a gender reveal party on Australia's Gold Coast. In what was supposed to be a celebratory event of revealing the gender of one's child using colored tire smoke, the car caught fire during a dramatic burnout.The man stopped in the middle of the road and began spinning the car's wheels. Small puffs of color began wafting from the tires before rupturing into a plume of blue smoke. The car then caught fire  spectacularly. According to The Guardian, burnouts, caused by spinning the wheels of a stationary car to produce large plumes of tire smoke are a recent popular method of revealing the gender of one's baby.Sgt. Hilton Buckley of Queensland Police Service told 7 News Brisbane, "I know people like to do unique things for gender reveals these days, but use a bit of common sense." The incident took place last year and according to police, the driver was convicted on one count of dangerous operation of a motor vehicle. he was charged a $1,000 fine and banned from driving for six months.The video of the burnout was released Tuesday to local media outlets, who filed a request for the footage after the court case concluded last year.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DBB/BA9/DBBBA90E35FC3287D1D4834FA59F8732.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>105</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>gender reveal burnout</Tag>
          <Tag>gender reveal gone wrong</Tag>
          <Tag>gender reveal car catches on fire</Tag>
          <Tag>burnout</Tag>
          <Tag>Australian man's baby burn out reveal goes wrong</Tag>
          <Tag>gender reveal car fire</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 11:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>300,000 join event to storm Area 51 to 'see them aliens'</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/300-000-join-event-to-storm-area-51-to-see-them-aliens--3858953</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858953/3858953_1617234A1D3E440FA2D86F0870951B8C_190712_3858953_300_000_join_event_to_storm_Area_51_to__see_them_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#area51 #aliens #stormarea51AMARGOSA VALLEY, NEVADA  Bored users have crawled out of the social media woodwork pledging to storm the infamous Area 51, because why not.According to CNN, over 300,000 people have signed on to a September 20 Facebook prank event to raid Area 51 in Nevada and "see them aliens."The game plan, says leader Jackson Barnes, is to put Monster Energy-fueled 'Kyles'  on the front lines since they like punching holes in walls so much. They'll have rock throwers chuck pebbles at the enemy less to hurt and them and more to just annoy. And the piece the resistance: battalions of internet folk running Naruto-style and moving faster than any bullet. Those poor soldiers won't know what hit 'em.Come September 20, we'll finally know what extraterrestrial wonders or horrors the U.S. government is hiding in the mysterious military base.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/872/EE9/872EE96FCF1E0FD108028760CF7BFCBF.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>78</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>storm area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>aliens</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook group</Tag>
          <Tag>storm area 51 prank</Tag>
          <Tag>conspiracy theorists</Tag>
          <Tag>UFO</Tag>
          <Tag>aliens</Tag>
          <Tag>area 52 raid</Tag>
          <Tag>prank event</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 11:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>ByFusion is definitely NOT building plastic houses anymore</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/byfusion-is-definitely-not-building-plastic-houses-anymore-3858934</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858934/3858934_1EE39ADACE60487785DEB75C9668C95A_190712_3858934_ByFusion_is_definitely_NOT_building_plastic_hous_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BROOKLYN, NEW YORK  Back in 2016, we did an animation about a machine that turned waste plastic into bricks. It was a straightforward piece explaining how the stuff worked, so you know, free positive publicity.So imagine our surprise when just last weekend, the company behind the machine, ByFusion, sent an email demanding the 2016 video be taken down, even threatening legal action if we didn't comply.The shady email said the video had been rendered inaccurate since the company wasn't building houses for the poor no more. Hmm, wonder why that is? So what DOES the company do now? Apparently building retaining walls, landscaping, and other non-load bearing structures. Emphasis on non-load.According to a juicy Stuff article, there's bad blood between ByFusion and the actual inventor of their machine  a Kiwi named Peter Lewis.Lewis says he got kicked out of ByFusion and didn't get zilch. Turns out he didn't own the 26 percent of the company he thought he did.In a rebuttal to Lewis' claims on the article, ByFusion swore up and down that the inventor wasn't kicked out, and was duly compensated after opting out of a position.But documents Stuff got its hands on shows Lewis was actually ousted, and even got issued a trespass notice from the company factory in New Zealand.Lewis still gets the last laugh though. The 69-year-old claims the ByFusion machine has a fatal flaw. He didn't say what, but we can hazard a few guesses.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/845/27B/84527B9739FD00D1D61755CDBFB90ACB.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>91</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Satire</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>byfusion</Tag>
          <Tag>byfusion machine</Tag>
          <Tag>replast</Tag>
          <Tag>rebuttal</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic pollution</Tag>
          <Tag>legal threat</Tag>
          <Tag>clapback</Tag>
          <Tag>replast blocks</Tag>
          <Tag>plastic trash</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 10:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Drunken dudes use Uber to rescue injured baby bird in Utah</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/drunken-dudes-use-uber-to-rescue-injured-baby-bird-in-utah-3858788</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858788/3858788_1968760EF9EC4FF5988158EA39103E1B_190712_3858788_Drunken_dudes_use_Uber_to_rescue_injured_baby_bi_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[OGDEN, UTAH  Some dudes in Utah didn't let a few too many drinks stop them for helping an injured bird.According to the Salt Lake Tribune, Tim Crowley and his buds were hanging out at a neighbor's house when a wee visitor literally dropped in  it was a baby lesser goldfinch, and the poor thing was injured.The friends snapped a photo of the baby bird and sent it to the Wildlife Rehabilitation Center of Northern Utah, who told them to bring the little thing in. Problem was, they'd been day drinking and were in no condition to drive. Luckily, someone got the bright idea to call an Uber, and the men loaded up the bird in a box.The first driver they got canceled after learning of the bird box situation, but second time's the charm.Driver Chrissy Guyn told Fox 13 she turned down the A/C and cracked the window open to make the bird more comfortable in its leaf-padded box, then drove the chirper 25 minutes to the rescue center. The little guy survived and has since been named "Petey."According to the center, Petey is doing good and currently hanging with his new cage-mate and buddy. They hope he'll be ready to be released in about a month.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6AD/FD9/6ADFD946D7800C5C25EB55523F755462.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>89</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>uber bird rescue</Tag>
          <Tag>bird rescue</Tag>
          <Tag>utah bird rescue</Tag>
          <Tag>injured baby bird</Tag>
          <Tag>baby bird rescue</Tag>
          <Tag>man saves baby bird</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 07:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ancient Egyptian curls perfectly preserved after 3,000 years</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ancient-egyptian-curls-perfectly-preserved-after-3-000-years-3858740</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858740/3858740_679A0EAE6BD34203A4274DA75E7CEE68_190712_3858740_Ancient_Egyptian_curls_perfectly_preserved_after_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Russian scientists have determined the components of a substance that ancient Egyptians used to perfectly preserve hair for millennia. According to RT, natural mummification in ancient Egypt involved placing the bodies of the deceased in shallow pits in the fetal position, where they gradually dried in the sand.At the same time, artificial mummification, which involved embalming the bodies, became available to the elites.Scientists at the Kurchatov Institute Research Center found embalmed hair in good condition on three mummies dating back to the first millenium BC, and analyzed them to determine how they had been preserved for 3,000 years.Using mass spectrometry, researchers identified beef fat, castor oil, beeswax, pine gum, and pistachio oil as components of a substance applied on the hair of deceased Egyptians. This hair embalming agent is believed to be different than that applied to the body.The discovery was part of large-scale research conducted on a collection of mummies at the Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts in Moscow.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F32/BFE/F32BFE785F6700526E8C305AB36F05F1.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>78</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient egyptian hair</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient egyptian hair wax</Tag>
          <Tag>egyptian mummy hair</Tag>
          <Tag>egyptian mummy</Tag>
          <Tag>mummy hair</Tag>
          <Tag>egyptian hair secrets</Tag>
          <Tag>egyptian curls</Tag>
          <Tag>egyptian mummy curls</Tag>
          <Tag>Egyptian hair embalming</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient Egyptian hair serum</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 06:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Canadian man survives plunge into Niagara Falls</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/canadian-man-survives-plunge-into-niagara-falls-3858703</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858703/3858703_893120F967A649F292DD49C2148EBCB0_190712_3858703_Canadian_man_survives_plunge_into_Niagara_Falls_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[NIAGARA FALLS, CANADA  A man was swept over Niagara Falls and miraculously survived a fall down into the waters below, on Tuesday, July 9.Niagara Falls Park Police tweeted they were called to rescue the man at the waterfall at 4:00 a.m.They rushed to the scene and watched the man, identified as Canadian, as he climbed over the retaining wall at the Horseshoe Falls and was swept away by the water. Officials then searched the lower river basin and found the guy beneath the Journey Behind the Falls observation platform, the Buffalo News reports.The police said the man was "sitting on rocks" at the edge of the water. He was rescued with non-life threatening injuries and was taken to the hospital for further assessment.Jim Diodati, mayor of Niagara Falls, Ontario told the Buffalo News he believes record high water levels may have saved the man's life."When Lake Erie is higher and flowing more robustly to Lake Ontario, there is a better chance of missing the massive boulders under the Horseshoe Falls," Diodati told the newspaper.Authorities have yet to reveal the identity of the man due to privacy laws.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C67/058/C670580FEF6DDA036B9184E7300D123C.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>72</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>swept over niagara falls</Tag>
          <Tag>Niagara Falls fall</Tag>
          <Tag>waterfall fall down</Tag>
          <Tag>fall off waterfall</Tag>
          <Tag>fall off niagara falls</Tag>
          <Tag>niagara falls going over</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls in niagara falls</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls down waterfall</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls down niagara falls</Tag>
          <Tag>man goes down niagara falls</Tag>
          <Tag>swept over waterfall</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls from niagara</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 05:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Wildlife officials may soon dump rat poison on the Farallon Islands</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wildlife-officials-may-soon-dump-rat-poison-on-the-farallon-islands-3858617</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/12/3858617/3858617_25397B24D7CD4D2BA4651B0CF152A640_190712_3858617_Wildlife_officials_may_soon_dump_rat_poison_on_t_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[FARALLON ISLANDS, CALIFORNIA  The U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service has proposed a plan to drop 1.5 tons of rodenticide via a helicopter twice over a three week period to eradicate invasive house mice from the South Farallon Islands.The agency says the dead mice would then be removed by authorities and collected by hand.Wildlife authorities plan to use fireworks, predator calls and air cannons to prevent seagulls from consuming the poison.According to a report by the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service, the removal of house mice is expected to indirectly reduce predation by migratory burrowing owls, which prey on native species such as the ashy stormy-petrel. The owls stay on the islands through the winter to consume mice. After the mouse population crashes, the owls start preying on storm-petrels. House mice further harm the island's ecosystem by consuming native species such as the Farallon camel cricket and competing with the Farallon arboreal salamander for food.Native vegetation on the islands is also threatened due to mouse predation, allowing invasive plant species such as the New Zealand spinach to thrive.The agency said eliminating mice would likely increase survival rates of natives plants such as the maritime goldfield.The Fish and Wildlife Service says using poison is the most efficient method to get rid of the mice.Critics say that the rat poison may indirectly harm other animals that unknowingly consume the rodents, the Los Angeles Times reports.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/24A/B19/24AB19E1B77A1FA60442B0A953791B1D.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>101</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>rat poison</Tag>
          <Tag>farallon islands</Tag>
          <Tag>house mice</Tag>
          <Tag>poison pellets</Tag>
          <Tag>mice</Tag>
          <Tag>farallon islands mice</Tag>
          <Tag>mouse carcasses</Tag>
          <Tag>rodents</Tag>
          <Tag>rodents farallon islands</Tag>
          <Tag>california</Tag>
          <Tag>wildlife</Tag>
          <Tag>mice</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Fake Samsung Update app has millions of downloads, report finds</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/fake-samsung-update-app-has-millions-of-downloads-report-finds-3860303</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/15/3860303/3860303_3DA0245BC3874CA0A76DC54BAFCA9D5B_190715_3860303_Fake_Samsung_Update_app_has_millions_of_download_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK  A new report by the CSIS Security Group has found that "Updates for Samsung," a third-party app on the Google Play store, had been misleading users into paying for software updates on their Samsung phones.The app had more than 10 million downloads before it was taken down last week, USA Today reports.According to the report, once the app is downloaded, it takes you to their website, 'updato.com.'The website allows users to search for specific firmware then asks users for their credit card information and charges users a fee of US$34.99 for an annual subscription of Samsung software updates.The site offers free updates as well. However, the report found that free downloads are limited to a rate of 56 KBps and eventually time out.This happens despite the fact that Android phones offer free software updates on all their devices.Bleeping Computer reports that the app had clearly stated in their description that they are quote "not affiliated in any way, shape, or form with Google Inc or Samsung Electronics."CSIS Security Group Malware analyst Aleksejs Kuprins told ZDNet that the app didn't carry out malicious tasks on the device.Kuprins said the website displayed "a lot of full-screen advertisements, almost after every other tap on the screen."In a statement to Bleeping Computer, Updato's app developer said they aggregate software updates, "for the convenience of our audience."Adding that, "Our database allows people to easily search for firmware in any location for any version for any device. "Updato told Bleeping Computer that the app was taken down to make adjustments while Google says it had suspended the app for violating Google Play Developer Policies.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/662/965/662965D2A68A29A84EFB3EDE1E0BE3D4.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>115</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>android phones</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps privacy</Tag>
          <Tag>android apps privacy issues</Tag>
          <Tag>Google play store</Tag>
          <Tag>Android malware</Tag>
          <Tag>samsung app scam</Tag>
          <Tag>Google</Tag>
          <Tag>samsung</Tag>
          <Tag>third-party apps</Tag>
          <Tag>third-party android apps</Tag>
          <Tag>suspicious android apps</Tag>
          <Tag>Android OS</Tag>
          <Tag>updates for samsung malware</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 11:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Solar panel device uses waste heat to purify water</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/solar-panel-device-uses-waste-heat-to-purify-water-3860209</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/15/3860209/3860209_428FA43FD88345569F6462F48F176155_190715_3860209_Solar_panel_device_uses_waste_heat_to_purify_wat_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[THUWAL, SAUDI ARABIA  Researchers in Saudi Arabia have modified traditional solar panels into a system that cogenerates both electricity and clean water.Water and energy production are intertwined  a connection known as the water-energy nexus. Cosmos Magazine reports that water is used to produce energy, and in turn, a significant amount of energy is needed to produce clean drinking water.According to Peng Wang of the King Abdullah University of Science and Technology, solar panels only convert 20% of the light they absorb into electricity; the remaining 80% is released into the air.To address this, university researchers have designed a system that can use this waste heat to generate fresh, clean water.The system is made up of a three-layer distillation system attached to the underside of a solar panel.Waste heat from the panel is directed to the uppermost layer, where it vaporizes seawater. The vapor passes through a porous membrane to the second layer, where it condenses as freshwater. Heat produced during condensation passes through a thermal conduction layer, where the energy is recycled to purify more water.The stacked system was able to produce 1.64 liters of water per square meter of solar panel surface each hour.According to the researchers, it's more than double the output of more traditional solar stills. The panel's electricity output was also unaffected by the distillation going on underneath.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7C1/C0A/7C1C0AC16AA21CF897362EF660AFB3B0.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>87</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>solar panels</Tag>
          <Tag>water purification</Tag>
          <Tag>purifying water</Tag>
          <Tag>clean water</Tag>
          <Tag>drinking water</Tag>
          <Tag>solar energy</Tag>
          <Tag>solar tech</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 09:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>India's second lunar mission is delayed</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/india-s-second-lunar-mission-is-delayed-3860118</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/15/3860118/3860118_CC2CC78B34C34F5782FCF290FA12CE70_190715_3860118_India_s_second_lunar_mission_is_delayed_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#chandrayaan2 #india #moonSRIHARIKOTA, INDIA  India's space agency was set to launch the Chandrayaan-2 lunar mission from Satish Dhawan Space Center on July 15 before the mission was aborted due to a technical error, reports India Today. This would have been India's second moon mission, the Times of India reports.The Indian Space Agency said they will announce a new launch date.The mission's spacecraft comprises of a lander, a rover and an orbiter, the Indian Space Research Organization or ISRO. The rover is to be housed within the lander.The spacecraft will carry a total of 13 payloads. This would include the eight on the orbiter, three on the lander and two on the rover.The orbiter will be carrying items such as a terrain mapping camera, a solar X-ray monitor, an imaging IR spectrometer and a dual-frequency synthetic aperture radar. The lander will include an instrument for lunar seismic activity and a thermal probe. While the rover will carry an X-ray spectrometer and a laser-induced breakdown spectroscope.The orbiter and the lander will separate once the spacecraft has reached the moon's orbit. The lander will attempt a soft-landing between two lunar craters, according to the ISRO.Once on the moon's surface, the rover will be able to move around semi-autonomously. It will analyze the moon's surface and send data to the lander. The lander will then relay information to the orbiter and to earth, according to the ISRO.India had previously launched its first lunar mission  Chandrayaan-1  back in 2008.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/43A/048/43A048DAE96A2E560DD1EC754A3F9672.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>102</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>space</Tag>
          <Tag>space exploration</Tag>
          <Tag>india</Tag>
          <Tag>moon</Tag>
          <Tag>Chandrayaan-2</Tag>
          <Tag>Chandrayaan-2  spacecraft</Tag>
          <Tag>Chandrayaan-2 mission</Tag>
          <Tag>Chandrayaan-2 lunar mission</Tag>
          <Tag>Indian Space Research Organisation</Tag>
          <Tag>moon landing</Tag>
          <Tag>india moon landing</Tag>
          <Tag>lunar mission</Tag>
          <Tag>india lunar mission</Tag>
          <Tag>spacecraft</Tag>
          <Tag>india moon mission</Tag>
          <Tag>Chandrayaan-2 animation</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 07:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Massive cactus spears through windshield in Arizona car crash</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/massive-cactus-spears-through-windshield-in-arizona-car-crash-3860002</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/15/3860002/3860002_7DCAC83131D340B783475F9EBAFCAF01_190715_3860002_Massive_cactus_spears_through_windshield_in_Ariz_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[CATALINA FOOTHILLS, ARIZONA  Shortly before 9:30 a.m. Wednesday, a driver in the Catalina Foothills of Arizona survived a spectacular impact with a girthy cactus and walked away unscathed.According to the North West Fire Department, the driver, 39-year-old Kai Scott, crossed the median into another lane of traffic and crashed into the cactus. The Pima County Sheriff's Department is investigating the accident.According to KTVK, the car is in pretty bad shape, the windshield has been totaled, and the monstrous Saguaro cactus was protruding from the vehicle by several feet.Arizona Daily Star reported that the driver was arrested on suspicion of driving under the influence and for criminal damage.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6C1/F59/6C1F5991985CEA1CBFCB51387997203F.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>72</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>cactus car crash</Tag>
          <Tag>cactus car window</Tag>
          <Tag>cactus car accident</Tag>
          <Tag>cactus crash</Tag>
          <Tag>cactus accident</Tag>
          <Tag>cactus crash window</Tag>
          <Tag>car crashes into cactus</Tag>
          <Tag>car crash</Tag>
          <Tag>cactus crashes through car windshield in Catalina Foothills crash</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 02:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Sunken Soviet-era submarine found leaking radiation</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sunken-soviet-era-submarine-found-leaking-radiation-3859976</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/15/3859976/3859976_E5F9D271CD664C19A543E73CED0F98CC_190715_3859976_Sunken_Soviet_era_submarine_found_leaking_radiat_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BEAR ISLAND, NORWAY  Researchers from Norway and Russia have discovered radioactive leakage from a Soviet-era nuclear submarine wreck in the Norwegian Sea.The Komsomolets sank in the ocean in 1989, taking the lives of 42 sailors after a fire broke out.A joint expedition between the two countries was conducted this month via the remotely-operated vehicle Aegir 6000 to monitor and collect information about radioactive contamination at the wreckage site, BBC News reports.Researchers took several water samples from in and around a ventilation duct of the submarine, with the highest recorded level of radioactive caesium being around 100 becquerel per liter or 800,000 times higher than normal. In comparison, other areas in the Norwegian Sea have radiation levels around 0.001 becquerel per liter, according to a news release from the Institute of Marine Research.Researchers have also taken samples of seawater and organisms that now live on the shipwreck for further analysis.Researchers say the Soviet-era submarine wreck is 1,680 meters in the ocean.The Komsomolets sank while carrying two nuclear torpedoes with plutonium warheads.The team released a video of their expedition showing the remains of the submarine.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F3/E9F/1F3E9F786D7800EC38543F3D7632DB78.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>79</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>russian nuclear submarine</Tag>
          <Tag>norwegian sea</Tag>
          <Tag>komsomolets</Tag>
          <Tag>russian navy submarine</Tag>
          <Tag>russian submarine Komsomolets</Tag>
          <Tag>komsomolets</Tag>
          <Tag>russian submarine</Tag>
          <Tag>russian submarine K-278</Tag>
          <Tag>Komsomolets submarine</Tag>
          <Tag>Komsomolets wreck</Tag>
          <Tag>Komsomolets submarine disaster</Tag>
          <Tag>Komsomolets wreck russia</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Villa pizza chain to sell all-crust pizza slices</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/villa-pizza-chain-to-sell-all-crust-pizza-slices-3860761</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/16/3860761/3860761_F82CA5A7744C41C19428350FE658CFD8_190716_3860761_Villa_pizza_chain_to_sell_all_crust_pizza_slices_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MORRISTOWN, NEW JERSEY  The makers of the Pumpkin Spice Pizza and the Gender Reveal Lasagna are messing with all of us yet again by offering "Just the Crust" pizza.  Villa Italian Kitchen recently announced in a press release that they would start selling single-serve boxes of only pizza crusts - no sauce, no cheese, no toppings. Let's just say people are not taking it well.The pizza chain claims it's the perfect idea since their crusts are "everyone's favorite part." Not sure who they've been talking to but who is "everyone"?Villa told Food and Wine that the all-crust abomination is created by making a pizza outline out of dough, then "delicately positioning" splashes of cheese and sauce, for what they call an "authentic crust experience."It may just be us, but something else comes to mind with "authentic crust experience."There's likely some heathens out there who will appreciate an all-crust deal, but the other end of that spectrum who want all the saucy bits should get a no-crust pie too. Honestly though, there's no need to ruin a perfectly good thing. But if you absolutely must, Villa's $2.75 "Just the Crust" will hit stores from July 18.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/539/F67/539F67C4D5EE1308CF9AAAA7992A3B62.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>89</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>just the crust</Tag>
          <Tag>pizza crusts</Tag>
          <Tag>pizza crust</Tag>
          <Tag>villa pizza</Tag>
          <Tag>villa italian kitchen</Tag>
          <Tag>pizza chain</Tag>
          <Tag>all crust</Tag>
          <Tag>all crust pizza</Tag>
          <Tag>all crust pizza slice</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 11:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Brain implant restores partial vision to the blind</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/brain-implant-restores-partial-vision-to-the-blind-3860660</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/16/3860660/3860660_1720584166C641BC8B61FDC1B86D3DB8_190716_3860660_Brain_implant_restores_partial_vision_to_the_bli_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[HOUSTON  Doctors have restored partial sight to six blind people by using an implant that sends video images directly to the brain.Researchers from the Baylor College of Medicine and UCLA are collaborating to test the Orion device, which consists of a brain implant with 60 electrodes, and a pair of glasses with a camera to capture images.According to Second Sight, the company that created the device, the brain implant is put on the surface of the visual cortex, where it will receive deciphered information from the camera wirelessly.The gadget is able to bypass the eye and the optic nerve, which usually sends sensory information to the brain, reports The Guardian.In a medical trial, six patients with acquired blindness were asked to look at a black computer screen while using the Orion device, and pinpoint the location of a white square that appears at different times.Researchers said the participants were able to identify the location of the square the majority of the time.Daniel Yosher, chair and professor of neurosurgery at Baylor College of Medicine, explained in a news release that the device will not work for those born blind, since the parts of their brain that process sight have not fully developed.It is only suitable for those born with the ability to see and went blind at a later age. This is because their visual cortices are intact, just not stimulated because the eye is not receiving any information.Yosher explained that for these patients with acquired blindness, there is potential to directly activate the neurons responsible for seeing, in order to restore functional sight.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/606/C95/606C95158059D0A4385C5549413FD06D.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>103</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>brain implants</Tag>
          <Tag>neural implants</Tag>
          <Tag>brain implants</Tag>
          <Tag>brain implants for blind</Tag>
          <Tag>brain implants blindness</Tag>
          <Tag>visual cortex</Tag>
          <Tag>neural implant blindness</Tag>
          <Tag>visual impairment</Tag>
          <Tag>cure for blindness</Tag>
          <Tag>blindness</Tag>
          <Tag>cure for blindness brain implant</Tag>
          <Tag>Orion brain implant</Tag>
          <Tag>vision</Tag>
          <Tag>orion second sight</Tag>
          <Tag>bionic glasses</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 09:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>'Traffic light' food labeling lead to healthier food choices, study finds</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-traffic-light-food-labeling-lead-to-healthier-food-choices-study-finds-3860650</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/16/3860650/3860650_F72D9B8F692649459E5FE643AF1FD5DC_190716_3860650__Traffic_light__food_labeling_lead_to_healthier__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BOSTON  A new study by Massachusetts General Hospital has found that using "traffic light" colors  red, yellow and green  in labeling food items results in healthier food choices.The study took place over a two-year period. Participants were 5,695 employees who ate at the hospital's workplace cafeteria.Researchers assigned the color green to the healthiest food. Food labeled in yellow were less healthy than the ones labeled green, while those marked in red were the least healthy.According to the study, each food item was labeled based on whether it contained healthy ingredients such as fruit and vegetables, whole grains, and lean protein or whether it contained saturated fat and caloric content.Researchers tracked participants' purchases before and after the labels were added, via their employee ID numbers. They found that purchases of green-labeled food increased while those for red-labeled food products decreased.The study noted that the estimated reduction in calories was equal to around two kilograms of weight loss over time.In a Massachusetts General Hospital news release, lead author of the study Anne N. Thorndike said the study not only shows employees consuming fewer calories at work, but also that they were improving the quality of the calories they were purchasing.""Traffic light" food labeling is already in use in countries such as the United Kingdom and Australia, but has yet to be put in use in the U.S.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F45/389/F45389C55853F70D3C4F14A5E3376EAE.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>83</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>traffic lights</Tag>
          <Tag>traffic lights symbol</Tag>
          <Tag>food traffic light system</Tag>
          <Tag>Traffic light' food labels</Tag>
          <Tag>traffic light food labels explained</Tag>
          <Tag>traffic light food labelling guidelines</Tag>
          <Tag>traffic light food labelling countries</Tag>
          <Tag>traffic light food labelling effectiveness</Tag>
          <Tag>eating healthy</Tag>
          <Tag>eating healthy food</Tag>
          <Tag>eating healthy reduces calories</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 09:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Robber returns cash, says it's not enough for daughter's kidney transplant</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/robber-returns-cash-says-it-s-not-enough-for-daughter-s-kidney-transplant-3860630</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/16/3860630/3860630_763D6899836048AF817722E9049037E1_190716_3860630_Robber_returns_cash__says_it_s_not_enough_for_da_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA  Cops in Philly are on the lookout for a would-be armed robber, who gave back the cash he stole because it wasn't enough. According to CBS3, the masked man walked into a smoke shop Monday morning and threatened to shoot the sales clerk if she didn't open the cash register.Once the register was opened, the perp grabbed the money inside  but then did a complete 180. He abruptly gave back the 100 bucks or so he'd gotten his hands on, saying it wouldn't be enough to pay for his daughter's transplant.The suspect may have left without taking anything, but police say he could still face a charge for the attempted holdup.Good news is, the cops are also interested in knowing more about the daughter's situation, and may be able to offer the family some assistance.Police say they might have an idea about who the dude is, but are still trying to track him down.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C7D/623/C7D623C9BCE9ED6F4E79AEF7A7F071DD.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>50</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>robber returns money</Tag>
          <Tag>attempted robbery</Tag>
          <Tag>kidney transplant</Tag>
          <Tag>transplant money</Tag>
          <Tag>man robs store</Tag>
          <Tag>choosy robber</Tag>
          <Tag>picky rober</Tag>
          <Tag>armed robbery</Tag>
          <Tag>armed robbery</Tag>
          <Tag>kind robber</Tag>
          <Tag>friendly robber</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 08:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Woman hunts down stolen car, gets it back from thief</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-hunts-down-stolen-car-gets-it-back-from-thief-3860515</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/16/3860515/3860515_647A21EB6FCD4DBBAC8FE0B986C41CEF_190716_3860515_Woman_hunts_down_stolen_car__gets_it_back_from_t_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[KANSAS CITY, MISSOURI  A woman in Kansas City was out and about when her vehicle suddenly got stolen. She filed a police report, and then decided to take matters into her own hands.Danielle Reno was picking up her daughter from a gas station in Kansas city when her car, a Toyota 4Runner, was stolen.Reno said they stalked the car thieves for 48 hours, and the perps were none the wiser."KCTV5 News reports that Reno tracked her debit card, credit card, and phone  all of which had been left behind in her car.A gas station attendant told her that the car thieves were heading to Applebee's, so that's where she went.Reno said they were at the restaurant when the woman walked in the door. She swiftly slipped out the front and made her way to her vehicle.Reno opened the car door and was hit by a pungent smell  the backseat was filled with beer bottles and other nasty stuff, according to KCTV5 News.She later watched and filmed the car thief and her accomplices as they were arrested by the cops."Alas, Reno said she won't be driving the car anymore due to the damage caused by the car thieves.The police told KCTV5 News that they don't recommend people do this, though they did say Reno never technically put herself in harm's way.Commentators were quick to praise Reno, with one saying, "Sometimes you gotta do what you gotta do."]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C11/219/C11219E1A0148BD593AAEFDA06638FB8.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>77</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>carnapped</Tag>
          <Tag>carnapper</Tag>
          <Tag>car thief</Tag>
          <Tag>woman gets back stolen car</Tag>
          <Tag>woman takes back stolen car</Tag>
          <Tag>kansas woman</Tag>
          <Tag>woman car stolen at gas station</Tag>
          <Tag>woman hunts down stolen car</Tag>
          <Tag>woman takes back stolen car from thief</Tag>
          <Tag>woman hunts down car thief</Tag>
          <Tag>kansas city</Tag>
          <Tag>missouri</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 04:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Storm Area 51: US Air Force warns alien hunters</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/storm-area-51-us-air-force-warns-alien-hunters-3860512</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/16/3860512/3860512_48F1FA058DEC49CDADEAD1E39A41B1E7_190716_3860512_Storm_Area_51__US_Air_Force_warns_alien_hunters_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#stormArea51 #Area51 #aliensAMARGOSA VALLEY, NEVADA  For anyone actually thinking of raiding Area 51, the Feds have a message for you.The Facebook event to storm Area 51 is blowing up online, with just over 300,000 potential attendees late last week to nearly a million today.Though it's obviously a joke, we're pretty sure more than a handful of idiots are actually gonna show.The raid hinges on a strength-in-numbers strategy, since "they can't stop all of us." But then, they probably can. For one thing, the U.S. government is already well aware of the September 20 event.U.S. Air Force spokeswoman Laura McAndrews warned in a Washington Post article that Area 51 is an open training range for the armed forces. And rest assured, they are pretty ready to take on Naruto runners and other crazy trespassers.Alien hunters and conspiracy theorists have long believed the feds are hiding alien tech and other secrets at the facility.Knowing the U.S. government, there is probably a buttload of secrets, but Area 51 may be the least of our worries.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/513/900/5139001D28DA7798D09CE2C60379F65B.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>80</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>storm area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 event</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 prank event</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook prank event</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 aliens</Tag>
          <Tag>aliens</Tag>
          <Tag>UFO</Tag>
          <Tag>naruto run</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 04:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Chess grandmaster caught using his phone in huge scandal</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chess-grandmaster-caught-using-his-phone-in-huge-scandal-3860484</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/16/3860484/3860484_D038E7B7A0C7424C893E086FC5ED1D97_190716_3860484_Chess_grandmaster_caught_using_his_phone_in_huge_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#chessscandal #chessgrandmaster #cheatingSTRASBOURG, FRANCE  Chess grandmaster, Igors Rausis, has been accused of using his phone in a toilet to cheat in what is said to be the highest-profile cheating scandal since 2015. The 58-year-old Latvian-Czech had raised suspicions after he increased his chess rating in recent years to an almost impressive 2700.The Telegraph reported that the use of mobile phones at most chess tournaments is banned and that many high-level tournaments require players to pass through metal detectors when they enter playing. According to Chess.com, the phone was discovered in a restroom. Rausis later signed a declaration that the phone was indeed his; though his motives behind using the phone are still being investigated.Grandmaster and chess pundit Andrey Deviatkin commented, "I always considered huge progress in chess to be highly unlikely after 30." This is because it is believed players decline in strength with age. Rausis said in a comment to Chess.com that he confirmed he was, in fact, using a phone during a match. He claimed he was tired after the morning game and that accusers on Facebook impacted him  saying, "I played my last game of chess already."Emil Sutovsky, Director-General of FIDE, aka the World Chess Federation, said Rausis had been under suspicion for a while now and that the FIDE Ethics Commission would deal with this case. French police are also involved.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2DB/A46/2DBA46DD4CC6E3ECC2C38F8A681FE0EC.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>107</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>chess</Tag>
          <Tag>chess scandal</Tag>
          <Tag>chess cheating scandal</Tag>
          <Tag>chess grandmaster</Tag>
          <Tag>grandmaster using phone in toilet</Tag>
          <Tag>chess cheater</Tag>
          <Tag>caught red handed</Tag>
          <Tag>chess grandmaster cheating</Tag>
          <Tag>FIDE</Tag>
          <Tag>caught cheating</Tag>
          <Tag>igors rausis</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 03:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Flushing drugs down toilet could spawn meth gators, cops say</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/flushing-drugs-down-toilet-could-spawn-meth-gators-cops-say-3861173</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/17/3861173/3861173_DF6D147F9E8341DD90CC47774FCC4147_190717_3861173_Flushing_drugs_down_toilet_could_spawn_meth_gato_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[LORETTO, TENNESSEE  In what sounds like the plot of a gloriously bad B-movie, police in Tennessee are warning folks not to flush drugs down the toilet, or, get this, gators-who-broke-bad might just start taking over the South.CNN reports that the Loretto Police Department posted the warning to Facebook after their guys nabbed a suspect who tried to flush speed down the crapper.Though the dude wasn't successful, the cops say it's definitely a concern, since meds in the sewer system could end up in treatment ponds, and then get the duck and geese all hyped up and loca.Even worse, the stuff could make it all the way downstream and end up getting more than a few Alabama gators cranked. And we certainly don't want no crazy snappers. Lord knows Alabama already has enough speed-induced concerns to deal with.The Tennessee boys in blue ended their message by encouraging folks who wanna get rid of their stash to instead come in and surrender them for proper disposal.  Sure, not like you'll arrest them or anything.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0DE/A24/0DEA247056B78FB2026D3B8509BA277C.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>69</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>meth gators</Tag>
          <Tag>speed</Tag>
          <Tag>crank</Tag>
          <Tag>police warning</Tag>
          <Tag>don't flush drugs</Tag>
          <Tag>what not to flush in the toilet</Tag>
          <Tag>alabama gators</Tag>
          <Tag>high alabama gators</Tag>
          <Tag>gators on speed</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 09:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Facebook embeds tracking code to images uploaded by users</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-embeds-tracking-code-to-images-uploaded-by-users-3861881</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/18/3861881/3861881_6EDCC6780BCB4196B289421FFB020E61_190718_3861881_Facebook_embeds_tracking_code_to_images_uploaded_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  A law student at the University of New England in Australia claimed on Twitter that he has found evidence that Facebook is embedding 'hidden codes" on photos shared by users on its website.Edin Jusupovic, explained that he noticed a "structural abnormality" in the metadata of an image file.He discovered that it contained an IPTC special instruction, which is essentially a metadata watermark that would allow Facebook to track the photo even on other platforms.Facebook adds this to tag the image with its own coding, according to Forbes. The tags can be read later, enabling the social media giant to track ownership of the photo and use it to resolve copyright infringements.But he also told the Australian that the data gathered could also allow Facebook to track users who aren't on their platform, identify their political party affiliation, or even build profiles on where they go shopping.In a series of tweets, Jusupovic explained that the company could potentially use the data to identify if the same image was uploaded twice onto its platform and find out how the two users are associated with each other and the photo.Facebook has been embroiled in a series of scandals concerning privacy on its social media platform over the past few years. The company is currently facing a record US$5 billion fine by the FTC over its Cambridge Analytica scandals, according to the BBC. Facebook users weren't notified that their data was being shared with third-party apps such as Cambridge Analytica. The consultancy company was able harvest user data and even the data of their friends, via a personality type Facebook quiz.Facebook has said that up to 87 million users' data was compromised because of the Cambridge Analytica scandal.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A9A/A7C/A9AA7C56E96BF6DFE224726E37C07040.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>116</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook scandals</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook tracking</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook tracks photos</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook tracks user images</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook tracking</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook tracking user photos</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook embeds code to track user photos</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook scandals</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook hidden code</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook hidden codes in user photos</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 10:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Study links social media to teen gloom while gaming equals smiles</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/study-links-social-media-to-teen-gloom-while-gaming-equals-smiles-3861546</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/18/3861546/3861546_8E29DAEF1A8147289F80B54DA9A1727C_190718_3861546_Study_links_social_media_to_teen_gloom_while_gam_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MONTREAL  A new study published in the journal JAMA Pediatrics on Monday connected social media to depression in teens and not video gaming.  Lead researcher, Patricia Conrod, a professor of psychiatry at Montreal's Sainte-Justine Hospital and her colleague, Elroy Boersn examined the correlation between depression in teenagers and various types of screen time. They looked at four varieties of screen time including, social media, video games, television, and computer use.The researchers analyzed the data of 3,826 adolescents from 31 Montreal schools between 2012 and 2018, following their screen time from Grade 7 to Grade 11.CBC News reported that the teenagers self-reported the amount of time they spent in front of a screen per week. The research identified social media as the most harmful of all forms of screen time.They found that Instagram was the leading culprit in teen depression as, according to Conrod, it "exposes young people to images that promote upward social comparison and makes them feel bad about themselves."The same connection was not found for those of us who play video games.  Boers explained that more than 70 percent of gamers play with other people either online or in person, therefore they are not socially isolated.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2CE/238/2CE238D2E1846D4B3A400AC16A33E3CC.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>86</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>social media linked to depression</Tag>
          <Tag>video gaming and depression</Tag>
          <Tag>social media and mental health</Tag>
          <Tag>video games good for the brain</Tag>
          <Tag>video games good or bad</Tag>
          <Tag>social media depression study</Tag>
          <Tag>Instagram linked to depression</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 04:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>What is Area 51?</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/what-is-area-51--3861531</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/18/3861531/3861531_8038A5C39F81495AB1705FC1FD23FDCF_190718_3861531_What_is_Area_51__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#area51 #aliens #stormarea51GROOM LAKE, NEVADA  Over a million people have pledged to join a prank event to raid Area 51 in the wee hours of September 20. Whether you're one of those planning to go, or just a very amused spectator  here's all you need to know about the ever-mysterious facility.Area 51 is a remote U.S. Air Force military installation at Groom Lake in southern Nevada, about 80 miles from Las Vegas. The BBC reports that the facility is so named for its designation on 50's era maps of the Atomic Energy Commission.According to Reuters, extreme secrecy surrounded the facility for decades until the CIA publicly acknowledged its existence in 2013.According to declassified internal CIA documents, Area 51  was selected in 1955 to be the test site of the high altitude U-2 reconnaissance plane, which was developed to spy on the Soviet Union during the Cold War.Other top-secret aircraft were later developed at the site, including the supersonic reconnaissance A-12 OXCART aircraft, and the stealth F-117 Nighthawk jet.The secrecy shrouding Area 51 fueled wild UFO theories, the most sensational of which is that the remains of a flying saucer that crashed near Roswell, New Mexico in 1947 was brought to the facility for experiments in reverse engineering.In 1989, a man named Bob Lazar claimed he'd worked on extraterrestrial tech in Area 51, and saw alien autopsy photos inside the facility. He has since been discredited, but the theories continue to this day.While the CIA document didn't address any alien conspiracy theories associated with the site, it did suggest a connection between U-2 test flights and UFO sightings.The U-2 flew at much higher altitudes than commercial planes, and people who sighted them wouldn't have known what they were due to the secretive nature of the program, so in that sense they were unidentified flying objects.Area 51 is still an active military installation. It's currently under 24 hour surveillance and not accessible to the public.Air Force spokesperson Laura McAndrews told the Washington Post that the site is an open training range where American armed forces are trained.So unless you want to be pummeled by a battalion of soldiers, it's probably not a good idea to storm Area 51 to "see them aliens." Because while the raid may have all the manpower, that's still no match for all the U.S. military's toys.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/07D/FC8/07DFC81770A398F08F968D27B70904C6.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>154</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>storm area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>storming area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>area51</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 stormed</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 storm</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 news</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 alien</Tag>
          <Tag>aliens</Tag>
          <Tag>see them aliens</Tag>
          <Tag>secret base</Tag>
          <Tag>alien conspiracy</Tag>
          <Tag>alien conspiracy theories</Tag>
          <Tag>facebook group</Tag>
          <Tag>storm area 51 prank</Tag>
          <Tag>conspiracy theorists</Tag>
          <Tag>UFO</Tag>
          <Tag>area 52 raid</Tag>
          <Tag>prank event</Tag>
          <Tag>area 51 raid</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 03:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kyoto Animation studio arson attack devastates Japan</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/kyoto-animation-studio-arson-attack-devastates-japan-3862643</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/20/3862643/3862643_EEB316EB07124C81AA8A0BCECC14A6FE_190720_3862643_Kyoto_Animation_studio_arson_attack_devastates_J_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[KYOTO, JAPAN  More than two dozen people are dead and many more injured after a man set fire to an animation studio in Kyoto, Japan.The Mainichi reports that on the morning of July 18, a 41-year-old man broke into the three-storey Kyoto Animation Studio building in Kyoto's Fushimi Ward.According to the New York Times, he doused the building with a flammable liquid believed to be gasoline, and screamed 'Die!' as he set it ablaze around 10:35 a.m.The BBC reports that eyewitnesses described hearing a loud explosion, followed by a blaze that quickly engulfed the building.Around 70 people were believed to be working inside the studio when it was set on fire. Many attempted to escape by running up to the top of the building, according to the Guardian, but later collapsed on the stairs.The suspect tried to flee, but fell on the street outside. NHK reports that he has been detained but is currently being treated at the hospital for his burns.Firefighters said they found two bodies on the first floor, 11 on the second floor, and 20 on the third floor staircase leading to the roof  a total of 33 casualties. 36 others have been hospitalized for their injuries.Police have not yet established a motive for the attack, though eyewitnesses say the suspect appeared to be angry with the studio.The fire at Kyoto Animation shocked and devastated the studio's fans around the world. A GoFundMe campaign set up to "Help KyoAni Heal" has already raised over $1.2 million.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D6C/2CA/D6C2CAEA398A02DD13D60315CABE3755.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>98</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>kyoto animation</Tag>
          <Tag>kyoto animation fire</Tag>
          <Tag>kyoani</Tag>
          <Tag>arson attack</Tag>
          <Tag>arson</Tag>
          <Tag>arsonist</Tag>
          <Tag>animation studio</Tag>
          <Tag>japan anime studio</Tag>
          <Tag>japan animation studio</Tag>
          <Tag>kyoto fire</Tag>
          <Tag>kyoto anime studio</Tag>
          <Tag>anime studio</Tag>
          <Tag>kyoto studio</Tag>
          <Tag>anime</Tag>
          <Tag>animation</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 16:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>El Chapo may be serving life at 'Alcatraz of the Rockies' prison</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/el-chapo-may-be-serving-life-at-alcatraz-of-the-rockies-prison-3862470</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/19/3862470/3862470_F659D5A0DB0142BC95B6370B5DEC0237_190719_3862470_El_Chapo_may_be_serving_life_at__Alcatraz_of_the_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#chapo #supermax #elchapoFLORENCE, COLORADO  Mexican drug kingpin Joaquin 'El Chapo' Guzman has been sentenced to life in prison, plus 30 years, by a federal judge in Brooklyn. While authorities have not mentioned where, Reuters reports that he will likely serve the sentence at ADX Florence in Colorado, America's most secure "Supermax" prison.The prison, nicknamed "Alcatraz of the Rockies," currently has 376 inmates held in solitary cells, each with a narrow window through which only the sky is visible.Furnishings include a TV, lamp, stainless steel sink, toilet and mirror, fixed concrete stool, desk and a bed with a thin mattress.There is also a stainless steel shower cubicle that runs on a timer to prevent inmates from flooding their cells.Human interaction in the facility is kept to a minimum. Inmates are held alone for about 23 hours a day, even eating their meals in solitude.They can watch religious services and educational programs on the TV in their cell and have access to a commissary.Special restrictions are in place to ensure prisoners cannot exert influence or make threats beyond the facility walls. They are not allowed to move around without being escorted, and head counts are conducted seven times a day, according to the New York Times.Chapo has escaped two maximum security prisons in Mexico  the first in 2001 using a laundry cart and the help of corrupt prison guards, and the second 14 years later, through a tunnel.No inmate has escaped ADX since it opened in 1994.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D6D/680/D6D6803FD0E5A7FA57AE9E2F1E235467.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>101</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>chapo</Tag>
          <Tag>el chapo</Tag>
          <Tag>supermax prison</Tag>
          <Tag>supermax</Tag>
          <Tag>ADX Florence</Tag>
          <Tag>alcatraz of the rockies</Tag>
          <Tag>prison escape</Tag>
          <Tag>alcatraz</Tag>
          <Tag>prison break</Tag>
          <Tag>joaquin guzman</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 11:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Researchers head on mission across the Northwest Passage</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-head-on-mission-across-the-northwest-passage-3862457</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/19/3862457/3862457_67508FDAF78C45EEB22600D8C502FD91_190719_3862457_Researchers_head_on_mission_across_the_Northwest_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[THE ARCTIC  A group of American and Canadian scientists and students will be embarking on the Northwest Passage Project  an 18-day expedition through the Northwest Passage aboard the Swedish Icebreaker Oden. According to the project's website, the team will depart on July 18 from Thule, Greenland and make its way to Pond Inlet, Canada. Afterwards, it will sail through Lancaster Sound to Barrow Strait and stop in Resolute.The expedition will then go west to Melville Sound and south into Prince Regent Sound before arriving back in Greenland on August 4.Led by the University of Rhode Island's Inner Space Center, researchers plan to collect seawater, ice and air samples to make assessments on how climate change is impacting the Arctic.Instruments such as the Lowered Acoustic Doppler Current Profiler and the Current, Temperature, and Depth Profiler, or CTD, will also be taken aboard to measure the water currents in the Northwest Passage.The mission specifically focuses on four research areas. Scientists will gather data on water mass and circulation inside the Canadian Arctic Archipelago, and analyze how the water column chemistry affects greenhouse gas accumulation.They will also examine how microscopic habitats are transitioning because of climate conditions and monitor marine bird distribution in the Arctic region.The Inner Space Center will share live broadcasts of their expedition on Facebook along with videos on their Youtube channel.The journey will also be the subject of a two-hour TV documentary, which will air in 2020, according to Hydro International.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5B4/FDD/5B4FDDA6C630840D088DB6ED1610F42D.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>91</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Arctic</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic ice melting</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic ice melting news</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic sea</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic ocean</Tag>
          <Tag>climate scientists</Tag>
          <Tag>northwest passage</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic sea route</Tag>
          <Tag>northern sea route</Tag>
          <Tag>climate change</Tag>
          <Tag>global warming</Tag>
          <Tag>effects of climate change</Tag>
          <Tag>effects of climate warming</Tag>
          <Tag>climate warming</Tag>
          <Tag>climate warming arctic</Tag>
          <Tag>northwest passage project</Tag>
          <Tag>northwest passage exploration</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 11:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Elon Musk wants to merge humans and AI with brain implant</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/elon-musk-wants-to-merge-humans-and-ai-with-brain-implant-3862119</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/19/3862119/3862119_F98B52EF2EC843D299AA0E6A4DB0B668_190719_3862119_Elon_Musk_wants_to_merge_humans_and_AI_with_brai_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Is becoming cybernetically enhanced the next step in human evolution?According to Elon Musk, humanity is at risk of being left behind by the advancement of artificial intelligence, and claims the solution is to achieve symbiosis with it.To do this, his startup Neuralink has created a brain implant made up of a small, ultra-thin mesh thread that is laced with electrodes to detect neural activity.The threads are injected into the brain using a small robot developed by the company. Once inserted through tiny holes in the skull, the thread's electrodes relay brain activity to a small implant behind the ear.The implant connects wirelessly to a wearable device called the Link, which can be configured through an iPhone app.With some training, Neuralink senior scientist Philip Sabes, says users will be able to control their phone, and later redirect the output to control a keyboard or mouse.The Guardian reports that the company has so far only tested on animals, including recording a rat's brain activity and allowing a monkey to control a computer with its brain.Musk and his team say the tech is about ready to be tested on humans, but will have to first get approval from the FDA, and a few willing test subjects.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AD3/6A1/AD36A1B96E1E66F60CCA28B90D4F80DB.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>83</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>neuralink</Tag>
          <Tag>elon musk</Tag>
          <Tag>brain implant</Tag>
          <Tag>brain implant tech</Tag>
          <Tag>human AI symbiosis</Tag>
          <Tag>artificial intelligence</Tag>
          <Tag>AI</Tag>
          <Tag>cybernetics</Tag>
          <Tag>cybernetic enhancement</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 03:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>A new study uncovers bacteria's
drug defense mechanism</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-new-study-uncovers-bacteria-s%0Adrug-defense-mechanism-3862109</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/19/3862109/3862109_BDA15BCF6F414AE0A833C2C3E914E39A_190719_3862109_A_new_study_uncovers_bacteria_s_drug_defense_mec_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM / U.K  Researchers have discovered how a group of drug-resistant bacteria defend against medicine.Gram-negative bacteria have an additional outer membrane that makes them strong against antibiotics and responsible for serious drug-resistant infections. This outer membrane is made up of sugars, proteins, and lipids.How the sugars and proteins are made inside the cell and then transported to the outer membrane is understood, but how lipids get there was not.Researchers, led by Dr. Tim Knowles at the University of Birmingham, investigated the crystal structure of a protein called MlaC and found a mechanism that seems to open and close a pocket that lipids bind to. According to New Atlas, this controls inner-cell functions that dictate when lipids are sent to the outer membrane. This discovery, researchers believe, could one day lead to new drug design that can stop the outer membrane from forming and better treat infectious diseases.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/644/8BF/6448BFA12FECFE83891F3E56905E5789.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>64</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>bacterial defence mechanism</Tag>
          <Tag>Bacteria self-defense mechanisms uncovered</Tag>
          <Tag>antibiotics</Tag>
          <Tag>Bacterial defense construction revealed in step forward for new antibiotics</Tag>
          <Tag>Gram-negative bacteria</Tag>
          <Tag>Gram-negative bacteria's self-defense system has been uncovered</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 02:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Viral photo-editing app under fire over privacy concerns</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/viral-photo-editing-app-under-fire-over-privacy-concerns-3862096</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/19/3862096/3862096_4DADB1C6A8A9460A882DF58BCFAC2152_190719_3862096_Viral_photo_editing_app_under_fire_over_privacy__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SAINT PETERSBURG, RUSSIA  Photo-editing app Faceapp is facing security concerns over allegedly storing user data onto Russian servers. Faceapp uses artificial intelligence to alter human faces into aged versions of themselves.Forbes reports that the app's parent company is Wireless Lab, a Russian-based tech company.In a statement to TechCrunch, Faceapp explained that only images selected for editing by users logged into the app are uploaded onto a cloud database, and most are deleted within 48 hours.The company said the reason for this is "performance and traffic," to ensure that user images aren't uploaded repeatedly after every edit.Faceapp claims user data isn't transferred to Russia and is instead stored in Amazon Web Services and Google Cloud. It isn't sold or shared with any third parties, either."The company says users can opt out and remove their data from the app by sending a delete request, adding that they are working on a better user interface to deal with the issue.By agreeing to their Terms of Service, users are granting Faceapp permission to "modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, publicly perform and display[c]" any images they put into the app.This gives Faceapp the license to use the images for anything from training its AI algorithm to advertisement, according to Forbes.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE2/F87/FE2F87CADE37AB6FE2712F41679A9623.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>98</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>smartphone</Tag>
          <Tag>privacy</Tag>
          <Tag>smartphone apps privacy issues</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp russia</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp scandal</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp privacy issues</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp wireless lab</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp news</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp russia privacy</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp russian tries</Tag>
          <Tag>app privacy policy</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp privacy concerns</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp privacy concerns</Tag>
          <Tag>artificial intelligence</Tag>
          <Tag>faceapp wireless lab</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 01:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>U.S. Navy vessel downs Iranian drone in Strait of Hormuz</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-navy-vessel-downs-iranian-drone-in-strait-of-hormuz-3863831</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/22/3863831/3863831_7E383A37AA5F4A1A8542AE4E0A2C94C0_190722_3863831_U_S__Navy_vessel_downs_Iranian_drone_in_Strait_o_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[STRAIT OF HORMUZ  U.S. President Donald Trump claims a U.S. Navy ship destroyed an Iranian drone in the Strait of Hormuz after it came dangerously close to the vessel. Tehran, however, says they have no information about losing a drone.According to a U.S. Department of Defense statement, the USS Boxer was conducting an inbound transit in the Strait of Hormuz on Thursday, at approximately 10 a.m. local time. While the U.S. Navy vessel was sailing through the passageway, a drone came within 1,000 meters of the ship and ignored "multiple calls to stand down."Pentagon spokeswoman Rebecca Rebarich told CNN they assessed the unmanned aerial system to be Iranian.A U.S. military official told CNN that the marine unit aboard the USS Boxer used counter-drone jamming equipment, which is able to "detect, identify and defeat drones with an electronic attack."When the drone "closed within a threatening range" of the USS Boxer, the vessel took defensive action and immediately destroyed it.President Trump claims the incident was "the latest of many provocative and hostile actions by Iran against vessels operating in international waters." He called on other nations to condemn these attempts to disrupt freedom of navigation and commerce in the key transit point.Tensions between the U.S. and Iran have been escalating in recent months. The U.S. previously blamed two suspected oil tanker attacks in the region on Iran, and accused the Iranians of shooting down a U.S military drone just last month.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/141/90E/14190E46B3F25AEAF9931746D767A39D.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>103</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Trump</Tag>
          <Tag>Donald Trump</Tag>
          <Tag>iran vs usa</Tag>
          <Tag>Middle East</Tag>
          <Tag>Strait of Hormuz</Tag>
          <Tag>iran</Tag>
          <Tag>USA</Tag>
          <Tag>usa middle east</Tag>
          <Tag>usa vs middle east</Tag>
          <Tag>us iran drone</Tag>
          <Tag>iran news today</Tag>
          <Tag>USS Boxer</Tag>
          <Tag>US Marines</Tag>
          <Tag>us iran tensions latest news</Tag>
          <Tag>US Navy ship Iranian drone</Tag>
          <Tag>US downs Iranian drone</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 13:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Planned US-SoKor military drills to take place next month</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/planned-us-sokor-military-drills-to-take-place-next-month-3863622</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/22/3863622/3863622_F67F03C55CA742F19CE2629F59F61A02_190722_3863622_Planned_US_SoKor_military_drills_to_take_place_n_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SEOUL  South Korean and American armed forces are set to hold a scaled-down version of their annual military drills amid protests from North Korea.The U.S. and South Korea have announced that the 19-2 Dong Maeng military exercise will take place in August. South Korea's Yonhap News Agency reports that the exercise was first launched in March this year.Pentagon Spokesman Dave Eastburn said this is a regular exercise that shows U.S. commitment to their alliance with South Korea, and to the defense of the Korean Peninsula.During the exercise, the two sides will assess Seoul's initial operational capability. This is to verify whether South Korea is on track for its plan to retake wartime operational control of combined forces from the U.S. by 2022.The three requirements for the transfer include: South Korea acquiring key military capabilities to lead their combined forces, securing capabilities to respond early to nuclear and missile threats from North Korea and favorable security circumstances on the Korean Peninsula, according to Yonhap News Agency.North Korea is wary of the drills as it sees the joint military exercises as a threat to its sovereignty.According to North Korea News, the country's state-run Korean Central News Agency issued two statements criticizing the upcoming exercise as a violation of an agreement made between the U.S. and North Korea in last year's Singapore summit."North Korea said this would affect "working-level negotiations" between the U.S. and DPRK.North Korea also hinted that it may not abandon its nuclear weapons. In a statement, the country said, "As the U.S. unilaterally does not fulfill its commitments, the reason for us to stick to our promise with the U.S. gradually fades away."]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AB3/669/AB36692E8313486F575FD69C0D11DEF1.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>109</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>military drills</Tag>
          <Tag>joint military exercises</Tag>
          <Tag>North Korea</Tag>
          <Tag>South Korea</Tag>
          <Tag>US South korea joint military drills</Tag>
          <Tag>allied drills</Tag>
          <Tag>dong maeng exercise</Tag>
          <Tag>korean peninsula</Tag>
          <Tag>dong maeng 19-2</Tag>
          <Tag>us-south korea military drill 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>us-south korea Dong Maeng exercise</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 07:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>A woman stops a train from
leaving by using her foot</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-woman-stops-a-train-from%0Aleaving-by-using-her-foot-3863557</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/22/3863557/3863557_B261B17B081D44B786DDE3C980DCD7A5_190722_3863557_A_woman_stops_a_train_from_leaving_by_using_her__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[GUANGZHOU / CHINA   A woman had to be restrained in Guangzhou railway station when she successfully stopped an entire train using only her foot.According to The South China Morning Post, the woman surnamed Wong came to the station around 11:28 pm with her brother and friend. However, the trio were too late to catch their train to Changsha South.Wong explained she was worried about missing work the following day so she tried to convince staff to let her through the barrier. After arguing with the station officers, Wong jumped the gate and made a dash for the departing train. She began banging on the train windows, shouting, "Open the door!" She then daringly wedged her foot between the platform edge and the train.The station staff told her, "Get up, the train is about to depart so we cannot open the door. The door won't open! You can still take the next train, get up first!"Wong replied, "No, I don't want the next train, you can do it, please, I just want to get on this train!"The police were then called to the scene to apprehend the woman. Wong was sentenced to nine days in detention for disturbing order in a public place and impeding the normal flow of traffic.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/34B/4C4/34B4C4EF70A66D47F7B7EC8D5EE83B33.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>123</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>woman stops trains with foot</Tag>
          <Tag>woman stops train China</Tag>
          <Tag>woman uses her foot to stop a train in China</Tag>
          <Tag>woman stops train from leaving in China</Tag>
          <Tag>woman stops train</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 05:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Carbon-neutral science museum planned for Sweden</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/carbon-neutral-science-museum-planned-for-sweden-3864358</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/23/3864358/3864358_3D71D45A6F904ED5A361613E42CA01A3_190723_3864358_Carbon_neutral_science_museum_planned_for_Sweden_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[LUND, SWEDEN  An architectural firm is building a new museum powered by renewable energy in Sweden.Danish architecture firm COBE has unveiled plans to build a science museum in the Swedish city of Lund that would be powered with solar panels on its rooftop as well as energy bicycles located on its concave roof by 2024.According to the project's website, the building will mainly be built out of wood and will cover 3,500 square meters of floor space.The second story of the structure will consist of a viewing platform and a patio.The center of the structure will include a green urban space with trees, plants and other biodiversity. This will help in filtering out excess carbon dioxide.The museum will consist of exhibition halls, offices and an auditorium for the general public.The structure will be carbon neutral and will promote sustainability, according to the project's website.The museum will be part of Science Village Scandinavia, a high-tech urban district in Lund, which is still under development.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3F4/25B/3F425BB5105CE8D7E8E6E08C6AE8D85D.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>67</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>sweden</Tag>
          <Tag>carbon-neutral science museum</Tag>
          <Tag>science museum in Sweden</Tag>
          <Tag>COBE</Tag>
          <Tag>COBE sweden</Tag>
          <Tag>Science Village Scandinavia</Tag>
          <Tag>CO2-neutral building</Tag>
          <Tag>swedish infrastructure</Tag>
          <Tag>swedish architecture</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 11:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Philly Spiderman climbs 15 floors to save mom from fire</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/philly-spiderman-climbs-15-floors-to-save-mom-from-fire-3864258</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/23/3864258/3864258_B83151EA95774B4EA3B91FB0EBC57E4F_190723_3864258_Philly_Spiderman_climbs_15_floors_to_save_mom_fr_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA  A Philadelphia man went full-on Spiderman and climbed up 15 floors just to save his mama  despite having just busted his hip.WPVI reports that on Thursday night, 35-year-old Jermaine got a call from his sister that there was a fire at their mom's high-rise apartment.Most residents evacuated the building, but 65-year-old Sheila, who was bedridden, couldn't get out of her 15th floor flat.A worried Jermaine rushed to the scene and tried to get in through the front door, but police wouldn't let him in.So despite falling and cracking his hip earlier that day, he ran out back and began climbing up the building with a pair of wire cutters  buoyed by adrenaline and sheer determination, and fully intending to bust his mom out.After arriving at his mother's balcony though, she told him she was okay, and that the fire was contained, so he just scaled back down the building. You know, as you do.Despite being sure he'd be arrested as soon as he got back to solid ground, the cops were actually nice enough to let him go.The firefighters eventually put out the flames, and except for four civilians and three firefighters who were treated for smoke inhalation, everyone made it out a-ok.The video of Jermaine coming down the building is making the rounds online, and everyone and their mother is just slack jawed with amazement. Might be a stretch to say he's now everyone's favorite superhero, but the man is definitely the frontrunner for Son of the Year.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/059/AB8/059AB8C619AB82AF24C5C556644BD280.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>102</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>man climbs building</Tag>
          <Tag>man scales building</Tag>
          <Tag>spiderman</Tag>
          <Tag>philadelphia spiderman</Tag>
          <Tag>spidey</Tag>
          <Tag>burning building</Tag>
          <Tag>building on fire</Tag>
          <Tag>apartment fire</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>New Top Gun movie removes
Japanese &amp; Taiwanese flags</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-top-gun-movie-removes%0Ajapanese--taiwanese-flags-3864192</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/23/3864192/3864192_94EB01D44D4C4C98BC230DAACB12FB1B_190723_3864192_New_Top_Gun_movie_removes_Japanese___Taiwanese_f_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Hawk-eyed viewers detected something amiss in the new Top Gun trailer, 'Maverick's' bomber jacket, specifically its patch arrangement.The trailer for the upcoming sequel of the classic 1986 action film, due to be released in 2020, saw Cruise's character sporting his signature leather bomber, but this time, both Japanese and Taiwanese flags had been removed.The Japan Times reported on the sequel, titled Top Gun: Maverick, which was co-produced by Chinese company, Tencent Pictures, a film distributor and production company. The involvement of Tencent has some fans speculating whether or not Xi's Communist Beijing had a hand in the removal of both flags. The change in the patch was seen by many on social media as a move to propitiate and satisfy a Chinese audience that might feel uneasy having to endure the flags of enemies Japan and Taiwan. Others saw the move as an overruling by China's Communist Party, which, to put it simply, would have the last word over any projects Tencent invests in, therefore banishing any mention of the two nations. The report continued by identifying China as one of the biggest film markets in the world.According to a prediction by Deloitte, China will overtake North America in box office revenue and the number of movie-goers by 2020, becoming the largest film market in the world.China has also become the main consumer of American-made movies, resulting in Beijing managing how China is represented in movies Americans produce and see, pushing for it to be represented in a more peaceful and less threatening manner.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8A8/E97/8A8E975CBF0DB8CF2B57C4E2C77E7BDC.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>103</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Entertainment</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Top Gun 2</Tag>
          <Tag>Top Gun Maverick</Tag>
          <Tag>Japanese and Taiwanese flags removed from Top Gun 2</Tag>
          <Tag>viewers spot missing flags from Top Gun remake</Tag>
          <Tag>Top Gun remake removes Japanese and Taiwanese flags</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 08:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Police use tear gas as Hong Kong extradition protests turn violent</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/police-use-tear-gas-as-hong-kong-extradition-protests-turn-violent-3864045</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/23/3864045/3864045_2A00A5F355A145459079BD25CD7AA5E3_190723_3864045_Police_use_tear_gas_as_Hong_Kong_extradition_pro_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Demonstrators and police clashed violently Sunday as tens of thousands took to the streets of Hong Kong to protest for the seventh consecutive weekend.According to CNN, the Sunday march in Hong Kong began peacefully. But protesters continued past the police-designated end point in Wan Chai to the Chinese government's Liaison Office. There, they threw eggs, spray-painted messages on the wall and splattered blank ink on the Chinese national emblem.The Associated Press and CNN report that riot police later threw tear gas canisters and used rubber bullets to disperse protesters, most of whom retreated.Footage posted on social media also showed chaos at the Yuen Long MTR station, as masked assailants dressed in white assaulted commuters, protesters, journalists and even a lawmaker with bamboo sticks.CNN reports that 45 people were hospitalized following the violent incident.According to the BBC, Sunday's demonstrations were put on edge following a Friday night raid, during which police found TATP explosives, petrol bombs and weapons, as well as pro-independence protest materials and leaflets. A man was arrested at the site. Two others connected to the find have also been taken in.The next day, a counter-rally was held to support the city's police force and condemn violence. More than a hundred thousand were in attendance, reports the Associated Press, many of them pro-China supporters.Protests in Hong Kong began last month to oppose a controversial extradition bill that would have allowed accused residents to stand trial in mainland China.Chief Executive Carrie Lam has since suspended the bill, but protesters are dissatisfied with this resolution. According to CNN, they are calling for her to formally withdraw the bill and also to resign from her post.Other demands from protest movement include direct voting rights for all Hong Kong residents, dropping charges against anti-extradition bill protesters, removing the characterization of a clash between protesters and police as a "riot," and dissolving the Legislative Council.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C25/7B7/C257B7562301060E4943C24645318697.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>153</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong protests</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong extradition protest</Tag>
          <Tag>hk protests</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong extradition</Tag>
          <Tag>china extradition</Tag>
          <Tag>no to china extradition</Tag>
          <Tag>tear gas</Tag>
          <Tag>counter rally</Tag>
          <Tag>yuen long</Tag>
          <Tag>yuen long mtr</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 03:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Iran seizes British-flagged oil tanker in the Strait of Hormuz</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/iran-seizes-british-flagged-oil-tanker-in-the-strait-of-hormuz-3864036</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/23/3864036/3864036_4AAF256FF364430E96E5131272FEB86C_190723_3864036_Iran_seizes_British_flagged_oil_tanker_in_the_St_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[STRAIT OF HORMUZ  Iran has seized a British navy vessel in the Gulf region amid rising tensions between the two nations.According to an audio recording obtained by the U.K., Britain's Stena Impero tanker was in the Strait of Hormuz on July 19 when an Iranian patrol vessel issued a radio instruction telling it to alter its direction.Iranian authorities claimed the vessel was violating maritime rules by using an exit lane to enter the Strait, and said that they want to inspect the ship for security reasons.Reuters cited a British letter to the U.N. Security Council as saying that Britain's HMS Montrose then contacted the Iranian vessel in order to prevent the Iranians from boarding the ship. The HMS Montrose warned that they would be violating international law by boarding the tanker unlawfully.Footage obtained by Reuters shows masked Iranian Revolutionary Guards seizing the Stena Impero by descending from helicopters, similar to how British authorities captured an Iranian tanker a few weeks ago.The ship consisted of 23 crew members who were not British citizens, Reuters reports.The footage also showed the tanker  with an Iranian flag hoisted on top  docked in an Iranian port.Britain called the act 'hostile' but have yet to take action against Iran. Foreign Secretary Jeremy Hunt said in a statement that while the move was "unacceptable," their priority is to "de-escalate the situation."According to Sky News, Iran has suggested that its actions were a response to the UK detaining its oil tanker on July 4, with a spokesperson for Iran's Guardian Council saying "the rule of reciprocal action is well-known in international law."Sanam Vakil, a senior research fellow in the Middle East North Africa Program at London's Chatham House, told CNN that Iran's behavior is designed to show it can push back. But, she says, this dangerous strategy could backfire and instead push the U.K. and the U.S. to develop closer ties and increase coordination.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6AC/9B4/6AC9B4793CB149731ED3DCECECB79CB2.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>124</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>iran vs uk</Tag>
          <Tag>iran</Tag>
          <Tag>UK</Tag>
          <Tag>strait of hormuz</Tag>
          <Tag>british marines</Tag>
          <Tag>iran</Tag>
          <Tag>HMS Montrose</Tag>
          <Tag>british royal navy</Tag>
          <Tag>Stena Impero</Tag>
          <Tag>gulf tanker crisis</Tag>
          <Tag>Iranian revolutionary guards</Tag>
          <Tag>uk and iran news</Tag>
          <Tag>tension between uk and iran</Tag>
          <Tag>iran seizes tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>iran seized british ship</Tag>
          <Tag>iran seizes british tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>iran seize ship</Tag>
          <Tag>stena impero</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 03:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Activists protest against Hawaii's plan to build a giant telescope</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/activists-protest-against-hawaii-s-plan-to-build-a-giant-telescope-3864012</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/23/3864012/3864012_CD0800F64FD74136B290F5D5B03708F6_190723_3864012_Activists_protest_against_Hawaii_s_plan_to_build_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MAUNA KEA, HAWAII  Hundreds have gathered to protest the Thirty Meter Telescope project, which is planned to be built on the summit of Mauna Kea on Hawaii's Big Island. The ongoing protests began on July 15.Mauna Kea already has 13 telescopes built on its land, according to the BBC.Some native Hawaiians consider Mauna Kea's summit to be sacred and are against the construction of what would be one of the largest telescopes in the world.The Thirty Meter Telescope's primary mirror would be 30 meters wide. This would be three times as wide as the world's largest visible light telescope.According to the project's website, the telescope would be 200 times more sensitive in detecting objects, stars and other exoplanets in the universe, compared to existing ground-based telescopes and small telescopes in space.Scientists chose Mauna Kea's summit as an ideal location for the telescope for its clear skies and low atmospheric water vapor.Researchers plan to use the telescope to study the properties of distant supernovae to gain a better understanding of how dark energy and dark matter were involved in the evolution of our universe. Scientists also plan to use the telescope to study the links between black holes and their host galaxies.Hawaiian Governor David Ige announced on July 10 that construction on the summit was to begin on July 15.However, around 2,000 activists have since blocked Mauna Kea Access Road to the summit in a bid to prevent construction on the site, while 34 have been arrested.Those protesting say they are fighting for their families and to protect sacred land and culture, Hawaii News Now reports.Some Native Hawaiians believe the summit is a place of worship and prayer and considered it "kapu"  or forbidden.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FEE/CA9/FEECA9EFEDE703C47FD904D30E09B96C.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>120</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Mauna Kea</Tag>
          <Tag>mauna kea protest</Tag>
          <Tag>mauna kea protest 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>mauna kea telescope</Tag>
          <Tag>mauna kea telescope protest</Tag>
          <Tag>mauna kea telescope news</Tag>
          <Tag>hawaii giant telescope</Tag>
          <Tag>thirty meter telescope</Tag>
          <Tag>thirty meter telescope news</Tag>
          <Tag>thirty meter telescope protest</Tag>
          <Tag>thirty meter telescope (tmt)</Tag>
          <Tag>thirty meter telescope hawaii</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 02:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>South Korea fires 360 warning shots at intruding Russian plane</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/south-korea-fires-360-warning-shots-at-intruding-russian-plane-3864846</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/24/3864846/3864846_9DE762FFFEA84D86ADF1D8185F02E540_190724_3864846_South_Korea_fires_360_warning_shots_at_intruding_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[EAST SEA  Warplanes from four different countries were involved in an unprecedented confrontation over the East Sea.According to South Korean officials, two Chinese H-6 and two Russian TU-95 bombers conducted a joint Russian-Chinese military exercise on Tuesday morning.CNN reports that the four planes entered South Korea's Air Defence Identification Zone or KADIZ at about 8:40 a.m., and remained for 24 minutes.Seoul claims a Russian A-50 plane then flew beyond the KADIZ and entered airspace over the contested islands claimed by both South Korea and Japan.The plane flew over the islands, known to the Koreans as Dokdo and the Japanese as Takeshima, at 9:09 and then again at 9:33 a.m.In response, South Korea deployed F-15F and KF-16 fighter jets, which fired 10 flares and 80 warning shots the first time then 10 flares and 280 more rounds during the second.Russia's Defense Ministry initially denied the reports and accused the Korean pilots of unprofessional maneuvers, but later confirmed that their jets had taken part in a joint patrol with China.The BBC reports that Japan later confirmed that its military also sent fighter jets in response to the "Russian incursion."It has since lodged a strong protest against both the Russian and South Korean over what it regards as a violation of its airspace.CNN reports that South Korea has since dismissed Japan's protest, but have themselves sent a strong message of complaint to the Russians over the incident. Moscow has yet to respond to either country.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A76/1C8/A761C870DD8B3414E75763FDE5CC0CD1.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>102</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Asian confrontation</Tag>
          <Tag>South Korea vs Russia</Tag>
          <Tag>Russian intrusion</Tag>
          <Tag>Russian incursion</Tag>
          <Tag>South Korea warning shots</Tag>
          <Tag>South Korea warplanes</Tag>
          <Tag>south korean fighters</Tag>
          <Tag>Dokdo</Tag>
          <Tag>Takeshima</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 11:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Huawei's Czech unit collected personal data for Chinese embassy</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/huawei-s-czech-unit-collected-personal-data-for-chinese-embassy-3864770</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/24/3864770/3864770_D56AC6884C8547748FC471264162557F_190724_3864770_Huawei_s_Czech_unit_collected_personal_data_for__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[PRAGUE  A new investigative report has revealed that former Huawei employees in the Czech Republic routinely collected and shared sensitive client data with Chinese government officials.Two former managers at the Czech unit of Chinese telecom giant Huawei told Czech public radio that they had to enter people's personal details into an internal database, separate from commercial data.This included details like number of children, personal interests, and financial situation.One manager said access to the information stored in the Customer Relationship Management system or CRM is managed from the company's headquarters in China.""It was also standard practice for Huawei employees to share the information they gathered at meetings with Chinese embassy officials.The second employee claimed they had to gather information on state officials, mainly department directors or deputy ministers, who would then be invited to a conference or a trip to China.In response to the allegations, Huawei provided a written statement stating it was in compliance with General Data Protection Regulation rules that protect EU citizens' privacy.However, the Czech National Cyber and Information Security Agency had warned in December 2018 that Chinese laws require companies headquartered in China to cooperate with intelligence services.Huawei has repeatedly denied working with the Chinese government, but according to Radio Praha, an employee was arrested in Poland early this year on suspicion of spying.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CDB/8DB/CDB8DB4659F3F616B618C204DC30FCA6.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>84</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>huawei</Tag>
          <Tag>czech huawei</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese government</Tag>
          <Tag>huawei spies</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese government spies</Tag>
          <Tag>huawei personal data</Tag>
          <Tag>chinese embassy</Tag>
          <Tag>czech republic</Tag>
          <Tag>radiozurnal</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 09:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Russian next-generation missile defense system ahead of schedule</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-next-generation-missile-defense-system-ahead-of-schedule-3864757</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/24/3864757/3864757_651CFF2184BA4106A5A3585A47705156_190724_3864757_Russian_next_generation_missile_defense_system_a_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Russia's next generation missile defense system could be delivered sooner than expected, according to recent statements given by defense conglomerate Rostec and Russian Minister of Industry and Trade Denis Manturov to Russian media, the National Interest reports.Russia's S-500 missile defense system will consist of a long-range radar that tracks the target, a command vehicle that identifies the target and coordinates the missile launch, a launcher and an engagement radar that helps guide the missile. The system fires two missiles per target.Website Army Recognition cites Russian sources as saying that the S-500 is an advanced version of the S-400.The defense system will have a detection range of up to 800 kilometers, an intercept range of up to 600 kilometers and a maximum intercept altitude of up to 200 kilometers, according to Global Security.org.The S-500 can target intercontinental ballistic missiles, hypersonic cruise missiles and aircraft."The defense system will be capable of intercepting aircraft or missiles directly with two missiles: the 77N6-N and 77N6-N1, according to Army Recognition. These missiles will reportedly be able to hit targets flying at speeds of up to 7 kilometers per second.Rostec CEO Sergei Chemezov told Russia's Interfaks news agency that the first units will go into service with the Russian army in 2027, according to a report cited by the National Interest.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E03/4D6/E034D6DA62C8D473FE2F33AB8CF1F0CA.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>96</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>russia</Tag>
          <Tag>russia missile defense system</Tag>
          <Tag>s-500 missile defense system</Tag>
          <Tag>s-500 missile defense system russia</Tag>
          <Tag>russian missile system</Tag>
          <Tag>russia new missile defense system</Tag>
          <Tag>s 500 air defense missile system</Tag>
          <Tag>Russian military missile defense system</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Norway's semi-submersible fish pens to operate by 2020</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/norway-s-semi-submersible-fish-pens-to-operate-by-2020-3864689</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/24/3864689/3864689_5D1FD80EB67A4EAD9DF2C4F47DEBB208_190724_3864689_Norway_s_semi_submersible_fish_pens_to_operate_b_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[NORWAY  Norway Royal Salmon is all set to build a remote-controlled fish pen in Arctic waters.The company has unveiled plans to build a semi-submersible fishing farm off the coast of Norway by 2020.The farm consists of a top and bottom section, each with a buoyant pontoon ring supported by 16 columns. More than half the structure will be submerged underwater.According to the project's website, salmon will be grown 10 to 40 meters beneath the surface of the water, to limit exposure to sea lice and algae.They will live in a large net in the bottom section that drapes down 40 meters from the lower pontoon, while a roof net will prevent fish from swimming to the top section.To accommodate the fish, four decompressors will be added in the support columns to create air pockets.The fish farm will also make use of an automatic feeder that would release fish feed underwater one to three times a day.Each column will have camera and oxygen sensors to monitor the salmon. The sensors will transmit data to an onboard server, which is connected by fiber optic cable to a crewed barge 400 meters from the farm, according to IEEE Spectrum.Once the salmon weigh 1.5 kilograms, they will be moved to open ocean pens, where they will remain for 10 to 11 months before being harvested.According to IEEE Spectrum, the fish farm could help meet Norway meet growing demands for salmon as the country's third largest export is salmon.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/04E/0BC/04E0BCE6047896EAD497B06001A2CC57.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>81</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>salmon</Tag>
          <Tag>norwegian salmon</Tag>
          <Tag>offshore farming</Tag>
          <Tag>norway royal salmon</Tag>
          <Tag>fishing farm</Tag>
          <Tag>norway fishing farm</Tag>
          <Tag>norweigian fish farm</Tag>
          <Tag>fish pen</Tag>
          <Tag>salmon farm</Tag>
          <Tag>remote controlled salmon farm</Tag>
          <Tag>arctic offshore farming</Tag>
          <Tag>offshore technology</Tag>
          <Tag>submersible fish farm</Tag>
          <Tag>semi submersible fish farm</Tag>
          <Tag>fishing norway</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 06:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Future Gateway space station will be in a halo orbit around the moon</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/future-gateway-space-station-will-be-in-a-halo-orbit-around-the-moon-3864646</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/24/3864646/3864646_0AA3A436EDE44BC296DC1A95E2286287_190724_3864646_Future_Gateway_space_station_will_be_in_a_halo_o_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SPACE  NASA is planning to build a station for astronauts orbiting the moon, a project known as the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway.According to an ESA press release, the Gateway space station will follow a near-rectilinear halo orbit, or NRHO. Gateway will pass 3,000 kilometers from the lunar surface ant its closest, and 70,000 kilometers at its furthest. One revolution around the moon takes approximately seven days.The ESA reports that a halo orbit is possible due to the gravitational interplay between the Earth and the Moon, which creates a small area of stability or near-stability known as libration or Lagrange points.But as an NRHO isn't entirely stable, the Gateway will require periodic maneuvering to keep it from drifting off-course.The space station is slated for completion in the mid-2020s. NASA calls for launching the power and propulsion module into space in 2022. Two additional launches by 2025 will add habitation, logistics, and airlock functions.According to the ESA, Gateway will serve as a staging post where astronauts can dock and leave their spacecraft, then travel to the lunar surface in a lander.It will also provide them shelter, a place to stock up on fuel and supplies and relay communications, and a base to dispatch crew and robots to the moon.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A55/987/A55987CD7179D6E529762686762B7141.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>106</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>halo orbit</Tag>
          <Tag>gateway space station</Tag>
          <Tag>lunar outpost</Tag>
          <Tag>moon outpost</Tag>
          <Tag>lunar base</Tag>
          <Tag>gateway</Tag>
          <Tag>NASA</Tag>
          <Tag>ESA</Tag>
          <Tag>halo</Tag>
          <Tag>moon base</Tag>
          <Tag>moon mission</Tag>
          <Tag>lunar mission</Tag>
          <Tag>race to the Moon</Tag>
          <Tag>Moon race</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 05:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Dashcam footage shows police chase a 'dinosaur' down the road</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dashcam-footage-shows-police-chase-a-dinosaur-down-the-road-3864605</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/24/3864605/3864605_3AB7FF73A29C488380B9F20790F26926_190724_3864605_Dashcam_footage_shows_police_chase_a__dinosaur___2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[PLYMOUTH, U.K.  Police in Plymouth, Devon burst into hysterics when they witnessed a Saturday night merrymaker running down the street dressed as an 8-foot-tall T-Rex.According to the Plymouth Herald, the officers came across the "dinosaur" near Royal William Yard where they began their pursuit. A bemused onlooker is seen gawping at the T-Rex as it stomps passed her.The Walking with Dinosaurs-worthy dashcam footage ends with the prehistoric reveller knackered and out of breath. Charles Cross Police took to Twitter to share the spectacle and asked for everyone's best "Why did the dinosaur cross the road?" So please, leave your best joke in the comments section and we will pin the best one!]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DA0/B87/DA0B87B6E9C6E2E9AD9833B6E1DC0808.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>73</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Satire</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Devon police chase dinosaur</Tag>
          <Tag>Doyouthinkhesawus</Tag>
          <Tag>Watch as police chase a DINOSAUR down Plymouth street</Tag>
          <Tag>Police in Plymouth Devon burst into hysterics when they witnessed a Saturday night merrymaker running down the street dressed as an 8ft T-Rex</Tag>
          <Tag>dinosaur</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 04:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Decaying tanker near Yemen could trigger massive oil spill</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/decaying-tanker-near-yemen-could-trigger-massive-oil-spill-3865135</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/25/3865135/3865135_CB05759BF37D4DE3A43B5ABD1DFCE19C_190725_3865135_Decaying_tanker_near_Yemen_could_trigger_massive_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[RAS ISA PORT, YEMEN  A discarded tanker off Yemen's coast may trigger one of the largest oil spills ever.Safer, the decaying oil tanker, has been docked at Yemen's Ras Isa port without maintenance since 2015, according to CNN.The ship contains an estimated 1.1 millions barrels of oil, according to U.N. aid chief Mark Lowcock's speech to the U.N. Security Council.He said the U.N. is planning to send a team to assess the tanker within the next two weeks, once they have secured their entry permits.According to the Atlantic Council, crude oil is stored in a storage tank, its airspace needs to be regularly injected with inert gases to keep oxygen levels below 11 percent, otherwise the tank becomes flammable.Doug Weir, research and policy director at the Conflict and Environment Observatory, told CNN there are concerns about an explosion on the Safer. He explained that since the tanker's engines haven't been running, no inert gases are being pumped to stop the build-up of explosive gases.In his speech, Lowcock said that if the tanker explodes, it could pollute the coastline of the Red Sea.The oil spill could reach from Bab el Mandeb to the Suez Canal and as far as the Strait of Hormuz, depending on the water currents and time of the year.He warns that such an incident would be a global disaster, with dire consequences on the environment, shipping lanes and global economy.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/004/A7E/004A7E8DE9A668A08B1E3642D7713C01.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>87</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>oil spill</Tag>
          <Tag>oil tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>abandoned tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>SAFER FSO tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>decaying SAFER FSO tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>yemeni tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>ras isa port</Tag>
          <Tag>decaying safer tanker</Tag>
          <Tag>decaying tanker yemen</Tag>
          <Tag>threat of oil tanker explosion yemen</Tag>
          <Tag>crude oil</Tag>
          <Tag>yemen oil</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 04:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Man travels 1,500 miles to surprise girlfriend, finds her cheating</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-travels-1-500-miles-to-surprise-girlfriend-finds-her-cheating-3865092</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/25/3865092/3865092_A655657DB53349E2A9B9C405642D17A7_190725_3865092_Man_travels_1_500_miles_to_surprise_girlfriend___2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[CHINA  A tweet in Japan has gone viral after sharing the sad story of one man reportedly traveling 1,500 miles to surprise his girlfriend, only to find her with another man. The heartbreaking story that was shared by Twitter user @T_Radiosonde on the 19th of July has been retweeted more than 20,000 times and liked more than 80,000 times. The tweet stated that the romance scandal purportedly took place at a food stall in China.The tweet shared photos displaying the poor guy dressed as a bear mascot standing distraught as the girl he'd allegedly traveled 2,400km to see was in the arms of another man. A final image captures the girl bearhug the guy as he presumable weeps into his rental suit. The details and the incident itself cannot be verified by the tweet alone.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F3/69A/1F369A40AFB1D2975AC7E51D0CC67BB3.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>80</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>man travels 1</Tag>
          <Tag>500 miles to surprise gf</Tag>
          <Tag>finds her cheating</Tag>
          <Tag>man finds girlfirend cheating after travelling 1</Tag>
          <Tag>500 miles</Tag>
          <Tag>man dresses up as bear mascot and travel 1</Tag>
          <Tag>500 miles finds girlfriend cheating</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 03:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>U.S. resumes execution of inmates on federal death row</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-resumes-execution-of-inmates-on-federal-death-row-3865902</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>https://fl4e4kle4v6fhmr5ypjtqhz6oc.gcdn.anvato.net/up-video/717/1E8/7171E812B7E345349CD3AB4A009AD185?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1658770974&amp;Signature=AJUQMefjpBa1blPlO5HoLYidUcdcT9tJ7DVwv76jZqMLCzsYpGlZcvJR%2BxPbLcczn1G0gKBZVfqILTib6hmDZvKzyqbkC7HwhyYyioaghIsfErKYK9aVE5yFEyEDAP49cVQvT8sPvz3AnBrH2SUrXvgF7oEHYnWHEoNIY8C05%2BfQqF9UL3ioa%2BYzpZgzmrByJEL8HcK%2BXz4ZxTswPfXHchEhJ%2ByNQKAfqY8d4ZV0lxH50WFoltGtA0Ej5BWq7yiF8AsUTI68IhfTUoSrZEjpO4H7AG1kN6Pb6RqnBsCWfr0VeaYHdh80Ks6xZh8XJDu3aNkfo4DLp1aQOjb%2BGAdxbg%3D%3D&amp;Expires=1658863742&amp;KeyName=mcpkey1&amp;Signature=E-7kVSP1LthwPABAy4Aq6nOjvcw</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  The U.S. federal government has ordered the reinstatement of the death penalty for the first time in over 16 years.CNN reports that U.S. Attorney General Wiliam Barr has directed the Bureau of Prisons to schedule the execution of five inmates convicted of violent crimes against children and the elderly.The men will be executed in December 2019 and January 2020 at the federal penitentiary in Terre Haute, Indiana.According to the Death Penalty Information Center, capital punishment is currently legal in 29 states. There are 2,673 death row inmates, with California detaining the most.""The federal government also retains the death penalty, and has 62 inmates in federal death row.So far, though, only three federal inmates have been put to death since the reinstatement of the death penalty in 1988.The most recent was in 2003, when Louis Jones was executed for the 1995 kidnapping and murder of 19 year-old army private Tracie McBride.Per Barr's direction, the three-drug procedure previously used in federal executions will be replaced with a single drug, pentobarbital.According to the BBC, pentobarbital is a potent sedative which slows down the body, including nerves in the brain, to the point of death.The New York Times reports while public support for death penalty has been dwindling, President Trump has long been a supporter of it, even declaring last year that drug dealers should be put to death. According to the BBC, he thinks convicted criminals are treated too gently, and given too many chances to appeal their sentences.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/560/164/560164CBF6A4AEF7DB2E59270E536CBA.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>102</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>death penalty</Tag>
          <Tag>capital punishment</Tag>
          <Tag>federal execution</Tag>
          <Tag>US death penalty</Tag>
          <Tag>US capital punishment</Tag>
          <Tag>death row</Tag>
          <Tag>federal death penalty</Tag>
          <Tag>lethal injection</Tag>
          <Tag>executions</Tag>
          <Tag>pentobarbital</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Crazy squirrel on the lam after chewing its way out of carrier</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/crazy-squirrel-on-the-lam-after-chewing-its-way-out-of-carrier-3865858</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/26/3865858/3865858_CB733F6E18814A5D849DF0FD38A5BA8D_190726_3865858_Crazy_squirrel_on_the_lam_after_chewing_its_way__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SANTA CRUZ, CALIFORNIA  The craziness of motherhood isn't just a human thing, apparently. It applies to squirrels, too. Well, this squirrel, anyway.According to the Santa Cruz Sentinel, new mama squirrel Emily has gotten a bad rep for terrorizing anyone who even breathes in the direction of her home tree.She's bitten six people in Live Oak, California in the last two weeks, including one dude who tried to feed her with a potato chip.It took a team of firefighters, an animal service officer, and a wildlife handler to remove the aggressive animal from the neighborhood and place her into a plastic carrier. Nevertheless, mama persisted. She began aggressively chewing holes through the box almost immediately. By the time they got to the animal rescue's driveway, Emily was squeezing herself through the hole she'd chomped through and sprinted to freedom. She's still on the run. KPIX 5 reports that volunteers have been attempting to coax her out of hiding with baby squirrel sounds, but no dice.Her babies, meanwhile, are being cared for at the rescue, where they're being nursed round the clock with squirrel formula.Eventually, the young-uns will be released into the wild. Wildlife-rescue volunteer Frank Schmit says Emily too might soon revert back to her wild ways and avoid human contact. So who knows, maybe mama and her babies will be reunited in the wild.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ED6/CF1/ED6CF1ACBB645ED54333230253872923.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>84</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>crazy squirrel</Tag>
          <Tag>mad squirrel</Tag>
          <Tag>santa cruz squirrel</Tag>
          <Tag>terror squirrel</Tag>
          <Tag>squirrel terrorizing neighborhood</Tag>
          <Tag>squirrel on the run</Tag>
          <Tag>escaped squirrel</Tag>
          <Tag>squirrel on the lam</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 09:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>North Korea launches two short-range missiles into East Sea</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-launches-two-short-range-missiles-into-east-sea-3865761</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/26/3865761/3865761_2ED196510BF74C9F905E906406F86230_190726_3865761_North_Korea_launches_two_short_range_missiles_in_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[WONSAN, NORTH KOREA  South Korea says the North has launched missiles into the sea, amid growing uncertainty about nuclear negotiations between Washington and Pyongyang. According to South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff, North Korea fired two unidentified projectiles from Wonsan on Thursday, at 5:34 and 5:57 a.m.Each flew at least 430 kilometers, at an altitude of 50 kilometers, before landing in the East Sea.Based on the flight range, the projectiles are believed to be the North Korean version of Russia's Iskander ballistic missile. They resembles the two short-range missiles Pyongyang fired in May.Vipin Narang, an associate professor of political science at MIT, told CNN the launch may be a response to the news that joint U.S.-South Korea military exercises will go ahead as planned next month, despite objections from North Korea.CNN reports that the launch came just days after North Korean state media released a photo of leader Kim Jong-un inspecting a submarine under construction, in what may be an attempt to showcase Pyongyang's military capabilities.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/330/81F/33081FF1BDC920F88ED306666B89DDC7.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>75</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>north korea</Tag>
          <Tag>north korea missile test</Tag>
          <Tag>north korea missile launch</Tag>
          <Tag>Kimskander</Tag>
          <Tag>Iskander</Tag>
          <Tag>missile</Tag>
          <Tag>short range missile</Tag>
          <Tag>unidentified projectiles</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 07:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Nickelodeon slime will soon be oozing its way to space</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nickelodeon-slime-will-soon-be-oozing-its-way-to-space-3865655</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/26/3865655/3865655_6E63A7D9294F4760A0B7EDDD395235C5_190726_3865655_Nickelodeon_slime_will_soon_be_oozing_its_way_to_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[SPACE  After decades of sliming people on national TV and award stages, Nickelodeon's iconic green goo is about to ooze its way into space.According to CNN, the slime will be heading up to the International Space Station on a SpaceX Dragon capsule on Wednesday...along with other, less gooey things.90's kids know all too well how fun it was to see losers on Nickelodeon game shows get drenched in a bucket of the stuff. It's probably twice as fun to watch in space.The network says the plan is to slime a couple of astronauts, and then do a couple of experiments. Fancy playing ping-pong with a slime ball? Tossing slime-filled balloons? Making green goo bubbles?Sadly, it's not all fun and games. Nick claims its other purpose is to see how a non-Newtonian fluid behaves in microgravity. Basically, they're trying to educate the children.Which, ok, you do that. Meanwhile, us grownups will be over here eagerly anticipating a space slime-ing. Let's just hope the stuff doesn't come to life.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/484/9D9/4849D955DF9DAD7BDD0DE6959F63BC5C.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>71</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>slime</Tag>
          <Tag>nickelodeon</Tag>
          <Tag>nickelodeon slime</Tag>
          <Tag>slime in space</Tag>
          <Tag>spacex slime</Tag>
          <Tag>green slime</Tag>
          <Tag>green goo</Tag>
          <Tag>ISS</Tag>
          <Tag>international space station</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 05:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ancient temples, relics found in submerged city near Egypt</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ancient-temples-relics-found-in-submerged-city-near-egypt-3865596</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/26/3865596/3865596_644E71DB331B4917808569303D78C436_190726_3865596_Ancient_temples__relics_found_in_submerged_city__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[NILE DELTA, EGYPT  Archaeologists in Egypt have found the ruins of an ancient temple in the underwater city of Heracleion.The sunken remains of Heracleion were first discovered in Egypt's Aboukir Bay in the year 2000, according to Ancient Origins.Egypt's Ministry of Antiquities reports that during a recent two-month expedition, marine archaeologists uncovered part of a completely destroyed temple in the southern canal.The ruins were part of the city's main temple, Amun Garp. Researchers also found the remains of a smaller Greek temple, as well as ancient columns.Bronze and gold coins believed to be from the second, third and fourth century were also uncovered along with ancient pottery and jewelry.Lead researcher of the expedition Franck Goddio explains on his website that the marine research work during the expedition was carried out using devices such as remote operating vehicles and side scan sonars.According to Ancient Origins, Heracleion was submerged nearly 1,200 years ago and is believed to have sunk due to a gradual rise of sea levels and soil liquefaction.Archaeological research in Thonis-Heracleion is currently ongoing, as Goddio estimates only five percent of the lost city has been discovered to date.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/220/7FC/2207FC0002D69BBE90AD5183A2DD98F7.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>86</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>sunken city</Tag>
          <Tag>underwater temple</Tag>
          <Tag>temple ruins</Tag>
          <Tag>sunken temple</Tag>
          <Tag>heracleion</Tag>
          <Tag>thonis heracleion</Tag>
          <Tag>egypt</Tag>
          <Tag>artifacts</Tag>
          <Tag>relics</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient discovery</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient egypt</Tag>
          <Tag>heracleion lost city</Tag>
          <Tag>heracleion underwater city</Tag>
          <Tag>heracleion egypt</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient egyptian discovery</Tag>
          <Tag>ancient city</Tag>
          <Tag>sunken city</Tag>
          <Tag>sunken egyptian city</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 03:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>26,000 people plan to storm Loch Ness to 'find dat big boi'</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/26-000-people-plan-to-storm-loch-ness-to-find-dat-big-boi--3867349</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/29/3867349/3867349_196E58F083984A7A807DDFBDB35AB7CD_190729_3867349_26_000_people_plan_to_storm_Loch_Ness_to__find_d_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[#StormLochNess #Nessie #StormArea51LOCH NESS, SCOTLAND  Inspired by the UFO conspiracy theorists' plan to Storm Area 51, some monster hunters have now set up their own event to search for Scotland's most elusive mythical creature. Over 26,000 people have now signed on to a Facebook event to Storm Loch Ness, the Scottish Highlands lake that's supposedly harboring "dat big boi" Nessie, aka the Loch Ness monster.The event was organized out of California by one Bryan Richards, and is scheduled at 3 a.m. on September 21  exactly one day after the Area 51 gig.The truth seekers are using the foolproof logic that good ole Nessie can't hide from all of 'em. But the Royal National Lifeboat Institution warns that that's probably the least of their problems. Water in the 22-mile-long, 750-meter deep lake is a very chilly 43 degrees Fahrenheit, with waves up to 13 feet high. So sure, Nessie might not be able to hide, but it's not like any of the dying, hypothermic lads and lassies will get to dat big boi, either.Ironically, there's no need to 'storm' Loch Ness, since unlike the super secret, mega-restricted Area 51, the lake is open to the public 24/7.But good on anyone who actually manages to come face-to-face with Nessie and whatever else is lurking in that lake and lives to tell the tale.So far, the Loch Ness monster is the only mythical creature being singled out for now, but we're pretty sure the hunt for Bigfoot or the Yeti can't be far behind.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/92E/A0E/92EA0ECE09E7B1AC677598338C5DE9E4.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>90</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>storm loch ness</Tag>
          <Tag>loch ness monster</Tag>
          <Tag>loch ness</Tag>
          <Tag>storm area 51</Tag>
          <Tag>nessie</Tag>
          <Tag>lochness monster</Tag>
          <Tag>lochness</Tag>
          <Tag>lake monster</Tag>
          <Tag>mythical creature</Tag>
          <Tag>mythical monster</Tag>
          <Tag>find dat big boi</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 10:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Man survives plunge into Carribbean volcano</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-survives-plunge-into-carribbean-volcano-3867211</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/29/3867211/3867211_580DEAFD756B48D5B5E0D6BD57053F31_190729_3867211_Man_survives_plunge_into_Carribean_volcano_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[MOUNT LIAMUIGA, ST. KITTS & NEVIS  A relaxing, week-long honeymoon nearly turned tragic for an Indiana couple, after a frightening tumble down a Caribbean volcano.Clay and Acaimie Chastain were climbing up the peak of Mount Liamuiga when hubby decided he wanted a closer look at the lush greenery in the volcano's crater while Acaimie stayed behind, reports the Indianapolis Star.While climbing down the crater on a rope, it suddenly snapped and sent Clay falling 50 feet down.He was alive, but the fall had given him a severe concussion, cracked vertebra, skull fracture, and loss of hearing in his right ear.Acaimie started screaming and immediately went looking for her husband, first finding his phone and the orange bandana he was wearing before finally spotting him. His wife helped him climb out of the crater and the pair then walked the two miles down the mountain, according to a Facebook post by Clay.Acaimie called 911 when they were halfway down the mountain and paramedics arrived on the scene.The couple took an air ambulance out of the Carribbean island nation and are now back in the U.S. for further treatment, according to a Go Fund Me page for the Chastains.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A66/B7E/A66B7E101B24AE9618B0696CFC079EF2.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>85</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls into volcano</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls volcano crater</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls into crater</Tag>
          <Tag>honeymoon fail</Tag>
          <Tag>honeymoon gone wrong</Tag>
          <Tag>falling in volcano</Tag>
          <Tag>volcano fall down</Tag>
          <Tag>fall off volcano</Tag>
          <Tag>carribean volcano</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls into carribean volcano</Tag>
          <Tag>fall off mount liamuiga</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls in mount liamuiga</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls down volcano</Tag>
          <Tag>man falls down mount liamuiga</Tag>
          <Tag>man goes down volcano</Tag>
          <Tag>mount liamuiga volcano</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gilroy garlic festival shooting leaves three dead</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/gilroy-garlic-festival-shooting-leaves-three-dead-3867854</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>https://fl4e4kle4v6fhmr5ypjtqhz6oc.gcdn.anvato.net/up-video/20E/1D1/20E1D1E7610C448596CA90D17E824583?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1659107431&amp;Signature=GN8K%2FYOvK%2BGoCkqS2s8FqJF1nEB8k6yZRPy6tLmzLGAiSuUKtS7lSEqlHArNkINbVUOIl3tC1fq5P%2BFXuhyEaFBGq4xnOiGDJz8o9WQsCRVei251nc1w8PmUuBkqsaLZRygcYmr%2Fb2R75kcs%2FoAWIjAS53wKnh9kEUeaSrbEj5X0u0tXEsKk8ffLTjJgc%2FvRkJh0YL7WgFetnivTQyvoJ0hK0TF3aIfGF2a9WDwOTnAvlwAATxztrZSs%2FDCu1k6uzpiKDm%2FHqB72X8fgb3GrLehyvdZJMDz2yPkUBWi51Gyjo1XN0wCkEiqezCt%2FA%2Fgmngw9fG%2FVxXBkPrykVB510Q%3D%3D&amp;Expires=1659209341&amp;KeyName=mcpkey1&amp;Signature=DkoTzqtAo2fydVy7c_Q5ZpUF1WU</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[GILROY, CALIFORNIA  Three people are dead and about a dozen injured after a gunman opened fire at an outdoor festival in California on Sunday.The Los Angeles Times reports that according to police, 19-year-old gunman Santino William Legan avoided security checks at the Gilroy Garlic Festival by cutting through a fence in the back area of the venue.The BBC reports that Legan opened fire inside the festival with a WASR-10 semi automatic rifle, injuring at least a dozen people.A six-year-old boy was shot in the back while playing near a bounce house, and later died. A 20-year-old man and a 13-year-old girl were also among the casualties.Three police officers responded within a minute, exchanging gunfire with the suspect and fatally shooting him.The New York Times reports that police have yet to determine a motive for the shooting. There have also been reports of a possible accomplice, though authorities say they are still searching. According to the San Francisco Chronicle, the rifle used in the attack is banned in California. Legan legally purchased it in Nevada in early July.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B4E/6D2/B4E6D2C7D2F175E734E9738015E03DC8.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>71</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>U.S.</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>gilroy garlic festival</Tag>
          <Tag>garlic festival</Tag>
          <Tag>garlic festival shooting</Tag>
          <Tag>garlic festival shooting</Tag>
          <Tag>gilroy attack</Tag>
          <Tag>california gun laws</Tag>
          <Tag>california garlic festival</Tag>
          <Tag>nevada gun laws</Tag>
          <Tag>santino legan</Tag>
          <Tag>santino william legan</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 11:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tear gas, rubber bullets fired during Hong Kong demonstrations</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tear-gas-rubber-bullets-fired-during-hong-kong-demonstrations-3867594</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/30/3867594/3867594_10D8C0B5A713465782588EC5E4711B86_190730_3867594_Tear_gas__rubber_bullets_fired_during_Hong_Kong__2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Tens of thousands of protesters took to the streets over the weekend to continue protesting a widely unpopular bill that would allow suspects to be extradited for trial to mainland China.Opponents of the bill believe that Beijing may use it to extradite political activists, dissidents and other opponents in the city.The Hong Kong government suspended the extradition bill last month in the face of massive protests but has yet to officially withdraw it. The anti-government and pro-democracy protests have been going on for eight consecutive weekends.On Sunday, demonstrators in Hong Kong defied police orders, with one group of protesters marching towards the Causeway Bay shopping area, while the other made their way to China's Liaison Office through the territory's central business district.The activists who made their way to the heavily fortified Chinese office were blocked from entering by riot police, while a clear plastic shield was added to protect a national emblem that had been defaced by protesters on July 1, Reuters reports.As the crowds grew larger, police began firing rounds of tear gas, rubber bullets and sponge grenades, resulting in a cloud of burning smoke.Protesters across the city set up barricades and chanted slogans such as "free Hong Kong" and "reclaim Hong Kong," according to the BBC. The activists have called for greater democracy and for Hong Kong's leader Carrie Lam to resign, CNN reports. They are also pushing for an investigation into alleged police brutality.China's Hong Kong and Macau Affairs Office was to hold a press conference later today to "give its stance and views on Hong Kong's current situation," an announcement for the briefing stated.According to the South China Morning Post, this is the first time the administrative agency has held a briefing on Hong Kong since the city was handed over to China in 1997.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D1D/131/D1D13108A4C22BD712A4404CC5565DE6.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>120</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Asia</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>Hong Kong protests</Tag>
          <Tag>HK protests</Tag>
          <Tag>HK mass protest</Tag>
          <Tag>Hong Kong mass protest</Tag>
          <Tag>Carrie Lam</Tag>
          <Tag>Hong Kong</Tag>
          <Tag>Hong Kong protest 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>Hong Kong protest today</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong protest yuen long</Tag>
          <Tag>hk protests latest news</Tag>
          <Tag>hk protests 2019</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong police protest</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong protest 2019 tear gas</Tag>
          <Tag>hong kong police fire tear gas</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 03:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>American tourists brutally stab Italian police officer 11 times</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/american-tourists-brutally-stab-italian-police-officer-11-times-3867583</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/30/3867583/3867583_F7A08A1091364ED9A21EE6DDE50AE652_190730_3867583_American_tourists_brutally_stab_Italian_police_o_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[ROME  Carabinieri police officer Maria Cerciello Rega has died after he was stabbed by two American tourists in the Prati neighborhood of Rome on Friday, reports the BBC.Citing Italian wire service Ansa, the BBC reported San Francisco teenagers Gabriel Christian Natale-Hjorth, aged 18, and Finnegan Lee Elder, aged 19, snatched a bag from a man after a drug dealer allegedly sold them a fake product.Events unfolded when the bag's owner reported the theft to police. Cerciello Rega and his partner were sent as a ruse in plainclothes to collect the bag in exchange for the American's demand of 100 euros and a gram of cocaine.The Washington Post reported that despite both officers identifying themselves as law enforcement, Elder repeatedly stabbed Cerciello Rega, while Natale-Hjorth punched Cerciello Rega's partner.Ansa reported that during the autopsy it was discovered that Cerciello Rega had been stabbed 11 times, not eight as had previously been reported. The Carabinieri said that on Friday morning officers discovered a large knife, as well as clothes from the night, hidden behind a ceiling panel in the hotel room where Elder and Natale-Hjorth were arrested.According to a police statement, both Natale Hjorth and Elder confessed in the face of "overwhelming evidence" laid before them during police interrogation.Ansa reported that Vice-Brigadier Rega will be buried on July 29th in his hometown of Somma Vesuviana, near Naples. His funeral will be conducted at the same church where he married just 43 days ago.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/262/AE3/262AE3C6A09098610F639C41AB519A49.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>101</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>World</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>U.S tourist stab Itallian police officer</Tag>
          <Tag>U.S teenagers kill Italian policeman</Tag>
          <Tag>American tourists murder Italian police officer</Tag>
          <Tag>Italian police officer killed by American teenage tourists</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 02:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Intermittent fasting could boost weight loss, study finds</title>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/intermittent-fasting-could-boost-weight-loss-study-finds-3867571</link>
    <videoItems>
      <videoItem>
        <videoAddress>http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/30/3867571/3867571_7968F05C43C64C37B4F71228DBDC4963_190730_3867571_Intermittent_fasting_could_boost_weight_loss__st_2600.mp4</videoAddress>
        <videoFiletype>video/mp4</videoFiletype>
        <videoDesc><![CDATA[BATON ROUGE, LOUISIANA  Time-restricted eating, also known as intermittent fasting, may help curb someone's appetite, according to new research in the journal Obesity.Eleven overweight participants took part in the study. They tried two different eating patterns over a four-day period.One group of participants ate over a six-hour period between 8:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. While the second group ate over a 12 hour period between 8:00 a.m. and  8:00 p.m. Those taking part were told to eat the same number of calories every day. On the fourth day of the experiment, the participants were put inside a respiratory chamber. From there, researchers measured their metabolism by checking the amount of calories, carbs, fat and protein burned.According to Today, the researchers also tested to see how hungry or full the participants felt by checking their ghrelin hormones. This is the hormone associated with hunger.The study found that those who were fasting for 18 hours a day had decreased ghrelin levels, lower appetites and increased fullness levels.The study noted that intermittent fasting appeared to induce weight-loss by decreasing the appetite rather than burning more calories.]]></videoDesc>
        <videoCover>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6A9/A34/6A9A3487C72EC9C91D29E4D205445AA8.jpg</videoCover>
        <videoLang>en</videoLang>
        <videoDuration>80</videoDuration>
        <videoCategory>Sci&amp;Tech</videoCategory>
        <videoTags>
          <Tag>TomoNews</Tag>
          <Tag>Satire</Tag>
          <Tag>losing weight</Tag>
          <Tag>intermittent fasting</Tag>
          <Tag>fasting</Tag>
          <Tag>intermittent fasting weight loss</Tag>
          <Tag>intermittent fasting results</Tag>
          <Tag>lose weight fasting</Tag>
          <Tag>health</Tag>
          <Tag>how intermittent fasting could help you lose weight</Tag>
          <Tag>ways to lose weight</Tag>
          <Tag>lose weight</Tag>
          <Tag>dieting</Tag>
          <Tag>key to losing weight</Tag>
        </videoTags>
      </videoItem>
    </videoItems>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 02:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
</rss>
