<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mcp="http://schema.anvato.com/mcp/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>MRSS feed for Verta News</title>
    <link>//api.nm.anvato.net/v2/feed/K5DREWL4E6RRMTRDAIBA?start=0&amp;count=200&amp;filters[]=u_Slug_Dept_s:"DPS_iUS"&amp;filters[]=c_ts_publish_l:[1480435200%20TO%201480521600]&amp;fmt=mrss&amp;media_filters[]=video/mp4</link>
    <description/>
    <item>
      <title>Awesome science: MIT researchers turn spinach plants into bomb detectors</title>
      <description>CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS &#x2014; MIT researchers have modified spinach plants to turn them into bomb detectors.


Explosives such as landmines contain chemical compounds called nitroaromatics. If nitroaromatics are present in groundwater, they are absorbed by the roots of the spinach plant and transported to the leaves in a process called transpiration.


Researchers embedded the spinach plant leaves with molecules called bombolitins that bind to nitroaromatics. They also embedded the leaves with carbon nanotubes, which emit a constant fluorescent signal that serves as a reference, MIT News reported.


An infrared camera then reads these fluorescent signals.


When nitroaromatics are present, the fluorescent signal from the bombolitins decreases. Once the decrease is detected, the device sends a wireless signal to the user.


The experiments were conducted within a distance of 3.3 feet but researchers are confident that the radius can be increased and one sensor could monitor multiple plants, the BBC reported.


The study is published in the journal Nature Materials.</description>
      <tags>MIT,spinach plants detect explosives,spinach detects bombs,bionic spinach,technology,spinach with nanotubes,awesome science</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3220762</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 01:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5B0/895/5B089590E92A4370A50117A81FB79336_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/02/3220762/3220762_0634EA1DFF0F4367B89B776D7D532076_161201_3220762_Awesome_science__MIT_researchers_turn_spinach_pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living on Mars: Space igloos made for Mars show how humans could live on the Red Planet</title>
      <description>MARS &#x2014; The first Mars habitat designed for humans will be unveiled at an exhibition in the United Kingdom on Nov. 10 to tie-in with a National Geographic program that imagines colonists from Earth living on the Red Planet.


The exhibition in London is based on extensive consultations with astronomers from the Royal Observatory Greenwich and How We&#x2019;ll Live on Mars author Stephen Petranek, the Mirror reported.


The dwelling would be constructed with Martian soil, which would be microwaved until it forms a brick. The Martian soil bricks and recycled spacecraft parts would then be used to build an igloo-shaped dome. The walls of the dome would be around 10-feet thick and the entrance would be double air-locked.


The dome could be able to withstand the harsh Martian environment, including extremely low temperatures, micrometeorite impacts, thin atmosphere and cosmic radiation.


The exhibition coincides with the launch of a six-part NatGeo docu-drama called MARS, which tells the story of humans&#x2019; attempt to colonise the Red Planet in the year 2033.</description>
      <tags>Mars home,home on mars,mars house,national geographic mars,natgeo mars,space,mars,mars show,life on mars,space igloo,red planet</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3220697</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 23:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D56/C63/D56C6331360F45FC810CB6075140D83C_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/01/3220697/3220697_0EB61718BB934D72A553C67A0EEDA488_161201_3220697_Living_on_Mars__Space_igloos_made_for_Mars_show__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic crash livestream fail: Man livestreams himself speeding at 115mph and crashes</title>
      <description>PROVIDENCE, RHODE ISLAND &#x2014; Pawtucket man Onasi Olio-Rojas is recovering in the hospital after recklessly livestreaming himself driving his car at 115 mph. He wound up rear-ending a dump truck. 

According to local channel WPRI-12, the 20-year-old was in Providence on Wednesday and driving at speeds of up to 115 miles per hour on U.S. Route 6. He streamed some of that for his buddies to see on Facebook Live. 

This video lasts an entire three minutes. He&#x2019;s not wearing a seatbelt. 

According to reports, Rojas&#x2019;s vehicular mayhem ended when he lost control of the car and started spinning. He rear-ended a garbage truck coming onto the highway before being bounced across the road and into the barrier. 

Firemen rescued him from the car, and he&#x2019;s at a local hospital where he WPRI-12 reported him as being in fair condition. Other outlets reported him as critical.

Police told WPRI-12 that when Rojas recovers he&#x2019;ll be arraigned in hospital, and that the video more or less makes the case against him.</description>
      <tags>video,Epic crash,crash caught on camera,livestream fails,man livestreams speeding,speedster crashes,us route six,reckless driver accident,rhode island</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224027</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 05:43:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EE5/E9E/EE5E9E69EF994625A20B20DC8F4A696A_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/05/3224027/3224027_3E0BBB36EB184D1BB1859668E375E32B_161205_3224027_Epic_crash_livestream_fail__Man_livestreams_hims_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nude photos of more than a hundred young female borrowers leaked on Chinese social media - TomoNews</title>
      <description>BEIJING &#x2014; More than a hundred women are now in a bind after photos of them posing nude were leaked on Chinese social media.

Global Times reports that the racy photos originated from a 10-gigabyte zip file, which also contained videos and the personal information of around 167 women.

Most of the victims were born from 1993 to 1997, often desperate college students who turned to Jiedaibao, an online platform for loans. Shady lenders on the platform took advantage of the situation by not only charging exorbitant interest rates, but also requiring the women send nude pictures of themselves.

The debtors send photos of themselves holding up their ID, or a promissory note, to act as guarantees that they would pay back the money, plus interest.

If they were unable to pay up, the loan sharks would send the nudes to their families, harassing the victims until the debt was paid back.

Authorities have yet to determine who was responsible for the leak, though Jiedaibao denies any involvement. According to them, the nudes constitute a private deal, which they cannot regulate.</description>
      <tags>video,Female debtors,loan sharks,chinese loan shark,chinese debtors,nude photo leak,loan collateral,jiedaibao</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3223847</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 02:03:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/902/106/9021066C012F42418128A0C69E619A68_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/05/3223847/3223847_AF74C2876F694022805FFD24077BAA9A_161205_3223847_Nude_photos_of_more_than_a_hundred_young_female__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mile-High Club: teaching assistant jailed for doing the naughty with teen on airplane</title>
      <description>KINETON, ENGLAND &#x2014; A teaching aid in the UK has been jailed for committing sex acts on a teenage male student during a school trip. 

Last year, Jill Meldrum-Jones, 37, was chaperoning students on a school excursion to South Africa when she took a special interest in a 15-year-old in the class. The two started going for long walks together, which eventually led to an intimate bond. 

Meldrum-Jones first performed a sex act on the young man as they were riding a minibus with all his classmates on board. She then took things a step further by performing oral sex on him, and encouraged him to perform sex acts on her at a secluded spot where they could be alone.

Their relationship reached a high point during the 10-hour flight back to England, where Meldrum-Jones masturbated the boy three times, and performed oral sex on the boy three times as well. 

When rumors began to spread in February, the married mother of two was caught when her phone records revealed highly-sexualized text messages to the boy following the trip. This week, she pleaded guilty to seven charges of sexual activity with a child and inciting sexual activity.

For her crimes, she has been sentenced to 32 months in jail.</description>
      <tags>video,Coventry Crown Court,Jill Meldrum-Jones,kineton police,warwickshire,teacher sex,student teacher,teacher student,mile high club</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3223726</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 23:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AAE/558/AAE55836713344B0B46D17783B5E5D55_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/04/3223726/3223726_988E43DCE7A743DF9382FDE0A843C2FC_161204_3223726_Mile_High_Club__teaching_assistant_jailed_for_do_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trumps talks with Taiwan president: Tsai Ing-wen calls Donald, Western media flips out</title>
      <description>NEW YORK &#x2014; President-elect Donald Trump spoke with Taiwanese president Tsai Ing-wen on Friday in a major departure from decades of U.S. policy in Asia. 


Trump tweeted last Friday, &#x201C;The President of Taiwan CALLED ME today to wish me congratulations on winning the Presidency. Thank you!&#x201D;


About and hour later, he then tweeted, &#x201C;Interesting how the U.S. sells Taiwan billions of dollars of military equipment but I should not accept a congratulatory call.&#x201D;


During an approximately 10 minute phone call, Tsai and Trump talked about improving Taiwan&#x2019;s economy and strengthening its defense. 


Tsai expressed hope the U.S. and Taiwan would &#x201C;establish a closer cooperative relationship.&#x201D;


Trump also congratulated Tsai on her election win earlier this year. 


Whether or not Trump intentionally or unknowingly set off this latest diplomatic crap storm, it&#x2019;s a good thing for Taiwan. 


As for how China is going to react and what they&#x2019;re going to say &#x2014; who cares?</description>
      <tags>Trump Tsai Ing-wen,Trump Taiwan call,Trump Taiwan tweet,Taiwanese president Tsai Ing-wen,Taiwan Tsai Ing-wen,Taiwan US arms sales,Trump Tsai call</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3223652</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 22:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>98</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/425/0D0/4250D0A8BAB242DFA37E1ACF45DD8D74_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/04/3223652/3223652_A71A295A3F004EA8BAEEDADA29EB3449_161204_3223652_Trumps_talks_with_Taiwan_president__Tsai_Ing_wen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleazy car salesman borrows customer&#x2019;s phone and secretly sends out nude pics of his wife</title>
      <description>GRAPEVINE, TEXAS &#x2014; A young couple in Frisco are fighting for justice after a sleazy car salesmen undermined their privacy in the creepiest of ways.

In January 2015, Pastor Tim Gatreaux and his wife, Claire, walked into a Texas Toyota dealership looking to pick up a Prius. With the deal almost done, the salesman assisting them asked to borrow Tim&#x2019;s phone so he could show his manager a pre-approved financing document saved on an app.

Little did the couple realize, the salesman then snuck away to take a quick second to scroll through the photos on the pastor&#x2019;s phone. When he stumbled upon a few sexy nude photos of the pastor&#x2019;s wife getting in and out the bathtub, he secretly emailed them out to a swinger&#x2019;s website.

The dirtbag then returned the phone, and sent the couple to the dealership&#x2019;s finance manager to finalize the paperwork. But when Pastor Tim went into his phone to pull up a document, an old photo of his wife popped up. When he checked his inbox, the email of his wife&#x2019;s naked pics had been deleted, but a record of the email was saved in another app on his phone. The email in question was sent to an address that had a connection to a swingers website.

The salesman, Matthew Luke Thomas, 44, was arrested on charges of computer security breach in November 2015. He will appear in court later this month. Meanwhile, the Gatreauxs are suing Thomas, Texas Toyota of Grapevine and Toyota Motor North America for several grievances including breach of contract, intrusion, negligence and public disclosure of private facts.</description>
      <tags>video,Sleazy car salesman,toyota,grapevine toyota,matthew luke thomas,toyota motor north america,Claire Gautreaux,Tim Gautreaux,pastor Tim Gautreaux,grapevine police</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224217</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 09:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1C9/D10/1C9D100C11F645078FD066082F32410D_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/05/3224217/3224217_9B40EB519CEA40BBB8501497249D0B63_161205_3224217_Sleazy_car_salesman_borrows_customer___s_phone_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man fights kangaroo: Aussie dude punches kangaroo in the face after it attacks his dog</title>
      <description>AUSTRALIA &#x2014; New footage of a fight online is being billed as the most Australian thing on the internet &#x2013; a man going toe to toe with a wild kangaroo, to save his pet dog.


On June 15, a group of buddies set out on a hunting trip to show their dying friend, Kailem, one last good time before he passed away from cancer. The men travelled deep into the bush of the outback, searching for a massive wild boar.


Their dogs ran ahead of them, as the hounds are trained to pick up the scent of the pigs, while steering clear of kangaroos. Unfortunately, one of the dogs got too close to a tall buck kangaroo, who wasted no time grabbing hold of the canine. 


Realizing his dog was in danger, the dog&#x2019;s owner, Greig Tonkins, ran out to the rescue, ready to go toe-to-toe with the menacing marsupial. The dog happened to be wearing a protective vest, designed to protect him from the sharp tusks of a wild boar. Luckily, it shielded him from the nasty claws of the &#x2018;roo, too, which can cut through flesh. However, Greig Tonkins ran in unprotected, and one steady kick to the gut from the kangaroo could have injured him severely.


As Tonkins ran toward the two, the dog was able to break free. Suddenly, Greig Tonkins found himself face to face with the kangaroo, so he put his fists up in a fighting stance. The battle lasted all of one punch, a sweeping right bare-knuckle fist to the kangaroo&#x2019;s mouth. The roo, shaken up, took a moment to reconcile what had happened, and seconds later, he bounded off into the distance. 


Media reports following the viral circulation of the video indicate Greig Tonkins also happens to be a professional zookeeper at Taronga&#x2019;s Western Plains Zoo in Dubbo.</description>
      <tags>video,Kangaroo fight,kangaroo dog fight,kangaroo dog play,man punches kangaroo,kangaroo fights man,man fights kangaroo</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224720</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 03:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C7B/EBD/C7BEBD710A60402292F710F3A9DCC471_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3224720/3224720_D42740613C454EF1BA99F8B7BE936F40_161206_3224720_Man_fights_kangaroo__Aussie_dude_punches_kangaro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland warehouse fire: At least 33 dead after deadly blaze rages through Ghostship - TomoNews</title>
      <description>OAKLAND, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; At least 33 people are dead and many more unaccounted for, after a fire raged through a party in Oakland, California on Friday.


The San Francisco Chronicle reports that dozens of people were at a music party on the second floor of the Ghostship warehouse when the fire broke out.


Flames spread quickly throughout the structure &#x2014; an artist space and residence cluttered with art and wooden furniture. The building wasn&#x2019;t up to code and had no sprinklers or smoke detectors installed inside, reports the East Bay Times.


Survivors describe going down a rickety staircase made of wooden pallets, with smoke obscuring their sight halfway down. The first floor was a labyrinth, subdivided into rooms and similarly packed wall-to-wall with wooden artwork.


Some crawled blindly on the floor, trying to find a way out while choking on the thick smoke. The few who made it out reportedly did so with the help of a man yelling by the exit.


Many others remained trapped inside and likely perished in the blaze, which continued to burn for about five hours.


Authorities are still combing through the wreckage and are still looking into the cause of the fire.</description>
      <tags>video,Oakland warehouse fire,oakland ghostship fire,oakland fire,oakland ghostship,artists collective,fire hazard,deadly fire</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224705</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 03:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/178/DD4/178DD49FE0E4467F97A9BBE295AE96CC_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3224705/3224705_E11079178B8B43A39A9B8F185D0299D0_161206_3224705_Oakland_warehouse_fire__At_least_33_dead_after_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher sex scandal: engaged teacher busted for sex with teen student on park bench - TomoNews</title>
      <description>PLANO, TEXAS &#x2014; A young Dallas-area teacher has been arrested for knocking boots with one of her pupils. 

Alaina Ferguson, 23,  briefly taught algebra from September to October 2016. When a 16-year-old student handed in a test paper with his Snapchat username scribbled on the page, a sexual relationship soon followed. 

The two began communicating back and forth online, and reports indicate the naughty teacher also sent the young man some nude photos. What began as texting quickly escalated to having sex on a park bench. That encounter then led to a game of beer pong and more sex at Miss Ferguson&#x2019;s fianc&#xE9;&#x2019;s apartment while he was out of town. The two later had sex in the back of a pickup truck after a school football game.

Having taught at the school only a couple of months, Miss Ferguson decided to quit her job in October, but continued having sex with the teen in November. When rumors started to swirl at Plano Senior High, Miss Ferguson was arrested by police. Her wedding was also called off, and the arrest warrant noted that she told the student &#x201C;she knew it was not the right thing to do, but it felt right at the time. And that she was going to break it off with her fianc&#xE9; because she didn&#x2019;t feel anything with him.&#x201D;

Miss Ferguson was released on $100,000 bond, and has to wear an electronic monitoring device. She&#x2019;s also not allowed to use the internet, and was forced to deactivate her social media accounts.</description>
      <tags>video,Teacher sex,student teacher sex,teacher student sex,sex scandal,Alaina Ferguson,plano texas,plano senior high</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224687</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 02:48:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5FC/156/5FC15677EFD647E29119EE6B9B24A53A_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3224687/3224687_A53886C260734E8D9013F31CA311A73E_161206_3224687_Teacher_sex_scandal__engaged_teacher_busted_for__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal cruelty: New Jersey teen throws cat from third-floor balcony, feline survives</title>
      <description>NEWARK, NEW JERSEY &#x2014; A cat defied death last Thursday after it survived a 24 feet fall after being thrown from a third-floor balcony by a teenager in New Jersey.


Tikeemah Lassiter, aged 19, from Clinton, New Jersey was visiting her relatives in Newark on Thursday. She said the cat was bothering her because it kept entering the room, so she decided to do something about it. 


In the video, Lassiter can be seen picking up the cat and lobbing it from balcony. The person filming her can be heard laughing.

The cat bounced once and then didn&#x2019;t move when it hit the pavement below. The woman filming the video can be heard laughing and saying, &#x201C;Really?! It&#x2019;s dead?! Is it dead?&#x201D;

According to NJ.com, Lassiter was arrested on Saturday and charged with animal cruelty. New Jersey Transit Police said she also had an unrelated $10,000 warrant out for her arrest for an assault. It&#x2019;s unknown if the person who recorded the video was also charged.

The cat miraculously survived with only injuries to its paws. It was examined by a veterinarian and stayed with the vet on Sunday. It&#x2019;s unlikely the cat will be returned to the apartment, a spokesperson for the New Jersey Society for Prevention of Cruelty to Animals told NJ.com.</description>
      <tags>video,Animal cruelty,animal abuse,throw cat,cat abuse,Tikeemah Lassiter,girl throws cat out</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224651</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 02:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DDF/EE2/DDFEE26BD5C7484DAB11A5F2E88CD228_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3224651/3224651_777B94D7DF6047E2BC21130958164F3A_161206_3224651_Animal_cruelty__New_Jersey_teen_throws_cat_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standing Rock protests: Army denies construction permit for Dakota Access Pipeline</title>
      <description>STANDING ROCK INDIAN RESERVATION &#x2014; Chalk one up for the Standing Rock Sioux Tribe in its battle against Energy Transfer Partners after the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers said on Sunday it has decided to deny a permit for the construction of a key section of the Dakota Access Pipeline.

The Army said it will not approve an easement necessary to allow the $3.8 billion project to cross under Lake Oahe in North Dakota, which pretty much halts construction on the nearly finished 1,172-mile oil pipeline, the New York Times reported.

Alternative routes will now be explored. The Army Corps says it plans to issue an Environmental Impact Study with &#x201C;full public input and analysis,&#x201D; according to NPR.  

The controversial route has been the subject of months of protest by thousands of indigenous and environmental activists and more recently hundreds of veterans, who have argued that the pipeline threatens a vital, clean water source.   

Amid sweltering heat and blistering cold over the past months, the protesters have endured pepper spray, water cannons and rubber bullets. 

The easement marks a stunning victory for the protesters. Unfortunately, the war is far from over.</description>
      <tags>video,Standing Rock protests,Standing Rock protesters,Army halts Dakota Access Pipeline construction,Energy Transfer Partners,U.S. Army Corps of Engineers,Standing Rock</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225105</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 15:13:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>111</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/943/BF8/943BF8C147C64207B357FA48C8FB23AA_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3225105/3225105_CA73CD12F0E54FB6967AAFA401499346_161206_3225105_Standing_Rock_protests__Army_denies_construction_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upkskirt perv: Taipei store manager caught taking under skirt pics of TV news reporter</title>
      <description>TAIPEI, TAIWAN &#x2014; A television journalist in Taipei was the victim of a pervert trying to take a picture up her skirt, but using the power of the media, she was able to make him pay with a punishment that fit the crime.

Glori Liu, 32, was casually browsing for a refreshing drink in a FamilyMart store last week. Across the aisle, store manager Cheng Hsi-chan, 37, happened to notice her, and some unsavory thoughts started brewing. He decided to act on them, quietly creeping up behind Liu, snapping some shots from under her skirt.

He wasn&#x2019;t as smooth as he needed to be though, and accidently brushed against her thigh, causing her to realize she was being violated.

Luckily for her, she said: &#x201C;He didn't get the shot. He failed but he touched my leg.&#x201D;

Meanwhile, Cheng said, &#x201C;Actually I don't have any excuses for this. I can only say that different people have different ways of dealing with pressure."

Liu decided the best way to expose Cheng was to do a news story telling the world of his unwholesome deed. He was fired from FamilyMart soon after.</description>
      <tags>video,FamilyMart,Family Mart,Glori Liu,Cheng Hsi-chan,upskirt pics,upskirt vid,upskirt photos,&#x5289;&#x5B9C;&#x51FD;,&#x5168;&#x5BB6;&#x4FBF;&#x5229;&#x5546;&#x5E97;</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225665</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 03:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B60/F6D/B60F6D3C9C5C4702A2CBB96E899696F7_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/07/3225665/3225665_7E0CEE2798F04915AA161F108DC3DBEC_161207_3225665_Upkskirt_perv__Taipei_store_manager_caught_takin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant dancer in India shot dead on stage by men not allowed to dance with her</title>
      <description>BATHINDA CITY, INDIA &#x2014; A young pregnant woman&#x2019;s life was cut short on December 3 after she was hit by a stray bullet fired during a wedding celebration in India.

Moments before her death, Kulwinder Kaur, 24, was performing a dance routine on stage with three other women. She and her friends caught the attention of a group of men who wanted to dance with them. They attempted to get on stage to do so.

Unfortunately for the men, they were refused by security and escorted away from the stage area. They weren&#x2019;t too thrilled about being rejected, so they decided to grab some guns and fire shots into the air, as some have been known to do at Indian weddings. One of the men, Lucky Goyal, was shooting with a long gun, from which a stray bullet struck Kulwinder Kaur on stage. 

Kulwinder crumpled to the ground. She was rushed to the hospital, but died along the way. Her husband claims she was midway through her first trimester of pregnancy. Meanwhile, the four men have been arrested and are now facing charges for her untimely death.</description>
      <tags>video,Kulwinder Kaur,lucky goyal,Shiromani Akali Dal,Sanju Goyal,Jagsir Singh,Narinder Kumar,pregnant dancer shot,pregnant dancer killed,pregnant woman shot,indian wedding</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225508</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 01:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/172/329/1723293E39DF482697C8025D1DC694F4_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/07/3225508/3225508_3D6EABC806B94B038678793FF8C0544B_161207_3225508_Pregnant_dancer_in_India_shot_dead_on_stage_by_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbulence in flight: Several passengers thrown out of seats on Qatar Airways flight</title>
      <description>LAJES TERCEIRA ISLAND, PORTUGAL &#x2014; It was a rough ride for 300 people flying from Washington, D.C. to Doha, Qatar on state-owned Qatar Airways this Sunday. 

It all started when a passenger began suffering what was initially believed to be a heart attack. This prompted the captain to divert mid-flight to a Portuguese military base on the Azores for an emergency landing.

During this diversion, the plane reportedly hit severe turbulence upon descent. The plane apparently dropped so steeply, it threw people out of their seats. According to the Aviation Herald, a 3-year-old boy was sent flying across the aisle onto another passenger&#x2019;s lap. 

Several passengers also hit the ceiling, and some were left bleeding. One passenger broke a leg while others received minor injuries. 

Three received treatment at a local hospital and the heart attack that led to the diversion ended up not being a heart attack at all.</description>
      <tags>video,Flight turbulence,turbulence injuries,plane turbulence,passengers injured turbulence,qatar airways,lajes,azores,portugal</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225489</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 01:31:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/419/083/419083B14625471DB8C5038521EA31BE_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/07/3225489/3225489_AF9D770A57A341F68EDBF2D9614B1255_161207_3225489_Turbulence_in_flight__Several_passengers_thrown__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake US embassy in Ghana illegally issued visas for over 10 years</title>
      <description>ACCRA, GHANA &#x2014; The U.S. State Department recently uncovered a criminal operation in Ghana that had been passing off a ramshackle building in the capital as the country&#x2019;s official embassy.


The sham embassy was housed in a battered pink building with a U.S. flag. With white people manning the inside and a photo of Obama on the wall, most assumed it was legit.


According to a U.S. Department of State statement, the consular officers were Turkish citizens who spoke English and Dutch and were working with organized Ghanaian crime rings. Instead of getting clients nearby, they advertised via flyers and billboards to customers in remote parts of West Africa.


Clients were shuttled to the city, booked at a nearby hotel and taken to and from the fake embassy, which was open three mornings a week. Walk-ins were not accepted.


For a fee of $6,000, applicants could be issued fraudulently obtained but legitimate U.S. visas, or any other false identification documents they needed.


The scheme went on for a decade until the real U.S. embassy caught on, leading to the arrest of several suspects via police raid. Some others were able to escape, but authorities have already gotten warrants and are planning to pursue them.


More than a hundred passports, legitimate and counterfeit visas and documents were also found in the investigation, along with the discovery of another fake embassy &#x2014; this one for the Netherlands.</description>
      <tags>video,Fake us embassy,fake embassy,us embassy ghana,us visa,us embassy accra,embassy accra,embassy ghana,illegal visa,fake visa,fake documents</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225438</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 00:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C67/ACC/C67ACC677A47445EB04A135323038B31_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/07/3225438/3225438_D1E5569EA5EE4C9BAB4EC77BC7961CB8_161207_3225438_Fake_US_embassy_in_Ghana_illegally_issued_visas__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pizzagate shooting: Armed man storms DC pizzeria to bust bogus Clinton child sex ring</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; Conspiracy theories seem harmless until one dude decides to take matters into his own hands and show up with a weapon &#x2014; which is exactly what this North Carolina man did.

Edgar Maddison Welch targeted DC pizzeria Comet Ping Pong, the restaurant at the center of &#x201C;Pizzagate,&#x201D; one of the internet&#x2019;s most prevalent fake news stories.

According to the theory, leaked emails from Clinton campaign chairman John Podesta point to a child prostitution ring operating under the pizza joint, which is run by none other than HRC herself.

Welch read the story online and was convinced the story was real. So convinced, that he decided to arm himself with an AR-15 assault rifle and a pistol and trek all the way to the capital to, as he told police, &#x201C;self-investigate the rumors&#x201D; and rescue the poor child sex slaves, the Washington Post reports.

Around 3 p.m. on Sunday, Welch barged into Comet Ping Pong, where he told people to get out and pointed his gun at an employee.

The 28-year-old then spent 45 minutes searching the restaurant for the secret room, tunnel or doorway that supposedly led to the underground trafficking operation. He fired at least one shot in the restaurant, reportedly to force open a locked door.

After finding no evidence of Pizzagate, Welch walked out and surrendered to police.

He is now facing three felony charges for and a misdemeanor gun possession charge.</description>
      <tags>video,Pizzagate,clinton conspiracy theory,clinton conspiracy theories,podesta email,hillary clinton,comet ping pong,wikileaks</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225007</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 08:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5C5/3BC/5C53BC93977A4B188E5B1C3E5B8F0B1A_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3225007/3225007_9B0E84BEA58C4997A93287A3C38E0313_161206_3225007_Pizzagate_shooting__Armed_man_storms_DC_pizzeria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump angers China: After Taiwan call, Trump decides to double down against butthurt Chinese</title>
      <description>NEW YORK &#x2014;  POTUS-in-waiting Donald Trump and the Chinese have one thing in common &#x2014; thin skin, which is going to make for some great entertainment over the next four years. 

When Trump accepted a call from Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen last week, the U.S. media lost it. The first thing they did was Google &#x2018;TAIWAN&#x2019;, then they started churning out China talking points. 

China was clearly upset over the Tsai phone call, but they tried to play it off at first. 

Then Trump doubled down through his official spokesman &#x2014; Twitter. Trump called out China for manipulating its currency and heavily taxing U.S. imports. He also criticized their military presence in the South China Sea.  

China issued a warning in a front-page editorial on the overseas edition of the People&#x2019;s Daily warning the U.S. that it was creating trouble for itself. Too bad no one reads that garbage.

Who will make the next move?</description>
      <tags>video,Trump Taiwan call,Tsai Ing-wen Trump call,Trump China tweets,Trump vs China,Trump angers China,Trump angers Chinese,Taiwan vs China,Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225985</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 11:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>117</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D50/AAE/D50AAE5337F843DC93BE316431DC4930_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/07/3225985/3225985_239C69C387C542409910EC1E5CEA9024_161207_3225985_Trump_angers_China__After_Taiwan_call__Trump_dec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruel animal circus: Dolphins forced to jump through flaming hoops, bears rides tricycle</title>
      <description>JAVA, INDONESIA &#x2014; As members of a traveling circus on the island of Java, life for 72 captive bottlenose and stenella dolphins is as tough as it gets. Forced to do both dangerous and clownish tricks for the public as the stars of a traveling circus, their only reward is a few dead fish for completing routines successfully. Footage of their plight is now circulating rapidly online. 

The dolphins are transported from venue to venue, performing in plastic pools filled with artificial salt water and high levels of chlorine, which can cause blindness. They perform all sorts of unnatural feats, such as leaping through flaming rings. During the performances, music is blaring and the deafening roar of the audience is painful for the dolphins, known to be acoustic creatures.

Once the show is done, the dolphins are then caught in large nets, and transferred onto stretchers. Loaded onto the tarp-like stretchers, they are carted off by circus staff toward rusty old trucks. In the trucks are small individual shipping crates, half filled with water, which the dolphins are placed into. Then, the circus hits the road on the way to the next city, with trips reported to be along bumpy roads for as many as 14 hours, and possibly even longer.

Other animals forced to survive and perform in this cruel, portable operation range from otters doing oddball acts, to cockatoos doing stage tricks, and even sun bears riding tricycles are featured. The cruel traveling circuses rake in the equivalent of roughly $60,000 US dollars each month. 

Though dolphins are a protected species in Indonesia, the country&#x2019;s lack of enforcement on illegal captures and its poor monitoring of the welfare of these animals makes it easy and convenient for these circuses to remain in business.</description>
      <tags>video,Dolphin flaming hoops,bear rides tricycle,sun bear,circus animals,indonesia traveling circus,dolphin circus,dolphin tricks,dolphin cruelty,animal cruelty,ric o&#x2019; barry,dolphin project</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226766</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 05:31:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/853/589/853589D285D7460284523F61EA4CB266_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/08/3226766/3226766_BAF0BA6C93E04A82BBF4FA071BCD316D_161208_3226766_Cruel_animal_circus__Dolphins_forced_to_jump_thr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidnapped in Thailand? US tourist says she fought off attackers in Bangkok abduction</title>
      <description>BANGKOK &#x2014; An American tourist says she was kidnapped and robbed in Thailand but fought off her attackers when one of them tried to rape her.

Michigan woman Alexandra Fairfield arrived back in the U.S. last week on a flight supposedly paid for by a GoFundMe campaign to bring her home.

And although her story sounds like the latest installment of the &#x201C;Taken&#x201D; movie franchise, friends and family of the 25-year-old insist it is all too real.
 
Alexandra and her college roommate Joe were reportedly in an unnamed Bangkok bar on the first night of their Thai vacation, Alexandra&#x2019;s mother Cindy Fairfield told ABC-affiliate WZZM.

While Joe went to the bathroom, Alexandra said she began to feel woozy, possibly because she&#x2019;d been drugged. One member of the alleged kidnapping gang took Alexandra out of the bar, apparently without anybody seeing.

Cindy Fairfield said four or five others then picked her daughter up and threw her into a black car with tinted windows.

Alexandra woke to find herself bound by the hands, and a man in a Thai law enforcement uniform trying to rape her, but somehow she was able to get free and fight her attacker off.

Alexandra&#x2019;s sister Samantha Jo Moore wrote on Facebook that she then jumped from a second floor balcony. Alexandra asked several people nearby to help her, but they refused, so she hid in some bushes for seven hours.

Police officers looked for her with flashlights, but fearing they were corrupt cops, she stayed hidden. When she came out, Alexandra asked some security guards for help, but they laughed and asked her for money.

Alexandra flagged down a taxi and made it back to her hotel. She went to the U.S. Embassy, but they couldn&#x2019;t do much because she refused to file a police report.

Well-wishers then raised nearly $9,000 to help Alexandra and Joe get home after her boyfriend Nathan Jennings launched a GoFundMe appeal.</description>
      <tags>video,Taken,kidnapped,woman kidnapped in thailand,one night in bangkok,abducted in thailand,tourists in thailand</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226721</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 04:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1EF/4C5/1EF4C5E83A6D49F9A6B8AF800EE9EF41_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/08/3226721/3226721_0D1694CE7FF641A8AC3F4992BED7D461_161208_3226721_Kidnapped_in_Thailand__US_tourist_says_she_fough_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cockroach in ear: video of Chinese woman have having live insect pulled from ear</title>
      <description>HUAIHUA CITY, CHINA &#x2014; A woman in China received a doctor&#x2019;s diagnosis that will make your skin crawl. Video of the emergency procedure surfaced on December 6, and is making the entire internet squirm.

The woman, Liao, says she recently felt something fly into her ear. She could feel it buzzing around in there, but just couldn&#x2019;t get to it. She says its wings were flapping, and the pain and discomfort she was feeling became unbearable. 

When she went to the doctor&#x2019;s office, physicians used an endoscope to get a better look at the problem. Inside, they found a cockroach, making a commotion inside the woman&#x2019;s eardrum. The doctors sprayed her ear with a chemical to calm the bug down. Once it settled, they used tweezers to get up in there and carefully yank the cockroach out of her ear. 

Doctors believe the cockroach may have been attracted to the woman&#x2019;s warm ear as a result of food being left by the bed.</description>
      <tags>video,Cockroach ear,cockroach in ear,cockroach removed from,insect in ear,bug in ear,insect removed from ear,live cockroach in ear</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226601</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 02:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/245/79B/24579B3A656E425182A943E4079C571A_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/08/3226601/3226601_67C2D4E42C5C45BDA9D6CA8A09CAD957_161208_3226601_Cockroach_in_ear__video_of_Chinese_woman_have_ha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student teacher relations: Las Vegas math teacher kept diary of affair with student, 14</title>
      <description>LAS VEGAS &#x2014; A married former teacher is behind bars this week after a court found her guilty of having sex with a 14-year-old boy.

Nicole Wilfinger, aged 37, was a math teacher at Molasky Junior High School in Las Vegas. For the better part of a year, Wilfinger journalized her affair with the boy in a digital diary on her phone, reported the Las Vegas Review-Journal.

This diary includes everything from the first time they &#x201C;made out,&#x201D; to the first time they &#x201C;had sex,&#x201D; to the first time &#x201C;he was a cowboy&#x201D; for her. 

Police say Wilfinger and the student spoke with each other nearly 2,000 times by phone. They also recovered over 300 images and 156 texts she had deleted from her phone. 

Wilfinger and her victim admitted to having sex three times. Last Wednesday a judge sentenced her to between 28 months and six years in prison.</description>
      <tags>video,Student and teacher relations,las vegas,math teacher,affair journal,student teacher affair,student teacher relationship,nicole wilfinger</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226560</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 02:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BFA/434/BFA43434543B42288E75F5F1BCFCD5DA_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/08/3226560/3226560_0660B22372354C499C767962BB9A3B32_161208_3226560_Student_teacher_relations__Las_Vegas_math_teache_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Croydon tram crash: London tram was going more than three times the speed limit - TomoNews</title>
      <description>LONDON &#x2014; A tram that crashed in south London last week, killing seven people, was travelling at three and half times the speed limit.


An interim report found the Croydon tram was travelling at 43.5 mph in a 12 mph zone when it derailed on Nov. 9, the BBC reported. The trams are not fitted with an automatic braking system.


There were no defects or obstructions on the track, according to the report.
Driver Alfred Dorris, 42, was arrested on suspicion of manslaughter and released on bail. Investigators are trying to establish if he fell asleep or blacked out.


Seven people were killed in the crash and 51 others were taken to the hospital. The seven passengers who died ranged in age from 19 to 63. All of them lived in and around the Croydon area.


London transport authorities have offered to pay for the funerals of the victims.


The London Ambulance Service said eight of the 51 victims taken to the hospital were suffering from injuries that were serious or life-threatening.


The incident is the worst rail accident in the UK since 2002, when seven people died and more than 70 were injured in a high-speed rail crash at Potters Bar just north of London.


The Croydon tramlink system covers 17 miles of track in south London and served more than 27 million passengers in the past year.</description>
      <tags>video,Croydon tram,croydon tram crash,croydon tramlink,tram crash,london tram crash,croydon london,croydon,train crash 2016</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226540</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 02:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AC3/E57/AC3E57A974F049D2B8362A90A6D1A69D_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/09/3226540/3226540_5708CCB0077A4FCC98E0D0BF03308967_161208_3226540_Croydon_tram_crash__London_tram_was_going_more_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electric vehicle charging corridors: Long-haul trips in electric cars to now be possible - TomoNews</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; Taking your electric car out further than work or a nearby shopping mall is about to get a lot easier, thanks to a new initiative launched by the Obama administration.


The U.S. federal government plans to establish 48 electric vehicle charging corridors across the country to encourage the adoption of electric vehicles, the White House announced on Nov. 3.


The 48 corridors &#x2014; which will be designated by the Department of Transportation &#x2014; will cover nearly 25,000 miles, crossing 35 states and the District of Columbia.


The plans call for there to be either an existing or a planned charging station within every 50 miles along these corridors.


New signs approved by the Federal Highway Administration will help drivers to identify and locate these charging stations.


According to the Washington Post, the new signage and the existence of charging station at roughly 50-mile intervals will help overcome what analysts call &#x201C;range anxiety,&#x201D; one of the main barriers to using electric vehicles for long-haul trips. Electric cars such as the Volkswagen e-Golf, Chevrolet Spark and BMW i3 can travel only 80 miles on a single charge.


The new actions are part of a larger federal initiative to speed up the deployment of alternative-fuel vehicle infrastructure nationwide, the White House said in a press release published on its website.


Website Climate Central reports that among the 48 vehicle charging corridors are Interstate 5 from San Diego to the Canadian border; Interstates 10, 20, 30, 35 and 45 in Texas; and Interstate 80 from Nebraska to New York City.</description>
      <tags>video</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226537</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 02:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E01/AE9/E01AE986D72F41C882C6A123395F4324_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/09/3226537/3226537_DCB13BF319F2483AAEC04AAC3552160F_161208_3226537_Electric_vehicle_charging_corridors__Long_haul_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla solar roof: New Tesla-SolarCity panels look just like ordinary roof tiles - TomoNews</title>
      <description>LOS ANGELES &#x2014; Tesla has unveiled a solar roof product that doesn&#x2019;t distract from the aesthetics of a home, as they look just like ordinary tiles.


The company unveiled four types of solar tile during a launch event at the &#x201C;Desperate Housewives&#x201D; set at Universal Studios last Friday, TechCrunch reported.


Each Tesla roof tile is made up of a solar cell, quartz glass and a color louver film that makes it appear opaque from an angle.


Tesla CEO Elon Musk said the tiles have 98 percent of the efficiency of traditional solar panels. However, the tiles have the potential to go above normal efficiency if improved coatings can trap light inside to reduce loss of energy.


Tesla sees the solar roofs working in tandem with its Powerwall battery unit to provide energy for homes and its electric vehicles.


The tiles will be available next year through SolarCity, a solar installation company chaired by Musk, which he is trying to merge with Tesla.


Musk didn&#x2019;t reveal any specific prices but said the Tesla panels would cost less than the full cost of a roof, with the added benefit of being able to generate electricity.</description>
      <tags>video,Tesla solar,tesla solar roof,tesla solarcity,tesla solar panels,tesla solar power,tesla solarcity merger,tesla solar system,solar energy</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226520</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 02:03:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C87/735/C87735A783324E908F50D0C9A70673F5_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/09/3226520/3226520_D92A8372372F4C678D9904AEFD4D6131_161208_3226520_Tesla_solar_roof__New_Tesla_SolarCity_panels_loo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone delivery service in Singapore may lead to the flying car, says Airbus - TomoNews</title>
      <description>PARIS/SINGAPORE &#x2014; Aircraft manufacturer Airbus is set to trial a drone delivery service which, if successful, could potentially lead to tests of flying taxis for passengers.


The technology to be tested in Singapore next year will see drones being used to deliver parcels, according to an article in FORUM, the Airbus Group corporate magazine. During the trial, drones will navigate a network of delivery and pick-up points across the National University of Singapore campus. 


These drones, also known as octocopters because of their eight blades, will fly automated on routes along interconnecting sky corridors throughout the campus. Upon arrival, the drone will unload the parcel automatically, and its recipient will be sent a delivery notification.


Airbus says that if testing shows drones to be safe, this may increase the chances of passenger flight testing being accepted in Singapore. 


&#x201C;If the team is able to demonstrate the safe operation of Skyways over NUS, this could help shape the regulatory framework for unmanned aircraft system operations in Singapore and potentially increase acceptance for passenger flight testing, thus giving a boost to urban air vehicle projects,&#x201D; an excerpt from the FORUM article explains.


The company has been developing a electric flying vehicle named CityAirbus for several years, with the aim of reducing traffic congestion in cities. Airbus believes that in the future, people will use such vehicles, which could be operated via transport apps such as Uber.</description>
      <tags>video,Drone delivery service,drones,drone delivery,national university of singapore,the flying car,flying taxi,drone delivery service,Airbus,cityairbus</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226491</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 01:47:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>53</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DA3/97C/DA397C3317CB4D628CA5075231F8F803_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/09/3226491/3226491_C07B577095F04303926FE9EB56CF76C3_161208_3226491_Drone_delivery_service_in_Singapore_may_lead_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affordable housing? ByFusion turns waste plastic into RePlast bricks to make cheap homes - TomoNews</title>
      <description>NEW YORK &#x2014; A New York startup has developed an innovative way to recycle waste plastic, converting it into an alternative building material that can be used to build affordable housing.


The company, called ByFusion, has designed a machine that is highly compact and modular. It can be powered by propane gas or electricity and can process all types of plastic waste, according to the ByFusion website.


The plastic waste does not have to be pre-processed. Instead, it is shredded inside the machine before it&#x2019;s made into a new material called RePlast and compressed into bricks. The RePlast bricks are not as strong as concrete, so are reinforced with steel rods, wire and layers of mortar.


The company said RePlast has been used in projects including retaining walls in New Zealand and California, which have withstood environmental tests such as earthquakes.


ByFusion has so far raised around $30,000 of a $250,000 target on Indiegogo. On its campaign page, it says the machine will likely be available in the U.S. by May next year.</description>
      <tags>video,Byfusion,replast,replast bricks,byfusion turns waste plastic into bricks,waste plastic converted into bricks,cheap housing,alternative building materials</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226480</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 01:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B26/C21/B26C21219FBC44DE816D6A22BC45A198_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/09/3226480/3226480_B6198F8C621B4505981B83C1312DF01B_161208_3226480_Affordable_housing__ByFusion_turns_waste_plastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toblerone changed the shape of its chocolate bars so now everyone gets less chocolate - TomoNews</title>
      <description>UNITED KINGDOM &#x2014; Toblerone recently released new designs for two of their chocolate bars in the UK, which has resulted in the gaps being widened between the triangle-shaped pieces of the treat.


This means chocolate bars that were formerly 400 grams now weigh only 360 grams at the same length, a reduction of about 10% in chocolate for the same price.


A statement posted to Toblerone&#x2019;s Facebook page explains that rising costs in production of the famous treat is what led to the redesign of their 400-gram and 170-gram chocolate bars. However, the company maintains their other chocolate bars remain unchanged, and the new designs will not affect the taste of quality of their product.


The new design allowed the company to reduce the amount of chocolate, but retain the original size and shape of the bar&#x2019;s packaging.


Many consumers have taken to social media to voice their displeasure over the change, claiming that the redesign ruins what was so beloved about Toblerone chocolate bars in the first place &#x2014; their shape.</description>
      <tags>video,Toblerone,chocolate bars,chocolate gate,brexit,chocolate supply chain,chocolate crisis</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226479</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 01:39:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/882/287/8822876165144CC7B23584F37D729C3B_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/09/3226479/3226479_E5267E0789494AC28F86E43F3EAF2857_161208_3226479_Toblerone_changed_the_shape_of_its_chocolate_bar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian diver finds &#x2018;long-lost nuclear bomb&#x2019; off British Columbia coast - TomoNews</title>
      <description>BRITISH COLUMBIA, CANADA &#x2014; A Canadian diver may have found a long-lost U.S. military bomb that went missing in 1950.


Sean Smyrichinsky was diving near Haida Gwaii, an archipelago 80 km off the coast of British Columbia when he saw a strange object that looked like a huge bagel cut in half, with basketball-sized bowls molded into it, the Guardian reported.


It is possible the object was part of a Mark IV bomb that went missing during a mission on Feb. 13, 1950. The bomb was on board a U.S. Air Force B-36 strategic bomber for a training mission that included a simulated nuclear strike on San Francisco.


The bomb was a dummy capsule packed with lead instead of plutonium core and TNT, according to the Vancouver Sun. 


The crew was instructed to jettison the bomb over the Pacific Ocean when three of the plane&#x2019;s engines caught fire after it left Alaska. The bomb was reportedly released near Princess Royal Island in British Columbia.


The Mark IV weighed about five tons. It was also known as the Fat Man bomb, similar to the atomic bomb dropped on Nagasaki, Japan during World War II.</description>
      <tags>video,Mark 4 bomb,fat man bomb,diver finds mark 4 bomb,diver finds fat man bomb,haida gwaii,diver finds bomb,nuclear bomb</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226394</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 00:44:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D65/BC0/D65BC014269445A3BB90F3C68BE4DEB7_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/09/3226394/3226394_08AD61887592436D88BA0EDD3FA65939_161208_3226394_Canadian_diver_finds____long_lost_nuclear_bomb___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffe extinction: World&#x2019;s tallest animal endangered, says IUCN</title>
      <description>GLAND, SWITZERLAND &#x2014; The world&#x2019;s tallest creature is slowly veering closer to being wiped out. The International Union for Conservation of Nature has updated its Red List of Threatened Species, and among a number of birds and crops, the majestic giraffe now finds itself in serious trouble. 

With its population declining by roughly 40 percent over the past three decades, the giraffe has since been raised two categories from Least Concern to Vulnerable. The reason for the giraffe&#x2019;s demise is correlated with the growth of human populations. Illegal hunting has also escalated &#x2013; poachers use traps and rifles to kill giraffes for their meat, and some hunters still target them as trophies. With Habitat loss also contributing to their decreasing numbers in the wild, two decades from now giraffes may only reside in zoos. 

The African grey parrot has also been raised on the list due to concern over its declining population. Fondly nicknamed the Einstein parrot for its high level of intelligence and mimicking abilities, has been badly drastically reduced by habitat loss, and the exotic pet trade. With roughly 3.2 million captured between 1975 and 2013, one of the planet&#x2019;s brightest birds is now listed as Endangered, formerly listed as Vulnerable.

It&#x2019;s estimated that less than 98,000 giraffes are left in the wild. With the Red List having grown to nearly 25,000 different species, the time we have left to reverse the damage we&#x2019;ve done to other forms of life on Earth may not be enough.</description>
      <tags>video,Iucn,red list,endangered species,giraffe extinction,extinction,giraffe,Antioquia wren,Comoro blue vanga,african grey parrot</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3227607</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 03:40:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/68F/035/68F035CECFAF430E96DF79F5F78E26BD_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/09/3227607/3227607_AE110209A21A49CB867631B4385EE801_161209_3227607_Giraffe_extinction__World___s_tallest_animal_end_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot racism: New Zealand auto passport system fails to see Asian man&#x2019;s eyes - TomoNews</title>
      <description>NEW ZEALAND &#x2014; A New Zealand man of East Asian-descent found himself having trouble renewing his passport on the government&#x2019;s online website for a strange reason &#x2013; it could not detect his eyes.


Aerospace Engineering student and DJ Richard Lee was born in Taiwan, but raised in New Zealand. A citizen of New Zealand, when it came time to renew his passport on December 6, he had some trouble with the government&#x2019;s online portal. Lee&#x2019;s standard passport photos looked appear fine, but when he tried to upload them onto the New Zealand government website, the site rejected his application. Lee attempted to submit the photos two more times, but again and again, the automated system responded with &#x201C;Subject eyes are closed.&#x201D;


When Lee contacted Internal Affairs to find out what the real reason was, he was told &#x201C;uneven lighting on the face&#x201D; caused his photo to be rejected. Finding humor in the failures of the system&#x2019;s facial recognition technology, Lee used a Snapchat filter to add some absurdity to point out the website&#x2019;s gaffe. 


After retaking his photos soon after, his new shots were accepted, and his passport finally renewed.</description>
      <tags>video,New zealand passport,richard lee passport,passport fail</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3227569</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 03:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>78</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8FE/951/8FE951368C4148F5BC6EF8A2E938C981_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/09/3227569/3227569_205CEFE860184B4CA22D10A515FBFF30_161209_3227569_Robot_racism__New_Zealand_auto_passport_system_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pit bull attacks owner: Demon dog shot by cops and put down after severely mauling owner</title>
      <description>LAUDERHILL, FLORIDA &#x2014; Yasmin Adam owned three pit bull mixes that she reportedly once said to a neighbour &#x201C;don&#x2019;t bite,&#x201D; reported Broward and Palm Beach newspaper The Sun Sentinel. On Monday, at least one of them did just that &#x2014; after it turned on her.

Police told The Sun Sentinel that Adam&#x2019;s nephew came to her home at 5.p.m on Monday to find one of the dogs mauling her arms. He called 911 and told the operator &#x201C;it&#x2019;s killing her&#x201D; and &#x201C;it&#x2019;s chewing her arms.&#x201D; Audio of the call was posted to the newspaper&#x2019;s website.

When police arrived, they say Yasmin was still being attacked. One officer whacked the canine with her baton but that didn&#x2019;t stop it, so she tried pepper spray instead. That didn&#x2019;t work, either.  

Finally, the officer had to draw her weapon and shoot the animal to stop the attack. 

Adam is recovering at a local hospital, where she underwent surgery for severe injuries to her arms. 

The dog that was shot survived, but had to be put down due to the extent of its injuries. As for the other two canines, authorities say their fate is up to Yasmin.</description>
      <tags>video,Pit bull attacks owner,pit bull attacks woman,pit bull shot by police,pit bull killed,pit bull violence,pit bull gets shot,pit bull violence,lauderhill,florida,yasmin adams</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3227424</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 01:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3C9/1A8/3C91A84AABC94B4B8C4427436862E0AD_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/09/3227424/3227424_E40F863F91174779BA35020DFF8D1033_161209_3227424_Pit_bull_attacks_owner__Demon_dog_shot_by_cops_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School shooting: Campus cop shoots Reno high school student armed with knives</title>
      <description>RENO, NEVADA &#x2014; A Reno high school was sent into lockdown on Wednesday after campus police shot an armed teen on school grounds.

The Reno Gazette-Journal reports that a 14-year-old boy had been fighting with another male student outside the library of Procter Hug High School just before 11:30 a.m.

He pulled out two knives in the middle of the altercation and began swinging it at his opponent. Soon, he was brandishing the knife while threatening to attack other students as well.

A campus police officer who tried to get the teen to drop his weapons shot him in the shoulder when he refused and continued to wave the knives around.

Several videos of the incident have emerged online, though they only show the events before and after the shooting.

The teen is currently in critical condition at the hospital. Authorities have yet to determine what prompted his behavior, though one parent who knew the injured teen suggested he was constantly bullied.</description>
      <tags>video,School shooting,reno school shooting,hug high school shooting,knife wielding student,teen with knives,campus shooting,officer shooting,cop shooting,campus police,campus officer</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3227367</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B89/EE3/B89EE3941CB94FA0B142D99474136F77_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/09/3227367/3227367_776BCAB92CD3428FA6D36AB0C7E83F78_161209_3227367_School_shooting__Campus_cop_shoots_Reno_high_sch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bike safety: Airbag bike helmets &#x2018;five times safer&#x2019; than conventional foam versions - TomoNews</title>
      <description>STANFORD, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; Wearing helmets may reduce risk of serious injury to the millions of people around the world riding bicycles, but it turns out the type of helmet also matters.


Researchers from Stanford University found that helmets equipped with airbag technology offer five times more protection than your standard foam ones, according to Reuters.


The test was conducted using two test dummies &#x2014; one wearing a foam helmet, and another with an airbag helmet. Both were then dropped from varying heights to simulate an accident. 


Conventional helmets may prevent skull fractures during accidents, but don&#x2019;t often protect against concussions and other similar head injuries.


In lieu of foam as protection, airbag helmets are inflated with helium, and worn like a collar around the neck. Sensors monitor the cyclist&#x2019;s normal movements, and deploy automatically once they detect something abnormal, such as a collision.


Upon deployment, an inflated hood is released from the collar. The hood covers most of the head and absorbs shock during impact. 


The researchers warn however, that the airbag helmets may pose a bigger risk if not deployed properly.


The helmets are made by Swedish company Hovding and are currently only available in Europe.</description>
      <tags>video,Airbag helmet,hovding,bike helmet,bike safety,bike accident,bike collision,bike crash,safety,head injury</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226599</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 02:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CD9/8A2/CD98A23EF1AB45CB87DFB0D948644576_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/10/3226599/3226599_B349A8FEE6CF41879379EE2DCA665F3F_161208_3226599_Bike_safety__Airbag_bike_helmets____five_times_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space elevator: Canadian company Thoth plans 20-kilometer tower and space elevator - TomoNews</title>
      <description>PEMBROKE, ONTARIO, CANADA &#x2014; A Canadian space company wants to build a space elevator that reaches 20 kilometers high.


The company is called Thoth and the concept is called the Thoth X tower. The idea is to build a tower with reinforced inflatable sections. The middle is hollow.  An elevator car would encircle the tower until it reaches the top.


Thoth estimates the tower would cost $5 billion to construct. As a demonstration project, it would build a precursor tower measuring 1.5 kilometers tall.


One feature of the project is the wind farm about three quarters of the way up. The 50 turbines could produce 1 gigawatt of continuous energy. That&#x2019;s enough to power about 700,000 homes.


The main purpose of the tower is to provide a take-off and landing platform for spacecraft. If your aircraft takes off at a 20 kilometer altitude, you can get to space in a single stage without the need for additional fuel stages.


Thoth estimates this would save 30% on energy costs.</description>
      <tags>video,Space elevator,space tower,Thoth,ThothX</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226645</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 03:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>134</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/17D/D53/17DD5389B14D47AE8079B5EBBCAFEC57_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/11/3226645/3226645_61569C0680FF4844A74432E25156F05E_161208_3226645_Space_elevator__Canadian_company_Thoth_plans_20__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tank treads on a car: KIA concept car has tank treads on a family SUV - TomoNews</title>
      <description>LAS VEGAS &#x2014; Korean car manufacturer KIA unveiled a concept design of its Sorento SUV that drives autonomously using tank treads in place of tires. 


According to automotive news website Top Speed, the design was shown at the SEMA 2017 car show in Las Vegas earlier this month. 


Most cars distribute the vehicle&#x2019;s weight over four wheels. This concept performs well in regular driving scenarios. But when faced with snow, mud or other difficult terrain, the tires can sink &#x2014; leaving the vehicle stuck.


To get around this, KIA&#x2019;s concept Sorento supplants normal tires with tank treads.


Also known as continuous tracks or caterpillar tracks, these distribute weight better over a larger surface than tires, enabling vehicles to traverse difficult terrain. Vehicles such as tanks and tractors use these to maneuver across desert, mud and other obstacles.


The concept Sorento features an autonomous driving system and can also be controlled via a tablet rather than a regular steering wheel. The vehicle sports suicide-style doors to make getting in and out easier and seating similar to that of a gondola.</description>
      <tags>video,Tank car,tank treads on a car,kia gondola,kia gondola car,kia tank tread suv,suv,driving in winter,winter tank treads,stuck in snow,car stuck in snow</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226635</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 03:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>65</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/986/212/9862127FB6D744748BB3BF9DD4C315A2_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/11/3226635/3226635_679D3A3980544FA99A176BC1580D953F_161208_3226635_Tank_treads_on_a_car__KIA_concept_car_has_tank_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scotland&#x2019;s SPCA mistakes harmless snake for green mamba, then kills it</title>
      <description>DRUMOAK, SCOTLAND &#x2014; The Scottish Society for the Protection and Care of Animals is taking heat after it froze a harmless green snake to death in a case of mistaken identity.

The snake was found on a cargo ship that had returned from West Africa on Nov. 9.

Scottish SPCA workers were called in and captured the reptile, which they thought was a venomous green mamba. They moved the snake to their rehoming center in Drumoak in Aberdeenshire, Aberdeenshire&#x2019;s the Press and Journal reported.

But the closest anti-venom for a green mamba was in Bedford &#x2014; eight hours away by car. And workers could not find a reptile specialist who could take in the snake. So, due to &#x201C;severe health and safety concerns,&#x201D; the Scottish SPCA workers decided it had to be euthanized, in a freezer. 

After the poor thing died a horrible death did they realize it was a harmless green tree snake. It was not venomous and did not even have fangs.

PETA has of course criticized the SSPCA for the blunder, with director Elisa Allan saying: &#x201C;If a snake must be euthanized &#x2014; which means given a &#x2018;good death&#x2019; &#x2014; the animal shouldn&#x2019;t be frozen to death.&#x201D;

Allan also said &#x2018;&#x2019;major veterinary bodies, including the Association of Reptilian and Amphibian Veterinarians, said freezing was unacceptable. The formation of ice crystals on a snake&#x2019;s skin can cause acute pain.&#x2019;&#x2019;

Scottish SPCA chief superintendent Mike Flynn said it had been an &#x201C;innocent mistake.&#x201D; He said the charity &#x201C;genuinely believed&#x201D; it was a green mamba.</description>
      <tags>video,Snakes,snake freeze to death,green snake,green tree python,green mamba,venomous snakes,poisonous snakes,SPCA,scotland</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230357</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 02:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EBE/38E/EBE38E2CCCD6479CAFADF70C174FE853_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230357/3230357_A2322B5A0F3A4549A568E9FE0FCA6619_161213_3230357_Scotland___s_SPCA_euthanized_harmless_snake_by_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squirrel bulb bandit: sneaky squirrel makes off with 150 Christmas bulbs in 24 hours</title>
      <description>SEATTLE &#x2014; After a Seattle neighborhood&#x2019;s holiday decorations began to mysteriously go missing, residents thought they had a Grinch in their midst. The reality, as it turned out, was much more adorable.

Circa News reports that Margaret Rican had been stringing Christmas lights outside her home for more than a decade, and was confused when she noticed bulbs were suddenly going missing.

The culprit turned out to be a squirrel, who had been chewing through the wires to get the bulbs.

Rican soon caught the bushy-tailed thief red-handed, and filmed him on video as he made his escape. She later put the video up on YouTube, where it&#x2019;s been viewed nearly 70,000 times.

All in all, the bulb bandit managed to pilfer 150 bulbs in 24 hours. The hardworking critter probably thought it was food and stashed them in different yards to prep for winter, though it&#x2019;s also possible the bandit is just really into the holidays and was looking for decor to spruce up his home.</description>
      <tags>video,Squirrel,bulb bandit,squirrel steals christmas lights,squirrel steals christmas bulb,christmas bulb bandit,thieving squirrel,grinchy squirrel</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230348</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 02:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E94/A96/E94A96B0179148ACB1AC5AA3B9488E27_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230348/3230348_7AC8867177154AD5B09D8D2BB7550F93_161213_3230348_Squirrel_bulb_bandit__sneaky_squirrel_makes_off__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police body cam death: Cops fist bump over dead man&#x2019;s body outside New Mexico Wal-Mart</title>
      <description>BERNALILLO, NEW MEXICO &#x2014; Police bodycam footage of a coked-up man&#x2019;s arrest is causing outrage, especially after it was revealed that the man in question died after he was cuffed, hogtied and covered in a spit sock. It all went down on Sept. 6, 2015 at a Wal-Mart in Bernalillo, New Mexico. The Daily Beast posted the body camera footage on their website. 

Before the incident, Ben Anthony C de Baca, who has a history of mental illness, was behaving erratically, reported local news station KOB4 in November. He crashed into a parked car, went inside a Wal-Mart store and began wrecking merchandise while yelling &#x201C;You are all murderers, you killed my kid!&#x201D; reported the Daily Beast. 

Customers subdued him until the cops arrived. Due to the store&#x2019;s location, cops from three police agencies in Rio Rancho, Santa Ana and Bernalillo showed up. Footage from an officer&#x2019;s body cam shows them cuffing C de Baca in the store. He allegedly bit one of the officers in the leg during a struggle. 

Then they put a black spit sock over his head. In the video, C de Baca began screaming that he couldn&#x2019;t breathe and that he was dying as the officers appeared to ignore his pleas. Minutes later, the 45-year-old was dead. The cops tried their best to revive him, but to no avail. Around 12 minutes after he died, two officers appeared to greet each other with a fist bump while standing over C de Baca dead body. 

Later, the New Mexico medical examiner declared C de Baca&#x2019;s death was a homicide, with the cause being, &#x201C;excited delirium (cocaine intoxication) complicated by means of physical restraint,&#x201D; reported KOB4. However, Rio Rancho Police investigated the death and cleared the cops of any criminal intent. 

The family is now suing the police for wrongful death. Their lawyer says the spit sock wasn&#x2019;t used correctly. He told local news station KOB4 that positional asphyxia may have also contributed to his death. This occurs when someone&#x2019;s body position prevents them from breathing properly and has been known to occur during police restraint.</description>
      <tags>video,Police fist bump over dead man,police fist bump,cops fist bump,new mexico,death by spit sock,spit sock death,police brutality,police caught on camera,police bodycam death,new mexico,anthony c de baca</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230317</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 02:19:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0CB/83D/0CB83D8815FE441683324294D38E1D2C_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230317/3230317_471278DC30CC4504B1C2B8E0006CCF2F_161213_3230317_Police_body_cam_death__Cops_fist_bump_over_dead__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange surgery stories: Chinese hospital growing man a new ear on his arm - TomoNews</title>
      <description>XIAN CITY, CHINA &#x2014; A Chinese hospital in the process of creating a human ear almost entirely through the human anatomy alone.


According to Chinese state media news outlet CCTV, plastic surgeons have grown an ear on a patient&#x2019;s arm after he lost it in an car accident one year ago. The man, identified only as Ji, is being treated by surgeons at First Hospital Affiliated with Xian Jiaotong University in Xian City, Shaanxi Province.


Several months ago, a dilator was inserted into the man&#x2019;s right forearm, which received daily water injections that created a thin and stretched layer of skin. Next, the hospital removed some of the patient&#x2019;s rib cage cartilage and modeled them into the shape of an ear.


This cartilage model was then inserted into the expanded skin, which has formed around it in the shape of a human ear. 


&#x201C;It looks exactly the same as my old ear,&#x201D; Ji said, according to a China Daily/Asia News Network report on the Strait Times.


The next part of Ji&#x2019;s treatment &#x2014; transplanting the new ear to the patient&#x2019;s head &#x2014; will take around three or four months.</description>
      <tags>video,Strange surgery stories,replacement ear surgery,china growing ear arm,plastic surgery on ear,growing ear on arm,arm used to grow ear,rib used to make ear,ear surgery,xian,china</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230248</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 01:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>41</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/718/F7E/718F7E8768F54695BD7CA2C53795E9B3_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/14/3230248/3230248_EB9751A91456498F90B64865E75F418B_161213_3230248_Strange_surgery_stories__Chinese_hospital_growin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typhoon turbine: Japanese engineer develops wind turbine to harness power from typhoon - TomoNews</title>
      <description>TOKYO &#x2014; A Japanese engineer has designed a new type of wind turbine that he believes would be able to harness power from typhoons.


Atsushi Shimizu founded a tech company called Challenergy in 2013 and invented a wind turbine that not only can draw power from the force of wind, but can stay functional during typhoons.


The typhoon turbine consists of three vertical blades and a central rod. It has an omnidirectional axis so that it can respond to wind coming from every direction.


Instead of driven by a propeller, the turbine makes use of the principle of the Magnus effect: air curves when passing by a rotating object, and the downward deflection of the air-flow produces a lifting force that counteracts the force of gravity, enabling the object to remain airborne.


The blades are controlled by the central rod, which can be tightened to slow down, or stop the blades regardless of the external forces.


Under normal circumstances, the typhoon turbine can achieve about 30 percent efficiency while conventional wind turbine can achieve 40 percent, ScienceAlert reported. However, conventional wind turbines could be damaged by typhoons while the typhoon turbine would be able to function normally.


"Japan actually has a lot more wind power than it does solar power, it's just not utilized," Shimizu told CNN. "Japan has the potential to be a super power of wind.&#x201D;
According to the Japan Guide, about seven or eight typhoons pass over Okinawa prefecture each year, with about three hitting its main islands. Shimizu believes a single typhoon could generate enough energy to power Japan for 50 years.</description>
      <tags>video,Typhoon turbine,wind energy,wind power,typhoon energy,renewable energy,sustainable energy,japan,atsushi shimizu,challenergy,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230233</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 01:11:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BEB/C59/BEBC593F86D0454DB48C9A9E438C18A8_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/14/3230233/3230233_8A2842ADF6B341708922B65D49D4AC8B_161213_3230233_Typhoon_turbine__Japanese_engineer_develops_wind_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain implants: Researchers help paralyzed monkeys walk again with wireless implants - TomoNews</title>
      <description>LAUSANNE, SWITZERLAND &#x2014; Paraplegics may soon regain use of their legs, now that scientists have created an implant that proves effective in primates.


In a spinal cord injury, brain signals are unable to reach the neurons that activate movement, often resulting in lower limb paralysis. But researchers from the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology in Lausanne may have found a way to bypass this, having successfully restored movement in two paralyzed monkeys.


According to the study, published in Nature, the team developed a neuroprosthetic interface that uses two wireless implants. The first is a sensor surgically implanted in the brain&#x2019;s motor cortex &#x2014; the area that controls movement. The second is a nerve stimulator that is placed near the spinal injury.


The sensor picks up brain signals commanding leg movement and transmits them to a computer. The computer decodes the signals and sends them to the second implant in the spine. From there, pulses of electricity are released to stimulate certain nerves. This in turn triggers muscles in the leg, enabling it to move and flex.


CNN reports that the monkeys did not need any training and were able to walk immediately after activation of the interface.


The researchers plan to apply the technology to improve human lives, but say this may take several more years to achieve.</description>
      <tags>video,Brain implants,brain implant,wireless implants,paraplegia,paraplegic,paralysis,paralyzed monkeys,paralyzed,cure for paralysis,medical technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230222</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 01:02:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F28/2B6/F282B69C366B47DEA6475BB7F5F0955B_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/14/3230222/3230222_E292E72705C74FA9AAB0284E6D45EF10_161213_3230222_Brain_implants__Researchers_help_paralyzed_monke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biogas: the Netherlands to spend 150 million euros to turn cow manure into energy - TomoNews</title>
      <description>FRIESLAND, THE NETHERLANDS &#x2014; The Netherlands has committed to investing 150 million euros in a biogas project to turn cow manure into fuel.


Manure processing is important to the Netherlands as about 10% of the country&#x2019;s greenhouse gas emissions come from agriculture, mostly methane from animal manure. The Netherlands&#x2019; livestock produces about 74 million tons of manure a year, according to the International Dairy Federation. This is too much to directly apply to farmlands as fertilizer, as the excessive amount of nutrients could leak underground and cause algae growth and pollution in nearby water sources.


A way to solve this problem is by transforming manure into biogas. In one experiment conducted at a farm in the Netherlands, manure is transported into an anaerobic digester, where bacteria transforms solid manures into liquid form. The resulting substance releases biogas, which consists of mostly methane and carbon dioxide. The biogas can then be used as fuel while any left over manure can be used as fertilizer.


According to the Guardian, the digester generated 9,342 kWh of electricity in 20 days, which is enough to power three homes for a year. The Dutch government aims to get 1,000 large farms in the country to produce energy from cow manure within four years.</description>
      <tags>video,Biogas,netherlands biogas project,dutch biogas project,cow manures into biogas,animal manures pollution,greenhouse gas emission,renewable energy</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230197</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BB5/861/BB586161381B4196943B37F9AB11C8BD_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/14/3230197/3230197_AFC0B1F67DF14F4DA0D99870D69DFBCE_161213_3230197_Biogas__the_Netherlands_to_spend_150_million_eur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driverless cars: Driver assist tech is putting autonomous cars in the driving seat - TomoNews</title>
      <description>LOS ANGELES &#x2014; A future in which self-driving vehicles travel our roads is edging closer as automakers introduce an ever-increasing range of innovations to their cars.


Today&#x2019;s cars are smarter than ever and some are capable of driving by themselves for long stretches, the Globe and Mail reported.


The use of radar, sonar and camera technology has seen cars make great advances in recent years, with even standard models now offering assistance to help drivers stay in their lane, avoid accidents and warn of blind-spot obstacles.


Some cars, like the BMW 7 Series can even be parked from outside the vehicle, simply by pressing a key fob.


This animation explains how the technology present in today&#x2019;s cars is paving the way for a future where fully autonomous self-driving cars are a reality.</description>
      <tags>video,Driverless car,driverless cars,self driving car,self driving cars,self driving car 2016,self driving car 2017,autonomous car,future cars,cars of the future</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230136</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 22:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>124</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B16/F77/B16F7707F1454942BC7CDE7C6A066A0A_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/14/3230136/3230136_5FF65E4D2A244F418883A40EC8ED5924_161213_3230136_Driverless_cars__Driver_assist_tech_is_putting_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Trudeau Chinese fundraisers: Rich Chinese lobbying prime minister for $1,500 a head</title>
      <description>OTTAWA &#x2014; Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has been facing criticism about Liberal Party cash-for-access fundraisers that have generated hundreds of thousands of dollars. 

On May 19, Trudeau attended a fundraiser at the Toronto home Chinese Canadian business executive Benson Wong, the Tyee reported. The price of admission to spend time with the prime minister was $1,525. 

Photos show Trudeau drinking beer and helping to make dumplings for about 35 attendees, according to the Tyee. He gave a speech on China-Canada relations, according to Chinese-language media.

Insurance tycoon Shenglin Xian, who&#x2019;s waiting for federal approval for a new bank, was also in attendance. 

Chinese billionaire Zhang Bin &#x2014; with a partner &#x2014; donated $1 million to the Pierre Elliott Trudeau Foundation and the University of Montreal Faculty Law weeks after the event. 

Trudeau attended a similar private Chinese fundraiser in Vancouver on Nov. 7.

The Liberal Party has been hammered for &#x201C;cash for access&#x201D; fundraisers that critics say give rich people the chance to lobby the prime minister and members of cabinet, Tyee reported.</description>
      <tags>video,Justin Trudeau Chinese fundraisers,Justin Trudeau rich Chinese,Trudeau Benson Wong,Trudeau Shenglin Xian,Wealth One Bank Canada,Trudeau Zhang Bin,Justin Trudeau China</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230748</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 10:49:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>92</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DC8/3B5/DC83B5E8FFB1427A896D526D421C8C5F_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230748/3230748_8203EC5B377A44589630277687D9507E_161213_3230748_Justin_Trudeau_Chinese_fundraisers__Rich_Chinese_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unarmed grandpa shot dead by cop: Man with dementia Francisco Serna killed by CA police</title>
      <description>BAKERSFIELD, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; A 73-year-old man suffering from the early stages of dementia was gunned down by police, a case of mistaken identity that turned fatal. 

On the night of December 12, Francisco Serna was going for an evening walk in his neighborhood, a routine he&#x2019;d taken up when he was feeling restless before bed. At 12:35 a.m., police received a report of a man brandishing a gun in the area.

When an officer arrived on scene, he spoke to a witness, who pointed him to a man standing in a driveway nearby. The man he pointed out was Francisco Serna. The officer wasted no time in unloading his weapon, firing nine bullets at the elderly man, killing him on the spot. Serna happened to be standing in his next door neighbor&#x2019;s driveway at the moment he was shot dead.

When investigators searched the area in the aftermath of the shooting, they did not recover a gun. Records indicate police had visited Serna&#x2019;s home twice before due to a medical alarm he&#x2019;d set off when he found himself in a confused state.

The officer involved in the shooting has been placed on administrative leave.</description>
      <tags>video,Francisco Serna,Roy Serna,Rogelio Serna,bakersfield police,dementia,man with dementia shot by police</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231335</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 04:02:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/951/F1F/951F1FE4AF9B46FC94B55522F1CB1D35_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231335/3231335_7D52C29F1AAB40ACA98D29A78920EED7_161214_3231335_Unarmed_grandpa_shot_dead_by_cop__Man_with_demen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concealed carry shooting: Pizza customer shoots and kills armed robber in Pennsylvania - TomoNews</title>
      <description>LEVITTOWN, PENNSYLVANIA &#x2014; An unidentified customer who shot and killed an armed robber at a pizza takeout store in Pennsylvania on Tuesday will not face charges.


Police said the man had a concealed-carry license, and even though his permit had recently expired, he would not be charged, ABC-affiliate WPVI reported. 


The man, who was the last customer of the night, was waiting for his order at Porfirio&#x2019;s Pizza and Pasta II in Levittown, when two masked men burst through the doors.


Brandishing weapons that were later found to be pellet guns, the robbers pistol-whipped the customer, striking him in the head. But when suspect Shawn Rose turned away, the customer pulled out a handgun and shot the 24-year-old stickup merchant dead.


The customer then turned his attention to Rose&#x2019;s 22-year-old brother and would-be partner in crime, Justin, and fired two shots.


Justin Rose was blasted through the pizza shop&#x2019;s front door. He was later transferred to the hospital where he was reported to be in critical condition.


The customer refused treatment for cuts to his head sustained when he was pistol-whipped. The owners of the pizza shop hailed him a hero.</description>
      <tags>video,Concealed carry shootings,gun rights,pizza shop shooting,pizza store shooting,man with gun stops robbery,robbery fails</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231284</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 03:06:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>26</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FC8/EA9/FC8EA96A9EEA4F59888883B05D0A760E_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231284/3231284_2F44639C269E40EC99CC03E2F3681C02_161214_3231284_Concealed_carry_shooting__Pizza_customer_shoots__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian dude fires two crossbow arrows into his chest and survives</title>
      <description>ST. PETERSBURG, RUSSIA &#x2014; Late last month an unidentified man in Russia tried to end his life via two self-inflicted crossbow arrow wounds to his chest and heart.

One arrow struck his left ventricle, left atrium and mitral valve, while the other hit his abdominal aorta, reported the Daily Mail.  

He was taken to GBUZ Elizabethan hospital, but they didn&#x2019;t have the resources to help him, so he was taken to the Federal Almazov North-West Medical Research Center. There, deft-handed surgeons cut out his heart and removed the arrows. Next, they put his heart back and repaired the damage by using the man&#x2019;s own tissue. 

His condition was last reported as stable but serious.</description>
      <tags>video,Russia,man survives suicide,man shoots himself,man shoots crossbow into chest,crossbow wound,crossbow injury,failed suicide attempt,st petersburg</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231197</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 02:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/30A/D63/30AD63F2C28A466C8CF2A858034E54E0_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231197/3231197_10607579D3EF45C1883DD6F5C802F12B_161214_3231197_Russian_dude_fires_two_crossbow_arrows_into_his__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf: Elf goes rogue in 2016 and takes no prisoners this Christmas season</title>
      <description>&#x2019;MURICA &#x2014; With Christmas right around the corner, that little annoying Elf on the Shelf is back again. 


The Elf on the Shelf is as old as the story of Christmas itself. Okay maybe not. 


It began as a children&#x2019;s book in 2005 with the elf acting as a scout to spy on your kids to see if they are being naughty or nice.

Since then, it has become a viral &#x201C;tradition,&#x201D; popular in the U.S. and now even the U.K. 

During the month of December, parents are supposed to move the elf around to different places around the house so it can spy on their children and report back to Santa Claus. 

Children can talk to the elf, but they can&#x2019;t touch him &#x2014; otherwise he&#x2019;ll disappear forever, according to the book written by Carol Aebersold and her daughter Chanda Bell.</description>
      <tags>video,Elf on the Shelf,Elf on the Shelf video,Elf on the Shelf book,Elf on the Shelf animation,Christmas,Christmas traditions,Christmas Elf</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231128</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 01:19:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>122</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/49B/466/49B4661FF98B4BAF9A0A43B205270C7A_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231128/3231128_5AEE9D4F5A204FCFA97DF9D3FCFE65D0_161214_3231128_Elf_on_the_Shelf__Elf_goes_rogue_in_2016_and_tak_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stray dog dyed pink in Russia sparked public outrage</title>
      <description>IZHEVSK, RUSSIA &#x2014; A cruel prank has sparked public outrage after a stray dog&#x2019;s fur was dyed in bright pink in Russia.

The incident took place in the city of Izhevsk in Russia's Udmurt Republic. Someone must have thought it would be funny to make the canine look fabulous. 

The poor dog was picked up by wildlife volunteer Vera Ivanova, after reports about it appeared on Russian social media. Vera took the dog, who&#x2019;d been nicknamed the &#x201C;Pink Elephant,&#x201D; to a local shelter. 

Vera says the dog seems fine, though it has been vomiting. She suspects the dog is vomiting because it was recently dyed. At the shelter, volunteers have been washing the dog to get the dye out of its white fur.

Local police are now looking for the person who dyed the dog pink. The person may be charged with animal cruelty.

Dying animals pink seems to be a thing in Russia. Last year, a Russian writer was falsely accused of killing her cat after photos of the animal dyed pink appeared on social media. The woman really did dye her car pink for a pink-themed party &#x2026; although she did not kill the feline.</description>
      <tags>video,Animal cruelty,animal abuse,pink dog,stray dog dyed pink,Russia,animal prank</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230900</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 20:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6EC/601/6EC601D0116F4C1C9D2304BB58D34188_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230900/3230900_7C1ED60FDD2C430B94E45ABB2D6C5B82_161213_3230900_Stray_dog_dyed_pink_in_Russia_sparked_public_out_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seabirds eat ocean plastic because it emits a smell that makes them think it&#x2019;s food - TomoNews</title>
      <description>LOS ANGELES &#x2014; The corruption of a natural process that directs seabirds toward their prey is tricking the animals into eating plastic floating in the ocean.


Five trillion pieces of plastic litter the oceans, weighing a total of 250,000 tons. Meanwhile, more than 200 species of marine life have been found to eat plastic, including birds, fish, turtles and mammals, the Los Angeles Times reported.


Researchers from the University of California, Davis said that plastic sets an &#x201C;olfactory trap&#x201D; for seabirds, according to a study published in the journal Science Advances.


When seabirds&#x2019; prey such as krill eat algae, the plants emit a sulfurous compound called dimethyl sulfide, or DMS, which has a strong smell. The odor gives a chemical signal to seabirds about where they can find food.


However, plastic floating in the ocean accumulates organic matter, including DMS. The plastic then emits the smell of DMS, which entices seabirds to eat it, according to the study.


According to the projections of a recent Australian study, 99 percent of all seabird species will have eaten at least some plastic by 2050, the Los Angeles Times reported.</description>
      <tags>video,Why seabirds eat plastic,birds eat plastic,plastic in the ocean,seabirds eating plastic,ocean plastic pollution,ocean plastic</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231008</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 23:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/985/5BA/9855BA2431D04DAF88761C92C58550CD_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/15/3231008/3231008_D80D5D233F1C463288E98DEAFA0CE879_161214_3231008_Seabirds_eat_ocean_plastic_because_it_emits_a_sm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electric cars must emit alert sounds under new U.S. rules aimed at accident prevention - TomoNews</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; Electric vehicles and hybrids must give off an alert sound at low speeds under new &#x2018;quiet car&#x2019; regulations finalized by the U.S. government on Monday.


The new federal rules require &#x2018;quiet cars&#x2019; to emit alert sounds at speeds of up to around 19 miles per hour, according to  the U.S. Department of Transportation's National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).


Electric vehicles and hybrids must be fitted with external speakers that will help alert pedestrians, cyclists and the blind to their presence.


The alert sounds are not required at higher speeds because other factors, such as tire noise and wind noise, are considered sufficient warnings by the NHTSA.


Hybrid vehicles are 19 percent more likely to be involved in a pedestrian crash than gas-powered vehicles, according to the NHTSA.


The NHTSA estimates that the new rules will prevent 2,400 injuries a year by 2020.


All new hybrid and electric vehicles must be designed in compliance with the rules by September 2019 but the government has not specified what the alerts should sound like.</description>
      <tags>video,Quiet car rules,electric vehicle alert sounds,electric car alert sounds,road safety,electric cars 2016,electric cars 2017</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230396</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 03:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>36</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/00E/E17/00EE170985C547C3A6C99519AC3C1E19_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/15/3230396/3230396_ACC527F06847400BBB7BA2B39251CDB4_161213_3230396_Electric_cars_must_emit_alert_sounds_under_new_U_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Clinton sore loser: Hillary needs to give it a rest, accept her crushing loss to Trump</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; It&#x2019;s safe to say Hillary Clinton isn&#x2019;t taking her crushingly embarrassing election loss to Donald Trump very well. 

Sure she won the popular vote by over 3 million votes, but she lost where it counted most &#x2014; the electoral college. 

Clinton has been trying to get the election results overturned since her defeat. 

First, she backed a failed attempt for recounts in Michigan, Pennsylvania and Wisconsin. Now she&#x2019;s back to beating the Russia hacking dead horse again.   

The CIA concluded last week that Russia mounted a covert intelligence operation to to help Trump win. The Clinton camp is backing a request by some electoral college voters for an intelligence briefing on how the Russian government meddled in the U.S. election. 

Clinton just needs to give it a rest already. The Russians didn&#x2019;t make both candidates widely unpopular, they did that themselves. Russia also didn&#x2019;t keep 90 million Americans from voting &#x2014; we did that all by ourselves.</description>
      <tags>video,Hillary Clinton sore loser,Clinton sore loser,Clinton Russian hacking,CIA Russian hacking U.S. election,Trump Putin,Trump Russia,Donald Trump</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231603</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 13:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>131</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D9F/864/D9F8644EC6834A86806BC9C68BE0D127_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231603/3231603_6594BB63652146D38EDF9C7C2D7B1942_161214_3231603_Hillary_Clinton_sore_loser__Hillary_needs_to_giv_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana teen hurt in car crash shows up at Chick-fil-A job to help feed the homeless</title>
      <description>AVON, INDIANA &#x2014; A photograph of a Chick-fil-A employee working despite injuries he sustained in a car crash has inspired an online fundraising campaign to help feed the homeless this Christmas.

Teenager Jakeem Tyler busted his neck and arm when he was in a car accident recently. But after getting the all-clear from doctors, Jakeem went back to work &#x2014; not just to earn money for himself &#x2014; but also because he wanted to buy Christmas presents and donate to the homeless.

Chick-fil-A customer Cameron Nelson was amazed to see Jakeem working last week while wearing a neck brace and sling, CBS New reported. After learning why Jakeem was so determined to keep working, Nelson uploaded a photo of the teenager to Facebook and set up a GoFundMe page.

That appeal quickly smashed its $2,500 goal out of the park and had already raised around $10,000 when we decided to animate this story.

So it looks like the homeless folks of Indiana are going to have a good Christmas this year &#x2014; all thanks to the generosity of a dedicated fast food worker and the power of social media.</description>
      <tags>video,Chick-fil-a,chick-fil-a worker in neck brace,generous acts of kindness,everyday heroes,good heart,helping the homeless</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231481</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 08:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/353/8A1/3538A16D52B54280AA6F557800E0C892_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231481/3231481_D82568B83EA74D2C83456F79BCDABEC1_161214_3231481_Indiana_teen_hurt_in_car_crash_shows_up_at_Chick_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alligator rides manatee: Incredible image of rare team-up goes viral</title>
      <description>ORANGE CITY, FLORIDA &#x2014; In a sight you don&#x2019;t see every day, an alligator photographed riding a manatee is making the rounds on social media.

The fascinating photo uploaded to Facebook on Nov. 30 was taken by a woman visiting Blue Spring State Park. When she caught sight of an alligator catching a lift on board the manatee express, her picture instantly became a frontrunner in the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission&#x2019;s manatee photo contest.

In truth, manatees and alligators do cross paths from time to time. The curious manatees often follow the alligators around. Interestingly enough, alligators actually would prefer to steer clear of the 1,000-pound sea cows. Alligators are not known to pose a threat to manatees of any size.

In the now-famous photograph, while it appears the alligator was attempting to fast track across the pond, an FWC spokesman claimed the reptile was merely swimming over the top of the sea cow.</description>
      <tags>video,Alligator manatee,manatee alligator,symbiotic relationship,mutually beneficial relationship,alligator,manatee,animal odd couples,animal friendships,blue spring state park</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232218</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 06:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FBC/2DB/FBC2DB67639C4E4FA01D9365515FBF32_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/15/3232218/3232218_988FC38C644749A5893405DD5B491908_161215_3232218_Alligator_rides_manatee__Incredible_image_of_rar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wonder Woman fired from UN ambassador role because feminists say she&#x2019;s too sexy</title>
      <description>NEW YORK &#x2014; Wonder Woman&#x2019;s United Nations ambassador gig ended prematurely this week after feminists complained she was just too sexy for the job.

The curvy D.C. Comics superheroine was made the U.N.&#x2019;s honorary ambassador for the empowerment of women and girls in October.

But Wonder Woman was given the boot on Monday, when the U.N. crumbled under the pressure of an online petition against her appointment, which was signed by almost 45,000 people, Reuters reported.

The authors of the petition admitted that Wonder Woman&#x2019;s creators may have intended her to be &#x201C;a strong and independent warrior with a feminist message.&#x201D;

But they whined that the 75-year-old fictional character was actually the &#x201C;epitome of a pin-up girl.&#x201D;

Citing Wonder Woman&#x2019;s large breasts, curves, white skin, and skimpy clothes, the petitioners argued that the character was an overtly sexual image and wasn&#x2019;t culturally encompassing or sensitive enough.

Wonder Woman&#x2019;s appointment was protested by dozens of U.N. staffers back in October. Now it&#x2019;s been confirmed that the haters have got their wish.

The U.N. refused to elaborate on why the Wonder Woman campaign was ending this week, even though it was scheduled to run well into 2017, according to Reuters.

D.C. Comics said it was proud of the character&#x2019;s work with the U.N. to achieve gender equality and empower women and girls.

Wonder Woman will be back in June next year, when a feature-length movie starring Israeli actress Gal Gadot as the scantily clad superheroine is scheduled for release.</description>
      <tags>video,Wonder woman,wonder woman un,wonder woman fired,wonder woman fired by un,wonder woman sexy,wonder woman reaction,gal gadot</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232149</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 04:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>41</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0C3/B3E/0C3B3EE0BE3D465C9638DA8D58DB86A1_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/15/3232149/3232149_38340DE881F0415C9FC940660191CE2A_161215_3232149_Wonder_Woman_fired_from_UN_ambassador_role_becau_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tapeworm extraction: Man gets disgusting 5-foot-long parasite pulled from nose</title>
      <description>AUSTRALIA &#x2014; Hold on to your lunches, the latest viral video to come out of the internet is filled with blood, pain, and a person-sized parasite that&#x2019;s so disgusting it&#x2019;ll make you hurl.

Tapeworms often make themselves at home in a person&#x2019;s gut, but this Aussie guy supposedly had one living up his nose, according to a video posted on LiveLeak.

His doctor helped take care of the problem, yanking the 5-foot-long worm for a good 30 seconds as the man squirmed in agony.

The horrifying video was of course uploaded online, where it&#x2019;s no doubt made a lot of people sick.

Some netizens are skeptical though, pointing out odd things in the video that don&#x2019;t just add up to a parasite scenario. They suggest that rather than having a parasitic pet, it seems more likely the man had a sinus problem he got fixed.

So instead of extracting an icky 5-foot wriggler, the doctor could have just been pulling out a bloody strip of gauze that was used during surgery.

In the end, it doesn&#x2019;t really matter what that nasty thing is &#x2014; still doesn&#x2019;t make watching it get yanked out of a man&#x2019;s face any less disgusting.</description>
      <tags>video,Tapeworm extraction,nose tapeworm,tapeworm,tapeworm pulled from nose,parasite extraction,worm pulled from nose,5 foot long tapeworm</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232144</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 04:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DFD/C11/DFDC11C15E364A0290446FE523938725_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/15/3232144/3232144_86CFB5BC89F44EE28AD7E1AD940AD425_161215_3232144_Tapeworm_extraction__Man_gets_disgusting_5_foot__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye shows up late for concert then cancels it after rant about Beyonce and Jay Z - TomoNews</title>
      <description>SACRAMENTO, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; Kanye West fans are livid after he showed up to a concert late and called it off after performing just two songs. 


According to the Sacramento Bee, the artist was late by more than an hour for his concert on Saturday in California&#x2019;s capital city.


When Kanye finally arrived, he performed the songs Famous and Father Stretch My Hands from his latest album Life of Pablo.


Then he launched into a 15-minute-long rant on various topics. Kanye claimed Beyonce conspired with MTV to win this year&#x2019;s video of the year award. He also begged Jay Z not to kill him.


After the concert, it was announced that the rest of Kanye&#x2019;s Saint Pablo tour had been called off. Attendees of the Sacramento concert have been offered refunds by Ticketmaster.</description>
      <tags>video,Kanye,Kanye West,Yeezy,Kanye cancels concert,Kanye rant,Jay Z,Beyonce,Kanye angry,Kanye upset with Jay Z,Life of Pablo,Saint Pablo Tour,Kanye insane</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232078</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 03:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/350/862/350862FE26A547728BD848DBA0860A2E_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/15/3232078/3232078_3AD694B6153A402E92F42CDD93BBEA72_161215_3232078_Kanye_shows_up_late_for_concert_then_cancels_it__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impaled by arrow: Dog shot in chest with 3-foot arrow rescued by Chinese animal shelter</title>
      <description>CHENGDU, CHINA &#x2014; Photos of a dog who was shot in the chest with an arrow have gone viral on Chinese social media and drawn attention to the plight of stray dogs in the country.

As reported by the Chongqing Morning Post, a Chinese netizen identified only as Ren Hui spotted the dog at Yinxing Hospitality Management College in the city of Chengdu, in China&#x2019;s Sichuan province. 

Ren Hui posted photos of the injured animal on her Weibo account, along with a call for the public to help. Volunteers from the Sichuan Qiming Companion Animal Protection Center saw the post and found the dog. They removed the arrow, but the dog got scared and ran off.

It was later found and taken to Chengdu&#x2019;s Boai Veterinary Hospital for medical treatment. Fortunately, the arrow did not damage its internal organs. 

Photos of the dog with the arrow sticking through its chest sparked outrage on the Chinese internet. 

In China, stray dogs are often shot with arrows and captured by dog catchers, Chen Yunlian, founder of Chengdu Animal Rescue, told the Shanghaiist. 

In May, a stray dog with an arrow sticking out of its head was spotted in Beijing's 798 Art District. And in August, another stray dog that had been shot with an arrow was found in Wuhan. Both dogs were rescued and have been treated for their injuries, the Beijing News reported.</description>
      <tags>video,Impaled by arrow,animal fails,impaled,shooting dogs,animal cruelty,animal abuse,impaled with arrow,dog shot,shooting arrows at dogs,dogs,China news 2016</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231792</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:28:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/774/052/774052B98B0F4176B41CA898EC6E5922_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/14/3231792/3231792_42309A29879549D783A3D72655B310B8_161214_3231792_Impaled_by_arrow__Dog_shot_in_chest_with_3_foot__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squirrel eats mouse: Hungry squirrel has fellow rodent over for lunch</title>
      <description>&#x2019;MURICA &#x2014; If you&#x2019;re easily grossed out by the sight of Mother Nature in all of her raw and unadulterated glory, then perhaps it&#x2019;s time to look away now.


But those of you who think the natural world is completely awesome should stay tuned in for this one.


Stunningly clear video footage has captured a hungry and determined squirrel chowing down on an unfortunate mouse. 


And you thought squirrels were vegetarians.


Well, apparently not. So yes, while it&#x2019;s true that squirrels love nuts, they&#x2019;re not exactly what you&#x2019;d call fussy eaters.


Although several varieties of the species are in fact herbivores that live on a plant-based diet, many squirrels are omnivores with an unequivocal taste for meat.


Some ground squirrels like nothing better than scarfing down on insects, worms and even small mice &#x2014; something clearly demonstrated in this video.</description>
      <tags>video,Squirrel,mouse,squirrel eats mouse,squirrel eating mouse,squirrel eating rat,rodent,gross animals,cannibal animals</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231752</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 21:29:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/4EC/739/4EC7392FF29749D595161B048448B7A5_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/15/3231752/3231752_7C3D42E5418047E79A15CAA250766A89_161215_3231752_Squirrel_eats_mouse__Hungry_squirrel_has_fellow__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport shooting: Suspect found dead after gunning down Southwest employee in Oklahoma - TomoNews</title>
      <description>OKLAHOMA CITY &#x2014; Will Rogers World Airport in Oklahoma City was closed for most of Tuesday following a shooting that took the life of one Southwest Airlines employee.


KFOR reports that the 52-year-old shooting victim was identified as Michael Winchester, a former University of Oklahoma football player whose son plays for the Kansas City Chiefs.


Winchester was reportedly shot while walking near the airport parking garage shortly before 1 p.m. on Tuesday. He was found wounded and bleeding and brought to the hospital, where he later succumbed to his injuries.


Officers arrived at the scene and immediately put the airport on lockdown. Flights were suspended, vehicles barred from entering and leaving, and passengers told to seek cover.


Police armed with rifles searched the complex for the suspect, and later found him dead inside the parking garage hours later. His body was found in a red pickup truck. There was a gunshot wound to his head, which was believed to be self-inflicted, according to News9.


Authorities are still investigating the incident and have yet to disclose a motive for the killing, which some media outlets suggest was a premeditated act.</description>
      <tags>video,Oklahoma airport shooting,oklahoma shooting,airport shooting,southwest employee shot,michael winchester,michael winchester shooting,will rogers airport shooting,airport gunman</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231036</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 00:19:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FE2/59D/FE259DB295B24D9788F3251DBF0B551C_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/16/3231036/3231036_64C0F846C57942858F72FF2D1A388032_161214_3231036_Airport_shooting__Suspect_found_dead_after_gunni_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain implant device allows ALS patient to communicate with brain activity without help - TomoNews</title>
      <description>UTRECHT, NETHERLANDS &#x2014; Researchers in the Netherlands have developed a brain implant that enables a woman with Lou Gehrig&#x2019;s disease, also known as ALS, to communicate using brain activity, and without a doctor&#x2019;s supervision.

An electrocorticograph, developed by researchers at the University Medical Center Utrecht, consists of four electrode strips of about 5 cm long, with each holding four small electrodes. The electrode strips are implanted inside the skull against the brain.

According to the study published in the New England Journal of Medicine, two of the electrode strips are placed over the region of the left motor cortex that controls hand movements, and the other two are placed over the left prefrontal cortex as a backup. The electrode strips are connected to an transmitter device that is installed inside the left side of the patient&#x2019;s chest. The implant wirelessly connects to a receiver via an antenna and to a tablet computer mounted on the wheelchair.

To activate the electrodes, the patient thinks about moving her right hand, which triggers the electrodes to send signals down to the transmitter in the chest. This eventually resulting in her hand moving a cursor to make an input on the computer screen. If the patient&#x2019;s motor cortex degenerates over time, she would counter backwards to activate the backup electrodes placed over her prefrontal cortex, as this region is responsible for mental calculation.

ALS affects the neurons that are required for voluntary muscle control and causes complete paralysis within a couple of years. According to the ALS Association, about 6,000 people in the U.S. are diagnosed with ALS each year. There is no known cure to the disease.</description>
      <tags>video,Lou Gehrig,ALS,paralysis,paralyzed,ALS patient video,ALS communication device,brain implant</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231019</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 00:06:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/490/3CE/4903CEF1DC494B938619D322A5F6B3AA_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/16/3231019/3231019_C9E5471FAD734EE8B085CEEEED9B08C9_161214_3231019_Brain_implant_device_allows_ALS_patient_to_commu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old ladies fight off carjacker from notorious Milwaukee carjacker ring</title>
      <description>MILWAUKEE &#x2014; A couple of carjackers thought stealing from two old ladies would be a piece of cake, only to learn the hard way that it&#x2019;s best not to underestimate the elderly, especially if they&#x2019;re ex-military.

WISN reports that on Oct. 22, Miriam Ben-Shalom and her partner Karen Weiss pulled up to the valet stand of Hotel Metro in Milwaukee for a night of fine French dining.

But while Ben-Shalom was grabbing Weiss&#x2019; walker from the back of the car, a teen, later identified as 17-year-old Junior Moreno, attempted to steal the car. Unfortunately for him, ex-Army drill sergeant Ben-Shalom was not one to be trifled with.

She quickly tackled the carjacker to the ground, then stood up and threatened him with a boot to his privates.

While the teen was pinned down, Weiss pulled his hoodie back with her cane to ID his face. But before the police could arrive, a black Jeep Cherokee carrying the carjacker&#x2019;s accomplices pulled up.

Jesus Lazaro was in the driver&#x2019;s seat as 18-year-old Giovanni Zurfluh got out and threatened to shoot the women if they didn&#x2019;t let their friend go. The hooligans managed to get away, but not before the retirees got hold of their license number.

The three suspects, who turned out to be members of the Cut Throat Mob carjacking ring, were apprehended in December, thanks to key information from the women.

The trio was allegedly involved in more than a dozen other thefts, and together is facing 31 felony charges.</description>
      <tags>video,Old lady veterans,old ladies fight back,milwaukee carjacking,cut throat mob,cut throat carjackers,carjacking ring,milwaukee carjacking ring,miriam ben-shalom,karen weiss</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3233031</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 04:31:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E28/4EB/E284EB4F016442B2B9100193E4F3F906_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/16/3233031/3233031_1E9C5188798D49C09F40379F1C66E62B_161216_3233031_Old_ladies_fight_off_carjacker_from_notorious_Mi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian guy beats up white man after racial slurs: London student cleared of assault</title>
      <description>LONDON &#x2014; A 20-year-old Asian man has been cleared of all charges in the aftermath of a racially-charged incident earlier this year. In March of 2016, Sidney Chan and a group of his friends were on their way home from a night on the town in London.

As they passed the Royal Albert Hall, a man started calling out racial slurs in their direction, telling them to &#x201C;F--- off back to China,&#x201D; among a handful of other unfriendly comments. The group of friends tried to steer clear of the man, named Stephen Kent, but he kept on coming, and started running toward them. Kent then grabbed a female in the group and started spouting sleazy comments at her.

Sidney Chan stepped in and pushed Kent off his friend, but Kent retaliated with a swing. At that point, to protect his friends from the violent man, Chan did what he had to do as a matter of self-defense. Kent ended up with a fractured nose, a fractured eye socket, and a heavy concussion, injuries he tried to make Chan pay for. 

On Nov. 25, a jury unanimously found Chan not guilty of wounding with intent.</description>
      <tags>video,Stephen Kent,sidney chan,imperial college union,royal albert hall,racism</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3233017</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 04:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/11A/00A/11A00AFDF73C4D2A980927B8C7A88D57_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/16/3233017/3233017_C6808AB966C04F478EFFCFC777FE8FDF_161216_3233017_Asian_guy_beats_up_white_man_after_racial_slurs__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian woman drops cellphone into vat of molten chocolate, dies trying to get it back</title>
      <description>FEDORTSOVO, RUSSIA &#x2014; A worker at a Russian chocolate factory got a golden ticket to the afterlife when she fell into a vat of the sticky brown stuff and died.

Russian media reports said mom-of-two Svetlana Roslina dropped her cellphone into a vat of molten chocolate at the Sergiev-Posad confectionery factory in Fedortsovo, about 80 miles northeast of Moscow, the Telegraph reported.

The 24-year-old then tried to fish her phone out, but instead fell right into the thick choco gloop. Other reports said the woman was pouring flour into the mix when she fell in.

Regardless of the reason, Roslina wound up inside the container, and that was the end of the poor woman as she was minced alive by the vat&#x2019;s mixers.

Following the incident, staff at the factory said that only Roslina&#x2019;s legs remained. Local residents said they later saw a police car and a hearse driving into the factory.

The victim leaves behind a husband, Vladimir, and two young children.

Russian police were investigating, but this looks to us like a clear case of death by chocolate.</description>
      <tags>video,Weird deaths,drowned in chocolate,drowning in chocolate,Sergiev Posad,Sergiev Posad chocolate,chocolate factory death</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3233007</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 03:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D58/1E1/D581E11F667440E1B6D340319CF5DB7B_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/16/3233007/3233007_552FFEBE35CF43FFA5393C8B133C4C64_161216_3233007_Russian_woman_drops_cellphone_into_vat_of_molten_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim teen arrested for making up anti-Muslim attack</title>
      <description>NEW YORK CITY, NEW YORK &#x2014; A Muslim woman who claimed she was victim of a hate crime by Trump supporters was arrested after she confessed that she made up the entire incident. 

18-year-old Baruch College student Yasmin Seweid told New York police she was harassed by three white men shouting &#x201C;Donald Trump&#x2019;&#x2019; at the 23rd Street subway station on Dec. 1, New York Daily News reported.

Seweid&#x2019;s said the men called her a &#x201C;terrorist&#x201D; and tried to pull off her hijab, while bystanders just watched. Seweid later posted about the experience on her Facebook account. She also claimed that a Trump America is real since she witnessed it herself.  

Only problem was, Seweid made it all up. She had plenty of chances to tell the truth to the police as they devoted precious resources to investigating the incident

Doubts were raised when detectives failed to find witnesses or video of the incident. Suspicions surfaced when Seweid was reported missing last Thursday, then turned up safe at her sister&#x2019;s place in Fishkill last Friday. 

After again being questioned by detectives, Seweid confessed. She said she lied because she has issues with her strict Muslim parents over a Christian man she is seeing and she was out past her curfew drinking with friends. 

Seweid&#x2019;s parents allegedly shaved her hair off when they found out. 

She was charged with filing a false report and released after she appeared early Thursday in Manhattan Criminal Court. She faces up to a year in jail 

Seweid&#x2019;s father, Syeed, an Egyptian immigrant, said he didn&#x2019;t know why his daughter made up the story. He said: &#x201C;She&#x2019;s the one that can speak for herself.&#x201D;</description>
      <tags>video,Yasmin Seweid,false police report,Muslim hate crime,anti-Muslim,NYPD,trump supporters,discrimination,hate crime</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232702</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 01:02:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/270/CEE/270CEE54F012451DBDC66040F608F421_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/16/3232702/3232702_3DDE6C1FF5A547A29EF16DACAAE8DE48_161216_3232702_Muslim_teen_arrested_for_making_up_anti_Muslim_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte killing drug dealers: Philippine president brags he has hunted, killed suspects</title>
      <description>MANILA, PHILIPPINES &#x2014;  On Monday, Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte bragged that&#x2019;d he has killed people during his tenure as mayor of Davao City.

He was speaking to business leaders at the presidential palace in Manila when he boasted, &#x201C;In Davao I used to do it personally. Just to show the guys if I can do it, why can&#x2019;t you?&#x201D;, reported the BBC.

Duterte explained that he&#x2019;d drive around the city on his big boy bike and would go on patrol. He also admitted &#x201C;I was really looking for an encounter so I could kill,&#x201D; reported CNN. 

Since being voted in as president this summer, Duterte&#x2019;s extrajudicial death squads have reportedly killed around 6,000 suspects during his bloody war on drugs.</description>
      <tags>video,Facebook,mark zuckerberg,censorship,election 2016,donald trump,news censorship,fake news,fake news on facebook</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232627</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 22:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/00B/C40/00BC406028D24B40A368239014560B6C_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/16/3232627/3232627_FF08DB0D7A8C460BB077AFFF723A38E1_161216_3232627_Duterte_killing_drug_dealers__Philippine_preside_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RiverRide: Chicago may build floating, solar-powered bike path along Chicago River - TomoNews</title>
      <description>CHICAGO &#x2014; Chicago may consider building a floating bike path along the edge of the Chicago River in an effort to become the most &#x2018;bike-friendly city&#x2019; in the U.S.


Known as the RiverRide, the proposed bike path would float on the Chicago River between Horner and Ping Tom Parks, according to architecture firm Second Shore, which proposed the idea.


The bike path is built on steel-reinforced concrete pontoons, which are secured with pilings driven in the riverbed. Each 82-foot long by 12-foot wide segment is equipped with solar panels to generate power for lighting. More segments can be connected to extend the path.


The path is also embedded with a heating conduit to prevent icing on the surface. It also has retractable awnings that can roll out to shelter riders from rain and snow.


Each mile of the bike path might cost between $5 to $10 million. According to Co.Exist, Second Shore hopes a half mile of the bike path will be built in a pilot project by the summer of 2017.</description>
      <tags>video,Second shore,riverride chicago,chicago bike path,chicago floating bike path,chicago solar powered bike path,chicago bike friendly,cycling,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231211</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 02:29:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>60</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D5B/A3B/D5BA3B565A20480BA4768A14422914A3_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/17/3231211/3231211_AA04DF681C8F4DB8917FF74B7212A8AD_161214_3231211_RiverRide__Chicago_may_build_floating__solar_pow_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black gold: Largest oil deposit in the US discovered in West Texas, worth $900 billion - TomoNews</title>
      <description>MIDLAND, TEXAS &#x2014; The largest oil deposit ever found in the U.S. was recently discovered in Texas&#x2019; Permian Basin.


The discovery was announced by the U.S. Geological Survey, which says the area reportedly contains an estimated 20 billion barrels of oil and 1.6 billion barrels of natural gas liquids.


With a barrel of oil priced at $45, according to West Texas Intermediate rates, the entire deposit could be worth around $900 billion.


The shale deposits were found in the basin&#x2019;s Midland portion, in a section called Wolfcamp which already has more than 3,000 active oil wells.


Tapping into the deposits requires directional drilling, where the drill is turned horizontally at depth when it reaches the shale layer. Small fractures are created in the rock before fracking liquid is pumped in a high pressure to untap oil and gas deposits from the shale.</description>
      <tags>video,Oil deposit,shale oil deposit,texas oil,texas oil deposit,permian basin,midland basin,wolfcamp,black gold,oil in america,us oil</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231204</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 02:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/124/894/124894EA18DE4EAA8BCBF71A6398CF0E_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/17/3231204/3231204_6B69F9698ECC4F17B4E6877BEF78AE5E_161214_3231204_Black_gold__Largest_oil_deposit_in_the_US_discov_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pneumatic waste disposal: Swedish company&#x2019;s pneumatic vacuum tubes suck trash away - TomoNews</title>
      <description>STOCKHOLM &#x2014; Swedish company Envac has designed an underground pipeline system that can collect trash by vacuum.


According to the company, the waste inlets can be located outdoors or indoors. When the waste is being thrown into the inlet, it will then slide down a pipe and enter a waste tank underground. The waste tank is emptied by a vacuum truck when it reaches its capacity.


The truck empties the tank via a docking point, which is often located outside residential areas. It has a vacuum system on board, which sucks the waste out of the tanks and into the truck, where it is compressed.


The waste collection system can be upgraded to include a pay-as-you-throw function that charges users on what they throw into the inlets.


The vacuum waste collection system was developed in the late 1980s. It has since been installed in countries such as Sweden, Denmark and Norway.


According to Waste360, Coney Island and a new development in Chelsea district in New York are considering installing the vacuum system.</description>
      <tags>video,Envac,pneumatic vacuum tube,vacuum tube sucks trash away,mobile vacuum trash collection,envac vacuum trash collection,underground trash pipeline,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231267</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 02:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0A7/205/0A72053F847B4DBEA8966AD59F2E9245_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/18/3231267/3231267_11255DD305E649C79080973BB5905CA2_161214_3231267_Pneumatic_waste_disposal__Swedish_company___s_pn_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber flying cars: How Uber hopes to launch a fleet of self flying electric cabs by 2026 - TomoNews</title>
      <description>SAN FRANCISCO &#x2014; Ride hailing company Uber released a white paper in October that envisions a future where commuters jetting city from to city in compact aircraft is as normal as taking the train.


Uber&#x2019;s prediction of a world with commonplace urban air transit systems relies heavily on the widespread use of small self-flying electric aircraft with vertical takeoff and landing capability. Also known as VTOL, it is most commonly used by helicopters, as well as a small number of military aircraft.


According to the Uber white paper, a network of VTOL hubs or landing pads, dubbed &#x201C;vertiports&#x201D; and &#x201C;vertistops&#x201D;, could be used as terminals to ferry passengers. Unlike cars, buses and trains, VTOLs aren&#x2019;t susceptible traffic jams or delays  &#x2014; they can fly from A to B with no fixed route. The company estimates the cost of a 15-minute flight may eventually reach as low as $21.


The aircraft would fly at cruise speeds of around 150 miles per hour and won&#x2019;t go above 10,000 feet. The VTOL would be powered by rechargeable batteries that&#x2019;d maintain 30-minutes of reserve energy. 


Uber won&#x2019;t manufacture the aircraft, but reckons the market will create them in the next five years, reported Wired, citing the white paper.</description>
      <tags>video,Uber,The flying car,flying car,flying taxi,flying uber,vtol,uber vtol,uber vtol services,flying uber explained,urban air transport</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231250</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 02:47:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>115</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A46/4D5/A464D5F203BC4FAFAD7EA61244B5C913_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/18/3231250/3231250_11432E598BD6482489F7599F24807613_161214_3231250_Uber_flying_cars__How_Uber_hopes_to_launch_a_fle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software on US Android phones secretly sent personal user information to China - TomoNews</title>
      <description>SHANGHAI &#x2014; American security firm Kryptowire discovered preinstalled software on several Android phone models in the U.S. that secretly monitored its users.


The company stumbled upon the issue after noticing unusual network activity on a BLU R1 HD mobile phone owned by a researcher. According to the Kryptowire report, software on the device was found to be collecting message and call logs, contact lists, location information, and other personal data.


After encryption, the information was transmitted to four servers in Shanghai, later found to be registered to a Chinese company called Shanghai Adups Technology Co., Ltd. Data transmission occurred every 72 hours for message and call logs, and every 24 hours for other personally identifiable information.


Adups&#x2019; software was also capable of executing remote commands, including installing and updating applications on a phone. Anti-virus tools assumed the software was not malware since it came with the device, and were thus unable to detect its suspicious behavior.


Adups claims the software was designed to help a Chinese manufacturer monitor user behavior, but that it was never meant to be on American phones.


The full scope of the problem is still unclear, though 120,000 phones from American manufacturer BLU were among those affected.</description>
      <tags>video,Android phone,android spyware,android malware,data leak,adups software,security risk,china spying,android backdoor,blu phones,blu security risk</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231246</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 02:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/29C/2E9/29C2E94C37334860922D80CB489F9E96_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/18/3231246/3231246_97B82BBDD29C41EAAB9DCE2E0CE6DFD6_161214_3231246_Software_on_US_Android_phones_secretly_sent_pers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scenes: Trump hits the dance floor with Taiwan, China presidents in parody dance video</title>
      <description>For anyone who&#x2019;s ever wondered who the groovy people are behind Trump and Tsai Ing-wen&#x2019;s rad dance moves, here&#x2019;s a sneak a peek at the motion capture folks who gave their all so the US-Taiwan-China parody dance video could grace your screens.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Donald Trump,Tsai Ing-wen,Xi Jinping,parody dance video,mocap,motion capture,behind the scenes,BTS,Taiwan,China,USA</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3234750</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 02:36:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>98</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0DE/E16/0DEE16F805564E00B570409E97D7E58D_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/19/3234750/3234750_4D9097BD490142F7B4B9A9B1A6B00614_161219_3234750_Behind_the_Scenes__Trump_hits_the_dance_floor_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake beard disguise: Florida gas station victimized by robber with magic marker beard</title>
      <description>HOLIDAY, FLORIDA &#x2014; A robber hit up a gas station in Holiday, Florida with a disguise so effective the cops have no idea whether the criminal mastermind is a he or a she.

Instead of using a ski mask like a normal robber, this one simply used a magic marker to doodle on a fake beard before targeting the Holiday Gas Station around 8:30 p.m. on Wednesday. 

Patch Media&#x2019;s New Port Richey site reports that despite not having any sort of weapon, or even implying that there was one, the robber scared the gas station&#x2019;s female clerk enough to get her to comply to demands.

After managing to get some cash, the genius robber fled the scene in a gray Toyota pickup truck.

Police are looking out for the fake-bearded suspect, but have yet to zero in on his or her identity. The culprit won&#x2019;t be easy to spot, unless of course the facial hair was courtesy of a permanent pen.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Fake beard disguise,fake beard,robber disguise,magic marker beard,drawn on beard,sharpie beard,permanent marker,magic marker</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235745</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 06:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6D9/17D/6D917D646E8C47AE9E6B6F716D18B780_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235745/3235745_71FF62F0A0554766AD17AA36BE26258F_161220_3235745_Fake_beard_disguise__Florida_gas_station_victimi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia alcohol problem: 49 people die in Siberia after drinking bath liquid to get drunk</title>
      <description>IRKUTSK, RUSSIA &#x2014; Dozens of people have died in the Siberian city of Irkutsk, and a bath liquid commonly used as a cheap alcohol substitute is to blame. 

The liquid in question is reported to be a counterfeit version of a hawthorn-scented bath relaxant, which many Russians use to become inebriated. The bath liquid is less expensive than the cheapest vodka sold in Russia, making it an attractive alcoholic alternative for the poor. While it may be listed as 93 percent ethanol, tests reveal the liquid also contains methanol, a toxic ingredient in antifreeze that can be fatal if ingested.

Medical professionals estimate that as many as 12 million Russians consume alcoholic alternatives each year, which also include perfumes and window cleaners.

Authorities have detained seven people involved in the production of the substance and seized 2,000 bottles from stores.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Russia alcohol problem,russia alcoholism,russian alcoholics,alcoholics,alcohol,Bath liquid alcohol,Boyaryshnik,Hawthorn liquid,russian drunks</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235743</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 06:06:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EE6/E61/EE6E616F96554F14BE3277042798C90E_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235743/3235743_270623D1C03E47FD9351E9277EB6934E_161220_3235743_Russia_alcohol_problem__49_people_die_in_Siberia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity sex robots: Realistic sex doll clones expected to be on the market soon</title>
      <description>&#x2019;MURICA&#x2014; Advances in robot technology will soon allow manufacturers to replicate the finer details of appearance and sound when it comes to creating dolls for sexual pleasure.

Sex doll engineers will be able to create robot clones by using photographs to copy eye colour, voice, dimensions and personality traits, the Daily Star reported.

The sex droids will have a lifelike pulse and warm skin, and advances in artificial intelligence could allow for the robots to sound like their real-life counterparts.

Celebrity A-listers are expected to have the luxury of licensing their likenesses to rake in even more cash. Unfortunately for the average person, there won&#x2019;t be any way of preventing robotic clones from being produced. People will just have to accept that they may not own the rights to their appearance where robots are concerned.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Sex robots,robot clones,sex robot clones,sexbots,artificial intelligence,sex with robots,david levy,love and sex with robots,celebrity robots,celebrity clones,celebrity sex,celebrity sex robots</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235717</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 05:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F8A/88B/F8A88BBD43264982B6A54408CC125763_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235717/3235717_708703E3482F47B0AF9AC3A51DFD0FB5_161220_3235717_Celebrity_sex_robots__Realistic_sex_doll_clones__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wedding disasters: Falling giant tree kills guest, crushes 5 others in California</title>
      <description>WHITTIER, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; Disaster struck at a wedding in southern California on the weekend when a guest was crushed to death by a giant tree. 

The wedding party was posing for a group shot at Penn Park in Whittier on Saturday when the 100-foot eucalyptus tree came crashing down on them, the Whittier Daily News reported. 

As many as 20 guests were trapped underneath the tree, so the fire department used chainsaws to cut them out.

One of the guests, described as an older woman, died on her way to the hospital. Five other guests were injured, including a 4-year-old girl, but they&#x2019;re all reportedly all right.

It&#x2019;s unknown why the tree fell, but one theory is it could have been weakened by years of drought in California, which forced its thirsty roots above ground. Heavy rains last Friday night may then have loosened up the roots even further.

Witnesses said the tree split in two as it came crashing down to earth with a thunderous bang.

The traumatized wedding guests were offered counseling at the scene.

Authorities have been inspecting other trees in the park in case any more decide to come falling down.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Wedding disasters,wedding fails,tree falls on woman,tree falls on people,tree kills woman,crushed by tree,california drought</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235506</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 01:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2B2/275/2B227555DA46469FBA6CB4D23064854C_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235506/3235506_34B8CAE7D30F4CC3AC3A5A876E8C7EA7_161220_3235506_Wedding_disasters__Falling_giant_tree_kills_gues_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diver found dead with throat slit and body tied to concrete pole off Thailand beach</title>
      <description>PATTAYA, THAILAND  &#x2014; Police in Thailand are investigating the death of an unidentified man, possibly a Russian national, who was found on Friday with his throat slit near the resort of Pattaya.
 
A jet-ski driver discovered the body tied to a concrete pole near Samae beach on the island of Koh Larn, a short boat ride from Pattaya. The victim was wearing a diver&#x2019;s wetsuit and flippers, Asia One reported.

Police found a backpack strapped to the victim containing 1,500 Thai baht (about $42). The cops said the man was white, around 5 feet 6 inches tall, and between 45 and 50 years old.

As reported by the Bangkok Post, police divers found a snorkel, a cutter, a swimming cap, swimming goggles and other items from the seafloor near the concrete pole. 

Police later questioned a fisherman and his wife. They also spoke with the owner of a resort on the beach on Sunday. None of them recognized the diver. However, the owner of a dive shop told police that the man looked like one of his clients.

Cops said on Thursday that witnesses heard the victim speaking Russian. The body has been transferred to Bangkok for an autopsy.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Tourists in thailand,tourist died in Thailand,tourist killed in Thailand,mystery murder,murder,samae beach,pattaya,koh larn</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235403</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 23:44:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>45</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/777/7BF/7777BF294BF24C0F8E52738B2043E28C_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235403/3235403_BB1CDF0BB2C14F10A1C78A4578E8BE1B_161220_3235403_Diver_found_dead_with_throat_slit_and_body_tied__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber driver shoots robber: Would-be robber shot dead by armed Uber driver in Florida</title>
      <description>AVENTURA, FLORIDA &#x2014; An Uber driver turned the tables on an armed criminal, fighting back and possibly saving both his and his passenger&#x2019;s lives.

WSVN reports that the driver had picked up the passenger from a condo in Aventura, Florida just before 6 a.m. on Sunday.

The two were on the William Lehman causeway en route to Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood Airport when a Dodge Caravan minivan carrying two people abruptly cut them off.

A man jumped out of the vehicle and aimed two guns at the Uber driver, demanding he hand over his belongings.

Instead, the driver pulled out his own weapon and fired shots at the suspect.

Seeing his accomplice dead, the minivan&#x2019;s other passenger got behind the wheel and quickly drove away.

Police later located the vehicle, and are reportedly questioning a person of interest. Whether or not it&#x2019;s one of the suspects is unclear.

The Uber driver was revealed to have a concealed carry permit, and will likely not be charged. His Uber driving days might be coming to an end though, since the ride-sharing app expressly prohibits drivers and riders from carrying firearms when in a vehicle.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Armed uber driver,uber driver shoots robber,florida robbery,uber robbery,uber attempted robbery,armed uber,aventura,concealed carry permit,2nd amendment rights</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235398</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 23:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E9C/DC4/E9CDC4642B534C08BD4D6E5F874C7429_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235398/3235398_6461BDCF5A544EE79998DB090FD20C5F_161220_3235398_Uber_driver_shoots_robber__Would_be_robber_shot__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake eats dog: Python dies after being trapped in fence due to dog-sized stomach bulge</title>
      <description>WARRI, NIGERIA &#x2014; Karma came swiftly for one voracious python, who got screwed over by his dinner and ended up dying for it.

Naij.com reports that after gorging itself on a whole canine, the six-foot-long reptile tried to slither out of a grassy lot in Warri, Nigeria. But halfway through, its doggie bump got wedged in between two iron rods and just wouldn&#x2019;t budge.

With no way to squeeze itself out, the snake reportedly remained in the tight spot for several hours, and was dead by the time a local man discovered it.

Shocked at seeing such a huge animal, the man called a few more people to inspect slithers and make sure it had gone to serpent heaven.

The men freed the python and cut its stomach open to reveal the doggie dinner. They then built a fire and promptly burned the snake.

Photos of the snake were uploaded on Facebook back in July, but only recently went viral after being picked up by a number of news outlets.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Greedy python,python trapped in fence,trapped python,python eats dog,snake eats dog,python kills dog,snake kills dog,hungry snake,snake vs dog,snake attacks dog,snake attack,dead snake,dead python,snake swallows dog,python swallows dog</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235346</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 22:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>43</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/51A/A8B/51AA8B01DE694674B2DE168F74CB8615_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235346/3235346_ADB6B83ED4494B5FAB489A9979684666_161220_3235346_Snake_eats_dog__Python_dies_after_being_trapped__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio cop shooting: police officer killed inside squad car while writing a ticket - TomoNews</title>
      <description>SAN ANTONIO &#x2014; A Texas police officer was killed inside a squad car parked outside San Antonio police headquarters on Sunday.

Speaking at a news conference, Chief William McManus said Detective Benjamin Marconi was writing a ticket inside a police vehicle right before noon when the suspect&#x2019;s car pulled up behind him. The suspect, described as a slim black man in his 20s or 30s, reportedly walked up to the driver&#x2019;s side window and fired at Marconi, before reaching through the open window and opening fire again. Marconi was struck in the head and killed.

The suspect then reportedly walked back to his car, said to be a black Toyota or Nissan sedan with dark windows and chrome rims, and fled the scene through the police headquarters parking lot and from the west side of the building.

McManus compared the incident to to the recent deaths of police officers in Dallas and Baton Rouge, Louisiana. Both of those cases came after police were involved in the shootings of civilians that eventually sparked nationwide protests.

Police are still investigating the motive behind the San Antonio shooting.

Detective Marconi, 50, was a 20-year veteran of the force.</description>
      <tags>video,San Antonio cop shooting,cop killer,man shoots cop in texas,cop killed by black man,gunman shoots at cops,texas shooting 2016</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232892</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 02:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/341/487/341487703D4B44EE88584E3DA67BB44A_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/21/3232892/3232892_0031DFEC77824D4EACA26B9426010FC4_161216_3232892_San_Antonio_cop_shooting__police_officer_killed__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India train crash: 120 dead, 200 injured after Indore-Patna Express derails near Kanpur - TomoNews</title>
      <description>KANPUR, INDIA &#x2014; Over a hundred people were killed, and many more injured in one of India&#x2019;s worst train disasters in recent years.


The Times of India reports that the incident occurred early Sunday morning, when an overnight passenger train from Indore to Patna suddenly derailed in Pukhrayan, near the city of Kanpur.


The event took place at approximately 3 a.m., when most of the 500 passengers were asleep. A suspected rail fracture caused the train to jump off the tracks. People inside were jolted awake and reportedly violently flung around as the cars began to topple over.


Two sleeper cars also reportedly telescoped into each other and trapped those inside.


A total of 14 carriages were derailed, killing at least 120 people and injuring 200.


Rescuers have had difficulty cutting through the metal compartments. By Sunday afternoon, they were using heavy machinery to get survivors out.


India&#x2019;s railway system is the fourth largest in the world, but it is also reportedly one of the most unsafe, with thousands dying in accidents, collisions, and derailments each year, according to Reuters.</description>
      <tags>video,India train crash,india train accident,india train derailment,india train derail,train crash,train accident,india rail crash,india rail disaster,train derailment,train derail,train disaster,rail disaster</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232092</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 03:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>46</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/007/B32/007B32E20E6E475CB799F51895F35902_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/21/3232092/3232092_2E1C35D636DB46F08621E8EE1BDE7F20_161215_3232092_India_train_crash__120_dead__200_injured_after_I_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio cop shooting: police officer killed inside squad car while writing a ticket - TomoNews</title>
      <description>SAN ANTONIO &#x2014; A Texas police officer was killed inside a squad car parked outside San Antonio police headquarters on Sunday.


Speaking at a news conference, Chief William McManus said Detective Benjamin Marconi was writing a ticket inside a police vehicle right before noon when the suspect&#x2019;s car pulled up behind him. The suspect, described as a slim black man in his 20s or 30s, reportedly walked up to the driver&#x2019;s side window and fired at Marconi, before reaching through the open window and opening fire again. Marconi was struck in the head and killed.


The suspect then reportedly walked back to his car, said to be a black Toyota or Nissan sedan with dark windows and chrome rims, and fled the scene through the police headquarters parking lot and from the west side of the building.


McManus compared the incident to to the recent deaths of police officers in Dallas and Baton Rouge, Louisiana. Both of those cases came after police were involved in the shootings of civilians that eventually sparked nationwide protests.


Police are still investigating the motive behind the San Antonio shooting.


Detective Marconi, 50, was a 20-year veteran of the force.</description>
      <tags>video,San Antonio cop shooting,cop killer,man shoots cop in texas,cop killed by black man,gunman shoots at cops,texas shooting 2016</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232083</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 03:19:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>42</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/267/ED8/267ED84F13834370BEF2E74F5B334D7E_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/21/3232083/3232083_473EF472020B42F292B1F6ED00D7EA41_161215_3232083_San_Antonio_cop_shooting__police_officer_killed__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The democratic bubble: survey says left wing liberals more likely to unfriend opposers</title>
      <description>USA &#x2014; A new poll by the Public Religion Research Institute reveals people&#x2019;s political views have created serious division during the holiday season.

According to the poll, 28 percent of Democrats say they have blocked or unfriended someone on social media after viewing a post they disagreed with, compared to only 8 percent of conservatives who say they would do the same. Women surveyed were also twice as likely as men to unfriend someone, and 30 percent of female Democrats said they&#x2019;d cut someone out for their political views, compared to just 14 percent of male Democrats.

Democrats were also five times more likely to actively avoid friends and family as a result of their politics than Republicans were, 10 percent vs. 2 percent. Most Democrats also take exception to those wishing others a &#x201C;Merry Christmas.&#x201D; The majority of Democrats surveyed would prefer the greeting more commonly used be &#x201C;Happy Holidays!&#x201D; On the other hand, 67 percent of Republicans responded that stores and businesses should continue on with &#x201C;Merry Christmas.&#x201D;</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Facebook,unfriending,democrats unfriend,PRRI,happy holidays,merry christmas,left wing,liberals</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236401</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 02:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>25</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C38/9D7/C389D760414441C284492D205730D9D8_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236401/3236401_071AF9F194F54E219A91B14C517809F1_161221_3236401_The_democratic_bubble__survey_says_left_wing_lib_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koala covered in prickles gets a brush from a neighbor after escaping horny males</title>
      <description>APOLLO BAY, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; When a koala ended up on a friendly man&#x2019;s doorstep covered in prickles, he tried helping it in a variety of ways, until realizing all it needed was a good brush.

On the morning of December 17, Bruce Atkinson was on his way out the door to get breakfast. Standing on his front porch, he noticed a disheveled koala bear approaching him, covered in prickly burrs. Atkinson quickly tried to offer the koala a bowl of water, but the koala swiftly batted it away, as koalas get their water solely from eucalyptus leaves. 

Bruce Atkinson then tried his best to clean her up a bit, grabbing a brush and brushing her from head to toe, a treatment she seemed to enjoy. Bruce Atkinson says a wildlife officer suggested the koala may have been trying to escape the advances of the males in the area, who tend to get a little bit frisky this time of year due to mating season.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Koala,cute koala,koala prickles,koala brush,koala mating,koala video,apollo bay</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236394</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 02:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/661/19A/66119A4386334E678AC58B96F300955A_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236394/3236394_CDCB896B8442464DBF41792D001E9900_161221_3236394_Koala_covered_in_prickles_gets_a_brush_from_a_ne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti porn bill: South Carolina pill seeks to filter out porn from devices sold in state</title>
      <description>COLUMBIA, SOUTH CAROLINA &#x2014; State representatives Bill Chumley and Mike Burns are hell-bent on passing a bill that would make it harder and more expensive to access adult content online. Why? To combat human trafficking, they say.

The Spartanburg Herald Journal reports that under their Human Trafficking Prevention Act, all devices sold in South Carolina will need to be installed with a digital blocking system to filter out obscene content.

The proposed bill has a loophole though: Manufacturers or sellers could opt out if they fork over $20 per gadget.

Buyers who want the porn filters gone from their devices will also need to pay the same amount, on top of submitting a written request and proving they&#x2019;re over 18.

All the money collected will supposedly go to the South Carolina attorney general&#x2019;s human trafficking task force, as funding for anti-trafficking efforts.

The bill has already been referred to the South Carolina House Judiciary Committee and will be considered when the legislative session resumes in January.

As it is though, the bill will infringe on some pretty basic First Amendment rights, so who knows whether it will even get passed.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Human trafficking prevention act,Anti porn bill,south carolina bill,porn block,south carolina porn block,porn filter,bill chumley,mike burns,south carolina,anti human trafficking</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236387</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 02:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/136/E1C/136E1C22045E47FD9204FE48E3C24EDA_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236387/3236387_1437D31103814E36949849BDA817EE18_161221_3236387_Anti_porn_bill__South_Carolina_pill_seeks_to_fil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lonely Snowman: Taiwanese Animators and the Snowman wish y&#x2019;all a merry merry Christmas</title>
      <description>&#x2018;MURICA &#x2014; Tis the season to be jolly, and what would the Christmas season be without a cheery snowman.

With children across the U.S. enjoying the frosty weather and pre-Christmas snow, what better way to celebrate than by going out and building a snowman?

We here at the Taiwanese Animators also have a good old snowman of our own, and he&#x2019;s back again this holiday season to spread cheer to kids and parents across the globe.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Snowman,snowman animation,lonely snowman,lonely snowman animation,snowman cartoon,Santa Claus,elf,snow,Christmas</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236349</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 01:44:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>126</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/76F/B70/76FB70DBCAE74951BA1B4CA186A61F26_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236349/3236349_2BE8DFD3986D4A09B8CF1895CA7C0C59_161221_3236349_Lonely_Snowman__Taiwanese_Animators_and_the_Snow_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-life Rapunzel from Russia has been growing her hair for 13 years</title>
      <description>BARNAUL, RUSSIA &#x2014; A real-life Rapunzel&#x2019;s fairytale length long locks have their roots in a teenage dare.

When Darya Gubanova Freckle was 14, she cut her knee-length braid. Two years later, a friend told her her hair would never be that long again. Darya set out prove her wrong. And did she ever. Thirteen years later, her hair is so long that people follow her on Instagram for it.

More than 209,000 people from all over the world, to be exact. Nicknamed the &#x201C;Russian Rapunzel,&#x201D; Darya hasn&#x2019;t cut her hair since 2003 &#x2014; and says she won&#x2019;t until it reaches her feet, Metro reported. 

It&#x2019;s not easy having hair this long. Darya, who lives in Barnaul, in the Altai Krai region of Siberian Russia, uses up a 17-ounce shampoo bottle every two months and spends at least five minutes a day combing her luscious locks until they are silky smooth. 

But she&#x2019;s proud of how strangers react to her hair in public. Once, a woman with a cane chased her for three bus stops just so she could compliment Darya on her hair. 

Now, the rest of her family is getting in on the trend. Her 6-year-old daughter is growing her hair out like her mother. Even Darya&#x2019;s husband has started to let his hair grow out, although the family won&#x2019;t say how long he wants his hair to be.

You can find out more about Darya and how she maintains her hair on her Instagram @DASHIK_GUBANOVA.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Rapunzel,Russian Rapunzel,real-life rapunzel,Darya Gubanova,Dashik Freckle,long hair,viral</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236342</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 01:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F63/F7C/F63F7CB94BF847169CA20304C1A16FAB_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236342/3236342_3790C995482D441A9075AE4697111F55_161221_3236342_Real_life_Rapunzel_from_Russia_has_been_growing__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake in Christmas tree: Aussie woman finds venomous tiger snake on her Christmas tree</title>
      <description>FRANKSTON, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; Not even the holidays are safe from Mother Nature in Australia, as one woman realized after she found a slithery surprise waiting in her Christmas tree.

In a Facebook post by professional snake catcher Barry Goldsmith that has since gone viral, a one-meter long reptile was retrieved from Frankston, Melbourne residence, where it was peacefully nesting in the home&#x2019;s Christmas tree. 

The homeowner, a woman named Cheryl, spotted the deadly new Christmas decor one morning, which turned out to be a venomous tiger snake.

Notorious for their potentially fatal bites, tiger snakes are one of the most dangerous snakes in Australia, and are common during the summer.

Despite probably knowing all of this, the woman calmly holed herself up in a room before sending a photo of her guest to Goldsmith.

Twenty minutes later, the tiger snake was in a bag, and Christmas was back to normal.

Goldsmith said the snake was eventually released back into the bush, far from humans and other Christmas trees.

Netizens were confused as to how a live snake could get itself onto a plastic Christmas tree, to which Goldsmith replied that the reptile most likely slithered in through an open door.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Christmas tree snake,snake in christmas tree,tiger snake,australia tiger snake,snake in tree,australia christmas,venomous snakes</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236232</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 23:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>35</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2EE/8B1/2EE8B1CEC05D4A80B9A6031317D7663D_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236232/3236232_F2CDC34087C646AFB3C8C95A16F6E504_161221_3236232_Snake_in_Christmas_tree__Aussie_woman_finds_veno_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber driver attacks passenger: Cabbie stabs passenger five times for tapping window</title>
      <description>BLOOMFIELD TOWNSHIP, MICHIGAN &#x2014; An Uber driver is in jail this week after he allegedly stabbed a passenger five times for tapping on his car window.

According to a Bloomfield Township police report posted by ClickOnDetroit, Jacob Matthew Allemon, aged 23, picked up a couple from a holiday party in Bloomfield, Michigan early Saturday morning. 

The man tapped on Allemon&#x2019;s window to let them know they were coming into his car. Police say Allemon felt this action was disrespectful to his vehicle. 

He drove them for around a mile, then stopped at a parking lot and told them to get out. The couple asked if they could wait for another ride, since they were in the middle of a snowstorm.

Instead, Allemon started fighting with the man. He reportedly stabbed him five times in his face, chest and neck, but, amazingly the 49-year-old victim managed to disarm and restrain him until a nearby police officer arrived.

According to the Detroit Free Press, the victim was treated at a hospital and released the following day.

Allemon, meanwhile, was charged with assault and is being held on $250,000 bond. Uber banned him from the ride-hailing app and described the incident as &#x201C;appalling.&#x201D;</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Uber driver attacks passenger,uber driver,uber,bloomfield township,michigan,jacob allemon,jacob matthew allemon,uber stab attack</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236106</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 21:08:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5AD/62E/5AD62ED8445B415EB03A4159F3D7C87F_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236106/3236106_DECD4A1F09BD4803A0F970816E5760FE_161221_3236106_Uber_driver_attacks_passenger__Cabbie_stabs_pass_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungee jump gone wrong: Brazilian man dives head-first into the ground in fatal jump</title>
      <description>S&#xC3;O PAULO &#x2014; The shocking moment that a Brazilian thrill-seeker died in front of his family in a bungee jump gone horribly wrong has been captured on video.

The incident happened on Sunday in S&#xE3;o Paulo state, when Fabio Ezequiel de Moraes, 36, thought it would be a good idea to jump off a 130-foot high railway bridge with an elastic cord tied around his ankle.

The only problem with that was nobody had checked to see if the cord was too long.

Moraes slammed head-first into the ground, the Sun reported, citing Brazilian newspaper Reporter Diario.

First responders arrived on the scene and rushed Moraes to the hospital but the head trauma proved too great, and he died soon afterward.

Things could have been a lot worse, though. Moraes originally planned to jump with his 6-year-old son, but decided at the last minute that he would do it solo.

Sadly however, the poor boy witnessed his father&#x2019;s tragic death. Moraes&#x2019; horrified wife, brother, and his brother&#x2019;s girlfriend also watched the fatal bungee jump.

Moraes hired a team of extreme sports specialists to help him do the jump. Police seized the team&#x2019;s equipment and were investigating Moraes&#x2019; death.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,bungee jump gone wrong,bungee jump fail,bungee jump accident,bungee jumping fails,man dies bungee jumping,bungee jump</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237185</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 02:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F31/444/F31444CCCC254699AAC74884AB93677C_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237185/3237185_4A74E74A4BE847B78A2056961F332DF6_161222_3237185_Bungee_jump_gone_wrong__Brazilian_man_dives_head_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great white shark: Fisherman hooks mammoth 3,000-pound shark off South Carolina</title>
      <description>HILTON HEAD, SOUTH CAROLINA &#x2014; A fisherman who routinely catches and releases sharks had the experience of a lifetime after hooking not one, but two of the great predators in a single day.

The Island Packet reports that after setting off near the Hilton Head coast in South Carolina on Tuesday, Captain Chip Michalove and his two-person crew hooked a female great white shark weighing an estimated 3,000 pounds. Before they could catch the mammoth shark, however, it spit out the hook and swam away.

According to his Facebook post, Michalove was disappointed and nearly called it a day, but decided to give it another shot after a short rest.

Another great white, this time male, soon came biting; and though not as massive as the first one, was still relatively large at nine and a half feet long.

After a bit of a struggle, the crew finally caught the shark, put an acoustic tag on him, and sent him on his merry way.

Tags typically stay on for seven years, and provide scientists with helpful data to study and protect the majestic predators.

All in all, it was a very productive day for Michalove and his crew. Still, the fisherman can&#x2019;t help but pine for the one that got away.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Great white shark,shark tagging,shark catch and release,catch and release,sport fishing,shark,3,000 pound great white,great white,chip michalove</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237172</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 02:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CD7/2EB/CD72EB581EB24973822758FE8A2588EF_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237172/3237172_8EFA320C2CFB4AA096FA0AE4BB33FCBF_161222_3237172_Great_white_shark__Fisherman_hooks_mammoth_3_000_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher disciplined after posing inappropriate algebra question to students</title>
      <description>MIDDLEBURG HEIGHTS, OHIO &#x2014; A math teacher at Middleburg Heights Junior High School outside Cleveland has been disciplined for showing his students a naughty algebra question.

Teacher Daniel Rapp got in trouble after one of his students snapped a photo of a sexting-related math problem displayed on their classroom&#x2019;s projector screen.

The question: Tony can send five texts and three nude selfies in 19 minutes. He can also send three texts and one nude in nine minutes. How long would it take Tony to send one text and one nude selfie? 

The father of two 14-year-old students told local Fox affiliate WJW he was &#x201C;appalled&#x201D; by the question and had filed a formal complaint. 

The school&#x2019;s superintendent told the station that Mr. Rapp had been reprimanded for the inappropriate question but will remain in the classroom. The school would not give the station Mr. Rapp&#x2019;s file, but the superintendent did say a &#x201C;similar reprimand&#x201D; was already in the teacher&#x2019;s file.

In case you&#x2019;re wondering, the answer to the question is it would take Tony five minutes to send one text and one nude.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Math,naughty math problems,teacher,math teacher disciplined,inappropriate math problem</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237054</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/983/4C9/9834C9ED189A4621B951D6731A8A3742_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237054/3237054_9456C07E415B413695488DF853881FD3_161222_3237054_Teacher_disciplined_after_posing_inappropriate_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers security guard caught red-handed making self love in front of cheerleaders</title>
      <description>A security guard at an NFL game has been caught on camera doing what looks like the five-finger knuckle shuffle &#x2014; just feet away from dancing cheerleaders.

The footage of the out-of-bounds behavior was filmed by a dumbfounded fan at the Qualcomm Stadium in San Diego on Sunday before the Chargers played the Oakland Raiders. 

It seems the sight of the cheerleaders going through their pre-game dance routines was enough to trigger a solo raid inside the guard&#x2019;s pants as the young man charged it to the home team in front of a 68,000-person crowd. 

One shocked fan thought she was going to watch a game of football, but started filming when instead she saw the guard playing pocket billiards.

The fan uploaded the video to social media and wrote that she was disgusted. She said she couldn&#x2019;t believe the security guard had gotten away with such a complete disregard for public decency and was horrified by the man&#x2019;s lack of respect for women&#x2019;s rights.

The video quickly went viral, and came to the attention of the guard&#x2019;s employers, Elite Security. The guard was fired within hours, TMZ reported.

The San Diego Police Department has opened an investigation, according to TMZ.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Chargers security guard,caught on camera,caught on tape,self love,chargers guard caught on camera,chargers security guard video</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237047</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:28:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/83A/E7E/83AE7E39A9814F0FB5BACBB0F472A912_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237047/3237047_89FEB6E6ECF544A89A3AEE06E7F3735F_161222_3237047_Chargers_security_guard_caught_red_handed_making_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Zuckerberg Morgan Freeman-voiced Jarvis AI: Facebook CEO created his own Iron Man-like AI</title>
      <description>PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; Mark Zuckerberg decided to build himself a personal AI assistant, inspired by Tony Stark&#x2019;s Jarvis, and guess what? It&#x2019;s called Jarvis. 

But rather than have the Iron Man actor Paul Bettany voice the system, Zuckerberg asked Morgan Freeman to do it instead, Fast Company reported.    

Through his very-own iOS app, the Facebook CEO can talk to Jarvis when he wakes up and have him turn the lights on and off as well as open the curtains.  

Jarvis can also help Mark get dressed in the morning by way of a clothes cannon. 

The system is able to entertain his daughter Max, as well as teach her Mandarin lessons. 

And if anyone&#x2019;s hungry for toast, Jarvis can take care of that as well.  

The AI butler is also designed to automatically open their front gate for family and friends.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Mark Zuckerberg,Mark Zuckerberg Jarvis AI,Mark Zuckerberg Morgan Freeman AI,Mark Zuckerberg Jarvis,Iron Man Jarvis</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237557</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 10:49:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>102</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EB9/B5E/EB9B5E17DB5340569628CB240C9B5A73_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237557/3237557_0205E3C03F394661A41B6F113B30F091_161222_3237557_Mark_Zuckerberg_Morgan_Freeman_voiced_Jarvis_AI__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wedding proposal: Woman&#x2019;s priceless reaction to same-sex proposal goes viral</title>
      <description>CHICAGO &#x2014; An adorable old lady melted the internet&#x2019;s frigid heart with her delightfully candid reaction to a woman proposing to another woman.

Jess Rodriguez planned a public proposal for long-term girlfriend Chelsea Miller at the Art Institute of Chicago, which one unsuspecting museum-goer who had front row seats to.

The romantic proposal thrilled the older woman, who was snapped with a look of pure joy and excitement on her face.

Rodriguez and her fiancee didn&#x2019;t even notice the lady&#x2019;s reaction firsthand, only spotting it in the engagement photo later on.

Her brother put up the heartwarming scene on Twitter, where it soon went viral and made most netizens collectively melt into a puddle of goo.

Rodriguez has since announced on social media that the couple chose June 30, 2018 as their wedding date.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Wedding proposal,romantic proposal,marriage proposal,proposal,public proposal,best reaction</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237978</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 02:13:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B92/974/B929748F24B34C3FB95D72CEE814073D_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/23/3237978/3237978_AC38AAF1556A40C398F12B754A008BE0_161223_3237978_Wedding_proposal__Woman___s_priceless_reaction_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen breast milk: Hong Kong man steals breast milk from office fridge, sends NSFW pic</title>
      <description>SAI WAN HO, HONG KONG &#x2014; A man who stole breast milk from his office pantry and sent inappropriate text messages to the woman whose milk it was has pleaded guilty to theft, on account of stress.

On March 8, Lam Chung-kan decided to hit the office pantry to grab a refreshing beverage. Oddly, he chose to take a bottle of breast milk from the fridge. 

His colleague, the owner of the breast milk, began receiving text messages from an unknown caller who claimed of having drank the baby formula. A month later, more odd text messages came in &#x2013; one photo of a glass of milk, and the other, of an erect penis wrapped in a plastic bag.

Caught on CCTV camera footage in the office, 37-year-old Lam pleaded guilty to one count of theft, for which he&#x2019;ll have to pay for with 200 hours of community service. Lam&#x2019;s lawyer insisted her client is not mentally ill, but instead chose to steal the breast milk as a means of coping with stress.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Man steals breast milk,breast milk,Lam Chung-kan,upskirt,perv</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237845</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 23:46:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>25</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CA8/22E/CA822E6578F6424C8F880F1EAD190115_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/23/3237845/3237845_144DE2B9E8F84CAEB4C976C7FCA5D67C_161223_3237845_Stolen_breast_milk__Hong_Kong_man_steals_breast__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog strangled to death with leash trapped between elevator doors</title>
      <description>CHANGZHOU CITY, CHINA &#x2014; We all know that elevators in China like to eat people. But apparently they like to eat dogs, too. 

As reported by the Changzhou Daily Post, this unfortunate incident happened in Jiangsu Province when a dog&#x2019;s owner went up in an elevator without him. 

In surveillance footage obtained by the newspaper, an 80-year-old woman can be seen walking her dog to an apartment elevator in Yuhewan district of Changzhou City around  p.m. on Dec. 6.
 
But when they got into the elevator, the dog turned around and and walked out. The elevator&#x2019;s doors then closed and the elevator began its ascent. The old woman pushed the alarm button for help, but to no avail.

Technicians came to open the elevator doors, but the dog was dead. The woman was physically unharmed but emotionally scarred for the rest of her life. 

Local police told the newspaper that small or thin objects like leashes and dogs are difficult for elevators to detect. When a group of people enter an elevator, it is best to press and hold the open button until the entire group is inside.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Strangled to death,dogs strangled to death,elevator death,elevator accidents,dogs and elevator</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237789</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 22:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FCB/887/FCB887192D8945E78DCA40B30ECECD5A_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/23/3237789/3237789_2EFD4FC0CEF44D0383901FB322684FCE_161223_3237789_Dog_strangled_to_death_with_leash_trapped_betwee_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult entertainer Nikki Benz alleges director choked and stomped her in attack on set</title>
      <description>LOS ANGELES &#x2014; One of the world&#x2019;s most well-known adult entertainers has accused a director of attacking her on set during a film shoot.

Actress Nikki Benz  took to Twitter on Tuesday to allege that director Tony T choked her and stomped on her head in a vicious attack.

Benz wrote that in all of her 13 years working in the adult entertainment industry it was the first time she had gone into shock and cried on set.

The fallout from the incident has seen the star become embroiled in a furious row with the movie&#x2019;s producers, Canadian website Brazzers.

Benz wrote on Twitter that she told Brazzers she did not want the scene to be released and accused the company of pressuring her to say everything was OK so that she would receive her paycheck.  

Brazzers denied responsibility for the alleged attack and described the director as a third party.

However, several other adult stars have leapt to Benz&#x2019;s defense. Some actresses said the alleged attack was not an isolated incident, while others reported they had also had bad experiences with Tony T in the past.

Jenna Jameson, arguably the world&#x2019;s most famous adult film star, offered her support to Benz. Jameson told Fox News that producers like Brazzers were making money from rape scenes and it was time to call them out on it.

No criminal charges have been filed against Tony T.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Nikki benz,nikki benz attack,brazzers,porn star,porn star attacked,nikki benz attacked,jenna jameson,porn star assault</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237745</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 22:11:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/719/CEF/719CEF26A880493F9EF365C2BE0BEB45_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/23/3237745/3237745_D04792ED152E489C9BB42D257D1EC928_161223_3237745_Adult_entertainer_Nikki_Benz_alleges_director_ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida cops grab suspect by dreadlocks, share shaming photos on Facebook and Twitter - TomoNews</title>
      <description>PASCO COUNTY, FLORIDA &#x2014; A sheriff&#x2019;s office is facing a backlash after it posted a photo of two deputies gripping a crying suspect by his hair to social media.

The Pasco County Sheriff&#x2019;s Office labelled suspect Marquis Porter, 21, their &#x201C;Sad Criminal of the Day&#x201D; following his arrest last week.

Porter was arrested on Nov. 17 after he fled a traffic stop and then intentionally ran a deputy off the road, the sheriff&#x2019;s office posted to Facebook and Twitter.

Porter was found with multiple drugs in his possession, including 9.5 grams of crystal meth, according to the cops.

Following his arrest, two deputies grabbed a handcuffed and crying Porter by his dreadlocks and paraded him in front of a camera.

The Pasco County Sheriff&#x2019;s Office shared the photo to its social media accounts but later deleted the Facebook post following a barrage of criticism. The post remains on Twitter.

In response, the sheriff&#x2019;s office posted a grainy video to Twitter, which they said shows compassionate deputies giving Porter a blanket and water following his arrest.

The sheriff&#x2019;s office defended the original photo, saying it posted pictures of criminals online every day as a service to the community, the Tampa Bay Times reported.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Social media shaming,pasco county sheriff,marquis porter,cops grab dreadlocks,cops grab hair,cops vs criminals,dumb florida</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3238695</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 23:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>44</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AF1/F2D/AF1F2DB4572645ADA834F28D45DD6B34_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/24/3238695/3238695_B039C1B52FD64E929F98461551012DF8_161224_3238695_Florida_cops_grab_suspect_by_dreadlocks__share_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka Trump confronted by angry passenger on JetBlue flight who brags about it</title>
      <description>NEW YORK &#x2014; A JetBlue passenger was removed from his flight along with his husband and their child after a confrontation with Ivanka Trump last Thursday.

Passenger Marc Scheff told Reuters that when fellow passenger Dan Goldstein saw Ivanka and her family in the economy section of the New York to San Francisco flight on Thursday, he did a double take and said: &#x201C;Oh my God. This is a nightmare!&#x201D;

Goldstein, a 35-year-old attorney from Brooklyn, continued his rant, saying: &#x201C;Why is she on our flight? She should be flying private.&#x201D; Meanwhile, Goldstein&#x2019;s husband Matthew Lasner, a professor at New York&#x2019;s Hunter College, tweeted on his twitter @MattLasner that his husband was going to harass Ivanka&#x2019;s husband Jared Kushner, adding the hashtag #banalityofevil.

The plane was still boarding when the incident occurred, and JetBlue&#x2019;s cabin crew was able to escort Goldstein, Lasner and their child off the flight.

Scheff told CNN he overheard Ivanka tell JetBlue staff, &#x201C;I don't want to make this a thing.&#x201D; Scheff said it seemed like Ivanka was fine with letting her harasser stay on the plane.

When JetBlue staff approached Goldstein to &#x201C;make sure he was calm,&#x201D; he said: &#x201C;They ruin our country, now try (to) ruin our flight!&#x201D; As Goldstein and his family were being escorted off the plane, he could be heard asking: &#x201C;You're kicking me off for expressing my opinion?!&#x201D;

The couple were put on the next flight. Lasner defended his husband by tweeting: &#x201C;My husband expressed his displeasure in a calm tone, JetBlue staff overheard, and they kicked us off.&#x201D;

Responding to the incident on Fox News, a Trump spokesman said: &#x201C;To do that to a woman who was on there with her children, I don&#x2019;t care what your political background is or what your thoughts are, that&#x2019;s not the way we as Americans need to act.&#x201D;</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Ivanka Trump,Dan Goldstein,Matthew Lasner,Donald Trump,airplane harassment,public harassment</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3240748</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 06:18:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/56A/D16/56AD1669A85A4B938D6C25958BEDB79F_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/27/3240748/3240748_C7BB4575F7CB43F4943E930736DF7659_161227_3240748_Ivanka_Trump_confronted_by_angry_passenger_on_Je_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot boyfriend: French woman wants to marry her 3D-printed robot lover</title>
      <description>PARIS &#x2014; A French woman has built her own robot lover and she plans to marry him.

As a child, Lilly said she loved robot&#x2019;s voices. When she was 19, she realized she was &#x201C;robosexual,&#x201D; meaning she is only attracted to robots.

&#x201C;My only two relationships with men have confirmed my love orientation, because I dislike really physical contact with human flesh,&#x201D; Lilly told News.com.au.

Lilly built her robot lover, which she named Inmmovator, by 3D printing. She has lived with him for one year and the happy couple plans to marry when robot-human marriage is legalised in France.

Lilly did not reveal whether she is having a sexual relationship with her robot lover but she is training to become a roboticist to further her passion in the field of robots.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,French woman wants to marry robot,french woman robot relationship,robot lover,human-robot marriage,lilly French woman marries robot,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3240612</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 03:08:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/58A/D9E/58AD9E380BA3430B80C80E6F2686AAA8_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/27/3240612/3240612_9265966D0A044D80BB1A4D1A5DF9E348_161227_3240612_Robot_boyfriend__French_woman_wants_to_marry_her_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre deep sea creatures: Pictures of Russian fisherman&#x2019;s catch go viral</title>
      <description>MURMANSK, RUSSIA  &#x2014; Startling images of strange deep sea creatures are going viral, thanks to one Russian fisherman and his Twitter account, which the English-language Moscow Times discovered for a global audience.

His name is Roman Fedorstov and he crews a deep sea trawler based out of Murmansk in Russia&#x2019;s frigid far northwest. 

Fedorov has been cataloguing the strange finds his trawler pulls from the deep ocean, including the hellish Pacific angelfish and the frill shark, which lives up to 5,000 feet beneath the waves. Most of this stuff isn&#x2019;t intentionally harvested, but turns up in the trawling nets anyhow &#x2014; this known as &#x201C;by-catch.&#x201D;

His Twitter feed, which catalogues dozens of incredible images, now has a healthy 83,000 followers.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Deep sea,deep sea fish,deep ocean,Murmansk,Russia,Roman Fedorstov,fishing</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3240589</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 02:47:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5F0/F1C/5F0F1CE52B23412DA043EFEA356E8EFC_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/27/3240589/3240589_B9FECEFF316B4C5CB3274BD3FD7ED54C_161227_3240589_Bizarre_deep_sea_creatures__Pictures_of_Russian__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrie Fisher dead at 60: Famed Star Wars actress dies following heart attack on plane</title>
      <description>LOS ANGELES &#x2014; Yet another star has gone out in the sky during the waning moments of 2016. Actress Carrie Fisher, famous for her iconic portrayal of Princess Leia in the Star Wars universe has passed away at the age of 60. 

On a flight from London on Dec. 23, Fisher went into a bout of cardiac arrest just 15 minutes before landing in Los Angeles. A doctor and nurse on board the flight rushed to her aid, as EMTs on the ground stormed in to carry her off.

After being taken to hospital and treated, the entire internet breathed a huge sigh of relief on Christmas Day when reports indicated she was in stable condition. However, a mere two days later, Fisher was reported dead.

Carrie Fisher now joins David Bowie, Prince, Muhammad Ali, George Michael, and too many more on the tragic list of legends we lost this year. 

While fans mourn her loss, we are also left to wonder what will become of Princess Leia in future installments of the Star Wars saga. Shooting for Episode VIII wrapped in July, but with Leia said to play an integral role in Episode IX, mystery will now consume the future of the franchise.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Carrie fisher,princess leia,star wars,episode VIII,star wars episode 8,episode 8,episode 9,star wars princess leia,episode IX,star wars episode 9,celebrity deaths 2016,2016 celebrity deaths</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241480</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 04:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A86/2C7/A862C7D367184CF3A1F2019F3D93D1E1_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/28/3241480/3241480_AE6DF5CBC32847ED93868F63CE28FD3A_161228_3241480_Carrie_Fisher_dead_at_60__Famed_Star_Wars_actres_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned cat&#x2019;s matted fur grows into outrageous 2-pound dreadlocks</title>
      <description>PITTSBURGH &#x2014; A cat who&#x2019;d been neglected by her owner with Alzheimer&#x2019;s disease was found with fur matted so badly it had become dreadlocks.

On December 16, the Animal Rescue League Shelter in Pittsburgh posted these outrageous photographs to Facebook of a cat in desperate need of a cut. The cat&#x2019;s elderly owner had Alzheimer&#x2019;s disease, and last week, his family had him moved to a nursing home, deeming him unable to safely care for himself. Unfortunately, he forgot his two pet cats behind.

Paul Russel, a distant relative of the elderly man, showed up to leave some food out for the one cat he knew about. Walking around the house, he saw something raggedy bolt out from under the bed, and down to the cellar. Using a flashlight, Russel searched around until he spotted a cat, covered in matted fur that weighed in at roughly 2 pounds. 

When Paul Russel brought the cat into the vet, they anesthetized her so the long overdue fur-cut could finally commence. Now freed of her unwanted fur coat, the cat, whose name is Hidey, now has a new home with the man who saved her.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Cat dreadlocks,rasta cat,reggae,bong hits,dreadlocks,hidey the cat</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241185</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 22:54:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1E9/C2F/1E9C2FFC5E654CFEB0B99F30BA084A5D_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/28/3241185/3241185_CCDBEEFC2EA041CD8BF6FD58C653F7DC_161228_3241185_Abandoned_cat___s_matted_fur_grows_into_outrageo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teenager falls to his death trying to sled down snow-covered waterslide</title>
      <description>WISCONSIN DELLS, WISCONSIN &#x2014; A teenager from Florida fell to his death on Wednesday after attempting to sled down a snow-covered waterslide at a Wisconsin theme park.

Addison Williams, 16, was sledding on some hills with his brother and a friend, when the trio decided it was a good idea to hop a 7-foot high fence into a closed area of the Mount Olympus Water and Theme Park in Wisconsin Dells.

Williams raced down a waterslide on his sled but got stuck in the snow about halfway down, NBC-affiliate WTMJ reported. Williams tried to free himself but instead fell 35 feet to the ground, police said.

A paramedic was driving by at the time and jumped over the fence with a defibrillator, but was unable to revive the boy.

Police said Williams and his family from Port St Lucie, Florida were guests at the theme park and had traveled to Wisconsin to experience snow for the first time. A GoFundMe page has been set up to help the family with funeral expenses.

Authorities are investigating the incident but the Mount Olympus Park is not suspected of being at fault.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Sledding gone wrong,boy falls off waterslide,falling to death,mount olympus water slides,boy falls off waterslide,sledding fails</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241172</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 22:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/919/C0E/919C0E10D07549B8956D198DC0EFC801_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/28/3241172/3241172_2D85366AA7E54202ABE1C90EA8A53FAD_161228_3241172_Teenager_falls_to_his_death_trying_to_sled_down__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet owner slits throat of pit bull that mauled his poodle to death</title>
      <description>RIVERSIDE, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; A pet owner was arrested on animal cruelty charges for killing a pit bull that mauled his dog to death over the weekend.

Rudy Jesus Barajas, 30, cut the pit bull&#x2019;s throat after the dog took the life of his pet, a 10-month-old poodle mix named Spunky, CBSLA reported.

The incident took place on Saturday morning, when a neighbor&#x2019;s 2-year-old pit bull ran into Barajas&#x2019; property and went straight for Spunky.

Barajas and other neighbors tried to stop the attack, but they were too late, as the pit bull had already clamped down on the poodle&#x2019;s neck.

After the pit bull let go, Barajas grabbed the dog by its neck, dragged it into his kitchen and slit its throat with a knife. 

The pit bull ran back across the street to its owner and collapsed. It died on the way to the animal hospital.

Some witnesses said the pit bull tried to bite people at the scene after it let go of the poodle, according to the Press Enterprise.

But according to the Riverside County Animal Services, Barajas acted out of spite when he killed the dog. The police are investigating and Barajas could face felony animal cruelty charges.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Pitbull,pitbull attack,killer pitbulls,man slits pitbull throat,man cuts pitbulls throat,pitbull dog,dangerous pitbull dogs</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241163</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 22:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3B6/70B/3B670BA7FA7F469A8BF943480B132B0E_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/28/3241163/3241163_7EB86B34F1794AF29BCE674EBA080A19_161228_3241163_Pet_owner_slits_throat_of_pit_bull_that_mauled_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State attack: Somali muslim refugee stabs 11 people then gets killed by hero cop</title>
      <description>COLUMBUS, OHIO &#x2014; Nearly a dozen people were left wounded following a knife attack at Ohio State University on Monday morning.

Abdul Razak Ali Artan began his stabbing spree by driving his car onto the sidewalk and running over pedestrians, the Columbus Dispatch reported.

The incident took place near Watts Hall on the university campus. 

Artan, an 18-year-old student at the university, then exited the vehicle and began attacking people with a butcher knife, WBNS-10TV reported. He injured 11 people in his attack, including one critically.

Officer Alan Horujko of the Ohio State University police confronted Artan and ordered him to drop his weapon. Artan did not comply, prompting Horujko to open fire and kill him.

According to the Cleveland Plain Dealer, Artan was a Somalian Muslim refugee with permanent residence status who came to the U.S. in 2014. He graduated cum laude from Columbus State Community College before enrolling at Ohio State.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Ohio state attack,ohio state isis,ohio state knife man,abdul razak ali artan,ohio state university,stabbing,columbus,campus attack</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241380</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 02:46:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/035/80C/03580C877F7243818F2E15368A26AEE2_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/29/3241380/3241380_2732955A789A41D0BC1B250E9352B76F_161228_3241380_Ohio_State_attack__Somali_muslim_refugee_stabs_1_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets thrown from helicopter: Duterte says he threw a kidnapper out a helicopter</title>
      <description>MANILA &#x2014; Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte this week claimed he once threw a kidnapper out a helicopter when he was mayor of Davao city. 

That man and his cohorts had reportedly kidnapped and abused a Chinese girl.

Duterte&#x2019;s claims were made as he threatened to do the very same thing to corrupt officials over the city of Manila, reported The Philippine Star.

Earlier this month he admitted to hunting and killing suspects while he was mayor of Davao.  

Nearly 6,000 drugs suspects have been extrajudicially killed by police under orders from Duterte since he became president in the summer.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Man gets thrown from helicopter,Duterte,rodrigo duterte,Helicopter death,rodrigo duterte vs drug dealers,duterte vigilante,duterte kills people,davao city,philipines,manila</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3242290</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 04:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BF0/E47/BF0E479F2A4D47FFBCA2F625C65AC1D5_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/29/3242290/3242290_7E99D958D7A14651A95AE0DF108B1568_161229_3242290_Man_gets_thrown_from_helicopter__Duterte_says_he_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUI: California man charged with DUI for driving under the influence of caffeine</title>
      <description>SOLANO COUNTY, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; A California man charged in 2015 with driving under the influence of a drug says he wants to clear his name after blood tests revealed caffeine but no sign of any drugs.

On Aug. 5 of that year, Joseph Schwab, 36, was driving home from work in Solano County when he was pulled over by a police officer in an unmarked car, the Guardian reported. 

According to the police officer, Schwab was driving erratically and had cut her off. Although Schwab blew a 0.00% blood alcohol level on a breathalyzer test, he was was booked into the county jail and had his blood drawn for further testing.

The toxicology report showed that Schwab was negative for benzodiazepines, cocaine, opiates, THC, carisoprodol, methamphetamine, oxycodone and zolpidem. 

According to documents provided to the Guardian, a second test was conducted in a Pennsylvania lab. The test showed that Schwab did indeed have a chemical in his system &#x2014; caffeine.

Schwab later filed a motion to get the case dismissed, but the motion was denied. Now Schwab plans to take the case to court on Jan. 11. 

According to Sharon Henry, chief deputy district attorney for Solano County, her office was still investing the matter. She said &#x201C;the charge of driving under the influence is not based upon the presence of caffeine in his system.&#x201D;</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,DUI,police arrest,caffeine,police arrest,driving under influence of caffeine,Joseph Schwab,Solano County</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241891</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 21:29:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6C6/F96/6C6F96BA1C634F45B088C1523A171C35_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/29/3241891/3241891_44623CEDFAE642BB8B4623F701F356AD_161229_3241891_DUI__California_man_charged_with_DUI_for_driving_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seal waddles into Aussie suburb and jumps on some cars</title>
      <description>NEWSTEAD, AUSTRALIA  &#x2014; One Australian town got a late Christmas surprise on Boxing Day morning when a 200-kg fur seal waddled into town.

According to Australian broadcaster ABC, the creature jumped on two cars before being tranquilized by police on the island of Tasmania. 

Dubbed &#x201C;Lou-Seal&#x201D; by officers, the large male mammal will be released after a medical check-up, Tasmanian police said in a Facebook post.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Seal vs car,seal vs vehicle,seal jump,seal on land,seal walking,funny seals,seal compilation,seal 2016,seal tasmania,seal australia,fur seal,tasmania police</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241885</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 21:14:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>26</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2D5/E85/2D5E85040A3841C3AB98CF6CDF1D7772_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/29/3241885/3241885_EB9F9845D32D43EAB12EDFD8E7C531A0_161229_3241885_Seal_waddles_into_Aussie_suburb_and_jumps_on_som_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia plane crash: 71 dead on flight carrying Brazil football team Chapecoense</title>
      <description>MEDELLIN, COLOMBIA &#x2014; A plane carrying Brazilian soccer team Chapecoense crashed in the mountains less than 20 miles from its destination on Monday night, killing 71 people on board.

The chartered British Aerospace Avro RJ85 plane was carrying 72 passengers and nine crew members, Reuters reported. It was en route from Santa Cruz, Bolivia to Medellin, Colombia when it crashed just about 18 miles from Medellin airport.

According to the Telegraph, the Medellin airport said the pilots had declared an emergency, citing electrical failure, before losing contact. Data from Flightradar24 shows the last known altitude of the plane was at 15,500 feet and the pilot circled the plane in a possible attempt to drop off fuel before crashing.

The plane crashed in the mountainous terrain near Medellin and broke apart upon impact, but did not catch fire.

According to Reuters, the six survivors include players on the team, a journalist and two flight crew members.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Colombia plane crash,brazil football team plane crash,chapecoense team plane crash,plane crash,plane accident,medellin plane crash,medellin airport,colombia</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3241406</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 03:09:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>55</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/26A/23F/26A23F77D2464607BFFE0BE9904241E4_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/11/30/3241406/3241406_F86354F1B8494B32845D3B05F99B7D39_161228_3241406_Colombia_plane_crash__71_dead_on_flight_carrying_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ziggy stardust snake, Klingon newt among new species discovered with popular namesakes</title>
      <description>SOUTHEAST ASIA &#x2014; It&#x2019;s not every day scientists are lucky enough to stumble upon new species, but when they do, naming them is a huge part of the fun. 

The past year saw the exit of music legend David Bowie, but a slithery serpent with his likeness has since been discovered and introduced to the world, an homage of sorts. Named after its rainbowy resemblance to the rock icon&#x2019;s alter ego, the Ziggy Stardust snake was discovered sitting on a mossy rock by a team of scientists in Laos. 

Also among the new species met by the world is a tiny amphibian discovered in Thailand, fondly named the Klingon newt. Its features strikingly similar to those of the alien race of the Star Trek universe, the Klingon newt is roughly 6-7 cm in length.

In the mountainous regions of southwestern India, researchers found an especially odd-shaped arachnid crawling around. Though it got its name for having a body shape reminiscent of the sorting hat in Harry Potter, the Eriovixia gryffindori spider is actually trying to mimic dry foliage, in order to hide from predators.

Finally, as President Obama steps out of the White House, a fish discovered near his home state will carry on his fine name. The Tosanoides obama Pyle was discovered near the northwest Hawaiian islands. When the president decided to expand the boundaries of protected waters in the region, the scientists involved felt it was only fitting to honor the man responsible for keeping the fish &#x2014; along with countless other marine species &#x2014; safe.The fish has a circular red spot ringed with blue on its dorsal fin, which looks an awful lot like the president&#x2019;s campaign logo, a touch researchers say factored into the final naming decision.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Wwf new species,new species 2015,new species 2016,ziggy stardust,ziggy stardust snake,klingon newt,obama fish,sorting hat spider</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3242785</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 23:47:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A16/918/A1691881A4DD4AD281C66323E32D65CB_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/29/3242785/3242785_068EF0592DC04CE590DABCBC84F823C3_161229_3242785_Ziggy_stardust_snake__Klingon_newt_among_new_spe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear vs Russian truckers: bear gets run over then beaten to death with a crowbar</title>
      <description>YAKUTIA, RUSSIA &#x2014; Viral footage of a Russian bear being beaten and run over by a truck is sparking outrage online.

According to the Siberian Times, the video was captured in Yakutia in Northeastern Russia.

The cellphone footage shows the bear running from Ural trucks, before it gets run over and squashed. It survives, but one of the men then mercilessly beats it to death with a crowbar.

Reaction to footage of the assault was split among Russian netizens, reported the Siberian times. Some said the killing was justified because the bear could have attacked people, others suggest the men provoked the creature.

Russian authorities have reportedly opened a criminal investigation and are seeking those behind the brutal video.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Bear vs russian,bear vs russians,russian bear,animal cruelty caught on camera,animal cruelty,yakutia,moscow,russia,cruel humans</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3242753</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B63/610/B63610F317354660ABC7F8400416D6FC_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/29/3242753/3242753_5458E60A1AC84F7F9379CE3AAFE48A5C_161229_3242753_Bear_vs_Russian_truckers__bear_gets_run_over_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pit bull attack: Woman bitten by pit bull more than 30 times while she protected baby</title>
      <description>TACOMA, WASHINGTON &#x2014; A woman in Tacoma, Washington thought she was going to die when she was bitten more than 30 times by a vicious pit bull as she protected her best friend&#x2019;s baby.

On October 29, Felicia Hambrick, 24,  was at her best friend Cassy&#x2019;s place babysitting Cassy&#x2019;s three children.

During breakfast one morning, Cassy&#x2019;s pit bull, Roscoe, suddenly came running into the kitchen. Hambrick, standing at less than 5 ft tall, had not choice but to use her body as a shield to protect her best friend's 8-month-old daughter as Roscoe knocked them to the ground.

Roscoe bit the helpless Hambrick in her legs, arms, stomach and neck as she screamed for help.

Cassy&#x2019;s mother, who was smoking outside, rushed back inside to beat off Roscoe with a broom. During a moment when the dog relented, she managed to take the baby away to safety.

However, the dog soon came back to continue his attack Hambrick. The pain was so great that Hambrick said she wished she was dead.

Cassy&#x2019;s mother eventually managed to get the dog outside, after sustaining a few bites herself, and Hambrick was rushed to Tacoma General Hospital for treatment.

After spending five days in the hospital, Hambrick was sent home with 94 staples holding her wounds together.

Meanwhile, Roscoe was taken away to animal shelter and has since been euthanized, Cassy told The News Tribune.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Pit bull attack,pit bull mauling,dog attacks,mauled by pit bull,pit bull attacks man,attacked by pit bull</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3242788</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 23:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/200/777/200777DF633E4497868E4763A56A7EC3_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/30/3242788/3242788_BA89EF814AFA4C099BA9973111196F39_161230_3242788_Pit_bull_attack__Woman_bitten_by_pit_bull_more_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazi cosplay: Taiwanese students dress up as Nazi soldiers in school parade</title>
      <description>HSINCHU CITY, TAIWAN &#x2014; A group of Taiwanese students goose-stepped into worldwide infamy by parading around as Nazi soldiers at a cosplay event last Friday.

The incident happened during the annual celebration at Kuang Fu High School in the northern city of Hsinchu. History teacher Liu Hsi-cheng said his students voted to dress up as Nazis for the festivities, rejecting his own idea of an Arabic cosplay theme, reported Taiwan&#x2019;s Apple Daily newspaper. 

The students wore black Nazi uniforms with swastika armbands and waved Nazi flags. One even rode in a cardboard tank doing the Nazi salute. When photos of the parade were shared on the school&#x2019;s Facebook page and an online academic bulletin board, they went viral, sparking outrage in Taiwan. 

Taiwan&#x2019;s Presidential Office called the incident &#x201C;regrettable&#x201D; and &#x201C;disappointing.&#x201D; And
both Germany and Israel&#x2019;s diplomatic missions issued statements condemning the Nazi cosplay.

Israel&#x2019;s office said it was &#x201C;deplorable and shocking,&#x201D; while the German Institute in Taipei said it was unfortunate the students didn&#x2019;t understand that Nazi symbols represent &#x201C;the oppression of human rights.&#x201D;

On Sunday, the school&#x2019;s principal took full responsibility for the incident and resigned.

Teacher Liu, who double-majored in Eastern and Western history in college, said he was sorry and asked the public to give his students a second chance. He told Apple Daily that he had failed in his duties as a teacher. He said he should have explained to his students why dressing up as Nazis was bad. 

In an unrelated incident, a man and a boy were photographed last Saturday on Taipei&#x2019;s metro wearing Waffen-SS and Hitler Youth uniforms.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Nazi,nazi cosplay,taiwan nazi cosplay,adolf hitler,hitler costume,swastika,taiwan cosplay,ignorance</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3242736</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 22:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AFE/147/AFE1477D6FF54A9E84498ACBFCD93DCA_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/30/3242736/3242736_0953565B775A424DAA73792A1F3AACE9_161230_3242736_Nazi_cosplay__Taiwanese_students_dress_up_as_Naz_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia airplane crash: Plane suffered &#x2018;total electrical failure, without fuel&#x2019;</title>
      <description>MEDELLIN, COLOMBIA &#x2014; Investigators probing the site of this week&#x2019;s plane crash in Colombia are trying to determine whether or not the plane ran out of fuel.


Moments before LaMia Airlines flight 2933 crashed on Monday, its co-pilot reportedly told Medellin airport control that the plane suffered a &#x201C;total electrical failure, without fuel,&#x201D; reported AFP, citing a leaked recording to Colombian media.


The flight was carrying 77 passengers, including Brazil&#x2019;s Chapecoense soccer team, flight crew and journalists from Santa Cruz in Bolivia. Seventy-one people were killed in the crash, according to website Colombia Reports.


The team was flying to compete against Atletico Nacional in the finals of the Copa Sudamericana soccer tournament.


The distance between the two airports is some 1,839 miles, reported the Wall Street Journal, citing Great Circle Mapper. LaMia 2933 was a British Aerospace Avro RJ85 plane. According to Airliners.net, this plane&#x2019;s maximum fuel capacity would carry it 1,842 miles.


LaMia airlines CEO Gustavo Vargas told Reuters that the decision of whether or not to refuel enroute is at the pilot&#x2019;s discretion. The plane did not explode when crashing, and so far, investigators haven&#x2019;t found traces of fuel at the crash site, reported ABC, citing investigators.


Nearly all members of the Chapecoense team were killed in the crash.</description>
      <tags>Chapecoense crash,colombia plane crash,colombia crash,medellin crash,lamia 2933,Chapecoense crash,football tragedy,Chapecoense football team,football plane crash</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225429</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:36:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/089/BD7/089BD7DC371B469DB6A0CBFBC2D06AAB_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/01/3225429/3225429_11BD001D0B9342859EBC89746C2E3A31_161207_3225429_Colombia_airplane_crash__Plane_suffered____total_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York thief steals $1.6m bucket of gold from armored truck parked in Manhattan</title>
      <description>NEW YORK &#x2014;  Surveillance footage released by the New York Police Department this week shows the alleged theft of a bucket of gold flakes worth nearly $1.6 million from an armored truck.


The alleged theft took place on West 48th Street in Manhattan on Sept. 29 when the 86-pound bucket was left unattended by security guards in the back of the parked truck, the New York Times reported.


When one guard left to make a collection, the other went to retrieve his cellphone from the cab. Police said it was during this 20-second window that the suspect committed the crime.


The man saw an opportunity and probably did not know what was inside the bucket, according to police.


Surveillance footage captured the moment the suspect grabbed the bucket from the back of the truck and walked calmly away through the crowds.


Police said the suspect headed east down 48th Street, pausing often to regain his breath, before disappearing near Third Avenue, according to the New York Times. WNBC New York reported that the man got into a white van, but that was not clear from the surveillance footage.


Police described the suspect as a Hispanic man, aged between 50 and 60 years old. He is 5 feet 6 inches tall, weighs 150 pounds and was wearing a black vest, green shirt, blue jeans, and carrying a black messenger bag.


Police believe the man is hiding in Florida and could be in the Orlando or Miami area. The bucket of gold has not been recovered.</description>
      <tags>Bucket of gold,new york bucket of gold theft,man steals bucket of gold,most daring robberies,pot of gold,opportunity knocks,gold robbery,man robs gold</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225419</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1FE/D6C/1FED6CD9672847F6A7BAC5655EE0ACC3_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/01/3225419/3225419_2EFB6BFEA83A458BB1926A8CD19D7282_161207_3225419_New_York_thief_steals__1_6m_bucket_of_gold_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
