<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mcp="http://schema.anvato.com/mcp/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>MRSS feed for Verta News</title>
    <link>//api.nm.anvato.net/v2/feed/K5DREWL4E6RRMTRDAIBA?start=0&amp;count=200&amp;filters[]=u_Slug_Dept_s:"DPS_iUS"&amp;filters[]=c_ts_publish_l:[1483113600%20TO%201483200000]&amp;fmt=mrss&amp;media_filters[]=video/mp4</link>
    <description/>
    <item>
      <title>Joe McKnight shooting: Former NFL star shot dead in New Orleans road rage incident</title>
      <description>NEW ORLEANS &#x2014; Former NFL star Joe McKnight was shot dead in New Orleans on Thursday in what police described as &#x201C;a possible road rage incident.&#x201D;


Suspect Ronald Gasser, 54, was taken into custody for questioning after handing his gun to authorities at the scene.


A witness said she saw two men standing at an intersection in the city&#x2019;s Terrytown suburb, NOLA.com reported. One man was shouting at the other, who was trying to apologize, according to the witness.


McKnight, 28, was unarmed, police said. He was shot multiple times and died at the scene despite attempts by the emergency services to revive him.


McKnight was a star running back for the University of Southern California before he was drafted to the NFL by the New York Jets in 2010. He went on to play for the Kansas City Chiefs and most recently played in the Canadian Football League.


McKnight is the second former NFL star to be shot dead in New Orleans this year in a suspected road rage incident.


Former New Orleans Saints defensive end Will Smith was shot and killed in the city&#x2019;s Lower Garden District in April. The trial of suspect Cardell Hayes on charges that include first-degree murder is scheduled to begin on Monday in the city.</description>
      <tags>Joe mcknight,joe mcknight shot dead,joe mcknight shooting,road rage usa,road rage,road rage gun,road rage shooting</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225459</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>37</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DF0/F74/DF0F74AE294F4785B59D4F5351E6D166_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/02/3225459/3225459_FF9417869DA3480F852B966B28C0036E_161207_3225459_Joe_McKnight_shooting__Former_NFL_star_shot_dead_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Lunar X-Prize: Private German moon mission to inspect Apollo 17 lunar rover</title>
      <description>BERLIN &#x2014; A team of scientists in Germany has developed a lunar rover that will soon fly to the moon and visit the legendary Apollo 17 Lunar Rover Vehicle.


The rover is developed by the team called PTScientists, in collaboration with automaker Audi. Dubbed Audi Lunar Quattro, the rover is made of aluminium and titanium, and created almost entirely from 3D printing technology. It is equipped with 4-wheel drive technology, solar panels, rechargeable lithium ion batteries, as well as science-grade high-definition cameras.


Two rovers will be carried by the ALINA spacecraft, which stands for the Autonomous Landing and Navigation Module. ALINA will also carry several other payloads, including a lunar plant growth experiment. It has not been confirmed, but a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket is reportedly will likely be used to transport the rovers into space.


ALINA will touch down about 5 km from the Apollo 17 in the Taurus-Littrow valley. After landing on the moon, the two rovers will be deployed and will travel toward the Apollo 17 lunar rover. However, they are not allowed any closer than 200 meters of the Apollo rover, per NASA&#x2019;s request. The rovers will send live HD pictures of the Apollo rover to Earth.</description>
      <tags>Ptscientists,audi lunar quattro,german moon mission,google lunar x-prize,space,moon,apollo 17,apollo 17 lunar roving vehicle,science,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225455</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9C7/1BF/9C71BF02641843C686524222BD600C6E_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/02/3225455/3225455_0104844F8FB74022B7AA67CF09B2D558_161207_3225455_Google_Lunar_X_Prize__Private_German_moon_missio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAXA teams with fishing net maker to make took for space debris removal</title>
      <description>TOKYO &#x2014; The Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency has teamed up with a 106-year-old fishing net-making company to create a tether that might be able to help remove space debris.


Nitto Seimo has a long history of net-making and invented a knotless net machine in 1925. The knotless net is said to be stronger than the knotted net, as tension is usually concentrated on the knots. The nets are usually used in fishing and other commercial uses.


JAXA commissioned Nitto Seimo to make a mesh of metal cables into a 700-meter-long tether to be used in space. The tether will be attached to a relatively large-sized piece of space debris in low Earth orbit, with the other end connected to an electron emitter.


The tether collects electrons, which are abundant in near-Earth space, and electrons are projected into space through the emitter. This creates an electric current that flows through the tether. The current generates a Lorentz force on the opposite side of the orbital motion, thus weakening the orbital energy, resulting in a &#x2018;drag force&#x2019; that brings the debris into the atmosphere, where it will burn up.


This technology will be tested next month. If the test is successful, Nitto Seimo will build a tether as long as 10 kilometers.</description>
      <tags>JAXA,JAXA space junk removal,JAXA space debris,Nitto Seimo,JAXA net in space,space,technology,space,JAXA space tether</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225440</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:44:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>50</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FAA/982/FAA9828FFD9C4168AFF4B20BE440EFC5_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/02/3225440/3225440_48434504FF9046EEB612C2E8AAE1B946_161207_3225440_JAXA_teams_with_fishing_net_maker_to_make_took_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worm sandwich: McDonald&#x2019;s fish burger features worm, Michigan woman not happy</title>
      <description>SOUTHGATE, MICHIGAN &#x2014; A Michigan mother might be looking to quit fast food as a new year&#x2019;s resolution, after discovering her fish sandwich came with extra protein.

The News Herald reports that after getting McDonald&#x2019;s take-out on Wednesday night, Southgate resident Jerica Klaiss took a bite of her Fillet-O-Fish before picking it apart as part of her normal routine. She claims she does this due to past issues with an 
autoimmune disorder and open heart surgery.

While inspecting the deep fried patty, she found a worm weaved between the fish and its breading, and quickly became concerned that she had ingested its parts.

The woman went back to the store to complain, but they could only offer her a refund and a corporate number to call. She declined the refund, as well as an attempt to take the tainted sandwich away, supposedly for testing.

Instead, the woman stored the wormy patty into her freezer for safekeeping.

The corporate number initially given to Klaiss turned out to be disconnected, but McDonald&#x2019;s corporate seems to have already made contact with her. Whether or not the issue has been resolved though remains unclear.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Worm sandwich,fish worm,mcdonalds worm,fish sandwich worm,fillet o fish worm,mcdonalds tainted food,mcdonalds worm sandwich,jerica klaiss</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3245732</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 03:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>25</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/476/00D/47600DB3F98C42119FAE8B39734A2673_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/03/3245732/3245732_6CA8402C35B64DD69B22006E069E7F6C_170103_3245732_Worm_sandwich__McDonald___s_fish_burger_features_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python snake attack: Horse watches large python swallowing wallaby in Australia</title>
      <description>QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; Horrific photos of a horse watching a large python gulping down a wallaby are have gone viral.

Captured by Bernie Worsfold, the images show the reptile wrapping around the marsupial and unlocking its jaws to swallow it.

Worlsfold told the ABC that it took three hours for the snake to swallow the animal.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Python snake attack,python v wallaby,horse watches,python swallows,python swallowing,python attack,queensland,australia,python,snake</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3245708</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 02:49:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>17</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/272/19F/27219F8133504F4E8111D41C81E60E2E_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/03/3245708/3245708_9A065992DEEF45EE8D0DFE0A45C10383_170103_3245708_Python_snake_attack__Horse_watches_large_python__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama expels 35 suspected Russian spies and closes 2 compounds</title>
      <description>&#x2018;MERICA &#x2014; U.S. President Barack Obama Thursday announced like plans to retaliate against Russia for allegedly hacking the Democrats during the 2016 election. 

Obama expelled 35 suspected Russian spies from the country, reported the New York Times, and placed sanctions on Moscow-based spy agencies.

The soon-to-be ex-POTUS also ordered the closure of two Russian luxury compounds in Maryland and New York, reported Reuters, for being suspected intelligence bases.  

Russia denied the accusations and has vowed to strike back against the U.S. 

In response to the news, U.S. President-Elect Donald Trump said it was time for Americans &#x201C;to move on to bigger and better things&#x201D;, in a statement.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Obama v putin,usa v russia,barack obama,vladimir putin,russia,usa,russia hacking,russia hacks usa,2016 election hack,hillary clinton,russia v democrats</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3245318</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 20:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1E0/BA4/1E0BA4D2482942C08C7F29BF68BA76B3_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/03/3245318/3245318_562C96E6C4FE4893A0C1177E52930593_170103_3245318_Obama_expels_35_suspected_Russian_spies_and_clos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad parking confrontation: Man punches female Lyft driver and knocks her tooth out</title>
      <description>SANTA ANA, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; Last Friday a female Lyft driver&#x2019;s botched parking job annoyed a man so much he knocked her front tooth out.

The driver, identified only as Terri, corrected her substandard parking job, but the man reversed into the spot beside her. Then he got out of his car and became aggressive toward her.

According to local news channel ABC KABC-TV, Terri&#x2019;s passenger went into the Arco gas station for help while she began recording the extremely triggered man. 

In the video he can be heard asking her, &#x201C;You wanna tape me?&#x201D;

That&#x2019;s when he&#x2019;s seen punching her to the ground. The man then allegedly laid into her and hit her so hard that he knocked her front tooth out.

Police are investigating the attack and looking for the man involved.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Bad parking confrontation,Violent attack caught on video,caught on camera,lyft driver attacked,uber driver attacked,man gets triggered,parking fails</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3245976</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 09:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BB0/8E0/BB08E0E20E3946CE80F89D0A0F879F72_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/03/3245976/3245976_90AE552D22224341903E012C9C075064_170103_3245976_Bad_parking_confrontation__Man_punches_female_Ly_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog stuck in escalator: Terrier rescued after back paw gets stuck in airport escalator</title>
      <description>FORT LAUDERDALE, FLORIDA &#x2014; New Year&#x2019;s Eve was harrowing for one terrier, who almost lost a paw to an escalator at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International airport.

WPLG reports that the dog was set to fly back to New York with its humans, and was walking up an escalator when its left hind leg was swallowed by the escalator guard.

The terrified owners attempted to free their pooch, only to get bitten by the distressed animal.

Airport deputies tried to help, but couldn&#x2019;t free the pup without the proper tools.

Firefighters from the Broward Sheriff Fire Rescue finally saved the day, freeing the terrier from the escalator&#x2019;s clutches and returning it to its humans &#x2014; both of whom refused treatment for their bites.

The dog wasn&#x2019;t seriously injured, but the incident should serve as a warning to keep animals off the moving steps.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Dog stuck in escalator,stuck in escalator,dog caught in escalator,dog paw,injured pup,fort lauderdale airport,dog stuck in airport escalator,airport escalator,animal injuries</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3246549</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 05:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D3E/553/D3E553CF52B842878FB6665E789466F9_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/04/3246549/3246549_095F94090F6243508A3EDE7E84A0D426_170104_3246549_Dog_stuck_in_escalator__Terrier_rescued_after_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feeding hungry raccoons: teen wins hearts online for friendship with family of raccoons</title>
      <description>SEATTLE &#x2014; A young woman is quickly gaining attention on Twitter for her newfound kinship with a gaze of hungry raccoons.

In August of 2016, Kaylah Lynn, 18, began feeding a lone raccoon that came by her home in search of food. The teen opened her fridge to the raccoon with offerings of bread, and gave her the name Rosemary. 

After a few regular feedings, Rosemary the raccoon stopped coming as often. Weeks later though, the raccoon started showing up with a four other family members. Before long, Lynn found herself providing dinner for the hungry critters every night at 7:30 on the dot. 

The relationship was quick to catch fire on Twitter, garnering 22,000 retweets after Lynn&#x2019;s pics were posted on December 28. While this friendly feeding may seem harmless, others looking to befriend raccoons and other wildlife should keep in mind, if raccoons get used to coming over for handouts, it may hamper their foraging skills in the wild. Experts say those offering food should probably only do it once in awhile, so the raccoons do not become reliant on humans for meals.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Feedings raccoons,raccoons,funny raccoons,raccoons eating,kaylah lynn,raccoons trash</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3246535</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 05:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EC5/19A/EC519A7C528743B9BBA0FE5ED7664C79_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/04/3246535/3246535_AAB9AE02579A468D992360C3C5D7DF15_170104_3246535_Feeding_hungry_raccoons__teen_wins_hearts_online_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drinking and flying: Indonesian pilot attempts to fly commercial plane while drunk</title>
      <description>SURABAYA, INDONESIA &#x2014; A low-cost carrying airline is under investigation after one of its pilots was caught trying to fly a commercial Airbus while intoxicated.

On December 28, the tipsy pilot, 32-year-old Tekad Purna, successfully bypassed security checkpoints, stumbling through the metal detector and dropping personal items along the way. 

The pilot then entered the cockpit, and began making a largely incomprehensible pre-flight announcement that unnerved a number of the 154 passengers on board. 

Several passengers walked off the plane and reported the pilot&#x2019;s strange behavior to Citilink airline staff, who then quickly had him removed and replaced. The flight took off about an hour behind schedule.

The president and operational director of Citilink have both resigned over the incident, and the pilot has been fired as the investigation continues. 

One year ago, Airlineratings.com ranked Citilink among the bottom ten of the world&#x2019;s major airlines with the lowest safety ratings, nine of which were from Indonesia. Since 2001, a reported 40 air accidents in Indonesia have resulted in fatalities. 

Factors for the country&#x2019;s failings range from outdated equipment and planes, to runways that are too short. A shortage of skilled pilots, ground personnel and air traffic controllers is also to blame, with only 1,400 people charged with monitoring the more than 10,000 Indonesian flights per day. 

According to an MIT statistician working in airline safety, one out of one million airline passengers will die onboard an Indonesian flight, 25 times the death rate of airlines in the United States.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Drunk pilot,citilink,drunk citilink pilot,indonesian pilot,tekad purna,airbus</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3246533</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 05:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6AF/713/6AF713BC09B346148E1A3A774A33A9FC_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/04/3246533/3246533_29F95AE3524441CAB6E958B962B235D2_170104_3246533_Drinking_and_flying__Indonesian_pilot_attempts_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperloop One to build first Hyperloop System in UAE</title>
      <description>DUBAI, UAE &#x2014; Los Angeles-based start-up Hyperloop One has signed an agreement with Dubai&#x2019;s Roads and Transport Authority to build the world&#x2019;s first Hyperloop system, which will connect Abu Dhabi and Dubai in the United Arab Emirates.

The stations for Hyperloop One&#x2019;s system, called Hyperportals, will be located in the city centers. The Hyperportal in Abu Dhabi will be located near the Etihad Towers, while the one in Dubai will be located near the world&#x2019;s tallest building, the Burj Khalifa.

Passengers will travel in pods, which come in four different configurations: cargo, coach, meeting, and lounge. The pods will pick up passengers at gates and travel autonomously to an underground level. There, they will be loaded inside a transporter capsule. Each transporter capsule will carry four pods.

The capsules will be propelled by compressed air using magnetic levitation, which eliminates friction, inside a tube kept at a near-vacuum, to eliminate air resistance. They can travel at a speed up to 1,200 km per hour. The Hyperloop will reduce the normal two-hour travel time by car between Abu Dhabi to Dubai to just 12 minutes.

The capsules will stop at the Hyperportal upon arrival, while the autonomous pods can either stop at the gates or continue beyond the Hyperportal to take the passengers to destinations in the city.

Hyperloop One said in a press release that the infrastructure does not have to work with the pods alone and could work with other self-driving vehicles in the future.</description>
      <tags>video,Hyperloop one,hyperloop,hyperloop system,hyperloop in UAE,hyperloop dubai and abu dhabi,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224771</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 03:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>84</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7AD/CA2/7ADCA28226FA40D487B51C85540131D9_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3224771/3224771_24AAE694AC8E4ABE99244E8B82893DB4_161206_3224771_Hyperloop_One_to_build_first_Hyperloop_System_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private German moon mission plans to inspect Apollo 17 lunar rover</title>
      <description>BERLIN &#x2014; A team of scientists in Germany has developed a lunar rover that will soon fly to the moon and visit the legendary Apollo 17 Lunar Rover Vehicle.


The rover is developed by the team called PTScientists, in collaboration with automaker Audi. Dubbed Audi Lunar Quattro, the rover is made of aluminium and titanium, and created almost entirely from 3D printing technology. It is equipped with 4-wheel drive technology, solar panels, rechargeable lithium ion batteries, as well as science-grade high-definition cameras.


Two rovers will be carried by the ALINA spacecraft, which stands for the Autonomous Landing and Navigation Module. ALINA will also carry several other payloads, including a lunar plant growth experiment. It has not been confirmed, but a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket is reportedly will likely be used to transport the rovers into space.


ALINA will touch down about 5 km from the Apollo 17 in the Taurus-Littrow valley. After landing on the moon, the two rovers will be deployed and will travel toward the Apollo 17 lunar rover. However, they are not allowed any closer than 200 meters of the Apollo rover, per NASA&#x2019;s request. The rovers will send live HD pictures of the Apollo rover to Earth.</description>
      <tags>video,Ptscientists,audi lunar quattro,german moon mission,google lunar x-prize,space,moon,apollo 17,apollo 17 lunar roving vehicle,science,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224260</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/707/5C8/7075C86C7C21440F9EA887EAC26A59D6_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/05/3224260/3224260_E36ED927C94E4887BA558528DF23CCC7_161205_3224260_Private_German_moon_mission_plans_to_inspect_Apo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Taiwan phone call controversy and Taiwan-China relations explained</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014;  U.S. President-elect Donald Trump took one phone call from Taiwan and everybody lost their minds.

But why?

The congratulatory phone call U.S. President-elect Donald Trump took from Taiwan last week was a surprise to politicians and press, as his staff to downplayed the political implications of the conversation.

The widespread reaction to the call has left many members of the public wondering why a conversation with Taiwan&#x2019;s president would be so controversial.

Civil war in 1927 that involved Communist revolutionaries led by Mao Zedong, and the Nationalist government led to the Nationalists feat in 1949. They fled to Taiwan, where they kept control of their forces. Fighting ceased, with the two sides being ruled separately. However, both sides continued to claim authority over all of China.

China has maintained that Taiwan is a breakaway province and that the two sides will eventually unify. Meanwhile, the Taiwan-based government at the time declared mainland China was being controlled by illegitimate Communist rebels.

The Nationalists were originally recognized by the United States and its allies as China&#x2019;s rightful rulers, with the government in Taiwan taking China&#x2019;s seat in the United Nations. However,  Beijing eventually took over Taiwan&#x2019;s seat, and when the U.S. eventually switched recognition from Taiwan to Beijing in 1979, many other countries followed its lead.

Taiwan, now a democratic sovereignty, cannot reintegrate with China, as many of its people have said they will not surrender their freedoms. China has also threatened any declaration of independence with military force.

Although tension between the two sides continues, Taiwan and China have increased cooperation over the years in the forms of postal, trade and transportation links.

The U.S. passed a law requiring the government provide Taiwan with defensive weapons in case of potential aggression from China. However, to protect the status quo, the U.S. has at the same time maintained that its official policy does not support an independent Taiwan. To keep the peace, the U.S. has retained an ambiguous position of keeping close relations to Taiwan, while refusing to recognize its independence.

Trump&#x2019;s phone call with Taiwan&#x2019;s President Tsai Ing-wen has sent a shockwave to China, as taking her call alongside other foreign leaders&#x2019; could be seen as a nod to Taiwan&#x2019;s sovereign status. However, whether that one phone call signals an actual shift in U.S. policy regarding Taiwan remains to be seen.</description>
      <tags>video,Ptscientists,audi lunar quattro,german moon mission,google lunar x-prize,space,moon,apollo 17,apollo 17 lunar roving vehicle,science,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3224110</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 08:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>47</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F64/3FA/F643FAF9167D40D999859D4CE674CFA9_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/05/3224110/3224110_F4300749597D43D2B410E5A3A2C41184_161205_3224110_Trump_Taiwan_phone_call_controversy_and_Taiwan_C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pets on a plane: Stop pretending your pets are service or emotional support animals</title>
      <description>THE FRIENDLY SKIES &#x2014; Anyone who&#x2019;s been flying the friendly skies this past year has probably noticed that the passenger cabin has been looking more and more like a zoo with the sudden proliferation of service dogs and emotional support animals. 

By law, service and pet therapy animals fly for free. Enter the people now ruining it for everyone else because they are too cheap to pay to bring their pets on the plane.  

Service animal vests or tags can now be easily purchased online for varying prices, the Detroit Free Press reported.    

And with cases of emotional support animals, all a passenger has to do is show a letter from a mental health professional saying that they need the animal for air travel. 

The problem is counterfeit letters can also be bought online for less than $100. 

Blind people and other people with actual disabilities have fought hard to get public access for their dogs and service animals. 

If you&#x2019;re too cheap to pay for your pet to fly, rather than screw over people that actually need their service animals, take a road trip instead.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,service dogs,service pets,fake service dog,fake service pets,emotional support animals,pets on a plane,seeing eye dog</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3246737</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 10:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>111</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BA7/2D6/BA72D621008040DBAA0D10D96456F756_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/04/3246737/3246737_5BA9BE08B2E94CC7B98A172C6B7C9D4D_170104_3246737_Pets_on_a_plane__Stop_pretending_your_pets_are_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Chicago kidnappers live-broadcast torture of white special needs man on Facebook</title>
      <description>CHICAGO &#x2014; Chicago police are investigating a Facebook live video showing the sickening torture of a special needs man and already have four of the perpetrators in custody

CBS Chicago reports that four African-Americans &#x2014; two men and two women &#x2014; took the 18-year-old victim hostage in the suburbs and brought him into Chicago&#x2019;s West Side in a stolen van.

They kept him bound and gagged in an apartment, where they began brutally torturing him while high on weed and alcohol.

The foursome cursed Trump and white people before using a knife to cut through their captive&#x2019;s clothes, hair and scalp.

The poor victim was repeatedly hit and peppered with cigarette ash even as his head wound began to bleed.

He was eventually let go and later found by police, traumatized while wandering the nearby streets, according to a statement by the Chicago Police Department posted on Twitter. He was brought to the hospital for treatment and is now with his parents.

Criminal charges are expected to be filed against the four suspects, who are currently being questioned by the cops.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Facebook live torture,torture live stream,live stream,facebook live,white special needs victim tortured,man tortured,torture,attack,brutal attack</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247421</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 06:31:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E45/584/E455849239C34BD29DF019B3C049B709_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/05/3247421/3247421_2FBF4EC239E64FEBB472E424FB0429EC_170105_3247421_Black_Chicago_kidnappers_live_broadcast_torture__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car sinks in water: car rolls of barge, sinks to the bottom of ocean in Australia</title>
      <description>FRASER ISLAND, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; Viral video filmed last week on a barge travelling to Australia&#x2019;s tourist hotspot Fraser Island shows an SUV rolling off the vessel and sinking.

The footage was posted to Facebook by Chloe Swift on Saturday. She wrote on Facebook people had lost their phones, debit cards and passports. No one was in the car at the time of the accident. 

According to Queensland newspaper The Brisbane Times, the barge was operated by Manta Ray Fraser Island Barges. They told the newspaper they&#x2019;re probing the incident.

The vehicle was parked with handbrake on, but wasn&#x2019;t left in gear. The ramp was low while far into its journey, a passenger explained to the Brisbane Times.

The vehicle had been rented by a group of travelers who were in transit to Fraser Island.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Car falls off boat,epic boating fails,suv falls into water,sinking car,car sinking in ocean,car falls into water,fraser island,australia,manta ray fraser island</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247206</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 02:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8BE/3C0/8BE3C013B4AE49CBA120A0A147150549_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/05/3247206/3247206_8683AD2BFF4746069EA6E4B5EBABF129_170105_3247206_Car_sinks_in_water__car_rolls_of_barge__sinks_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police shootouts caught on tape: Gunman killed after firing at cops in Arizona Walmart</title>
      <description>CHANDLER, ARIZONA &#x2014; Surveillance footage from an Arizona Walmart shows the moment a man opens fire on cops in a surprise attack.

The shootout happened last year on April 23 at a Walmart store in Chandler, ABC 15 Arizona reported. The footage was released after Chandler police compiled a 288-page report on the shooting.

The footage shows officers Daniel Colwell and Joshua Puebla dealing with trespassing suspect Mitchell Oakley. The exchange appears nonchalant until Oakley pulls a gun and starts shooting.

He shot Puebla in the face, arm and back and Colwell twice in the torso. The footage then shows Oakley trying to escape the store, but little did he know Colwell was wearing a ballistics vest.

According to the Arizona Republic, Colwell shot Oakley five times before killing him.

Oakley, aged 24, was homeless and on parole at the time of the shooting.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Police shootouts caught on tape,Police shootings caught on camera 2016,Police gunfight,arizona shootout,police shootouts,cops v bad guys,police ambush,bad guy fails,walmart shootout</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247125</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 01:13:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>18</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/035/D47/035D4711B0DD4CA781C1339AA29464D2_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/05/3247125/3247125_62B52A3178374B81B88167B7B92ADD73_170105_3247125_Police_shootouts_caught_on_tape__Gunman_killed_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busting a nut: woman sprayed at Walmart, man arrested for spreading sticky substance</title>
      <description>MARIETTA, OHIO &#x2014; A married man has been busted by the cops for a number of nasty deeds he committed at a Walmart during the final weeks of 2016. The incidents involved the use of a syringe, filled with semen. 

In early November, a female shopper reported that she felt the presence of a creepy man lingering behind her while she perused the store&#x2019;s makeup aisle. With her back turned to him, she suddenly felt a sticky, wet substance dripping from her foot and lower back area. The woman ran to the restroom to wash out the goo, and when she walked out, the strange man was standing there, staring at her. 

The sperm-squirting assailant then took off, but not before the woman was able to get a good look at his truck. When another instance was reported at the same Walmart on December 28, police were able to identify and track down 28-year-old married man Timothy Blake, using surveillance footage and the truck description.

After being confronted by police, Blake admitted to unloading a semen-filled syringe on a dozen different women at that location. He claims the disgusting act was something he&#x2019;d discovered online, and was his way of having sex with his victims. He initially told police he&#x2019;d used egg yolks, but when they said they had &#x201C;had the material tested,&#x201D; he admitted to using semen on at least four separate occasions. 

Blake is currently free after posting $11,000 bond. He has been charged with two felony obscenity counts, and must wear a GPS monitor as part of his release conditions.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Walmart,only at walmart,man sprays woman,sticky substance,man attacks woman,walmart people,woman sprayed,ejaculate sperms,Timothy blake,the smoking gun,using syringes,busting a nut</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247101</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0AC/68E/0AC68EA701BF4B59AEFDCE96CBFB3E18_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/05/3247101/3247101_349327D13235485C9A3564A5F49DCB6C_170105_3247101_Busting_a_nut__woman_sprayed_at_Walmart__man_arr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyal dog: dog protects injured dog stuck on train tracks for two days in snowy weather</title>
      <description>UZHHOROD &#x2014; An injured dog that was stranded on snowy train tracks near Uzhhorod in Ukraine was watched over by her loyal friend for two days until help arrived. 

Local resident Denis Malafeev found the two dogs, named Lucy and Panda, on Dec. 26. 

To protect Lucy, who was injured and could not move, Panda became defensive when they were approached by the human rescuers. 

Malafeev said on Facebook that Panda took care of Lucy by curling up next to her, with both of them pressing themselves against the tracks when trains passed over them. Panda reportedly never abandoned Lucy during their two days on the train tracks.

The dogs were later taken to a animal protection center, where Lucy received medical attention. Thankfully, according to Malafeev, she only sustained bruises and hematomas. So it&#x2019;s not clear why the dogs stayed on the tracks.

The animal protection center returned the dogs to their owners after tracking them down. In a recent Facebook update, Malafeev noted that not all people would do what Panda did for Lucy.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Loyal dog,dog protects dog friend,dog saves,loyal dog waits for,dog helps friend,loyal dog stays by fallen companion,stuck on train tracks,Uzhhorod,Ukraine,cute dog videos</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247033</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 23:23:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>17</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/63E/A90/63EA906739A84302AD4CFCF1ED4A1975_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/05/3247033/3247033_10C291525FB24396BB7821B1EBF62145_170105_3247033_Loyal_dog__dog_protects_injured_dog_stuck_on_tra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cameroon to turn human waste to clean power in biogas project</title>
      <description>BUEA, CAMEROON &#x2014; Two towns in Cameroon have installed biogas systems to turn human waste into sustainable energy that can provide fuel and electricity for local communities.


The project was initiated by Bioenergy-Cameroon, a non-governmental youth organization. Local students, especially female students, are trained on how to install and maintain innovative technology systems such as solar power and biogas mechanisms.


According to Reuters, the system includes a septic tank, which is connected to a bio-digester at individual households. Human waste placed in the septic tank is converted into biogas inside the bio-digesters, which release energy into people&#x2019;s homes for cooking and lighting.


Reuters reports that more than 3,000 households and local schools in the towns of Buea and Bamenda have installed the biogas system. The Center for Environment and Development, an NGO in Cameroon, estimates that the biogas project may reduce greenhouse gas emissions in the vicinity by up to 60 percent.</description>
      <tags>video,Cameroon biogas project,buea biogas project,bamenda biogas project,biogas,clean energy,technology,bioenergy-cameroon</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225297</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 22:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EC1/5BE/EC15BEBCE74D41D9BD0816FC359E3C01_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/06/3225297/3225297_06B78041E91246D49634B4E51829C953_161206_3225297_Cameroon_to_turn_human_waste_to_clean_power_in_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly NBC News: Anchor dumping FOX News for brand new gig over at NBC</title>
      <description>NEW YORK &#x2014; After 12 long years of being fair and balanced at Fox News, anchor Megyn Kelly is leaving to take on a broad new role at NBC News. 

Kelly will host her own daytime news and talk show, anchor an in-depth Sunday night news show as well as take on a role in NBC&#x2019;s breaking news coverage, the New York Times reported. 

The anchor&#x2019;s move will shake things up in the land of cable news where she had become the second-most watched host after Bill O&#x2019;Reilly of Fox News. 

Kelly&#x2019;s exit also throws a wrench into Fox News&#x2019; primetime lineup, and adds to the drama following the Roger Ailes sexual harassment scandal.   

NBC is probably hoping that the addition of Kelly will get more conservative viewers to flip to their channel, but will it work?</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Megyn Kelly NBC News,Megyn Kelly leaving Fox,Megyn Kelly leaving Fox News,Megyn Kelly Roger Ailes,The Kelly File,Fox News vs NBC News</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247614</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 11:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>121</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7AB/9C4/7AB9C47F2D9F446DB35FCB2246D47186_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/05/3247614/3247614_E1A3801E97914612887323F245C6DB69_170105_3247614_Megyn_Kelly_NBC_News__Anchor_dumping_FOX_News_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher steals inappropriate photos from students, gets caught sharing them online</title>
      <description>LOUISVILLE, KENTUCKY &#x2014; The porn-addicted former principal of an Elizabethtown, Kentucky high school is facing child pornography charges after admitting he confiscated students&#x2019; cell phones to trade their nude images online.

Stephen Kyle Goodlett, 36, was indicted on Wednesday on federal kiddy porn charges after last month pleading not guilty to 63 state offenses, the Associated Press reported. 

The married father of three was arrested in October last year, then fired from his job after the offenses were discovered.

Goodlett admitted to investigators that he is addicted to porn. He said he seized students&#x2019; phones and traded their naked photos for dirty images with a porn site based in Russia.

The case came to light in September last year when a 20-year-old woman found naked photos of herself online. The sexy snaps were taken when she was aged just 15. The woman went to local cops, who called in federal investigators. The feds then tracked Goodlett down through his IP address.

Investigators found at least 60 examples of child porn on the former LaRue County High School principal&#x2019;s devices.

The authorities are appealing for any of Goodlett&#x2019;s former students who had their phones confiscated to come forward as they build a case against him.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Teacher steals from students,inappropriate photos,student pictures,teacher takes student&#x2019;s phone,selfies that went too far,teaching sexting,viral photos,teacher scandal,school scandal,Louisville,Kentucky</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3248258</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 04:14:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>25</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/31E/676/31E67651686B4C1A87FF2D8B25D6872A_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/06/3248258/3248258_5C33737F4B214F018F19E53E37B54B93_170106_3248258_Teacher_steals_inappropriate_photos_from_student_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un vs South Korea: Seoul creates &#x2018;decapitation unit&#x2019; to take out DPRK dictator - TomoNews</title>
      <description>SEOUL &#x2014; The South Korean Ministry of Defense is reportedly creating a hit squad with the sole purpose of taking out North Korean leadership &#x2014; namely dictator Kim Jong Un and his crony generals &#x2014; should war break out between the two nations.

Known as the &#x201C;decapitation unit&#x201D;, they would sneak into the North during the &#x201C;event of war&#x201D; and then begin to target the DPRK&#x2019;s &#x201C;wartime command&#x201D;, reported CNN.

The unit would be part of a &#x201C;kill chain&#x201D; operation. If war happens, this would see Seoul deploy anti-missile defences and a &#x201C;pre-emptive military strike&#x201D; against Pyongyang, the International Business Times reported, citing a South Korean official.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Kim jong un vs south korea,kim jong un death,kim jong un assassination,south korea kill kim jong un,North Korea v South Korea,Kim jong un funny</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3248183</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 03:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>26</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/89F/02B/89F02BE92EF34B10AEB029DABDCFE138_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/06/3248183/3248183_251621C532FC431B8CAAC7B136C03F94_170106_3248183_Kim_Jong_Un_vs_South_Korea__Seoul_creates____dec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old lady blacks out behind the wheel, crash SUV into roof of North Carolina house</title>
      <description>WINSTON-SALEM, NORTH CAROLINA &#x2014; Residents of a group home in Winston-Salem, North Carolina got a shocking surprise when an SUV crash-landed in their living room on Friday.

The Winston-Salem Journal reports that 84-year-old Janice Harrison Clodfelter was driving when she suddenly passed out behind the wheel from a medical emergency.

Her vehicle continued down the road at 70 to 90 miles per hour. It sped past an intersection before hitting a curb and going up an embankment.

The white Buick SUV got launched into the air and crashed through the roof of a nearby house, right into the living room.

The house was a residential facility for autistic adults, six of whom were home during the crash. With the vehicle blocking the exit, two were trapped in the living room and had to be helped out by witnesses who broke through the house&#x2019;s front window.

One of the witnesses also kept Clodfelter company until officers, firefighters and emergency medical personnel arrived to pull her out of the SUV. She was taken to the hospital and treated for minor injuries.

Firefighters later removed the car, pulling it back out through the hole in the roof.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Crazy car crashes,crazy car accident,insane car crash,insane car accident,car crashes into roof,car flies through air,car crashes into house,lost consciousness,woman blacks out,passing out,black out,behind the wheel,north carolina,SUV</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3248114</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 02:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BC5/5C3/BC55C36D88AF488DBAA1D1F8FE5666C7_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/06/3248114/3248114_0E0AEA7FAEA24A5BAFE651321695DE0E_170106_3248114_Old_lady_loses_blacks_out_behind_the_wheel__cras_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Llama on the loose: escaped llama running across busy highway photographed by motorists</title>
      <description>OCONEE COUNTY, GEORGIA &#x2014; Motorists had more than just other cars, bikes, and pedestrians to watch out for on the road after a llama was seen running around a town just outside of Athens.

On Jan. 4, police responded to calls from citizens of a camel in the streets, but they quickly found out the suspect in question was actually an escaped llama, who&#x2019;d somehow broken out of its owner&#x2019;s property and decided to trot along down a busy highway. 

Police managed to corner the llama behind a dumpster in the back of a restaurant. The restaurant owner also provided a bag of carrots to lure the creature into custody, and its owner arrived with a van shortly afterward to bring the fearless camelid home to safety.

During its adventure, the llama quickly rose to fame on social media, spotted by drivers both amused and confused by its presence.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,llama on the loose,escaped llama,llama running,animals on the run,escaped animals,oconee county sheriff&#x2019;s office,baby camel,escaped camel,running camel</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3248109</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 02:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F7C/779/F7C77933F4884CADA82AB830A5954DA6_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/06/3248109/3248109_0C92DF87C26A4EACABCFF5F9B408C54E_170106_3248109_Llama_on_the_loose__escaped_llama_running_across_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman&#x2019;s son drops a dab on House Speaker Paul Ryan</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; A Congressman&#x2019;s son was grounded by his dad this week for teaching House Speaker Paul Ryan how to dab.

Cal Marshall, 17, is the son of Roger Marshall, the Republican representative for the First District of Kansas.

Young Cal caused a bit of confusion at his dad&#x2019;s swearing-in photo call on Tuesday, when Ryan asked if he was leaning into his elbow to sneeze. But no, like countless sports stars, performers and 12-year-old kids over the past two years or so, Cal was dropping a dab on &#x2019;em folks, the New York Times reported.

Afterward, Cal wrote on Twitter that he was surprised by the media coverage of his antics. But the House Speaker failed to see the funny side, posting on Twitter that he was still clueless about dabbing. 

In the end, Ryan got the last laugh. Congressman Marshall posted on Twitter that Cal was now grounded, which should give the teenager time to work on some new dance moves.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Dab dabbing,dabbin dance,paul ryan,cal marshall,swearing in,congress,congressional,roger marshall,kansas,swearing-in,roger marshall son,house speaker,inappropriate dancing,prank,pranking my dad,prank dab,son pranks dad,sneezing</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247854</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 22:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/08D/1B0/08D1B05EE9704F34B0144088BFD56C9D_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/06/3247854/3247854_2480B4CCF6C942A7AA03A70FA67A6B01_170106_3247854_Congressman___s_son_drops_a_dab_on_House_Speaker_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demon caught on camera: picture of demon sighting in Arizona goes viral on Facebook</title>
      <description>LAVEEN, ARIZONA &#x2014; This photo of what appears to be some sort of winged creature has gone viral, with some saying it&#x2019;s a demon, while others insist it&#x2019;s an angel. 

Richard Christianson from Laveen, Arizona posted the photo on Facebook on Jan. 1. In his post, Christianson asked: &#x201C;What the hell do you see in this picture for reals ??? Anybody.&#x201D;

The post was shared 80,000 times before Christianson took it down on Wednesday. But many people are skeptical, suggesting the dark shape looming over the sidewalk is likely just a tree or a Photoshop job. 

However, Facebook user Crissy Love seems convinced of the photo&#x2019;s authenticity. Love noted that there weren&#x2019;t any palm trees in Laveen that look like a demon. &#x201C;I knew Laveen was haunted,&#x201D; she wrote.
 
But what do you think? Is this just a tree shaped like a winged spirit? A Photoshop stunt? Or is it evidence of the supernatural? Let us know in the comments.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Picture of demon,demon photos,viral content,demon sightings,photoshop prank,photoshop trolls,photoshop stunts,paranormal activity,evidence of paranormal activity,devil sightings,hell on earth,evidence of the devil,evidence of demons,demon seen on camera,demon caught on camera,angel sightings,angel caught on tape</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3247814</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 21:31:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3BC/F58/3BCF5884AA3B454BA3F0D8076F58E894_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/06/3247814/3247814_062C3071040A4698A87A7EBF512EE9BA_170106_3247814_Demon_caught_on_camera__picture_of_demon_sightin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesia earthquake: Nearly 100 dead, hundreds more injured as quake strikes Sumatra</title>
      <description>SIGLI, INDONESIA &#x2014; Rescuers were continuing to search for survivors after an earthquake struck Indonesia&#x2019;s largest island, Sumarta, on Wednesday, killing at least 97 people and injuring hundreds more.

The 6.5 magnitude quake hit the east coast of Aceh province, about 11 miles southeast of the town of Sigli, according to the United States Geological Survey (USGS).

Indonesian authorities said the Pidie Jaya regency, which has a population of 140,000, was the worst-hit area, Reuters reported.

Indonesia sits on the Ring of Fire and has experienced 15 earthquakes measuring 6 or more on the Richter scale since December last year, according to the USGS.

Around 120,000 people were killed in Aceh when the region suffered huge destruction in the Indian Ocean tsunami of 2004, which was triggered by a 9.2 magnitude earthquake.

However, no tsunami warning was issued in relation to this most recent quake.</description>
      <tags>video,Indonesia earthquake,aceh earthquake,indonesia quake,earthquake indonesia,quake hits indonesia,earthquake,quake</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226792</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 06:14:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A51/D55/A51D55B6D878467E841119A0365F07BF_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/08/3226792/3226792_A87CE9D4BE3A410988BE48DA5E031FC7_161208_3226792_Indonesia_earthquake__Nearly_100_dead__hundreds__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Go grocery store gets rid of long, tedious checkout lines</title>
      <description>SEATTLE &#x2014; Amazon is opening a grocery store in downtown Seattle early next year where customers can make their purchases without waiting in checkout lines.


The store, called Amazon Go, allows customers to make purchases without the aid of a cashier.


Customers would simply need to download the an app onto their phones, open an Amazon account, and visit the Amazon Go store.


Amazon&#x2019;s promotional video shows how customers are admitted into the store after opening their Amazon Go app and scanning it on the turnstiles. The app generates a QR code that logs the customer into the store&#x2019;s network and connects to the customer&#x2019;s Amazon account. This prevents shoplifting as the customer&#x2019;s identity is recognized and stored.


The entire store is equipped with computer vision, sensor fusion and deep learning technology. It can automatically detect when products are taken from the shelves and records them in virtual shopping carts. The products are removed from the carts if they are placed back onto the shelves.


When leaving the store, customers have to pass through turnstiles equipped with sensors that signal the app to calculate the cost of the purchases. The payment is then charged to the customer&#x2019;s Amazon account.


The pictures shown on the Amazon website suggest that some staff might still be responsible for making ready-to-eat meals or other preparations at the store, but the store would probably not include any cashiers or people to bag groceries. 


According to the Bureau of Labor Statistics, about 3.4 million Americans are working as cashiers. The New York Post quoted Britt Beam, president of America&#x2019;s Research Group &#x2014; a consumer-behavior research firm &#x2014; saying that Amazon&#x2019;s technology might wipe out 75 percent of typical grocery-store staff.</description>
      <tags>video,Amazon go,amazon go grocery store,amazon grocery store seattle,amazon go seattle,amazon technology,technology,grocery store of the future</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3226263</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>51</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9D9/238/9D9238900E8048938939FECD68B1C685_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/07/3226263/3226263_29CC47C822C846279F6E4A8D0B0D1D4D_161207_3226263_Amazon_Go_grocery_store_gets_rid_of_long__tediou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian drone sub: New drone can imitate any enemy submarine</title>
      <description>ST. PETERSBURG, RUSSIA &#x2014; Russian President Vladimir Putin could soon have an ocean-going robotized system at his disposal that can mimic the characteristics of different submarines, making it useful for naval exercises as well as reconnaissance missions.

The Surrogat, an autonomous, unmanned submarine powered by lithium-ion batteries  that can operate for 15 to 16 hours at a time, is being developed by military designers from Russia&#x2019;s Rubin Central Design Bureau for Marine Engineering, Russian news agency TASS reports. 

The drone measures more than 50 feet long and weighs almost 40 tons, with a maximum diving depth of almost 2,000 feet.

It can employ towed sonar arrays to simulate another submarine&#x2019;s acoustic and electromagnetic fields and imitate both conventional and nuclear submarines.

The Surrogat can also be used for underwater terrain mapping and reconnaissance.

Military designers claim the drone is simple to operate, with low maintenance and upgrade costs. They are currently in talks with the Russian Navy, and believe there may be interest from foreign customers.</description>
      <tags>video,Surrogat,underwater robot,putin underwater robot,underwater drone,russia drone,submarine imitator,russia navy,military submarine,sub imitator</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3225875</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 08:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>41</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/11D/5FA/11D5FA844490487D84EAA2758BB45ADA_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/07/3225875/3225875_8ACC632530634ECE93B736B65B54A8FF_161207_3225875_Russian_drone_sub__New_drone_can_imitate_any_ene_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese propaganda animation targets Chinese millennials, Apple helps clamps down on New York Times</title>
      <description>BEIJING &#x2014; As China&#x2019;s millennials have become more tech-savvy, the Chinese Communist Party has tried to retool its propaganda machine for a new audience.   
 
Xi Jinping has forced propaganda officers to utilize digital media to resist foreign popular culture influences, and to target younger audiences, the New York Times reported.

The party has invested millions in animated videos, while Chinese scholars copy TED-style talks to criticize the West. 

They even have lame &#x201C;hip hop&#x201D; groups that suck up to the CCP and warn about America&#x2019;s efforts to topple the regime. 

And now even Apple is getting in on the selling out game. At the behest of Beijing, Apple has kicked the New York Times out of China&#x2019;s Apple Store. 

Chinese law prohibits the publication of &#x201C;harmful information&#x201D; &#x2014; aka reality &#x2014; online. 

Funny how Tim Cook will refuse to unlock an iPhone in the U.S., but turns to putty for the CCP. But hey, who needs freedom of information when you can buy a shiny new iPhone.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Chinese propaganda animation,Chinese millennials,China propaganda department,Xi Jinping animations,chinese cartoons,china cartoons,New York Times app,new york times apple,china apple store,apple app store,CD Rev this is China,Chinese Communist Party,CCP</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3248568</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 10:18:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>113</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EB9/7DD/EB97DD0A88A946C9BC908E837DC7FC8C_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/06/3248568/3248568_16C20F37F28049638558D0AFA294BDE0_170106_3248568_Chinese_propaganda_animation_targets_Chinese_mil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffes face threat of extinction after numbers drop by 40% in just 30 years</title>
      <description>GLAND, SWITZERLAND &#x2014;  Once thought to be abundant in number, giraffes are now in danger of extinction, according to the authors of a report published on Thursday.

The International Union for the Conservation of Nature (IUCN) said the number of giraffes in the wild has declined by about 40 percent in the last three decades, the New York Times reported.

Giraffes, the world&#x2019;s tallest land mammal, are mostly found in southern and eastern Africa, with smaller populations in West and Central Africa.

In 1985, there were approximately 163,000 giraffes in the wild, but that number now stands at around 97,000, according to the IUCN report.

However, of the nine giraffe subspecies, three are increasing in number and one is stable. The five other subspecies are decreasing in population size.

The biggest threats to giraffes&#x2019; survival are the encroachment of humans, poaching, destruction of their habitat by economic activity such as mining, and war.

The IUCN monitors endangered species on its Red List. The organization now classifies giraffes as vulnerable, meaning the species faces a high risk of extinction in the wild.</description>
      <tags>video,Giraffe,giraffes,giraffes in danger,giraffes under threat,giraffes extinction,giraffe in africa,IUCN red list,conservation</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3227668</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 04:29:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>41</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C0E/091/C0E091AD3EF4493DAD4957CA09313A80_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/09/3227668/3227668_74838F9601ED481B9A049CDCBEF550F1_161209_3227668_Giraffes_face_threat_of_extinction_after_numbers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear football: US president's emergency satchel of nuclear codes will go to Trump</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON  &#x2014; The mysterious &#x201C;nuclear football&#x201D; that contains classified information to allow the U.S. president to order a nuclear attack at anytime and from anywhere in the world is about to be handed over to president-elect Donald Trump.

The &#x201C;nuclear football&#x201D; is formally known as the Presidential Emergency Satchel. It contains four things: a folder of instructions for the Emergency Broadcast System; a black book of strike options, another book that lists secure shelters for the president, and a card with authentication codes for the president to confirm his identity. It also allows the president to communicate with the Pentagon from any location.

The briefcase is hand-carried by one of five military aides. In order to qualify for the responsibility, the candidate must pass a special security investigation known as &#x201C;Yankee White.&#x201D; The criteria for the position includes having U.S. citizenship, possessing unquestionable loyalty to the country, and the individual, his or her family or anyone the individual is closely linked with must be absolutely devoid of foreign influence. The officer carrying the &#x2018;football&#x2019; must always be within reach of the president.

If the president decides to deploy nuclear weapons, he must use a special code on the card to verify his identity, which has to be confirmed by the Secretary of Defense. However, the Secretary of Defense no veto power over the president&#x2019;s decision.

The black book contains a menu of nuclear strike options, allowing the president to choose to eliminate all of the country&#x2019;s enemies at once, or to only target individual countries. Once the orders have been verified, the military issues the attack.</description>
      <tags>video,Nuclear football,nuclear briefcase,us president nuclear football,trump and nuclear football,pentagon,us president nuclear power</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3227369</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>64</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E5E/61A/E5E61A66FCB64BBF97DEBD734DA4007A_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/09/3227369/3227369_5633E1F47C604560953C2E866AF40449_161209_3227369_Nuclear_football__US_president_s_emergency_satch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake eats snake alive: Deadly brown snake eats carpet python in rare Australia video</title>
      <description>BRISBANE, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; Extremely rare footage of a brown snake eating a carpet python has been captured on film &#x2026; where else, but Down Under?

The incident was filmed on Jan. 2 at a suburban house near Brisbane in the state of Queensland. It shows a deadly brown snake taking several leisurely hours to devour his less-fortunate fellow serpent, presumably after a fight to the death. 

Brown snakes are the world&#x2019;s second-most venomous land snake and are responsible for about half of all human deaths from snake bites in Australia. The non-poisonous carpet python &#x2026; Mmm, well, not so much. 

The incredible scene was discovered by fearless snake-catching duo, Norman and Sally Hill and posted to their Facebook page.

It might have taken three hours, but eventually the brown snake finished his meal and was then removed from the house.

Usually brown snakes eat frogs, birds, rats and mice but according to the Australian Museum, the species is known to be cannibalistic in captivity and can prey on snakes of a similar size.

Which just goes to show that in deadly Australia, even some of the biggest predators can sometimes become the prey.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Snake eats snake,snake eats snake alive,brown snake eats carpet python,brown snake,brown snake eats python,snakes eating animals</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3250181</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 03:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>15</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B9B/83B/B9B83B79E029458284EE6A26A869DF5A_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/09/3250181/3250181_104C63598CD64122B13CDB6101E58E60_170109_3250181_Snake_eats_snake_alive__Deadly_brown_snake_eats__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man speared through head: spearfishing accident goes horribly wrong, impales man&#x2019;s face</title>
      <description>THE BAHAMAS &#x2014; Alarming photographs are circulating on social media of a man reportedly speared through the head while on a diving excursion off the coast of the Bahamas.

Not much is known about this incident just yet, not even the man&#x2019;s name. Photos of the man in hospital, both before and after the spear-removal surgery, are inciting a collective gasp among users online. Though most would call this an unlucky situation, doctors would probably say he&#x2019;s the luckiest man alive. Had the spear pierced his head just a few millimeters higher, it would&#x2019;ve likely proved fatal.

Instead, his surgery appears to have gone well, based off a post-surgery photo of the man offering a smile and gesturing with the peace sign.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Spearfishing,spearfishing accident,spear through head,man impaled,man speared,fisherman speared,spear though face,graphic highway accident,impaled in butt,construction fail,bullfighter impaled,man imppaled on lamppost,bullhorn,shenzhen,chinese driver impaled,mineworker impaled,child impaled,biker impaled on fence,kappa alpha,natalie eaton,discovery TV</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3250090</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 02:11:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/19A/55C/19A55C9FC454490F8D27D28724076E2D_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/09/3250090/3250090_39BCD06FB72D4B58A11F31F1BFBCD543_170109_3250090_Man_speared_through_head__spearfishing_accident__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree man disease: Bangladesh man receives 16 surgeries to restore hands to normal</title>
      <description>DHAKA, BANGLADESH &#x2014; It may have taken a year and an insane number of surgeries, but this Bangladeshi man couldn&#x2019;t be happier to finally have his hands and feet back.

CNN reports that Abul Bajander suffers from epidermodysplasia verruciformis, a rare disease that began causing lesions to appear on his skin at age 10. The lesions worsened over time, eventually encompassing both his hands and making it difficult for him to make a living as a rickshaw driver.

Bark-like growths had also started sprouting from his hands and feet, making it impossible to do anything except scratch his neck.

The 27-year-old has been dubbed &#x201C;Tree Man&#x201D; by international media, and is one of only four people in the world to ever be diagnosed with the disease.

Doctors in Dhaka offered to treat him free of charge, and moved him and his family to the hospital last February to begin the first of many groundbreaking surgeries.

Sixteen operations later, doctors have removed eleven pounds of growth and restored tree man&#x2019;s hands.

He&#x2019;ll still need a few more surgeries for beautification, but he now can at least eat, write, and hold his 3-year-old daughter on his own.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Bangladesh tree man,tree man of bangladesh,tree man,tree man disease,strange condition,rare disease,medical breakthrough,skin disease,skin condition,bangladesh</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3251156</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 07:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>29</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/85F/03F/85F03FB85C474937AA12A5B9658FCBBC_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/10/3251156/3251156_63F3193BF2684AD39304332375123EFC_170110_3251156_Tree_man_disease__Bangladesh_man_receives_16_sur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fat-shaming video: Kansas pastor films obese woman in wheelchair towed by pickup truck</title>
      <description>KANSAS CITY, MISSOURI &#x2014; A Kansas City pastor felt the wrath of social media after posting a video of an obese woman in a wheelchair being towed by a pickup truck to Facebook.

The video was shared more than 11,000 times over the weekend, but Pastor Lamond Rushing felt the heat after many failed to see the funny side.

The whole saga began on Saturday when disabled woman Becky Kittrell&#x2019;s power wheelchair ran out of battery on the freezing cold streets of Kansas City, Fox 4 reported.

Luckily for Becky, a Good Samaritan in a pickup truck stopped and offered to tow her home.

That&#x2019;s where Pastor Rushing comes in. The flabbergasted man of God thought he was seeing a miracle and began filming on his cellphone.

Becky doesn&#x2019;t have Facebook but found out she was a viral sensation when her son saw the video and told her.

Becky said that instead of filming her, the pastor could have asked if she needed any help.

Temperatures dropped as low as 7 degrees Fahrenheit in Kansas City that day and Becky just needed to find some shelter from the cold. After all, wouldn&#x2019;t offering to help have been the Christian thing to do?

Pastor Rushing said he never intended to hurt Becky&#x2019;s feelings. The preacherman said he&#x2019;d just never seen anything like it before.

However, after reading some ungodly comments about Becky online, the pastor said he understood why people were so upset with him. He apologized for filming the video and later removed it from Facebook.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,fat people,funny fat people,fat shaming video,fat woman towed by pickup truck,obese woman,kansas city</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3250953</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 03:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/99D/F21/99DF21E4FEB746A6ADA6193DE6DD6853_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/10/3250953/3250953_F1BC4210FD0A4249B2CC8318617F14D9_170110_3250953_Fat_shaming_video__Kansas_pastor_films_obese_wom_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-11 axe attack: security camera shows Sydney woman go medieval on two people</title>
      <description>SYDNEY &#x2014; Police have arrested a woman after a vicious attack on two customers inside a 7-Eleven with an axe.

On January 7, Evie Amati, 24, strolled into the convenience store, carrying an axe, as well as a knife in her back pocket. Meanwhile at the register, customer Sharon Hacker, 43,  was pulling money from her purse, with customer Ben Rimmer, 32, waiting behind her in line with a meat pie. 

When Amati walked over to Rimmer with the axe in hand, he reportedly thought she was kidding around. Seconds later when he turned away, Amati started swinging. After laying Rimmer out, blood gushing everywhere, Amati turned her attention to Sharon Hacker, and clubbed her in the back of the head with the axe. Her victims on the ground, Amati then casually walked out of the store. It wasn&#x2019;t long before police caught up to her. 

Luckily, both customers survived the attack, though Ben Rimmer&#x2019;s face had been opened up. A witness present said his blood was all over the store of the floor. He remains in hospital with serious head injuries. Sharon Hacker suffered a fractured skull, but she claims her thick dreadlocks may have prevented further injury. 

Evie Amati has been charged with wounding a person with intent to cause grievous bodily harm.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,7 11,7-eleven,axe attack,benjamin rimmer,evie amati,sharon hacker,surveillance camera,surveillance video,shotgun,convenience store,twerking,gas station</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3250948</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 03:18:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/833/4BA/8334BA58E28B40FCA057FD048741C9AD_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/10/3250948/3250948_C7612A062D5C4FF782C2FE461D92BACA_170110_3250948_7_11_axe_attack__security_camera_shows_Sydney_wo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salt and Ice challenge: Severe burns teach UK schoolboy valuable lesson</title>
      <description>SWANSEA, UNITED KINGDOM &#x2014; A high school student in Wales took part in the internet craze known as the &#x201C;salt and ice challenge,&#x201D;  and a photograph of his damaged hand is making the rounds on social media.

The salt and ice challenge involves placing salt somewhere on the body, and then using an ice cube to press down on the area for as long as possible. Doing this creates a burning sensation in the area, as the salt and the ice combined become significantly colder than the ice on its own, at -18&#xB0;F (-28&#xB0;C). 

Once the participant finally gives up, initially they may feel an immediate numbing sensation in the affected area, meaning they&#x2019;ve likely experienced nerve damage resulting from second- or third-degree burns, similar to frostbite. 

The teen&#x2019;s mother published the photograph of the skin burn to warn other parents of the dangers of this salt and ice challenge.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Salt and ice challenge,internet craze,cupping therapy,rotting flesh,nose job,squid cartilage,andressa urach,thigh enlargement,skin cancer,nose falls off,self-inflicted injuries,gruesome injuries</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3250807</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 01:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DEF/251/DEF25179BF8346268A7DA1A7C4178E02_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/10/3250807/3250807_2BFE05608F4B4EE491EB7402E57F15EC_170110_3250807_Salt_and_Ice_challenge__Severe_burns_teach_UK_sc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seagull poop has antibiotic-resistant E. coli, infections caused by human pollution</title>
      <description>KENAI PENINSULA, ALASKA &#x2014; A team of scientists studying seagull feces at landfills in Anchorage have found a strain of E. coli bacteria that has proven to be resistant to antibiotics.

In a study published in the journal Infection Ecology and Epidemiology last November, at researchers the U.S. Geological Survey explain in detail how the resilient strain of E. coli bacteria has strengthened to the point where human-developed medicines have no answer for it. 

When antibiotics are ingested, they pass through our bodies and get flushed down the toilet, into the sewage system. However, water treatment plants aren&#x2019;t designed to treat antibiotic residues, allowing them to make their way into the environment. Bacteria in the environment then meet the antibiotic residues, and over time, they become resistant to them. Animals who hang out in places of high-human activity, like seagulls, then contract the E. coli.

The researchers aren&#x2019;t sure the E. coli found in the seagull fecal matter can be transmitted to humans, but they are certain that humans are the cause of these infections in the birds. In the United States, the CDC reports 2 million illnesses and 23,000 deaths are caused each year by drug-resistant bacteria.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Seagulls pooping,bird Poop,antibacteria resistance,e. Coli,e coli,germs,diarrhea,alaska e. Coli,Escherichia coli,bird disease,super strains,bacterial resistance to antibiotics,human pollution</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3250739</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>26</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D15/911/D159116BCC964845A0A9630E8366E0F4_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/10/3250739/3250739_8A74617BEF3C402B825BE07D96EE6E44_170110_3250739_Seagull_poop_has_antibiotic_resistant_E__coli__i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oral pleasure tour: Actress Paola Saulino embarks on tour to thank referendum voters</title>
      <description>ROME &#x2014; Paola Saulino, who promised to tour Italy providing oral pleasure to people who voted no in her country&#x2019;s recent referendum, has just completed the first stop of her tour.

The twenty-seven-year-old Saulino, who is now based in Los Angeles, dreamed up the stunt to encourage her countrymen to reject Italy&#x2019;s constitutional referendum.

Before announcing her tour dates in December, Saulino made the promise to perform &#x201C;pompa&#x201D;, or felatio, on those who would do their part for the country on November 23. 

The tour will take place in Rome, Florence, Bologna, Verona, Milan, Turin, Naples, Bari, Lecce and Palermo. That&#x2019;s a lot to get your mouth around.

Over on Saulino&#x2019;s Instagram page, some users slammed the the thing as a crass publicity stunt. Others have asked for evidence she&#x2019;s honoured her promise. Still, one man defended the actress and claims the men who took part were asked to sign non-disclosure agreements. 

Saulino recently announced dates for her second tour on her Instagram. Starting from February to early March, she will be in Foggia, Campobasso, Latina, Positano, Catanzaro, Salerno, Cagliari, Bodduso, Cannigione, Perfugas, Catania, and Bomarzo.  

Do you live in any of those cities? Register now or be filled with regret!</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Paola Saulino,the pompa tour,Italy&#x2019;s constitutional referendum,italian referendum,Matteo Renzi</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3250667</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 22:01:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/15E/575/15E57517E3AF42C2BDDEF19A3AE9FCAB_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/10/3250667/3250667_E8CD95C0EB8A492DAC5CDB575FAC31B1_170110_3250667_Oral_pleasure_tour__Actress_Paola_Saulino_embark_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Russia dossier: Ex-spy claims Trump has been cultivated by Russians, likes showers</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; U.S. intelligence agencies briefed Donald Trump about allegations that the Russian government is in possession of compromising information about the president-elect. 

A two-page summary of a 35-page dossier was presented to Trump and President Obama last week in meetings with the CIA, FBI, National Security Agency and director of national intelligence, CNN reported. 

The dossier from a former British spy claims Russia has been cultivating Donald Trump for the past five years.
 
It claims Russia asked Trump for intel on oligarchs living in America. They also wanted Trump to play down Russia&#x2019;s invasion of the Ukraine, which Trump can do once he becomes president next week.

In exchange, they would help Trump defeat Hillary Clinton via Wikileaks.

Russian intelligence also promised not to use the &#x2018;kompromat&#x2019; they compiled on Trump. The dossier said Trump wanted prostitutes to defile a Ritz Carlton hotel room because the Obamas had once stayed there.

To his credit, Trump didn&#x2019;t take Russia up on the business opportunities offered him. He only seemed interested in the sex parties.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Donald Trump,Donald Trump Russia connection,Donald Trump Russia dossier,Donald Trump Russian blackmail,Donald Trump showers,Trump lawyer Michael Cohen,Trump Carter Page,Trump Paul Manafort,Trump Putin</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3251997</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 07:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>89</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1E8/F25/1E8F25E2B5B24CBBA2105A6A715BA9C4_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/11/3251997/3251997_13502B1896D64E70822DDA56E19E6D98_170111_3251997_Trump_Russia_dossier__Ex_spy_claims_Trump_has_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidnapped Uber driver streams bomb-carrying passenger&#x2019;s bizarre Miami bank robbery</title>
      <description>MIAMI &#x2014; You&#x2019;d think the bizarre string of events that unfolded in Miami on Tuesday was from a movie, but nope, it&#x2019;s all real.

The drama began when a bomb-carrying man in a suit, later identified as 35-year-old Enrique Antonio Gamez, took his Uber driver hostage, reports the Miami Herald. 

The driver, known on Facebook as Mikebilly So-Focused, livestreamed his kidnapper as the latter was robbing the Navy Federal Credit Union. In the video, Gamez can be seen calmly approaching a bank attendant, likely threatening her with the explosive device. The bank attendant goes up to a teller and soon hands the robber a pink envelope full of cash. Gamez tries to get the attendant to come with him as a hostage, assuring her he plans to surrender before then going on a rant about Russian hacking and World War III.

Two more live streams are taken in the car, with the man continuing his long-winded rant against the government. The driver tries to get him to show the bomb, but the suspect instead flashes his loot.

The pair eventually end up at Ocean Drive in Miami Beach, where the robber makes like Robin Hood and starts giving the cash to random passers-by.

True to his word, Gamez then calls the cops, who eventually arrive and take both him and his Uber driver into custody.

Sections of Ocean Drive had to be closed off, and a bomb squad called in to secure the premises. Gamez is now with the feds and facing charges, but the Uber the driver was eventually let go, according to NBC Miami.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Miami bank robbery,kidnapped uber driver,uber driver hostage,uber passenger with bomb,uber passenger robbing bank,uber driver live stream,enrique gamez,robin hood</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3251861</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 04:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D31/336/D313367E43AD4783B213475864CABBD7_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/11/3251861/3251861_D1A8A299271C43E08EEF47E72657E917_170111_3251861_Kidnapped_Uber_driver_streams_bomb_carrying_pass_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attempted robbery fail: Gun store owner fights back, kills robber in self defense</title>
      <description>MABLETON, GEORGIA &#x2014; An armed robber was shot dead and his accomplice is on the run after a failed hold-up at a gun store in Georgia.

Security camera footage of the fatal Dec. 26 incident was released this week.

It shows gun store owner Jimmy Groover, 64, moving faster than green grass through a goose to defend his property and his life.

Two unidentified armed men burst into the store in broad daylight, pointed their pistols, and threatened to kill the owner and his assistant if they didn&#x2019;t get down on the floor, NBC affiliate WXIA reported.

But they didn&#x2019;t count on old Jimmy Groover being armed and ready.

In the blink of an eye, the gun store owner fired at the first robber, shooting him dead. The other suspect skedaddled and he&#x2019;s now wanted by the police.

Groover said he felt bad about killing the guy but knew he had little choice after the robbers made threats to kill.

Groover&#x2019;s store has been robbed around 20 times over the years but this is the first time he&#x2019;s ever shot one of the bandits.

Detectives said it was unlikely the grandfather would be charged with any crime because he acted in self-defense.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Armed robbery fail,self defense,store owner fights back,armed robbery gone wrong,armed robbery gone bad,second amendment,gun store robbery,robber gets what he deserves,robber gets owned</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3251859</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 04:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>19</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/273/683/273683012F2A41B2BCBECBFA0855E094_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/11/3251859/3251859_81AD63A41748432EAF79703E29CC9CAF_170111_3251859_Attempted_robbery_fail__Gun_store_owner_fights_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biodegradable bullets: seeds inside ammunition grow into plants after bullets fired - TomoNews</title>
      <description>ARLINGTON COUNTY, VIRGINIA &#x2014; The United States Department of Defense is issuing a call to contractors to develop biodegradable bullets for military training exercises. 

The U.S. Army runs through thousands upon thousands of ammunition rounds every year. The bullets currently being used take hundreds of years to break down, while also corroding and polluting the planet&#x2019;s soil and water sources. 

The DoD&#x2019;s new proposal would see specialized seeds encased in the bullets, designed to grow plants that eliminate ammunition debris and contaminants. The seeds would begin to sprout long after landing in the ground, and would eventually become a source of food for animals, too. 

Through the Small Business Innovation Research agency, the Department of Defense is accepting applications until February 8. They are looking for ammunition designs for 40 to 120 mm training rounds that perform on the same level as bullets being used today. Applications will also need to include potential ways the technology provides benefits, in addition to defensive capabilities.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,DoD,department of defense,biodegradable bullets,eco-friendly bullets,seed-planting bullets,green tech,solar panels,ocean swell energy,wind turbines,solar roads</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3251699</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 02:07:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/199/4FC/1994FC13252E4E3DB459D8C772F2A370_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/11/3251699/3251699_A76945D916DB4E4B9F22CF6D79D6FAD8_170111_3251699_Biodegradable_bullets__seeds_inside_ammunition_g_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man saves woman from burning car: Texas senior, 85, rescues two women from car wreck</title>
      <description>BURLESON, TEXAS &#x2014; An elderly man from Texas is being hailed a hero after he rescued two women from the wreckage of a burning vehicle.

Lindell Marbut, 85, was minding his own business at home on Sunday, when a speeding car crashed into his driveway and burst into flames, Fox 4 reported.

When Lindell&#x2019;s caretaker Sondra Young ran next door to call 911, the senior citizen searched for the hero inside himself, then went into full-on Superman mode.

Lindell usually relies on a cane to get around, but that didn&#x2019;t stop him from single-handedly pulling the 22-year-old driver out of the car. The valiant senior then dragged a female passenger from the fiery deathtrap with Young&#x2019;s help and got her safely out of harm&#x2019;s way.

Responding firefighters said things could have turned out a whole lot toastier for the two women if it wasn&#x2019;t for Lindell&#x2019;s heroic actions.

Speed was a factor in the crash, according to the authorities. Both women sustained internal injuries but are expected to survive.

Lindell played down his courageous good deed, and said he&#x2019;d do it all again if he had to.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Man saves women from burning car,man rescues women from burning car,everyday heroes,saved from burning car,car crash</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3251502</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 22:28:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0F7/C07/0F7C07FD79EC469FA19089867A7366A5_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/11/3251502/3251502_C19DA165147E4C80ADDBF25040CD5F12_170111_3251502_Man_saves_woman_from_burning_car__Texas_senior___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prostitution: German politician proposes government handouts to pay for prostitutes</title>
      <description>BERLIN, GERMANY &#x2014; A German politician wants the government to pay for the needy to have sex with prostitutes.

The patient would need a doctor to approve the treatment and would claim the &#x201C;sex prescription&#x201D; as a medical expense to be reimburse by the local government, according to a proposal by Elisabeth Scharfenberg, care spokeswoman for the German Green Party.

Scharfenberg told Germany&#x2019;s Welt am Sonntag newspaper that a similar policy is already in place in the Netherlands. The policy allows those with severe health issues to claim sex with prostitutes as a medical expense, Deutsche Welle reported. 

Scharfenberg said patients would need a medical certificate showing they can&#x2019;t achieve sexual satisfaction in other ways. They would also have to prove they can&#x2019;t afford to pay for sex.

But some members of the Green Party worry that niche policy proposals like this one contribute to the perception that the party is not serious. 

Green parliamentarian and T&#xFC;bingen mayor Boris Palmer attacked the proposal, saying &#x201C;well intentioned&#x201D; ideas like these cause the public to dismiss the Greens as &#x201C;unworldly oddballs.&#x201D;

Prostitution is legal in Germany, where it does not carry the same stigma as in many other Western countries. Prostitutes in Germany can even visit nursing homes to service elderly residents.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,German Green Party,Alliance '90/The Greens,Elisabeth Scharfenberg,German prostitution,prostitution in Germany,B&#xFC;ndnis 90/Die Gr&#xFC;nen,german politics,german politicians</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3251483</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 21:36:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F34/512/F34512BA8B094EF3994E2BECC6528BDE_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/11/3251483/3251483_07341ACE1CF14E50BE9409FB0E2051B1_170111_3251483_Prostitution__German_politician_proposes_governm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar bears in danger: Global warming will wipe one third of polar bears out by 2050</title>
      <description>GLAND, SWITZERLAND &#x2014; Polar bear numbers could drop by a third over the next 35 years because of global warming.

The warning comes in a study by the International Union for the Conservation of Nature (IUCN), phys.org reported.

The global polar bear population is estimated to stand at 26,000. The study suggests there is a 70 percent chance that figure will drop 30 percent by 2050.

Melting sea ice caused by global warming is the main threat to the survival of polar bears. Polar bears depend on sea ice as a floating platform to hunt seals, which can outswim them in the water.

The presence of manmade chemicals in the food chain is another major threat to polar bear numbers.

The IUCN monitors endangered species on its Red List. The organisation classifies polar bears as &#x201C;vulnerable,&#x201D; meaning the species faces a high risk of extinction in the wild.</description>
      <tags>video,Polar bears,polar bears in danger,red watch list,global warming,melting ice caps,conservation,bear,polar bear</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230603</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 07:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>40</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8D0/AF1/8D0AF1E5C47944AE8695DCAF673ECB97_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230603/3230603_0C239363D5754830BC8C9274C86D8166_161213_3230603_Polar_bears_in_danger__Global_warming_will_wipe__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chemotherapy hair loss solution: scalp cooling cap may reduce hair loss from chemo</title>
      <description>HOUSTON &#x2014; Cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy may not have to suffer hair loss anymore, thanks to a &#x2018;cooling cap&#x2019; technology.

Chemotherapy drugs are designed to attack rapidly dividing cells, and as both cancer cells and hair cells divide rapidly, chemotherapy can cause damage to hair cells, which leads to hair loss.

A cooling cap system was developed by scientists at Baylor College of Medicine. The system can lower the scalp temperature to about 66 degrees Fahrenheit. The low temperature constricts the blood vessels and reduces blood flow to the area by up to 40 percent. Less blood flow to the scalp means fewer chemotherapy drugs can attack the hair cells.

&#x201C;Hair loss takes a tremendous toll on the patient&#x2019;s body image, and they no longer have the anonymity of hiding the disease; everyone can see that they&#x2019;re sick,&#x201D; Julie Nangia, assistant professor in the Lester and Sue Smith Breast Center at Baylor College of Medicine said in a press release. 

Researchers say the cooling caps should work on patients with solid tumors, but will not work for patients with leukemia or blood cancers.</description>
      <tags>video,Scalp cooling cap,hair loss,alopecia,chemotherapy,cancer,Baylor College of Medicine,cancer side effects,cancer symptoms,chemotherapy side effects,chemo side effects</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230557</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 06:28:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/959/BC0/959BC0A5E80B4FA68E6FAAD217C0434A_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230557/3230557_6EE1489411894528B54BC56439DF56EA_161213_3230557_Chemotherapy_hair_loss_solution__scalp_cooling_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South China Sea dispute: Vietnam begins dredging on Ladd Reef in disputed waters</title>
      <description>LADD REEF, SOUTH CHINA SEA &#x2014; Satellite images taken by a U.S. based firm revealed suspected dredging work on Ladd Reef, a coral reef controlled by Vietnam in the South China Sea.

Ladd Reef is about 450 km from Vietnam&#x2019;s southeastern coast and is completely submerged at high tide. It has a 42-meter-tall lighthouse, which is operated by a small number of Vietnam soldiers and worker.

Analysts told Reuters that such dredging work could be the precursor to more extensive construction on other reefs, and Ladd Reef might be used to boost access for supply ships and fishing boats. It could also help defend the nearby Spratly Islands, where Vietnam has expanded its airstrip.

Vietnam is one of the many nations that claims the South China Sea as part of its territory. China, the Philippines, Malaysia, Brunei and Taiwan have also made claims in the region. Vietnam has become China&#x2019;s main rival in the disputed South China Sea. According to Reuters, the mobile rocket launchers installed on several islands controlled by Vietnam are capable of striking China&#x2019;s runway and military installations.</description>
      <tags>video,Ladd reef,vietnam,south china sea claims,south china sea dispute,spratly islands dispute vietnam south china sea dredging</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230423</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 03:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D49/06A/D4906AC46C9C4FB4A3457C60113785DE_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230423/3230423_3EB5B8053E2E4D28BB1DB68AC709CBAF_161213_3230423_South_China_Sea_dispute__Vietnam_begins_dredging_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border patrol: 150 extra agents deployed in South Texas after illegal immigration surge</title>
      <description>EDINBURG, TEXAS &#x2014; Migrants trying to get into the U.S. are doing so in droves recently. One border patrol veteran said it&#x2019;s because immigrants are worried Trump will start building his wall once he is sworn into office in January.


CNN reports that recent months have seen an increase in the number of people caught illegally crossing into Texas from Mexico, from 37,048 in August, and 39,501 in September, to 46,195 in October.


Detention facilities that used to see 31 to 34,000 individuals on average are now holding 41,000, most of them families and unaccompanied children.


As a result, the U.S. Customs and Border Patrol has announced in a press release that it plans to send an extra 150 agents from Tucson, Arizona, and San Diego and Del Rio, Texas to processing centers near the border. They will be stationed there temporarily, for around two months.


These agents will be screening and classifying the undocumented migrants in the McAllen and Weslaco centers, in effect freeing up local agents to focus on border security.


A similar surge occurred in the South Texas border in 2014, after hundreds of thousands of migrants escaped Guatemala, Honduras, and El Salvador to seek refuge in the US, reports Reuters.</description>
      <tags>video,Border patrol,illegal immigration,illegal entry,us mexico border,migrants,refugees,donald trump wall,immigration,south texas border,border security</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3230192</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 00:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>39</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/431/7AC/4317ACF5E3604A6EA9C95F2F7081737F_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/13/3230192/3230192_8E8D29F988EA4DBD9D830736303740D6_161213_3230192_Border_patrol__150_extra_agents_deployed_in_Sout_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python vs Alligator: video shows massive snake suffocate and drown gator in Florida</title>
      <description>BIG CYPRESS, FLORIDA &#x2014; A journalist riding his bike near near the everglades witnessed an unnatural sight that has been becoming increasingly more common &#x2014; a Burmese python drowning an alligator.

On the morning of Dec. 21, while cycling, journalist Joe Capozzi heard some commotion coming from a swamp up ahead. He hopped off his bike to investigate and spotted a 6-foot alligator, belly up and fighting for its life, as a 15-foot python coiled itself around the gator&#x2019;s body.

Capozzi wasted no time, grabbing his smartphone to record the intense encounter. He recalls that while the gator would pop up from the water every few minutes, the snake had total control over it, tightening its grip and robbing it of air, until it finally stopped moving. Capozzi says the scene looked like an alligator trapped in a stack of tires underwater. After watching for roughly 10 minutes, a clear winner having emerged, Capozzi continued on his bike ride, and wrote about what he saw two weeks later in a piece for The Palm Beach Post. 

Burmese pythons have invaded Florida&#x2019;s ecosystem over the past decade, a result of irresponsible exotic pet owners and the destruction of a python breeding facility in 1992 caused by Hurricane Andrew. More than 2,000 snakes have been removed from the area, but the snakes continue to breed at a rapid pace.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Burmese python,alligator python fight,snake alligator fight,everglades,big cypress national preserve,palm beach post,joe capozzi,pythons florida,animal fights,python attack,python kills,caught on camera,caught on film,eagle canada goose,python dog,alligator shark,bull shark alligator,gator attack</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3252747</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 04:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A36/9C0/A369C09C5E74453DB3221E9C2A5B835E_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/12/3252747/3252747_DCD34A5E1BA046B59703C6DBA6B8637F_170112_3252747_Python_vs_Alligator__video_shows_massive_snake_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road rage USA: Crazed white lady hounds and abuses Mexican family on Facebook Live</title>
      <description>SEATTLE &#x2014; A crazed white woman, aged 48, has been charged with a hate crime after following and abusing a Mexican family on Facebook Live.

In November Seattle resident Sandra Jametski filmed herself ranting for 10 minutes while stalking the immigrant family as they were taking their kids toschool. 

She road rages about the un-American driving, how she&#x2019;s surrounded by foreigners and calls out the family for what she dubs their &#x201C;Spanish privilege.&#x201D;

At the most heated point in the exchange, she threatens to ram the family&#x2019;s car off the road and get them deported, reported the Seattle Times. 

The worst part is she also ranted at them in front of the son&#x2019;s school, all for the world to see.
 
She claims one of their kids caused a car accident last year. According to the cops, that crash was Jametski&#x2019;s fault.

Seattle police charged Jametski with a hate crime and threw her in jail. Her bail was set at $500,000 dollars. If found guilty, Jametski could be looking at a prison sentence of up to five years, a $10,000 fine or both.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,racism in america,white woman rants against hispanics,hate crime,facebook live rant,road rage on tape,crazy white lady yelling,sandra jametski,seattle</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3252628</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 02:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>26</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/23B/D7C/23BD7C2B93164521A7CF09A8A28AEAA7_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/12/3252628/3252628_B7F101836EA54A0BAE7E0358FCEEEE0B_170112_3252628_Road_rage_USA__Crazed_white_lady_hounds_and_abus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero golden retriever: Injured owner saved from freezing to death on NYE by loyal dog - TomoNews</title>
      <description>HARBOR SPRINGS, MICHIGAN &#x2014; The year 2017 started out horribly for one Michigan man, who spent New Year&#x2019;s Day injured and helpless in the snow. Luckily, it was man&#x2019;s best friend to the rescue.

The Petoskey News Review reports that around 10:30 p.m. on Dec. 31, Bob (the newspaper did not publish his name citing &#x201C;privacy reasons&#x201D;) ran out in his slippers and pajamas to get another log for his fire. Halfway there, he slipped and fell on the ice, breaking his neck, which rendered him paralyzed.

Unable to move, he screamed for help. But with the nearest neighbor a quarter mile away, it was his 5-year-old golden retriever Kelsey that ran to his side.

The temperature dipped to freezing, but Kelsey stayed by Bob, barking for help and licking his face and hands to keep him warm.

The 64-year-old lost consciousness, but Kelsey&#x2019;s howling eventually got the attention of a neighbor, who finally discovered Bob 20 hours later.

He was rushed to the hospital, where a doctor performed emergency surgery to save him. Miraculously, he didn&#x2019;t have frostbite, and is recovering nicely &#x2014; a feat he claims he owes to two heroes: his dog, and his doctor.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Golden retriever,hero golden retriever,dog saves owner,hero dogs,hero pets,golden retriever dog,animal heroes,dog heroes,pet heroes</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3252610</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 02:48:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/124/A99/124A99BF9C8E47089E534857EE17D87A_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/12/3252610/3252610_EB7E8F9F8781491BB3641548ED4557A0_170112_3252610_Hero_golden_retriever__Injured_owner_saved_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child found dead: couple who reported daughter missing hid body in family restaurant</title>
      <description>NORTH CANTON, OHIO &#x2014; A couple of thought-to-be concerned parents in North Canton, Ohio, who reported their 5-year-old daughter missing have turned out to be more concerned with saving their own hides, after police found Ashley Zhao&#x2019;s body hidden in the family&#x2019;s Chinese restaurant a day later. 

The mother, MingMing Chen, 29, has admitted to police that on the morning of Jan. 9, she beat the girl with her fist, repeatedly. The child&#x2019;s father, Liang Zhao, 34, then came over to tend to Ashley, and noticed a green fluid dripping out of her mouth. He also noticed she&#x2019;d stopped breathing. He attempted to revive her by performing CPR, but was unsuccessful. 

That evening, the couple reported Ashley missing, saying she&#x2019;d gone to the back of the restaurant for a nap, but somehow vanished. When investigators searched for her in the area, it didn&#x2019;t take long for them to find her body &#x201C;concealed&#x201D; in the restaurant, near the freezer.

The mother has been charged with murder and felonious assault, and the father with complicity to commit felonious assault and complicity to commit murder. The restaurant, Ang&#x2019;s Asian Cuisine, is now permanently closed, and has become a makeshift memorial for little Ashley Zhao. Regular customers say she was a very sweet and social child.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Ashley zhao,missing children,amber alert,ang&#x2019;s,mingming chen,Liang Zhao,sabrina allen,julian hernandez,missing girl,child abusing</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3252583</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 02:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>26</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B0F/97E/B0F97E3D154240C3A42688101EE081FA_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/12/3252583/3252583_791089A1F80345EDB17E4A5BC492EFBE_170112_3252583_Child_found_dead__couple_who_reported_daughter_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attempted kidnapping caught on tape: Security images show man trying to abduct child</title>
      <description>OKLAHOMA CITY &#x2014;  Police are looking for a man who last Friday tried to pick up an 8-year-old boy and walk away with him. 

The incident took place during a wrestling event at Oklahoma City State Fairgrounds.

The man is pictured grabbing the boy from behind and then trying to walk away with him. According to a post by the Oklahoma City Police on their Facebook page, the child kicked and screamed until the stranger put him down. The man then fled the scene.

Police and the boy&#x2019;s father are calling the incident an attempted child abduction. 

Security was reportedly tight at the fairgrounds, where some 2,000 people were in attendance, but no guards saw the incident unfold, reported local news outlet KFOR-TV.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,child kidnapping caught on camera,child kidnapping caught on tape,child abduction caught on tape,child abduction caught on camera,child abduction stories,man kidnaps child in public,oklahoma city state fairground,oklahoma,child kidnapping,child abduction</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3252463</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5EF/F31/5EFF318656B34D53B20F1AB4A5F4ABE3_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/12/3252463/3252463_9BE0414AFD114E09816F61A70D8AF8A8_170112_3252463_Attempted_kidnapping_caught_on_tape__Security_im_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese macaque monkey caught on camera having sex with deer</title>
      <description>YAKUSHIMA, JAPAN &#x2014; A monkey was caught on camera humping a deer in the woods of Yakushima Island in southwestern Japan. What&#x2019;s more, it seems like the action was consensual. 

Japanese macaques are known to hitch rides on deer in the wild, but this was a different kind of ride. The video, recorded in November of 2015 by scientist Alexandre Bonnefoy, shows a macaque doinking a Sika deer, humping it 15 times in 10 seconds. Afterwards the deer was seen licking its butt.

The monkey then went at it with a second deer, chasing away two bystanders so they could have some alone time together. Another monkey tried to get in on the action, but he was thrown from a deer&#x2019;s back.

According to a study by Bonnefoy and his colleagues, the strange behavior may be the result of &#x201C;mate deprivation,&#x201D; when monkeys who lack access to females of their own species are more likely to look for love elsewhere in the animal kingdom.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Monkey sex,monkey humps deer,Japanese macaque humps deer,animal mating,animal breeding</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3252333</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 22:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A38/2CA/A382CAE63B424419A5600DDCC41EF1C6_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/12/3252333/3252333_8C907C3A85E4428FA9639FF61558F5E7_170112_3252333_Japanese_macaque_monkey_caught_on_camera_having__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Harvey Asian men: Daytime talk show Mr. Potato Head thinks Asian men are undateable</title>
      <description>CHICAGO &#x2014; When Steve Harvey isn&#x2019;t learning how to read, he apparently hosts a daytime talk show called the Steve Harvey Show. 

Last week, Harvey started his show by making fun of some self-help books. One of them was sadly called How to Date a White Woman: A Practical Guide for Asian Men. 

Just reading the title caused Harvey to break down in laughter. 

Harvey then asks his audience, &#x201C;Excuse me, do you like Asian men?&#x201D; He answers for them, &#x201C;No. Thank You.&#x201D;

Then he launched into this bit, &#x201C;How to Date a Black Woman: A Practical Guide to Asian Men. Same thing. &#x2018;You like Asian men?&#x2019; I don&#x2019;t even like Chinese food. It don&#x2019;t stay with you no time &#x2026; I don&#x2019;t eat what I can&#x2019;t pronounce.&#x201D;

Interesting that Harvey is joking about pronunciation, considering his moronic Miss Universe debacle last year. In his defense, the words &#x2018;Colombia&#x2019; and &#x2018;Philippines&#x2019; look practically identical.    
 
Hopefully Harvey will get a nice warm welcome when he heads comes to Asia in two 
weeks to host the Miss Universe pageant in the Philippines. Maybe he should try out his Asian men jokes again.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Steve Harvey,Steve Harvey Show,Steve Harvey Asian men,Steve Harvey Asian man,Steve Harvey Asian men joke,Steve Harvey Miss Universe mishap,Steve Harvey Miss Universe</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3253845</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 07:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>143</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CE3/CAD/CE3CADE454CE46348C104BE11FE38721_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/13/3253845/3253845_55973ABCA08945EE8ECFAAC6DEE6090D_170113_3253845_Steve_Harvey_Asian_men__Daytime_talk_show_Mr__Po_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale slaughter: Dead 8-ton whale butchered outside office building in Jiangxi, China</title>
      <description>XINYU, CHINA &#x2014; A huge whale was butchered right outside an office building in China for God knows what reason, and now the stomach-churning video is making rounds on Chinese social media.

The Global Times reports that the giant animal was a gift to the director of Risun Solar Energy Technology Corporation in Xinyu, Jiangxi province. It had to be hauled from the coast of Zhejiang to Jiangxi province for nearly $600.

It was offloaded right beside the office canteen and prepped for slaughter by workers. In the video, a chef is seen standing in front of the enormous whale while sharpening his knives. Two workers were also captured using a saw to cut the mammal&#x2019;s tail part.

The foul stench attracted the attention of locals, who quickly began filming the 8-ton carcass being horrifically cut up.

Authorities claim the meat was going to be used to feed dogs, but earlier reports and conversation in the video indicate that it was going to be given out to employees as a year-end bonus.  

The Jiangxi Bureau of Fishery Administration started looking into the incident after the video was posted online on Friday. Apart from two particular species, it&#x2019;s technically not illegal to transport and use whales, which are second-class nationally protected animals in China. What&#x2019;s unclear though, is whether the company had the required permits and licenses to do so.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Whale slaughter,save the whales,bryde&#x2019;s whale,brydes whale,dead whales,whale cut open,whale cut up,china whale cut,giant whale china,jiangxi whale</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3253847</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 07:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>30</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/75C/034/75C0347E4E0C476EB1EE37B81B951DAC_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/13/3253847/3253847_1DAB94748E9A4F8ABF7527560178F2D1_170113_3253847_Whale_slaughter__Dead_8_ton_whale_butchered_outs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider vs snake: huge tarantula photographed eating snake for first time in wild</title>
      <description>SERRA DO CAVER&#xC1;, BRAZIL &#x2014; In October of 2015, a group of researchers conducting work on tarantula diversity stumbled upon a Grammostola quirogai tarantula, feasting on the body of an Almaden ground snake. The team photographed the spine-tingling spectacle and published a report of their findings in the December issue of the journal Herpetology Notes. 

What happened leading up to the meal is unknown, but the researchers suspect the snake may have slithered past the arachnid&#x2019;s cozy dark den with plans of calling it home. Little did the 15-inch snake realize, the space already had a tenant. The tarantula was quick to give him notice. Her fangs, which measure almost an inch, would have plunged into the snake, liquefying its insides. Once decomposed, the tarantula then enjoyed its dinner.

The incident is believed to be the first known account of of a wild tarantula eating a snake in the wild. The researchers report that previous incidents of tarantulas eating snakes have only been witnessed in controlled settings, where the snake would be introduced to the spider.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Spider eats snake,world&#x2019;s biggest spider,giant spider,spider fight,snake eats spider,Tarantula eats snake,grammostola quirogai,tarantula grammostola,snake fights tarantula,huntsman spider,spider in salad,spider in banana,goliath birdeater,redback spider</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3253429</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 01:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F73/2EF/F732EFA111A549DBA5A9062324CB245C_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/13/3253429/3253429_C8D209B050B746B3993BD379698C9C33_170113_3253429_Spider_vs_snake__huge_tarantula_photographed_eat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guard dog fail: video shows burglars lure unsuspecting pooch out of house using treats</title>
      <description>PEORIA, ARIZONA &#x2014; A couple of burglars were quick to take advantage of a guard dog who was distracted by a handful of treats.

On December 8, the unidentified man and woman pulled up to the house in their Chevy Impala and parked in the driveway. After knocking and realizing no one was home, the man then hopped over the wall and proceeded to the dog door. He didn&#x2019;t show up empty-handed, carrying some sort of food for the dog.

Luring the unsuspecting canine out through the doggy door, the man squeezed his way into the small flap door and proceeded to ransack the home, stealing multiple goods with the greatest of ease.

One by one, the thieves carried the furniture to the car, as the dog watched. When they finished packing up the loot into their car, the pooch watched them speed away, leaving him behind in the driveway. Luckily, a neighbour spotted the dog and returned him to his owners. 

Police are asking for the public&#x2019;s help to track down the two criminals.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,dumb dog,prank on dog,guard dog fail,caught on camera,how to trick a dog,Burglar vs dog,cam,surveillance footage,CCTV robbers caught on camera,burglars on camera,burglars caught on tape,burglar fail,robber fail,peoria police department</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3253243</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 22:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3A2/7DB/3A27DB883FDD49FB954CF52D24975D2B_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/13/3253243/3253243_43D5B33B2B7A4144A0AD496F08D0BBA0_170113_3253243_Guard_dog_fail__video_shows_burglars_lure_unsusp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An animated retelling of Boston&#x2019;s Great Molasses Flood of 1919</title>
      <description>BOSTON &#x2014; It&#x2019;s been referred to as the Great Molasses Flood, the day a tank filled with more than 2 million gallons of molasses burst, and swept through Boston&#x2019;s city streets swallowing everything in its path. The exact reason for what caused the tank to blow has yet to be known, but cheap materials, faulty maintenance and weather conditions largely factored into the extent of the damage done. 

Reports indicate that on Jan. 15, 1919, the weather in Boston was a cool 41 degrees Fahrenheit, an unseasonably warm temperature for that time of year. The open hearth steel iron tank, stationed over at the city&#x2019;s North End neighborhood, stood 50 feet tall and measured 90 feet in diameter.

The tank had been filled 29 times before and had received 2.3 million gallons of molasses from Puerto Rico two day prior. Apparently, basic safety procedures weren&#x2019;t adhered to. Having leaked many times in the past, the tank was painted brown to hide the leaks. A steep price for the neglect was paid when, on that fateful afternoon, rivets burst along the side of tank. Locals said it sounded like a machine gun firing. Suddenly, the top of the tank blew off, and its circular iron walls ripped apart, pulled in opposite directions. Twenty-six million pounds of warm molasses were unleashed upon the city, moving at a speed of roughly 35 miles per hour. 

Some reports at the time indicated a 40-foot wave of syrup oozed through the city, crushing buildings and overturning vehicles. The molasses was so powerful, it knocked an elevated rail off its tracks and hurled a truck into the Boston Harbor. 

Horses, dogs and humans were swept up and scattered through the city. The molasses waist-deep, their attempts to struggle and escape the sticky goo only proved to worsen their plight. The warmer temperature is believed to have caused the molasses to cool faster than it would have in the summer, impeding rescue efforts.

The disaster claimed the lives of 21 people and left 150 badly injured. Nearly a century later, the exact cause of the tank&#x2019;s failures remain unknown, but fermentation, hasty construction and thin, brittle steel walls have been suspected as reasons for its undoing.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Boston molasses flood,great molasses flood,molasses disaster,1919 molasses,molasses accident 1919</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3253074</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 18:11:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>60</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1F8/D53/1F8D534B30414AA4BFDE1DB08DC87D68_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/13/3253074/3253074_E77D93FB93EB4C8799D6CB11152C52A7_170113_3253074_An_animated_retelling_of_Boston___s_Great_Molass_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithless electors: electors voting against their pledge aim to stop Trump&#x2019;s America</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; With only a week left until the Electoral College makes U.S. President-elect Donald Trump&#x2019;s win official, a handful of rogues will be voting against their pledge in hopes of derailing a Trump presidency.


For most states, the candidate that wins the majority vote in a state gets all of its electoral votes. In Maine and Nebraska, the votes are tallied by congressional district. Each state is allocated a certain number of electors, for a current total of 538, which makes up the Electoral College.


According to the National Archives and Records Administration, on the Monday after the second Wednesday in December, electors convene in their states to cast the votes for the president and vice president.


But sometimes, electors who are bound to vote for a presidential candidate choose not to do so. Called faithless electors, these members either pick a different candidate or abstain from voting altogether.


To prevent this from happening, 29 states plus the District of Columbia legally bind their electors to their pledged vote, under threat of a misdemeanor charge or a fine.


A group of rogues who call themselves Hamilton electors are currently trying to deny Trump his presidency, but they need to convince at least 37 Republican electors to turn in order to successfully do so.


Faithless electors rarely alter the outcome of the electoral vote, except for one instance in 1836, when 23 Virginia electors abstained in voting for the vice presidential nominee.


In the event of a deadlock, or if no candidate gets the absolute majority of votes, a contingent election is held where the presidency is decided by the House of Representatives and the vice presidency by the Senate.


At this point, whether or not the U.S. and the rest of the world witness Trump&#x2019;s America is up to the faithless.</description>
      <tags>video,Faithless elector,electoral college,faithless electors,hamilton electors,contingent election,how to stop trump presidency,how to stop trump,never trump</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231913</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 00:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>52</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0F1/D7D/0F1D7D4B73C64DF3B61AFA25BD3F4CFC_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/15/3231913/3231913_56799EDC58D74882B478312BEF9FC6CF_161215_3231913_Faithless_electors__electors_voting_against_thei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar vortex to bring &#x2018;dangerously cold&#x2019; weather to New England</title>
      <description>BOSTON &#x2014; A large part of the U.S. is preparing for the coldest December in years after the polar vortex made a comeback.


The polar vortex is located in the middle and upper tropospheres and extends into the stratosphere. It is in fact a band of low pressure Arctic air normally centered around the North Pole.


It is held in place by the jet stream, a river of wind that divides cold air from warm air. The jet stream bends around high or low pressure weather systems. When it does, the center of the vortex moves south into North America. 


The polar vortex can strengthen or weaken. A strong polar vortex keeps the cold air closer to the North Pole, whereas a weak polar vortex spreads the cold air southward.


Two arctic blasts will make their ways into the U.S., with the first round of cold air already affecting the Plains and Upper Midwest. The second wave will plunge south of the Canadian border by this weekend. The most intense lobe of the polar vortex will cover New England by Friday, bringing &#x2018;dangerously cold&#x2019; weather to the area.</description>
      <tags>video,Polar vortex,polar vortex in us,polar vortex impact,snowstorm,dangerously cold weather in us,arctic blasts</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3231795</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:36:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C8F/88E/C8F88ED742A54F99AB9885DC9DF1E165_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/15/3231795/3231795_6F206D38E324431587D2D746FBBC9260_161215_3231795_Polar_vortex_to_bring____dangerously_cold____wea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You are the not the father: man forced to pay child support for baby he found isn&#x2019;t his</title>
      <description>TULSA, OKLAHOMA &#x2014; An Oklahoma man in is getting a raw deal after finding out the child he&#x2019;s fathered for three years isn&#x2019;t his. The victim of an unusual state law, the man is also forced to make child support payments.

When Thomas&#x2019; high school girlfriend told him she was pregnant, he wanted to do right by her, and so the two got married. Five months later, Thomas&#x2019; wife gave birth to a baby boy, but the two couldn&#x2019;t make things work and eventually split. 

Having suspicions about whether his son was actually his, Thomas decided to take a paternity test &#x2013; the test came back 0.00%. Shocked at how he could be so misled, he took his case to the courtroom. 

When a judge ordered that Thomas take another paternity test, the results came back the same. Initially, the courts deemed he was not financially responsible for the child, but the judge later reversed the decision. Under Oklahoma law, paternity must be tested before the child&#x2019;s second birthday. After that, the presumed father becomes the legal father, and DNA tests are no longer of consequence.

Now, Thomas finds himself paying the child&#x2019;s mother $500/month in child support, as well as an additional $15,000 in back support, with interest.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Child support,baby daddy,paternity,maury povich,you are not the father,baby mama drama,babymama,sperm donor,deadbeat dad</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3254280</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 02:54:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>34</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/575/FD6/575FD64CEC914F10BF67EAFE458A57C4_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/14/3254280/3254280_846345ED60AD442A97318AB282599021_170114_3254280_You_are_the_not_the_father__man_forced_to_pay_ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JonBenet Ramsey case: New DNA testing planned after report revealed flaws</title>
      <description>BOULDER, COLORADO &#x2014; New DNA testing is planned in the investigation of the unsolved murder of 6-year-old JonBenet Ramsey, who was found dead in 1996. An exclusive report revealed flaws in the interpretation of previous DNA testing.

According to a joint report by Daily Camera and 9News, the DNA samples from JonBenet&#x2019;s long johns belong to at least two people, in addition to herself. Also, the DNA profile gathered from JonBenet&#x2019;s underwear could be a composite and not just from a single individual. The new findings make the link between the DNA found in the underwear and the long johns extremely weak, and could result in the DNA findings being considered evidence.

Mary Lacy, the district attorney at the time, was given this analysis of the DNA. However, she concluded that the DNA found in JonBenet&#x2019;s underwear and the DNA found in her long johns pointed to an unknown male. This conclusion exonerated the Ramsey family from suspicion in 2008.

Lacy did not respond to requests for comment after the report revealed the DNA findings failed to support her decision to exonerate the Ramsey family.

JonBenet was found murdered in the basement of the family house in Boulder, Colorado. Her mother, Patsy Ramsey said she realized her daughter was missing after finding a ransom letter on the kitchen staircase the morning after Christmas and quickly phoned the police. However, police did not find her body during the initial search of the house. It was her father, John Ramsey, who found JonBenet&#x2019;s body in the wine cellar room in the basement that afternoon.

JonBenet was duct taped over the month and her wrists were tied. A garrote was found around her neck and her skull was fractured due to a heavy blow.</description>
      <tags>video,Jonbenet ramsey case,jonbenet murder,murder of jonbenet,jonbenet ramsey,boulder,colorado,unsolved homicide,dna testing jonbenet case</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3232983</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 03:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>81</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7CF/65E/7CF65E128ECA4BD98811BE08018639E1_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/16/3232983/3232983_4982774DFDB94FDAB881CD852966CDBB_161216_3232983_JonBenet_Ramsey_case__New_DNA_testing_planned_af_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating black men: teen says parents cut off college tuition of her black boyfriend</title>
      <description>EADS, TENNESSEE &#x2014; A Tennessee high schooler has raised thousands of dollars online to pay for her college tuition after claiming that her parents took away her college funds because she is dating a black guy.

According to Allie Dowdle&#x2019;s Gofundme page, she started dating her boyfriend Michael about a year ago. When the Eads, Tennessee student first shared this news to her parents, they did not approve.

&#x201C;My dad did not give me an option:  he told me that I was not allowed to see Michael ever again. Why? Strictly because of skin color.  It wasn't a quiet "no," either. I'll never forget the yelling my parents did, when they expressed how disappointed they were in me, that I could do so much better,&#x201D; Allie writes on the fundraising site.

Allie reported ignored her parents and continued to see Michael secretely. She wrote that she and Michael approached her parents last month, but was again met with fierce opposition. Eventually, their relationship cost her her phone, car and college funds.

The goal on Allie&#x2019;s Gofundme page was set at $10,000, but she received over $24,000 from almost a thousand people in just two days.

Do you believe Allie&#x2019;s claim that her parents simply didn&#x2019;t want her dating a black guy? Or do you think Allie is simply spoiled?</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Gofundme,allie dowdle,gofundme scams,gofundme campaigns,gofundme tips,gofundme success,allie dowdle,dating black men,dating a black guy,spoiled teenagers</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3255404</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 01:14:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>25</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CF0/4FA/CF04FA4B34D448B6BB6FF3C9181CB3F3_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/16/3255404/3255404_CB960FE10FEE405FAAEC59F91090294E_170116_3255404_Dating_black_men__teen_says_parents_cut_off_coll_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police harassment: Black PhD student arrested on suspicion of stealing HIS OWN car</title>
      <description>EVANSTON, ILLINOIS &#x2014; Police have released dashcam footage that shows a black PhD student being arrested on suspicion of stealing his own car.

The incident took place on Oct. 10, 2015,  when driver Lawrence Crosby was 25 years old and studying for a doctoral degree in civil engineering at Northwestern University.

Earlier that night, Crosby aroused the suspicions of a member of the public, who saw him trying to fix some loose molding on his car roof with something that looked like a metal bar, the Chicago Tribune reported.

The woman called 911, said she felt bad about racial profiling, but reported a potential case of grand theft auto anyway. She then jumped in her own car and started following Crosby.

The student noticed he was being tailed and decided he would drive to the police station to explain the situation before things escalated.

But by that point, the cops were already in hot pursuit.

During the arrest, Crosby was kneed and struck with open hands as he was swarmed by officers and wrestled to the ground. 

Crosby proved to the cops that the car was his and explained he&#x2019;d been trying to fix something on the roof. So when they couldn&#x2019;t pin anything on him for theft, the police charged Crosby with resisting arrest and disobeying officers.

Those charges were thrown out by a judge in March last year. Crosby has filed a civil lawsuit against the city and the arresting officers, alleging false arrest and excessive force.

The police however, claim the use of force was justified.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Police harassment,cops harassing black people,cops harassing people,driving while black,dash cam,police dash cam,police dash cam 2017</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3255401</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 01:13:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/383/685/38368545B39B40C2A7C87C9E207DF3C6_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/16/3255401/3255401_BD539528D53F4B8BBF47D66D8369F38C_170116_3255401_Police_harassment__Black_PhD_student_arrested_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrified dog: video shows abused dog chained to roof of trailer behind speeding SUV</title>
      <description>FLAGLER COUNTY, FLORIDA &#x2014; A videoclip of a dog riding on top of a trailer, as its being pulled by an SUV on the highway, is going viral online, and has animal lovers outraged.

On January 11, Brenna Cronin was in a car travelling down the I-95, when she spotted the dog up ahead. The dog was chained to the roof of a trailer being pulled by an SUV going at speeds of over 70 mph. Cronin says as she passed, she noticed the letter &#x201C;S&#x201D; branded into the dog&#x2019;s back right leg. Disgusted, Cronin pulled out her phone, and recorded a clip of the sad scene, which she uploaded to Facebook. 

She then called the police, and offered the cops a description of the vehicle, and the pet in peril. The next day, Cronin received a photograph from another Facebook user who&#x2019;d caught sight of what appears to be the same dog, in the exact same predicament.

Once the video surfaced, the owner was reached for comment by media. He claims he did nothing wrong, and went as far as to say the dog prefers riding on top of the cage, rather than inside with his other dogs. Animal control from two nearby counties went over the owner&#x2019;s home to do a wellness check on the animals. 

In some counties in the area, animals must be transported in secure pet carriers or cages. Violators of this could be subject to a $93 fine, depending on which county the infraction took place.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Scared dog,Animal abuse,dog in car,dog caught on video,dog caught on camera,brenna cronin,flagler,dog chained to crate,caught on camera,caught on video</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3255382</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 00:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>20</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/87B/929/87B929DB9F3C4E34AEC5AFB3A227C25B_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/16/3255382/3255382_494F312BE37A452D85E4360192BEC792_170116_3255382_Terrified_dog__video_shows_abused_dog_chained_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bestiality: Florida boned pit bull more than 100 times over three years, police say</title>
      <description>PENSACOLA, FLORIDA &#x2014; A Florida man was arrested for having sex with his family&#x2019;s pit bull for years before a roommate finally told the authorities. 

Bradley Hubbard, 23, moved in with his dad and his dad&#x2019;s girlfriend in Pensacola three years ago. The family had a pit bull named &#x201C;Baby Girl.&#x201D; 

A family member who lived in the home says she saw Hubbard bringing Baby Girl back to his room. She says she could see the action through a hole in the door. At first she would hear the pit bull whimper and cry out. When asked what was going on, Hubbard would say the dog was in heat. Eventually the dog stopped making noises &#x2014; probably because she was traumatized, Pensacola News Journal reported. 

On Dec. 28, Hubbard took the dog from the woman&#x2019;s room and locked his door. The woman heard noises and &#x201C;could not take it anymore,&#x201D; so she called the cops. Hubbard&#x2019;s father denied that his son was involved in any wrongdoing. But the person who reported the incident said the father had covered for his son before. 

A local veterinarian examined the dog for signs of rape and found that the dog&#x2019;s genitals showed signs of sexual abuse. 

Hubbard is being held at the Escambia County Jail on a $15,000 bond. He faces charges of engaging in sexual conduct with an animal and causing death, pain or suffering to an animal. He is set to appear in court on Feb. 2.

There was no word on why the roommate waited so long to report the abuse.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Florida man sexually abuses dog,bestiality,bestiality in the US,man rapes dogs,Bradley Jean Hubbard</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3255254</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 22:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>25</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/94C/C47/94CC47F1A71F4BBDA2F5B3F12BB02AED_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/16/3255254/3255254_28B0B4ACC210474988B211B8DCD51D15_170116_3255254_Bestiality__Florida_boned_pit_bull_more_than_100_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV host meltdown: Australian Amber Sherlock fights co-host Julie Snook over white outfit</title>
      <description>SYDNEY &#x2014; Two news presenters for Australia&#x2019;s Nine News got into a tense wardrobe stand-off after one forced the other to cover up.

The exchange happened off-air, but was leaked online on Mumbrella, and is now being dubbed jacketgate.

The Sydney Morning Herald reports that the now-infamous clip stars Amber Sherlock, who was in between segments with a guest and a fellow reporter when she noticed all three of them were all wearing white outfits.

Annoyed, Sherlock began berating reporter Julie Snook for not wearing a jacket despite being told to do so two hours earlier, dismissing her excuses that she was busy and just flat-out forgot.

Guest psychologist Sandy Rea tried to diffuse the situation by suggesting she&#x2019;d cover up with a jacket instead, but Sherlock was adamant that Snook cover up.

Eventually, someone did manage to find a black jacket to put on Snook. The trio was soon all smiles as the cameras rolled, with hardly any sign of the passive-aggressive drama that had been front and center just moments before.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Reporter fail,reporters fighting,women fighting,live mic,TV host fighting,TV host angry,TV catfight,tv meltdown,reporter meltdown,reporter catfight,wardrobe malfunction,epic meltdown,work fight,work drama,news anchor meltdown,australian news anchors,amber sherlock,julie snook,leaked video,channel 9,nine news,amber sherlock video,diva meltdown,tv rant,tv catfights,Jacketgate,jacket gate,reporter controversies</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3255814</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 09:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>19</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/65B/073/65B0733A75594D02AE8E82FC3404E77C_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/16/3255814/3255814_8400A7F59D6D425EBD4F8D6833D1FFCE_170116_3255814_TV_host_meltdown__Australian_Amber_Sherlock_figh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speak English: Greek-American couple harassed for speaking Greek in LA store</title>
      <description>LOS ANGELES &#x2014; Viral video filmed inside a California supermarket last week shows a Greek-American couple being harassed by a woman for not speaking English.

According to USA.GreekReporter.com, the incident took place in Los Angeles.

Blogger Thanasi Papoulias and his wife were waiting in line and speaking Greek when the woman confronted them. In a post to his Facebook Page, Papoulias wrote that the woman repeatedly cursed at them and told them, &#x201C;Speak F*@king English, this is America.&#x201D;

Toward the end of the footage the store manager can be seen telling the woman to leave.

The video has been viewed over 370,000 times since the weekend.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3256429</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 05:14:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>18</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/53E/ACF/53EACFB6444548009D4EC8A38C7E926D_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/17/3256429/3256429_FD315EE401D24B3CB42CFE1AC55D253B_170117_3256429_Speak_English__Greek_American_couple_harassed_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vape pen explosion: E-cig blows up in Idaho man&#x2019;s face, he loses 7 teeth</title>
      <description>POCATELLO, IDAHO &#x2014; A former vapist is warning others about the dangers of e-cigarettes after his vape pen blew up in his face.

Car salesman Andrew Hall suffered second-degree burns and lost seven teeth in the horrific incident.

The explosion happened on the weekend when Andrew was enjoying a few toots of electronic smoke while getting ready for work.

Andrew wrote on Facebook that he was vaping in his bathroom when his vape pen exploded. The blast was so powerful that it shattered his bathroom sink.

Posting from the hospital ICU ward, Andrew wrote that he&#x2019;d been pulling chunks of plastic, teeth and foreign objects from his mouth, throat and lips.

Andrew said he had been vaping for about a year and had properly maintained the battery of his vape pen. He added that he&#x2019;d never had an issue with overheating.

He said he wanted his experience to serve as a warning to others.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Vape pen exploding,vape pen explosion,e cigarette explodes,e-cigarette explosion,vaping,vape,e-cig blows up in mans face</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3256334</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 03:01:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>17</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EDF/4EB/EDF4EB8D9C414912B4423DFA75203109_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/17/3256334/3256334_1DB3F494A49C414D86190C3A68710F00_170117_3256334_Vape_pen_explosion__E_cig_blows_up_in_Idaho_man__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired! Maryland school employee axed for correcting kid&#x2019;s spelling on Twitter</title>
      <description>FREDERICK, MARYLAND &#x2014; A social media manager for a Maryland school district was recently fired for being sassy on Twitter &#x2014; the victim of higher-ups with sticks up their you-know-wheres.

The Frederick News Post reports that the incident began after a student sent a tweet to Frederick County Public Schools account, asking for school to be cancelled the next day, but misspelling the word tomorrow as &#x201C;tammarow.&#x201D;

Katie Nash, who manages the school&#x2019;s Twitter account, replied in jest, asking how the student would learn how to spell the word correctly if school closed.

The spectacular burn lit up the Twitterverse, with netizens very amused by the quip.

The student didn&#x2019;t take it personally, and even continued with the harmless banter. Unfortunately, the uptight members of the school board did. They called Nash to a meeting and promptly fired her for what they deemed to be inappropriate tweets.

The firing led to a social media uproar, with Twitter users coming to Nash&#x2019;s defense, and students clamoring to get her back.

Nash admitted that she didn&#x2019;t think she was going to be fired, instead expecting the school to give her counseling or suggestions on how to do her job. Still, she claims she she understands where the school is coming from.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,political correctness gone wrong,teacher fired,dumb student,school fails,social media fail,free katie,employee fired for social media,frederick county public schools,maryland school district,katie nash</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3256306</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 02:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1F6/28E/1F628EAC7E1C49958E09288B091F55BD_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/17/3256306/3256306_A994493972A1421DB640C2EF25B2DA8A_170117_3256306_Fired__Maryland_school_employee_axed_for_correct_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Japanese whaling: ship caught with minke in Australian sanctuary - TomoNews</title>
      <description>AUSTRALIA &#x2014; Despite its whaling program having been ruled illegal by the International Court of Justice in 2014, Japan continues to antagonize the global community with its despicable practices. 

On Jan. 15, conservation Organization Sea Shepherd posted these disturbing photographs of a dead minke whale aboard the Nisshin Maru, the primary vessel of Japan&#x2019;s whaling fleet. As the Japanese fleet traveled through the Australian Whale Sanctuary in the Southern Ocean, the ships must have caught sight of the whale and killed it. They weren&#x2019;t as covert as they needed to be, because a Sea Shepherd helicopter spotted the whale&#x2019;s carcass lying on the flensing deck of the Nisshin Maru.

Realizing they were exposed, the crew of the whaler factory ship tried to cover their tracks, spreading a blue tarp over the body of the dead whale. The fleet&#x2019;s harpoon ships then quickly followed suit, covering their deadly weapons.

The discovery of the unlawful whaling comes just a day after Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe met with Australian Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull in Sydney. This is the first dead whale seen aboard a Japanese ship since the country was ordered to end its Antarctic hunt, when the International Court of Justice concluded that the scientific research being conducted was illegitimate.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Minke whale,japanese whaling,sea shepherd,australian whale sanctuary,dead whale,nisshin maru,whale meat,japan scientific research,whale harpoon gun</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3256198</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 01:19:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C46/211/C4621193FFEE4E52812880704A9231CF_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/17/3256198/3256198_332A353DF0944925A8C7EF74F3421FE9_170117_3256198_Illegal_Japanese_whaling__ship_caught_with_minke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexism: Chinese company Tencent faces PR crisis for sexually suggestive game</title>
      <description>SHENZHEN, CHINA &#x2014; Chinese company Tencent is facing a major PR crisis after video of a sexually suggestive game being played by employees was posted online on Jan. 12. 

The footage was shot at an annual party hosted by Tencent's instant messaging application department. Two female employees were brought on stage and asked to drop to their knees in front of other male employees, whom were each holding closed water bottles between their legs. Spectators can be heard off camera cheering the girls on while they tried to unscrew the bottle caps with their mouths, reported by China&#x2019;s Sina news. 

The video has sparked widespread public backlash, with commenters expressing their shock and disgust at the blatant sexism displayed through the game.

Tencent later released a statement apologizing for the incident, adding that employees responsible for the game have been given &#x201C;demerits&#x201D; on their employee records. However, it isn&#x2019;t clear whether this will result in any actual</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Tencent,China sexism against women,Tencent,chinese new year party,inappropriate games,inappropriate workplace behavior,sex game,sexually suggestive</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3256161</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 00:46:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>18</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BA3/88B/BA388BDA46CF44A4B942A3D4866A5A8C_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/17/3256161/3256161_E1CDB935C4944A68B37F5A12E5CB3354_170117_3256161_Sexism__Chinese_company_Tencent_faces_PR_crisis__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer research: Cells that rise from the dead may spread cancer in the body</title>
      <description>SAN FRANCISCO &#x2014; Cells that undergo a near-death experience but refuse to die could be responsible for helping cancer spread in the body.

Scientists once thought that cells killed themselves in a process called apoptosis, which is triggered when a molecule called a caspase is activated, Science News reported.

However, research conducted within the last decade indicates that cells can abort their own suicide in a process named anastasis, and now scientists say this could have implications for the treatment of cancer.

Unpublished research from biologists at the University of California, Santa Barbara, indicates that despite receiving chemotherapy treatment, cancer cells can come back to life through the anastasis.

Those cancer cells can then multiply and spread throughout the body. 

That means that stopping anastasis could provide more effective cancer treatments, according to the researchers.

However, in some cases, such as saving heart cells after a heart attack or brain cells after a stroke, provoking anastasis may be beneficial.

Scientists still don&#x2019;t know how anastasis works, which means this kind of cancer research is still very much in its infancy.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Cancer,cancer research,anastasis,anastasis cancer,apostasis cancer,apostasis,cancer treatment,treating cancer</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3234866</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 04:04:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>33</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6C3/5F2/6C35F26301FE4785B6572F403901526A_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/19/3234866/3234866_0C132924104049FA8E6F9C9797F37C54_161219_3234866_Cancer_research__Cells_that_rise_from_the_dead_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man and woman swap body fluids outside family resort in Phuket, Thailand</title>
      <description>PHUKET, THAILAND &#x2014; A photograph allegedly showing a couple mid-coitus outside a Thai family resort is causing outrage online. 

The photo was tweeted on Monday by Ogilvy Asia Marketing Head Greg Carton with the text: &#x201C;Just one of the great sessions from #teadssummit. Smoking + public sex around kids. Terrorising resort staff + guests. #Branding Tks @Teads!&#x201D; 

Teads is a digital video advertising company, and the Teads Summit is an annual get-together for the ad industry. 

The image was said to have been captured at the Angsana Laguna hotel in Phuket.
 
This guest, Carton claims, complained to Teads, reported Agency Spy. But they didn&#x2019;t respond, so Carton tweeted it out two days later in anger. The guest said the man in the image was part of the conference.

Teads told Agency Spy they&#x2019;re investigating the incident, but according to reports, no one has been identified so far.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Man and woman swap body fluids,couple caught hooking up,phuket,couple caught at in hotel,caught in the act,doing it in public,couple caught,couple caught in Thailand,teads,teads summit,greg carton</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3257440</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 07:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/74F/9F9/74F9F90DE56E4CE98DCC8BE233070AAF_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/18/3257440/3257440_0172052C709E4D0BAB5A1EE962DAC61B_170118_3257440_Man_and_woman_swap_body_fluids_outside_family_re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Clinton WikiLeaks emails: HRC wanted to dump Taiwan in 2011 over U.S. debt with China</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; An alleged email by Hillary Clinton shows that the former secretary of state was willing to discuss an op-ed piece in the New York Times that called for Washington to ditch Taiwan in exchange for China writing off U.S. debt. 

According to the document released by WikiLeaks, back in 2011, Clinton adviser Jake Sullivan sent the New York Times editorial titled &#x201C;To Save Our Economy, Ditch Taiwan&#x201D; by Paul V. Kane to Hillary. Clinton replied, &#x201C;I saw it and thought it was so clever. Let&#x2019;s discuss.&#x201D;  

Kane suggested the U.S. negotiate to have China write off $1.14 trillion in American debt in exchange for ending U.S. military assistance and arms sales to Taiwan. 

In Kane&#x2019;s opinion this would cut American debt, help the economy and keep the U.S. and China from going to war over Taiwan.  

It&#x2019;s clear from reading Kane&#x2019;s piece that he is clueless about Taiwan, as well as how China&#x2019;s economy would be affected by such a massive write off.

The WikiLeaks emails did not show whether Clinton actually discussed the article.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Hillary Clinton,Hillary Clinton WikiLeaks,Hillary Clinton WikiLeaks emails,Hillary Clinton Wikileaks news,Clinton wanted to dump Taiwan,HRC wanted to ditch Taiwan,Trump Taiwan</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3256640</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 08:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>110</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EF1/B37/EF1B37BA5B104BE5A545716DD1536BB4_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/17/3256640/3256640_9CE501E61A124B73B2786EB2E9A2F291_170117_3256640_Hillary_Clinton_WikiLeaks_emails__HRC_wanted_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kangaroo attack: Jogger gets 35 stitches from vicious mauling by 2m tall crazy kangaroo</title>
      <description>TEMPLESTOWE, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; A personal trainer in Melbourne had to have emergency surgery after being brutally mauled by a large male kangaroo.

The Manningham Leader reports that Debbie Urquhart was jogging through a bush track in Templestowe Saturday morning and didn&#x2019;t see the towering threat that was coming her way.

A fully grown 2-meter-tall male kangaroo suddenly jumped at her and knocked her down. It kicked and clawed at her ferociously, shredding her clothes and ripping through her flesh.

The 54-year-old played dead to try and get the roo to stop attacking, and soon the big boy backed off.

Urquhart got back up and walked half a kilometer back home while bleeding from her injuries. She was rushed to the hospital by husband Robert and ended up getting more than 35 stitches.

A kangaroo expert told the ABC that this particular kangaroo&#x2019;s show of aggression was rare, as unprovoked attacks rarely occur. 

And while the harrowing encounter hasn&#x2019;t slowed Urquhart down, she says she probably won&#x2019;t be going near the tracks anytime soon.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Kangaroo attack,kangaroo claws,crazy kangaroo,kangaroo maul,roo attack,kangaroo attacks woman,animals attack,wild animal attack,animal attack,kangaroo attacks jogger</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3257262</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 03:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>28</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/47E/757/47E757F3619E40D1A3128477F00BBB50_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/18/3257262/3257262_4173A20E3CAA4007972700098F697925_170118_3257262_Kangaroo_attack__Jogger_gets_35_stitches_from_vi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black man eating with white girlfriend harassed for not dating a black woman</title>
      <description>USA &#x2014; A video of a biracial couple eating at a restaurant has gone viral, as it was filmed by a man who walked up to them and chastised the black man for being with a white woman.

Not much is known about the couple, but the man recording mentions them being in a black restaurant. As the couple enjoyed a nice meal, another patron of the establishment took exception to their being together. So, he decided to &#x201C;interview&#x201D; them using his smart phone. Once the rude man interrupted their date, he just kept on going, chastising the poor guy for dating a white woman, whom he called &#x201C;the lowest rung of humanity.&#x201D;

Somehow, the black boyfriend showed restraint and simply just laughed the rude customer off, doing his best to calmly de-escalate the situation. The video has since been posted to World Star, where it&#x2019;s been viewed more than 800,000 times.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Racist black man,interracial couple,Biracial couple,mixed race,how to date a white woman,how to date a black man,black man with white woman,worldstar,daniele watts police video</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3256981</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 23:18:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FE6/B5A/FE6B5A0D83DB4D19A0C24101DA2DE169_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/18/3256981/3256981_B71A492C63844205854D97B629CA96D1_170118_3256981_Black_man_eating_with_white_girlfriend_harassed__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin attack: Truck plows into crowded Christmas market, killing at least 12 people</title>
      <description>BERLIN &#x2014; A truck plowed into a crowded Christmas market in central Berlin on Monday night, killing at least 12 people and injuring 48 others.

The incident took place at a Christmas market outside the Kaiser Wilhelm Memorial Church in the German capital. 

The truck was loaded with steel beams. It was registered to a company in Poland, from where it traveled to Berlin on Monday afternoon, the Guardian reported. The company that owns the truck said it had been unable to contact the driver since 4 p.m. on Monday.

The truck jumped the sidewalk and crashed through several market stalls before coming to a stop. A passenger was found dead inside the vehicle while the driver allegedly fled the scene. Police made an arrest near the market but it is not yet confirmed whether the man was the driver.

German police believe the incident was an attack. It highly resembles the July terror attack in Nice, France when an Islamist extremist deliberately drove a 19-ton truck into the city&#x2019;s promenade and killed 86 people.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Berlin truck attack,berlin attack 2016,berlin christmas market attack,truck plows into christmas market,germany terrorism,berlin attack,germany terrorist</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235588</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 02:57:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/694/2D8/6942D8D186A54A5798DA85DA9CF34EF9_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235588/3235588_E4290566760B41A2B3160EFC87711781_161220_3235588_Berlin_attack__Truck_plows_into_crowded_Christma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter cars: New technology enables cars to recognize road signs and alert drivers</title>
      <description>LONDON &#x2014; A new technology has enabled some cars to recognize road signs and alert the drivers when driving on congested roads.

Volkswagen recently released its Dynamic Road Sign Display system, which is described as the driver&#x2019;s &#x201C;companion on board&#x201D;. The system can automatically detect the traffic signs and display the signs on both multifunction display and on the navigation system unit display.

The car is equipped with a forward facing mirror and a rain sensor. It can recognize important traffic signals such as speed limits, highway exits, no overtaking signs and end of motorway indicators.

The on-board computer system cross-references the traffic signs detected by the camera, information from the navigation device and current vehicle data to make sure the information given to the driver is correct.

The technology is also available on selected car models produced by companies such as Audi and Mercedes.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Volkswagen sign assist,Dynamic Road Sign Display system,car technology,automobile technology,car recognizes road signs,smart car technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235440</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FED/F66/FEDF6670F47E4DD8BB91003AF975D721_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235440/3235440_2530B073EB7047509589B80A6A6D255B_161220_3235440_Smarter_cars__New_technology_enables_cars_to_rec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter cars: new technology enables cars to recognize road signs and alert drivers</title>
      <description>LONDON &#x2014; A new technology has enabled some cars to recognize road signs and alert the drivers when driving on congested roads.

Volkswagen recently released its Dynamic Road Sign Display system, which is described as the driver&#x2019;s &#x201C;companion on board&#x201D;. The system can automatically detect the traffic signs and display the signs on both multifunction display and on the navigation system unit display.

The car is equipped with a forward facing mirror and a rain sensor. It can recognize important traffic signals such as speed limits, highway exits, no overtaking signs and end of motorway indicators.

The on-board computer system cross-references the traffic signs detected by the camera, information from the navigation device and current vehicle data to make sure the information given to the driver is correct.

The technology is also available on selected car models produced by companies such as Audi and Mercedes.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Volkswagen sign assist,Dynamic Road Sign Display system,car technology,automobile technology,car recognizes road signs,smart car technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235354</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 22:55:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/78F/8BE/78F8BE8553524F14AA8501F7E9B3B237_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235354/3235354_939B961BED4644749194C47900F11B69_161220_3235354_Smarter_cars__new_technology_enables_cars_to_rec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan attack: Canadian woman among 10 killed in terrorist siege of Karak castle</title>
      <description>KARAK, JORDAN &#x2014; At least 10 people, including a Canadian tourist, were killed and 29 others were injured when militants opened fire from a Crusader-era castle in Jordan on Sunday.

A series of attacks in the southern city of Karak began when a police patrol went to check on a house fire. One policeman was wounded when gunmen fired from inside the house before the attackers fled in a car, Al Jazeera reported.

Soon afterward, gunmen shot at another police patrol, while at the same time an unknown number of assailants opened fire on police and civilians from the city&#x2019;s 874-year-old castle. 

Police and security forces surrounded the castle and exchanged fire with the militants for several hours.

Four gunmen were killed at the castle, where police found large quantities of explosives, weapons and suicide belts.

The dead Canadian woman was named by CBC News as Linda Vatcher, 62, a retired teacher from Newfoundland who was visiting her son in the Middle East.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Jordan attack,jordan terrorism,jordan terrorist attack,karak castle,karak castle attack,jordan castle attack,attack in jordan</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235259</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 20:09:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>38</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/26C/3ED/26C3EDB32F47473CBDCBF7F988B6DA2C_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235259/3235259_95424B205DD346AC987F0348A7292DE0_161220_3235259_Jordan_attack__Canadian_woman_among_10_killed_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of the world: Astronomers say giant sun will destroy all life on Earth</title>
      <description>LEUVEN, BELGIUM &#x2014; Astronomers predict that all life on Earth will be wiped out in 5 billion years, as the sun balloons in size and scorches the planet.

Scientists at the University of Leuven in Belgium used ALMA, the world&#x2019;s most powerful radio telescope, to forecast the future of the planet, according to a study published in the journal Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics.

They predict that within 5 billion years, the sun will grow into a red giant star one hundred times its current size. The sun will swallow up and destroy its two closest planets, Mercury and Venus, and all life on Earth is likely to be destroyed.

There is, however, a possibility the rocky core of the planet could survive.

In 7 billion years, the sun will then experience intense loss of mass due to strong stellar winds that will see it evolve into a tiny white dwarf star.

If the earth&#x2019;s rocky core survives, it may continue to orbit the white dwarf star.

The white dwarf star will be similar in size to Earth but much heavier. One teaspoon of its matter will weigh about 5 tons.

The astronomers&#x2019; findings are based on an examination of L2 Puppis, an evolved star 208 light years away from Earth, which 5 billion years ago was very similar to our sun.

The scientists said an object orbiting L2 Puppis is likely to be a planet, and further study could offer unique insights into Earth&#x2019;s eventual fate.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,End of the world,L2 Puppis,giant sun,end of the earth,ALMA radio telescope,astronomy,red giant star,red giant sun</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3235174</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 16:54:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/872/7CD/8727CDC2AA8D41C3B2E5E7E42C3E0C07_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/20/3235174/3235174_AA3051B4828545D2B54CD28927356754_161220_3235174_End_of_the_world__Astronomers_say_giant_sun_will_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers moving to LA: San Diego movers are refusing to help the team relocate to Los Angeles</title>
      <description>SAN DIEGO &#x2014; Now that the Chargers have decided to ditch San Diego in exchange for Los Angeles, they&#x2019;re having trouble finding logistics companies that will help them with the move. 

Billionaire owner Alex Spanos is finding it hard to score a mover after San Diego companies banded together to refuse to relocate the team to L.A. 

So far, 22 movers in the city have told the Chargers to eff off, and so have five L.A.-based companies.    

Moving companies are basically saying goodbye to a massive payday upwards of $100,000 not to move the Chargers offices and training equipment. 

It may not be the smartest way to send a message, but it sure is funny. 

Unfortunately, the noble actions of these bold movers will no doubt go unnoticed by Spanos.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,San Diego Chargers moving,Chargers relocation,LA Chargers,Chargers moving to LA,Chargers Alex Spanos,San Diego HireAHelper Chargers,Chargers Philip Rivers,LA Rams,NFL</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3257595</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 11:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>118</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C0F/56A/C0F56A5DBFF24E808C3A3404C50CBCF8_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/18/3257595/3257595_890AD73679C6435A8F485DD32DF5631E_170118_3257595_Chargers_moving_to_LA__San_Diego_movers_are_refu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home intruder gets shot gets by off-duty cop after breaking into Ohio home</title>
      <description>PLEASANT TOWNSHIP, OHIO &#x2014; A burglar is lucky to be alive after being wounded while trying to rob an off-duty cop&#x2019;s home. 

According to the newspaper Columbus Dispatch, Sergeant Stephen Carr woke on Tuesday afternoon to the noise of breaking glass at his home on Gay Road in Pleasant Township, Ohio.

He went to see what was going on and found would-be burglar Jason Bosswell. Carr confronted him but was pushed back.

So the 15-year veteran grabbed his gun and shot Boswell in the torso. 

Boswell fled the scene in a car but was tracked down by police. He later admitted to breaking into Carr&#x2019;s home, reported the Columbus Dispatch.

Boswell&#x2019;s injuries weren&#x2019;t life threatening.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3258198</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 04:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>21</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E34/1A5/E341A578A9C24E62A7A6504981C29CDA_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/19/3258198/3258198_54098971A9114806AE4EC42D31CF6362_170119_3258198_Home_intruder_gets_shot_gets_by_off_duty_cop_aft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico school shooting: Student shoots teacher, classmates before killing himself</title>
      <description>MONTERREY, MEXICO &#x2014; Chaos erupted inside a private school in Monterrey, Mexico Wednesday morning after a student opened fire inside his classroom.

Reuters reports that the incident began during a class at the American School of the Northeast, when a 15-year-old student suddenly pulled out a 22-caliber pistol.

CCTV footage shows the student, identified as Federico Guevara, first shooting a male classmate in front of him and then his 24-year-old teacher. He then went around the room and randomly shot at other students.

A total of seven shots were fired, some at point-blank range, before the teen turned the gun on himself. He shot at his temple but missed before running out of bullets.

After running back to his desk to reload his weapon, Guevara shot himself in the chin. His classmates rushed to the door as he lay in a bloody heap on the floor.

Guevara later died in the hospital. Three of his victims were hit in the head and are in critical condition. One took a bullet to the arm and has been declared stable.

Authorities believe the gunman brought the pistol from home and say it may be necessary to re-implement a protocol to have students&#x2019; bags checked when they enter school.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Mexico school shooting,school shooting,school violence,violence on campus,campus violence,campus shooting,classroom shooting,classroom violence,american school of the northeast,mexico shooting,monterrey shooting,guns on campus,guns in school</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3258153</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 03:32:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>26</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/858/FE0/858FE0A3CFE54BA7874AD91DF2CFC382_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/19/3258153/3258153_DA23457347A44F7C8AF958D9BB34C2C7_170119_3258153_Mexico_school_shooting__Student_shoots_teacher___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn studio: Arizona man arrested for operating a porn studio as brothel</title>
      <description>PHOENIX, ARIZONA &#x2014; A 52-year-old man in Phoenix has been arrested for running a porn studio as a brothel. 

William J. Hartwell, owner of New Media Studios, thought he was skirting the law by having clients pay for equipment rental to create their own sex scenes while providing &#x201C;free&#x201D; models.

Clients registered online and would pay a receptionist for equipment and studio fees. 

Once inside the studio, clients would be asked to show their genitals to prove that they were not undercover cops. Then the client and a model would photograph or film a short video of whatever fantasy or sexual act the customer desired. The studio reportedly generated $40,000 a month in profits.

A few days after the shoot, customers could return to pick up a USB drive with the photos or videos. About half of the customers actually returned to pick up the video or images, NBC-affiliate KPNX reported.

Hartwell says he was not running prostitution ring. He says he he ran a legitimate business, one that was protected under the First Amendment of the Constitution.

Several female employees who worked at the studio have already pleaded guilty and are expected to testify at Hartwell&#x2019;s trial.

Hartwell faces charges of operating a house of prostitution, sex trafficking, and sexual assault. His trial begins next week.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Porn studio,porn studio and brothel,arizona porn studio,porn shoot,homemade sex videos,first amendment,constitution</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3257943</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 21:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/537/2D8/5372D86814844970834A749693CEEFE0_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/19/3257785/3257785_95BDA9EFC7BC429D86DF9A60EA89ACE0_170119_3257785_Porn_studio__Arizona_man_arrested_for_operating__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen girl stolen at birth reunited with biological parents</title>
      <description>WALTERBORO, SOUTH CAROLINA &#x2014; A girl stolen from the hospital as a newborn baby has just been discovered alive, having lived her entire life with a different identity. 

In July 10, 1998, little Kamiyah Mobley was born at a hospital in Jacksonville, Florida. Eight hours later, she was taken away by a woman posing as a nurse, Gloria Williams. After detectives realized where the girl was living, they reconnected the 18-year-old with her biological parents. On January 14, she was taking selfies with them.

Moments after she was born, her young mother, 16 at the time, was approached by a woman wearing flowered hospital scrubs. The woman happened to be carrying a purse, which the family thought was a bit odd. She whisked the baby away saying it had a fever, and just like that, the baby was gone. Every year, her devastated mother would wrap a piece of birthday cake for her, and leave it in the freezer. 

It wasn&#x2019;t until late last year that a couple of hot tips led detectives to a girl living in a small town in South Carolina. They tracked her down, to find a young woman named Alexis Manigo. The authorities asked her for a DNA sample, and after eventually attaining it with a warrant, they found out they had a match. 

On the same day, the woman the girl had lived her entire life thinking was her mom was arrested by police. The baby-snatcher, 51-year-old Gloria Williams, has been charged with first-degree kidnapping and third-degree interference with custody. She faces life in prison, if convicted.

Now, the teen, who most know as Alexis Manigo, is left to pick up the pieces and figure out how to go forward. She says despite the revelations of her kidnapping, she still has nothing but love for Gloria Williams, the woman who raised her and gave her a happy life. In her eyes, one mistake doesn&#x2019;t change that.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Stolen baby,baby kidnapped,Kamiyah mobley,Alexis Manigo,gloria williams,stolen at birth,baby snatcher,sabrina allen,julian hernandez,missing children</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3257850</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 23:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/392/2A4/3922A45BB9C64E3FA480CF0BF090FCF6_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/19/3257850/3257850_755C9A46BC154DA4AC4856BDC37C9A27_170119_3257850_Teen_girl_stolen_at_birth_reunited_with_biologic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#x2018;Rasta&#x2019; dog one of 69 animals rescued after being neglected for years</title>
      <description>BAD OEYNHAUSEN, GERMANY &#x2014; On January 12 at a vacant home, 62 dogs were seized, found covered in their own filth, the victims of years of neglect. One dog&#x2019;s fur had become so matted, animal care workers almost confused it with a sheep. 

When the sad site was discovered, reinforcements were called in to help give the poor animals some much-needed care. Thorough haircuts from groomers who&#x2019;d donated their services to help the animals quickly did away the urine and feces-drenched coats.

Five guinea pigs were also found in need of help, one whose skin had torn off due to the weight of the excess fur. After getting the spa treatment though, he too appears to be in much better shape. Two rabbits were also rescued, and in total, 69 animals were placed into two nearby shelters. 

A social media plea resulted in donated dog food, shampoos, a shearing machine, and some funds to help until homes could be found for the now-cuddly creatures. Meanwhile, an investigation to identify and locate the person behind this disgusting display of neglect is underway.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Dog grooming,dog fur cutting,how to groom a dog,overgrown dog fur,animal neglect neglected dog,Rasta dog,animal abuse,rasta cat,vlotho,rasta animals,guinea pig matted hair,dog matted hair,dog dreadlocks</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3257823</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D71/DD4/D71DD4B573BA4D81B998687BBFE6EF9A_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/19/3257823/3257823_F955988373784937A15EE8F2E62228A9_170119_3257823____Rasta____dog_one_of_69_animals_rescued_after__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn studio: Arizona man arrested for operating a porn studio as brothel</title>
      <description>PHOENIX, ARIZONA &#x2014; A 52-year-old man in Phoenix has been arrested for running a porn studio as a brothel. 

William J. Hartwell, owner of New Media Studios, thought he was skirting the law by having clients pay for equipment rental to create their own sex scenes while providing &#x201C;free&#x201D; models.

Clients registered online and would pay a receptionist for equipment and studio fees. 

Once inside the studio, clients would be asked to show their genitals to prove that they were not undercover cops. Then the client and a model would photograph or film a short video of whatever fantasy or sexual act the customer desired. The studio reportedly generated $40,000 a month in profits.

A few days after the shoot, customers could return to pick up a USB drive with the photos or videos. About half of the customers actually returned to pick up the video or images, NBC-affiliate KPNX reported.

Hartwell says he was not running prostitution ring. He says he he ran a legitimate business, one that was protected under the First Amendment of the Constitution.

Several female employees who worked at the studio have already pleaded guilty and are expected to testify at Hartwell&#x2019;s trial.

Hartwell faces charges of operating a house of prostitution, sex trafficking, and sexual assault. His trial begins next week.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Porn studio,porn studio and brothel,arizona porn studio,porn shoot,homemade sex videos,first amendment,constitution</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3257785</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 21:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>32</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/537/2D8/5372D86814844970834A749693CEEFE0_8_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/19/3257785/3257785_95BDA9EFC7BC429D86DF9A60EA89ACE0_170119_3257785_Porn_studio__Arizona_man_arrested_for_operating__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico explosion: 29 dead, 72 injured as blast rips through Tultepec fireworks market</title>
      <description>TULTEPEC, MEXICO &#x2014; At least 29 are dead and dozens more were injured after an explosion tore through a well-known fireworks market in Mexico &#x2014; the third such blast to hit it since 2005.

On Wednesday, the open-air San Pablito artisanal pyrotechnics market in Tultepec on the outskirts of Mexico City was bustling with shoppers stocking up on fireworks for the holidays, reports the Chicago Tribune.

An explosion around 3 p.m. set off a chain reaction that ignited nearby pyrotechnics and caused flames to quickly ravage the area.

Twenty-six were killed at the market, while three others died at the hospitals. Seventy-two others are being treated for their injuries, which include severe burns.

Authorities have yet to determine what caused the blast, but have opened an investigation and have promised to punish those responsible.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Mexico explosion,mexico fireworks explosion,mexico market blast,tultepec explosion,tultepec blast,san pablito market,pyrotechnics market,fireworks market,deadly blast</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236178</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 22:54:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>17</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E3E/841/E3E8419F668849F5A5B4A01BD36848D7_4_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236178/3236178_A3B5E10A05A74C9C91D1690CA37DCEAB_161221_3236178_Mexico_explosion__29_dead__72_injured_as_blast_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$50 million fund set up to tear down &#x2018;deadbeat dams&#x2019; in order to restore rivers in the West</title>
      <description>MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; A $50 million fund will be devoted to help communities in the U.S. to remove old and unneeded dams in an attempt to restore rivers.

The funding was provided by the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation to establish a 10 year program in order to remove obsolete dams and restore rivers across the West.

&#x201C;The Open Rivers Fund honors this legacy by boosting local efforts to remove aged dams that have broad support in the community. The safety, economic, and environmental benefits of removing these dams will be immediate and long-term,&#x201D; Hewlett Foundation president Larry Kramer said in a press release.

Three projects will be benefited by the funding, including the removal of the Matilija Dam in Ventura, California; a series of dams in Oregon&#x2019;s Rogue River basin; and the Nelson Dam in Yakima River watershed in Washington.

According to the New York Times, of the more than 80,000 dams in the U.S., more than 26,000 pose high safety hazards, the majority does not serve any real purpose while only about 1,750 produce hydropower.

These deadbeat dams block the natural migration and spawning of some fish, threatening the ecosystem. They also block the movements of nutrients and sediment in the river, which deprives downstream estuaries of nutrient-rich water. The reduced water flow raises the temperature and results in algae bloom.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Deadbeat dams,deadbeat dams in us,deadbeat dams problems,dams problems,open river fund,matilija dam,oregon dams,hydropower</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236148</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 22:13:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>58</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0B5/413/0B5413BB552B40F49EEC95044A5F6E61_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236148/3236148_4BCEB48B16C541C9A9B0E1284DFECBAC_161221_3236148__50_million_fund_set_up_to_tear_down____deadbeat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump inauguration day: Donald made inaugurations most greatest again with incredible line up</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; Donald Trump&#x2019;s inauguration was by far the hottest event on the planet this week, with everyone wanting tickets. 

Demand was so great, Trump had to take out ads on Facebook and other social media to try to give them away, while scalpers lost money.   
The musical talent Trump was able to attract was probably the greatest group of musicians ever assembled, with huge names like The Piano Guys, 3 Doors Down and DJ RaviDrums. 

It&#x2019;s a shame the Bruce Springsteen cover band, B Street Band, had to drop out.  

And what can we say about the crowds? Who would have thought so many people could be packed in front of the Capitol Building? 

Unfortunately for Trump, not everyone in Washington this week was there to show their support for him. 

The swearing-in was probably the greatest oath over given by the greatest human in the history of humans. 

Now that Trump is officially the man in charge, get ready world because America is coming for you.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,President Trump,Trump inauguration,Trump inauguration day,Trump inauguration 2017,Trump inauguration protest,Trump inauguration performers,Trump inauguration speech</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3258945</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 01:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>125</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FEF/CD6/FEFCD6FA97804B9D90C300DFDC741730_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3258945/3258945_D09918E3AD5D4BF48376C80B1B409485_170120_3258945_Trump_inauguration_day__Donald_made_inauguration_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese mile high club fun: airline stewardess snapped giving man special service</title>
      <description>CHINA &#x2014; Photos from a 2015 story that reportedly show a Shenzhen Airlines hostess giving head to a lucky dude have surfaced again.

The image shows the woman giving the guy some serious oral service in an airline aisle.

The oral servicing reportedly took place some time ago, but that hasn&#x2019;t stopped it from once again making the rounds on Chinese social media once again. 

According to reports, prude Chinese netizens are crying foul, with many apparently threatening to boycott Shenzhen Airlines. 

In a tragic twist, however, some unconfirmed reports suggest the publication of the images drove the woman in the photo to suicide.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3259270</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 07:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>22</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/199/19F/19919F232FC14E64ABC7AB60FBDC9142_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3259270/3259270_C5DB3F99C6AE4987AF24BF6EF6FAF52A_170120_3259270_Chinese_mile_high_club_fun__airline_stewardess_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venus Williams gorilla row: ESPN&#x2019;s Doug Adler says he said &#x2018;guerrilla,&#x2019; not a racist</title>
      <description>MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; A TV sports commentator has denied accusations of racism after he appeared to compare tennis star Venus Williams to a gorilla.

ESPN pundit Doug Adler insisted he was describing Williams&#x2019; &#x201C;guerilla&#x201D; tactics during her second round victory over Stefanie Voegele at the Australian Open on Jan. 18, not comparing the 7-time Grand Slam winner to a great ape.

The 59-year-old commentator apologized and said he &#x201C;simply and inadvertently&#x201D; chose the wrong word to describe Williams&#x2019; play, the New York Post reported.

However, that didn&#x2019;t stop an outpouring of outrage on Twitter. New York Times tennis writer Ben Rothenberg said Adler&#x2019;s comments were horrifying and there was no shortage of others who were offended too.

ESPN said in a statement that it had dropped Adler from his remaining assignments, adding that he should have been more careful with his word selection.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Venus williams,doug adler,venus williams gorilla,venus williams guerrilla,tennis,australian open 2017,race relations</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3259193</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 05:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>20</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/00C/CE5/00CCE58FF489434FB4A80BC196AE940B_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3259193/3259193_FC27CCC8C25947DD9A1E3E4E90F39E71_170120_3259193_Venus_Williams_gorilla_row__ESPN___s_Doug_Adler__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pit bull attack: Owner charged after pit bulls maul young boy to death</title>
      <description>ATLANTA, GEORGIA &#x2014; A man in Atlanta has been charged with involuntary manslaughter after his two pit bulls mauled a young boy to death and severely injured a young girl. 

The incident occurred on Tuesday morning, when Logan Braatz, 6, and Syrai Sanders, 5, were walking to F.L. Stanton Elementary School.

Pit bull owner Cameron Tucker didn&#x2019;t know anything was wrong until he stepped out to his fenced backyard and realized his pit bulls were not there. The dogs had gotten out and were chasing the school kids. Neighbors went after the dogs with sticks and bats, but it was too late for Logan, who was mauled to death, while Syrai was badly bitten. 

Logan&#x2019;s mother said a courageous witness carried her son to an ambulance that had just arrived. She said it was already too late for her to do anything to help him.

What prompted Tucker&#x2019;s pit bulls to attack the children is not known. Tucker&#x2019;s attorney said his client was shocked by what happened. He said the dogs were part of the family and were around kids all the time, CBS-affiliate WAFB reported.

Sanders was hospitalized and was listed in good condition on Wednesday.

Tucker was given a $70,000 bond by a judge on Wednesday. The two pit bulls are being held in the custody of animal control.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Pit bull mauling kid to death,pit bull attack,pit bull mauling kid,pit bull kills child,pit bulls,pitbull violence,pit bull mix</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3258928</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 01:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/96D/99F/96D99F4464124F25BE77EE205410F674_3_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3258928/3258928_6AE47168158E48CB90195956275D78D2_170120_3258928_Pit_bull_attack__Owner_charged_after_pit_bulls_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog starts house fire: dog tries to reach treats on stove and starts fire killing cat</title>
      <description>ROLESVILLE, NORTH CAROLINA &#x2014; After searching for clues through the charred remains of a kitchen fire, fire officials came to the conclusion that the dog did it. 

The morning of January 18, fire officials believe one of the pet dogs noticed a box of treats sitting near the stovetop. Determined to get to them, the dog likely turned the knob on one of the burners, sparking the flame. The paper box of treats so close to the burner, it caught fire, and then quickly spread to the rest of the kitchen.

The three dogs in the house managed to survive, along with one of the two cats. Unfortunately, the other kitty perished. No humans were present in the home during the blaze. 

The firefighters figured out it was the dog when they spotted burnt milk bones scattered across the stovetop. The Rolesville Fire Department claims this is a common occurrence, so please, don&#x2019;t underestimate your pets.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,House fire,dog starts fire,dog vs cat,dog gets treats,rolesville,dog stuck in tree,dog eats chocolate,cops chase dog,chihuahua on highway,dog impaled on fence</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3258849</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 00:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7D6/B54/7D6B54D7D4404B5D8EE1B46DB833E437_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3258849/3258849_8A912558ED894D958FBE9A95FEAEE351_170120_3258849_Dog_starts_house_fire__dog_tries_to_reach_treats_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman shoots black teen in the head after complaints about &#x2018;bad blacks&#x2019; on her street</title>
      <description>MACON, GEORGIA &#x2014; A woman is facing charges after a firing multiple gunshots at a group of black teens walking by her front yard, and striking one in the head.

Earlier in the week, Elisabeth Cannon claims the boys had been throwing rocks at her house for months. According to one of the teenagers though, Cannon had been yelling racial slurs at them all week, and accusing them of breaking into her house. 

On January 16, police say Cannon called to notify authorities of the rock-throwing harassment she was being subjected to by the teens, and warned that if they continued, she was going shoot them. Roughly three hours after that call, police report a call came in about a 15-year-old black teenager shot outside Cannon&#x2019;s home. When officers arrived on scene, Elisabeth Cannon admitted to shooting young Vernon Marcus Jr. in the head, and told the cops she didn&#x2019;t mean to actually hit one of them, just scare them. 

Cannon, 47, was arrested and charged with aggravated assault, but is currently out on bond. Meanwhile, the boy she accidentally shot in the head remains in critical yet stable condition at a nearby hospital.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Elisabeth cannon,black teenager shot,vernon marcus jr.,n-bomb,racial slurs,chili&#x2019;s racism,spirit airlines racism,alexandra wright,margarita festival</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3258748</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 23:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>23</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AE4/1EB/AE41EB54B8FB42DF9BD1F7E0FDF309CE_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3258748/3258748_CA9B979A90814DEE8B5F0F0F96D84DE4_170120_3258748_Woman_shoots_black_teen_in_the_head_after_compla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin truck attack: asylum seeker suspect was investigated in terror probe</title>
      <description>BERLIN &#x2014; New information has revealed that the suspect connected with this week&#x2019;s truck attack in Berlin was previously investigated by German police in a terrorism probe.

Documents found inside the vehicle used to kill 12 people in Berlin on Monday have been linked to a Tunisian asylum seeker, reported Reuters. That suspect was identified as Anis Amri, reported the Washington Post. He&#x2019;s said to have left Tunisia seven years ago. 

According to Reuters, Amri initially came to Italy as an illegal immigrant. His father explained to a Tunisian radio station that he spent four years in jail there on accusations of setting a school on fire. 

In 2015, he wound up in Germany, where he was investigated for allegedly planning a robbery to finance a terror attack, but this was dropped due to a lack of evidence, reported the Washington Post

Authorities were also aware that Amri had &#x201C;interacted&#x201D; with ISIS-linked Abu Walaa who was arrested last month for allegedly sending fighters to Islamic State.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Berlin truck attack,asylum seekers,anis amri,berlin terror attack,berlin isis attack,truck isis,tunisia,islamic state,abu walaa</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237306</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 05:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D4E/1AD/D4E1ADC9CDBB4695932B6B00388B222B_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237306/3237306_258654A6767549C0AD26B861A5903D38_161222_3237306_Berlin_truck_attack__asylum_seeker_suspect_was_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Obama bans offshore drilling in portions of Arctic and Atlantic waters</title>
      <description>WASHINGTON &#x2014; U.S. President Barack Obama has invoked a provision in the 1953 Outer Continental Shelf Lands Act to indefinitely block drilling in millions of acres of the Arctic and Atlantic Oceans, a move that is unlikely to be reversed by President-elect Donald Trump when he takes office.

According to a statement published by the U.S. Department of Interior, President Obama&#x2019;s withdrawal decision protects 31 canyons in Atlantic waters, extending from the coast of New England to Virginia.

The Arctic withdrawal encompasses the entire Chukchi Sea and large portions of the Beaufort Sea, leaving just about 2.8 million acres between Kaktovik and Utqia&#x121;vik for oil production.

However, Alaska&#x2019;s three-member congressional delegation sharply criticised the withdrawal plan.

&#x201C;President Obama has once again treated the Arctic like a snow globe, ignoring the desires of the people who live, work, and raise a family there,&#x201D; Los Angeles Times quoted Sen. Lisa Murkowski, chairwoman of the Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources as saying. &#x201C;I cannot wait to work with the next administration to reverse this decision&#x201D;.

Canada also imposed a five-year ban on all oil and gas drilling licensing in the Canadian Arctic, but this decision will be reviewed every five years.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Obama bans arctic offshore drilling,1953 Outer Continental Shelf Lands Act,obama bans drilling,donald trump,arctic withdrawal,atlantic withdrawal,u.s. Energy production</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237150</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 02:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/63F/1A5/63F1A51F1CBD42E1AF78DC4E8F1368E6_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237150/3237150_4E61B5324518436C9676604C4491CEDA_161222_3237150_President_Obama_bans_offshore_drilling_in_portio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rolling guardrail invented in South Korea could save more lives in auto accidents</title>
      <description>SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA &#x2014; A South Korean company has designed a rolling guardrail system that is almost unbreakable in accidents and thus could save lives more lives than traditional guardrails during serious auto accidents.

South Korean company Evolution in Traffic Innovation (ETI) has named the guardrail as the &#x201C;Rolling Barrier System&#x201D;. It consists of rotating barrels made of ethylene-vinyl acetate and metal frames. Ethylene-vinyl acetate has excellent shock absorption power and is more durable than rubber or urethane.The guardrail has a luminescent quality which makes it highly visible to drivers during the night time.

When a car hits the guardrail, the barrels rotate to convert shock energy from the vehicle into rotational energy. As a result, the car is propelled forward back onto the road rather than breaking through the barrier. The upper and lower frames of the guardrail can prevent both large and small vehicles&#x2019; steering systems from suffering functional loss.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Evolution in traffic innovation,eti south korea,south korea rolling barrier system,rolling guardrail south korea,road safety,auto accident prevention</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237119</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/390/B15/390B152BFB4F48F6A34ACA2D93099E47_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3237119/3237119_C3786BD438A84419997F0D4A2F3F9AFB_161222_3237119_Rolling_guardrail_invented_in_South_Korea_could__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport control gaffe sends EVA flight into another plane&#x2019;s flight path</title>
      <description>LOS ANGELES  &#x2014;  An EVA Airlines jet flying to Taipei, Taiwan from Los Angeles International was mistakenly sent into the path of another plane last Friday morning.

An air traffic controller told the EVA pilot to make a 180-degree-left turn when she actually meant right, reported ABC 7. This sent the aircraft into the path of an Air Canada flight and close to terrain on the San Gabriel Mountains.

The controller realized the mistake and told the EVA Airlines crew, who managed to get the plane onto the correct path before anything happened.

The two planes remained the required distance apart, a Federal Aviation Administration official told CBSLA.  However, aviation investigators are still trying to determine how close EVA Airlines plane was to the San Gabriel Mountains. 

The required distance between aircraft and such mountainous regions is 2,000 feet.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Airport mistakes,lax,taipei,eva airlines,FAA,close call,air canada,planes flying toward each other,low flying planes</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236998</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 23:46:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5FE/8F4/5FE8F4FCE4D94CABB19C4AC8619FDC69_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/22/3236998/3236998_04D1341B9B3043F88D16B7A0630BE803_161222_3236998_Airport_control_gaffe_sends_EVA_flight_into_anot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin terrorist attack: ISIS claims responsibility for Christmas market attack</title>
      <description>BERLIN &#x2014; The Islamic State has claimed responsibility for the attack in which a truck plowed into a Christmas market outside Berlin&#x2019;s Kaiser Wilhelm Memorial church, killing at least 12 people on Monday evening.

The announcement came after German authorities released a man whom they arrested on Monday evening, the Telegraph reported. The initial suspect is a 23-year-old Pakistani national, who was arrested at the Tiergarten park near the Christmas market shortly after the attack. He was released due to lack of evidence.

The passenger who was found dead in the cab of the truck has been identified as the original driver of the truck, 37-year-old Polish national Lukasz Urban. He appeared to have been stabbed and shot to death.

According to the Telegraph, Lukasz Urban was delivering steel from Turin, Italy to a warehouse in Berlin on Monday morning. However, the warehouse said they couldn&#x2019;t unload the delivery and told Urban to return on Tuesday. Urban then waited in Berlin with the delivery. He talked to his wife at 3 p.m. before losing contact. It is believed that his truck was hijacked during this time.

The company that owns the truck said the truck&#x2019;s GPS history shows unusual movements from 3:45 p.m. onwards, which indicate Urban was not in control. The truck seemed to have been driven by by someone learning how to drive.

German authorities are urging people to remain &#x201C;particularly vigilant&#x201D; and to report any suspicious movements, as the real culprit is still at large and possibly armed.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Berlin truck attack,berlin attack 2016,berlin christmas market attack,truck plows into christmas market,germany terrorism,berlin attack,germany terrorist</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3236755</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 11:47:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D03/1CA/D031CA7E9C124FCB8F6427F7DB91A5A0_2_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/21/3236755/3236755_8BFCEE183623462CBF5A46DE73A80C56_161221_3236755_Berlin_terrorist_attack__ISIS_claims_responsibil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crocodile attacks: Giant crocodile chomps river wading man</title>
      <description>NORTHERN TERRITORY, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; A 47-year-old man was killed by a crocodile in Australia&#x2019;s Northern Territory on Thursday afternoon.

The man was crossing the East Alligator River in Kakadu National Park with two women. The group are believed to be from the nearby indigenous Gunbalanya community.

Noticing that the man did not make it across the river with them, the two women immediately informed the police, believing he had been attacked by a crocodile 

The man&#x2019;s dead body was found about 2 kilometers downstream. Next to him was a giant crocodile that may have been the one that killed him. Police shot and killed the crocodile as soon as they found the man&#x2019;s body and the crocodile, Sydney Morning Herald reported.

Northern Territory police said the area is a known habitat for saltwater crocodiles, which can grow to be 3 to 4 meters long. Warnings are posted in the area warning people not to enter the water.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Crocodile attacks in Australia,Crocodile attacks in Northern Territory,Crocodile attacks men,crocodile kills men,crocodile attacks,crocodile accidents</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3259386</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 10:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>31</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/97A/2FD/97A2FDF69B104D5E9DA492F6D2D4AE9C_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3259386/3259386_E03DBF1B59354620AFA0DCE5B72D610E_170120_3259386_Crocodile_attacks__Giant_crocodile_chomps_river__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting caught on camera: Jamaican man slaughtered execution-style in Florida</title>
      <description>LAUDERHILL, FLORIDA &#x2014; Police are on the lookout for a ruthless killer who repeatedly shot a man in broad daylight on Martin Luther King Day.

The Belleville News-Democrat reports that Gary Wallock and his girlfriend had just left a seafood market in Lauderhill, Florida, not knowing that a cold-blooded killer was lying in wait just around the corner.

The gunman made his move as the couple stood near their car, running up to Wallock and firing at the back of his head. The 34-year-old tried to make a run for it as more shots rang out, but ultimately fell to the ground.

The shooter kept the bullets coming, repeatedly firing at Wallock for up to 13 times. When the girlfriend tried to run away, she was shot at twice.

Both shots missed, and instead of pursuing her, the killer took off. He got into a getaway car across the street, a blue Nissan Altima which authorities believe had at least two other people inside.

Police estimate that a total of 25 or more shots were fired. They released CCTV footage of the shooting in hopes of getting more information. They later identified the suspect as 26-year-old Trace Obrian Walker.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Shooting caught on camera,shooting caught on video,ambush murder,execution shooting,execution video,execution style shooting,shooting,murder</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3259378</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 10:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>24</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/532/6E2/5326E2417EA842B49234019717549D1A_5_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/17/01/20/3259378/3259378_04E0271CB5CD45F58BB38C53AEE1CCB5_170120_3259378_Shooting_caught_on_camera__Jamaican_man_slaughte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space robot: NASA to launch autonomous satellite repair robot Restore-L in summer 2020</title>
      <description>PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA &#x2014; In the summer of 2020, NASA will launch the Restore-L, a robotic spacecraft tasked with carrying out maintenance and repair on satellites orbiting earth.

NASA awarded a $127 million contract to California-based Space Systems/Loral build Restore-L, reported Vice&#x2019;s technology news website Motherboard.

According to information posted on the Restore-L section of NASA Robotic Servicing Mission website, it will navigate Earth&#x2019;s orbit using a combination of advanced hardware and algorithms at speeds of over 16,000 miles per hour. This technology will allow it to calculate how to connect with a satellite orbiting the earth at the same speed.

Restore-L will use dexterous mechanical arms to service satellites in low earth orbit. This service will reportedly involve a maintenance check and repairs as well as 
redeployment of the satellite. The robotic spacecraft could also upgrade satellites and, all-in-all, prolong the lifespan of those already in space.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Space robot,repair robot,robots in space,nasa,restore-l,space systems,space repair,NASA,NASA robot</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237859</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 23:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>48</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/41E/118/41E1183BA07A45D7A7384892906CA5B3_6_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/23/3237859/3237859_149A903E82BE44F3955592643EA84068_161223_3237859_Space_robot__NASA_to_launch_autonomous_satellite_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fly Transpose: Airbus unveils new concept that allows custom modular plane interiors</title>
      <description>TOULOUSE, FRANCE &#x2014; Airbus has released a new concept called Transpose, which may allow travellers to enjoy dining in restaurants or even go to the gym while flying in the air.

The plane interiors are built in modular sections, and can be tailored to the customers&#x2019; liking, by including a gym or a play zone for children.

The new concept does not require any new plane models. Instead, it makes use of existing cargo planes and their large doors and reinforced floor rails. The modular sections can easily be loaded onto the cargo plane. Once in the plane, they are securely latched on the floor.

Different interiors can be swapped. For example, sleeping compartments for red eye flights can be exchanged for a coffee shop and seating for short daytime flights.

According to Wired, Airbus has already recruited engineers and designers to work on a demonstration module in a full-sized plane mockup. The company says the concept could be fully realized in just a few years.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Airbus transpose,fly transpose,airbus swappable plane interior,airbus modular plane interior,airbus transpose concept,technology</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237834</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 23:39:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>54</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8D4/E2F/8D4E2FC1A1324BFAA5FB675C092D55DB_7_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/23/3237834/3237834_48F719107EA4477EAC0B8A50985B1B0B_161223_3237834_Fly_Transpose__Airbus_unveils_new_concept_that_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian cops thwart ISIS-inspired Christmas Day terrorist bomb plot in Melbourne</title>
      <description>MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA &#x2014; Australian law enforcement said Friday they stopped a terrorist bomb plot that targeted high profile locations and public places in in Melbourne.

According to the Herald-Sun, the plan included attacks on Flinders Street Station, St Paul&#x2019;s Cathedral and Federation Square. It was believed to possibly be planned for Christmas Day.

Police also believe the Islamic State-linked suspects planned to use bombs, and firearms or knives, reported News.com.au.

Officials had reportedly been surveilling the suspects for weeks and carried out a series of raids across the city. Five men were arrested as a result, the BBC reported.</description>
      <tags>video,animation,NAS,Next Animation Studio,Police wins,australian cops,melbourne,isis,islamic state,isis gets arrested,isis,melbourne,terrorism melbourne,malcolm turnbull</tags>
      <guid>MCP1_3237814</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 23:23:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <duration>27</duration>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/55F/87F/55F87FC4B9A240D58D9A20F5E0B8BF83_1_160x90.jpg"/>
      <media:group>
        <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/764/16/12/23/3237814/3237814_3C6EDB9865CA468791F16A457A40A071_161223_3237814_Australian_cops_thwart_ISIS_inspired_Christmas_D_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4" bitrate="2600" width="1280" height="720"/>
      </media:group>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
