<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 19:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3806392</guid>
      <title>Boeing 737 Max anti-stall system activated before Ethiopia crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ADDIS ABABA  Details of the final moments of the doomed Ethiopian Airlines flight have begun to emerge, with investigators believing the plane's anti-stall system contributed to the disaster.According to the BBC, findings reported in the Wall Street Journal show that Ethiopian Airlines flight ET302 had been 450 feet or 137 meters above ground when the aircraft's nose began to pitch down.A pilot was heard saying 'pitch up, pitch up!' before their radio died.The BBC reports that the aircraft, which was carrying 157 people, crashed just six minutes into its flight, killing everyone on board.According to the Wall Street Journal, investigators have determined that the anti-stall system on the 737 Max 8 jet automatically activated before the crash.The New York Time reports that the controversial MCAS anti-stall system takes readings from one of two angle of attack sensors on the plane that aligns itself with oncoming airflow.If it detects that the plane is pointed up at a dangerous angle, it automatically swivels the horizontal stabilizer and pushes the nose down to prevent stalling.The same software is being blamed for the deadly Lion Air crash that killed 187 in Indonesia.According to the BBC, the Lion Air investigation suggested that MCAS malfunctioned, and forced the plane's nose down over 20 times before it plunged into the sea.The Guardian reports that Ethiopian Airlines officials and Ethiopia's transport minister have previously said that their 737 jet flew in a similar pattern to the Lion Air plane.Two safety features could have kept the MCAS in check: the angle of attack indicator displays readings from both sensors, and the disagree light activates when the sensors' data do not match. However, both were sold as optional extras and not included on the crashed planes.According to the BBC, the company has since announced that it will make the disagree light standard on all new 737 aircrafts, and will be redesigning the software to disable MCAS if the sensors receive conflicting data.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 16:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806392/3806392_9D6C112060C14C379606D00D1B2ACCC5_190402_3806392_Boeing_737_Max_anti_stall_system_activated_befor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E9A/268/E9A2686453D46B87D47F991C8215E541.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Ethiopian Airlines, 737 max 8, Boeing 737 max, Ethiopian Airlines crash, Lion Air crash, plane crash, 737 Max 8 MCAS, Boeing anti stall, anti-stall system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806265</guid>
      <title>Migrant worker tracked 
down for abandoning baby in Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW TAIPEI CITY, TAIWAN  A female Vietnamese factory worker in Taiwan was tracked down by police after a man found her newborn baby on the side of a road last Wednesday, reports Asia Times.The baby was found by a 56-year-old Taiwanese man who posted a photo of the newborn girl on a Taiwanese online forum.On the post, the man explains that he was on his way to play Pokemon Go with friends when he noticed a moving box which he assumed was a kitten. When taking a closer look he found it was, in fact, a baby. He contacted the police soon after.According to Asia Times, the police took the child to a hospital for treatment of mild hypothermia. They also tracked down the mother, a 20-year-old Vietnamese migrant worker who works at a factory in New Taipei City. The father had to return to Vietnam earlier this year.She told authorities that her lack of financial stability drove her to abandon her baby, adding that she hid her pregnancy for fear of losing her job or being deported. The woman is now barred from leaving Taiwan.Lennon Wong, leader of Serve the People Association, an NGO that advocates migrant worker rights in Taiwan, told TomoNews that 'theoretically' female migrant workers in factories have the same rights as Taiwanese female workers, however, migrant workers do not have maternity rights.According to the Labor Standard Act, the minimum wage for migrant factory workers and inshore fishermen is NT23,100, roughly $750. Most migrant workers send a large portion of their salaries to their families back home and another percentage to their brokers, who help them find a job.Wong added, "Some migrant workers are lucky enough to hide their pregnancies and give birth, but then they still can't feed and raise their children. Most of them are forced to abandon their child. It's a crime of the system, it's a shame of Taiwan."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/01/3806265/3806265_86E4F588BDEF4855BA33748E57252D85_190401_3806265_Migrant_worker_tracked__down_for_abandoning_baby_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC1/425/DC142590E8B5CC40F6A4E27F99D93BDA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, migrant worker, migrant worker abandon baby, abandoned baby, abandoned child baby in a box, baby box, mother abandons baby, baby, newborn, abandoned newborn]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806258</guid>
      <title>Apple planning implants for third-generation AirPods</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA  Apple may have just dropped its much anticipated second-generation AirPods, but according to Wired, the third-generation iterations could be the real game-changers. According to 9to5Mac, Apple engineers have been working on radical new design method, which involves implanting AirPods subcutaneously into the ear canal.According to TechCrunch, Apple stores in select cities like New York, San Francisco, Los Angeles and Chicago have begun outfitting facilities to handle the implant procedure.The third-generation AirPods will be designed with the new Apple H2 wireless chip, which delivers clearer and crisper acoustic sounds. Battery life lasts approximately 13 hours on a single charge, but when paired with the Apple Pillow wireless charger or AirPoles wireless zones, recharging only takes 10 minutes. The AirPod 3s supports hands-free Siri, as well as the option to change the voice setting to a female Siri, a male Siri, a cis trans non non binary Siri or an otherkin Siri. Apple plans to offer the third-gen AirPods for $1099. The release date has yet to be announced, but many analysts believe they could hit the market as early as late 2019.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 12:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/01/3806258/3806258_71F7527F686D464CA3D614214F77F5D1_190401_3806258_Apple_planning_implants_for_third_generation_Air_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/546/E91/546E91F646832923ED76288BF93C080D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Apple, Apple AirPods, AirPods, AirPods second generation, AirPods third generation, Apple products]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806216</guid>
      <title>China drops hot fire with brand new national anthem</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China has released a brand new national anthem. Out with the old, in with the new:MARCH OF THE SLAVESStay down, continue to be pathetic slaves!With your flesh and blood, let us build a Great Fire Wall!As China faces its orangest peril From each one the urgent call to action comes forth. Stay down! Stay down! Stay Down!Billions of voiceless citizens Braving the CCP's nonsense! March to your own doom!Braving the CCP's nonsense! March to your own doom!March to your doom! March, march to your doom!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 11:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/01/3806216/3806216_A7FE7BED366F4E04B3836FBEBFD21053_190401_3806216_China_drops_hot_fire_with_brand_new_national_ant_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/218/243/21824389C168233F9D7FFC89974C34FF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China National Anthem, Chinese National Anthem, China Official Anthem, March of the Volunteers, China Anthem]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806029</guid>
      <title>Woman with two wombs delivers twins a month after first birth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KHULNA, BANGLADESH  A Bangladeshi woman gave birth to twin bundles of joy just a month after delivering her first child, thanks to a second womb she never knew she had.A doctor told the BBC that Arifa Sultana had given birth to a premature baby boy in late February. Just 26 days later, the 20-year-old complained of stomach pains and was rushed to the hospital, where doctors discovered that she was pregnant with twin babies in a second uterus.An emergency C-section was performed to get the twins  a boy and a girl  out. Luckily both were healthy, and left the hospital with mom after a four-day stay.The official name for having two uteruses is uterus didelphys, and it's apparently not that rare, at least according to one gynecologist in Singapore.He says it's likely that three eggs ovulated and were fertilized at the same time, which then resulted in three embryos.An ultrasound could've easily detected the double wombs and the babies in them, but Sultana was very poor, and never had one done.According to an AFP report cited by the BBC, the woman's husband earns about $95 a month as a laborer. But despite the financial burden of having three newborns, the couple are happy with what they say is a "miracle from Allah."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 06:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/01/3806029/3806029_B1ECB3412D5349A19E80E7BC71A0814B_190401_3806029_Woman_with_two_wombs_delivers_twins_a_month_afte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/37A/AB1/37AAB159219222073646059F3FDD5115.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, woman with two wombs, double womb, uterus didelphys, double uterus, surprise twins, surprise babies, I didn't know I was pregnant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3805946</guid>
      <title>India carries out successful anti-satellite missile test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ODISHA, INDIA  India has successfully used anti-satellite technology on a low-orbit satellite - a milestone its Prime Minister claims establishes the country as a global space power.The Economic Times reports that India launched a DRDO Ballistic Missile Defence Interceptor off the coast of Odisha on Wednesday, as part of Mission Shakti.According to the Times of India, the anti-satellite missile flew 300 kilometers from Earth, shooting down an Indian satellite in low orbit within three minutes of its launch.CNN reports that the U.S. was aware of the test and is currently tracking 270 pieces of debris that resulted from it.According to The Print, Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi said during his national address that debris from Mission Shakti will come down in the coming weeks and burn up safely in the atmosphere.Apart from India, only the U.S., Russia, and China have the capabilities to use an anti-satellite missile.According to CNN, such weapons have raised concerns about the increasing militarization of space, with some also warning that India's latest test might be seen as a provocation by both Pakistan and China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 02:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/01/3805946/3805946_68FDA4A61B8A4920BE44EC10DFDE6680_190401_3805946_India_carries_out_successful_anti_satellite_miss_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/729/6F1/7296F1CFA500296076494D65EE1D9A19.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ASAT, anti satellite missile, anti satellite technology, ballistic missile interceptor, low orbit satellite, mission shakti, india missile, india space power]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806879</guid>
      <title>Taiwan and Japan scramble jets after Chinese incursion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN/JAPAN  Taiwan and Japan both scrambled jets over the weekend after Chinese aircraft  incursions. According to Taiwan's Ministry of National Defense, or MND, two Chinese military aircraft crossed the median line of the Taiwan Strait at 11 a.m.  According to the MND, the Taiwan Air Force scrambled jets to intercept the two J-11 fighter planes. According to a statement issued by the MND, the Chinese planes retreated to the west side of the median line after they were issued a radio warning.  According to CNN, on Saturday, the Japanese Self-Defense Force announced it also scrambled fighters after Chinese aircraft flew between the Japanese islands of Okinawa and Miyako. Japan's Self Defense Forces said in a statement that the Chinese air force had sent four Xian H-6K long range bombers, one Shaanxi Y-8 electronic countermeasures aircraft, one Tupolev Tu-154 MD electronic intelligence plane and at least two fighter jets though international airspace between the two islands on Saturday. According to the AFP, the flights come a week after the U.S. sailed a destroyer and a coast guard ship through the Taiwan Strait, angering Beijing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 13:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806879/3806879_43151F3EB071420ABA296BE5FF02AD7B_190402_3806879_Taiwan_and_Japan_scramble_jets_after_Chinese_inc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/41C/051/41C05171C6856019AF84AE940E7A190F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwan, Japan, China incursion, Taiwan Strait, China J-11 fighter jets, China crosses median line]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806765</guid>
      <title>Chinese marathon runner disqualified for riding a bike</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XUZHOU, CHINA  A Chinese marathon runner was disqualified at the Xuzhou International Marathon for doing something you don't see every day in a raceshe rode a bike. According to Runners World, the race took place last weekend in the eastern province of Jiangsu. Apparently, after the Chinese Forest Gump was spotted on the bicycle, she was told by race officials over and over again to get off the bike. According to Fit World Sport, Blade Not Runner ignored their instructions and proceeded to pedal away. Unfortunately, Not-So-Speedy Gonzales can't ride a bike too well either, because it still took her 5 hours, 38 minutes and 36 seconds to cross the finish line. The marathon organizers announced that Flash had been disqualified and received a lifetime ban. Guess there's always cycling. Too bad she'd probably end up cheating by driving a car. According to Runner's World, since running has become popular in China, so has cheating in marathons. In the Shenzhen Half Marathon just last November, more than 250 runners were caught taking a shortcut.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806765/3806765_143788BB21954411B69932AE3AFD4453_190402_3806765_Chinese_marathon_runner_disqualified_for_riding__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/92B/FC0/92BFC089A3A6FEE00571FBC6AEFF490E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese marathon runner, Xuzhou International Marathon, marathon runner riding bike, marathon runner riding bicycle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806760</guid>
      <title>Chinese tourist tries taking selfie, falls into Grand Canyon instead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRAND CANYON WEST, ARIZONA  A Chinese tourist's plan to take a selfie by the rim of the Grand Canyon fell through, well in this case, moreover.According to David Leibowitz, a spokesman for Grand Canyon West, a 12-person tour group from Hong Kong was visiting the Grand Canyon last Thursday.  According to the SCMP, the group was on day two of a week-long tour of the West Coast when things started to go downhill.   According to AZ Central, while trying to snap a selfie at Eagle Point, adjacent to the Skywalk, a 50-year-old man from Macau accidentally plunged 1000 feet over the edge. AZ Central reports that according to Leibowitz, a helicopter search later located the man's body at the bottom of the canyon. His body was transported to the closest hospital by helicopter. His name has not been released.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806760/3806760_95730EDD98074F78ACDB564579A7D7FA_190402_3806760_Chinese_tourist_tries_taking_selfie__falls_into__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A7E/12D/A7E12D61FA9A19ABD0184351700E6B2B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese tourist, Chinese tourist grand canyon, tourist selfie grand canyon, Macau tourist grand canyon, Chinese tourist selfie, selfie]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806745</guid>
      <title>U.S. residents are being held in Xinjiang detention camps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA   Over 1.5 million individuals are being held in detention camps in China's northwest region of Xinjiang, and legal U.S. residents may be among them.CNN reports that Ambassador at Large for International Religious Freedom Sam Brownback received an unconfirmed report that a California man's father had been detained during travels back to China.Brownback said at a State Department briefing on Thursday that the 75-year-old is a legal U.S. resident who had a number of chronic illnesses, and had not been heard from since he went to Xinjiang.Brownback said he raised the issue with Chinese officials at the UN, who first denied anything, but later said the camps were for "vocational training."An estimate from a 2018 State Department Human Rights report indicates that China had "arbitrarily detained 800,000 to possibly more than two million Uyghurs, ethnic Kazakhs, and other Muslims in  internment camps designed to erase religious and ethnic identities.According to CNN, former detainees claim they were forced to undergo intensive brainwashing sessions, which include studies of Communist Party propaganda.China has tried to pass off the camps as vocational and educational training centers, meant for counter-terrorism, de-radicalization and to fight against a rise in extremism in Xinjiang.Chinese Foreign Ministry spokesman Geng Shuang has fired back saying the U.S. is merely using the Xinjiang issue to meddle in China's internal affairs.He also claims he has no information regarding Americans being held in the Xinjiang camps.The U.S. says they are "committed to providing consular assistance to US citizens in need abroad" but did warn that China doesn't recognize dual nationality, and could stop the U.S. Embassy from stepping in.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806745/3806745_2D19B58D24DD438F9A515C0924694D1B_190402_3806745_U_S__residents_are_being_held_in_Xinjiang_detent_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/401/DE2/401DE222FD0EA2960B5C0CB2DE4FB984.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese camp, Chinese detention camp, Xinjiang detention camp, internment camp, Uyghurs, ethnic cleansing, Xinjiang internment camp]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806739</guid>
      <title>Chicago O'hare Airport getting new terminal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO    Chicago's international airport is set to undergo an $8.5 million expansion, reports DeZeen.A design proposal submitted by a team of architecture firms called Studio ORD has been selected as the blueprint for a new Terminal in Chicago's O'Hare Airport.This will be called 'O'Hare Global Terminal and Global Concourse.' The design features a 'Y' shaped terminal representing the two branches of the Chicago River. It will cover 2.25 million square feet.The terminal's central hub will contain green spaces, restaurants, and a retail area with a high ceiling supported by 'Y' shaped beams spaced roughly 100 feet from each other.The hub's roof is decorated with a large skylight in the shape of a 6 point star, referencing the Chicago flag.The gates and plane hangars will be built on the sides of the terminal. The central section will contain the ticketing, immigration, and baggage retrieval areas for departing passengers.Construction is set to begin in 2023.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806739/3806739_82A44D234B5E45DBB8296CDAB8095C23_190402_3806739_Chicago_O_hare_Airport_getting_new_terminal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6FF/6AF/6FF6AFF3A47CD21E751F8E3EA33A1E9A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, chicago, airport, chicago airport, ohare airport, airport design, architecture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806715</guid>
      <title>Attack to North Korean embassy in Madrid: Explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRID  A group called Cheollima Civil Defense Group is being accused by the Spanish High Court of raiding the North Korean Embassy in Madrid. According to a statement issued by the Spanish High Court, on February 22 at 4:34 p.m. a man named Adrian Hong Chang arrived at the North Korean embassy in Madrid and requested to meet with an attache whom he had previously met.While Chang distracted the embassy staff, members of a group called Cheollima Civil Defense, or CDC, broke into the embassy allegedly carrying machetes, knives, crowbars among other weapons and proceeded to assault and handcuff embassy personnel.After holding the staff in the embassy's meeting room for an hour, three members of the group took the attache to a room in the embassy's basement where they allegedly pushed him to denounce the North Korean government and defect. The attache refused.According to Spanish judge, José de la Mata, who is in charge of the case, staff was held hostage and beaten for hours by members of the group. They took two USB drives, two computers and a cellphone. At 9:00 p.m. most of the group left the embassy in embassy vehicles they had seized. Chang and another member of the group left in another vehicle at the back of the building.Following the raid, Chang traveled to Lisbon where he took a flight to the US. He arrived in Newark, New Jersey on February 23. According to a statement by the Cheollima Civil Defense Group, they have contacted the FBI and handed over information they extracted during the raid.The CDC first made headlines when it helped Kim Jong-un's nephew, Kim Han-sol, escape from Macau after the assassination of his father.In a statement, the group claims this was not an attack and state, quote, 'No one was gagged or beaten. Out of respect for the host nation of Spain, no weapons were used,' adding, 'Some of us will be imprisoned, tortured or killed in the course of this fight.']]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806715/3806715_4C8F36CAABB74CB28BA0BD66F156F78F_190402_3806715_Attack_to_North_Korean_embassy_in_Madrid__Explai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/702/A3D/702A3D4841793AA77362BFD554105414.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north korea madrid embassy, north korea, spain, madrid, n korea, north korea madrid embassy attack, embassy attack, north korea embassy attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806707</guid>
      <title>Nearly 50lbs of plastic found inside dead sperm whale</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SARDINIA, ITALY  A dead sperm whale washed up on the Italian island of Sardinia, where it was found to have 48 pounds of plastic in its stomach, reports CNN. Luca Bittau, president of marine life non-profit SEAME Sardinia, told CNN that garbage bags, fishing nets, tubes and even a bag of washing machine liquid was found in the whale's stomach.The whale was pregnant and was carrying a dead fetus, according to CNN. Bittau explained that the whale had "almost certainly" aborted her fetus before beaching.He said that examinations would be carried out on the whale to determine its exact cause of death. Italian environment minister Sergio Costo reacted in a Facebook post saying that "Are there still people that say that these are not important problems?"He added that he believes this issue takes priority.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806707/3806707_92BAAB1506B047F1BF10681681B306A5_190402_3806707_Nearly_50lbs_of_plastic_found_inside_dead_sperm__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/91F/9F5/91F9F57DDCA6771723E3788D96A337D2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, whale, sardinia, plastic pollution, ocean pollution, marine plastic pollution, ocean plastic pollution, whale sardinia italy, whale sardinia, sperm whale sardinia, plastic pollution in italy, whale with plastic in stomach, whale with plastic inside, whale with plastic in belly]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3806635</guid>
      <title>Global frog die-off caused by deadly pathogen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANBERRA, AUSTRALIA  A disease is wiping out numerous species of frogs the world over, in what scientists say is one of the biggest disasters ever to hit the animal world. Chytridiomycosis, or chytrid, is caused by two strains of the Batrachochytrium fungus and originally found on the Korean Peninsula. The BBC reports that the disease has spread to over 60 countries, likely facilitated by humans through the legal and illegal pet trade.According to the New South Wales Office of Environment and Heritage, chytrid produces spores that can stay in fresh water or moist environments until they find an amphibian host.The fungus attacks keratin in the frog's skin, disrupting its ability to breathe and absorb water. This causes the skin to degrade and get shed off, and eventually triggering cardiac arrest that results in death.According to a paper published in Science, an estimated 501 amphibian species have declined due to chytrid, with 90 confirmed or presumed extinct.The authors say their research highlights the need to take biosecurity risks to wildlife  more seriously in order to prevent new strains from emerging and spreading.They further hope their study can help save surviving frog species, as there is still a high risk of more becoming extinct over the next few decades.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 07:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/02/3806635/3806635_E511B2D2A88D48469E74B442577C111D_190402_3806635_Global_frog_die_off_caused_by_deadly_pathogen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1BD/4E1/1BD4E1B9618B12459375783AFD8F9F3A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, frog disease, frog fungus, frog pathogen, deadly pathogen, frog extinction, frog apocalypse, amphibian apocalypse, global frog die off, frog die off, chytridiomycosis, chytrid, korea]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3807469</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman with malware arrested at Trump's Mar-a-Lago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PALM BEACH, FLORIDA  A 32-year-old Chinese woman carrying two passports and a thumb drive infected with malware gained access to Mar-a-Lago during President Trump's visit to his resort over the weekend, federal court records show. According to the failing New York Times, Yujing Zhang showed up at the Palm Beach resort and got in saying she wanted to use the pool. According to a complaint filed in federal district court in South Florida, Secret Service agents let her in after the Mar-a-Lago security manager on duty verified her last name matched the surname of a member at the club. Too bad the last name Zhang or Changdepending on how you pronounce itis like saying your last name is Smith.After she got in, Zhang told a receptionist she was there for a United Nations Chinese American Association event. Unfortunately, one wasn't scheduled, so Secret Service was called in. During several rounds of questioning Zhang kept changing her story and then became quite "verbally aggressive" and was detained.When they searched her belongings, they found she was in possession of four cellphones, a hard drive, a laptop and a thumb drive infected with malware. She was arrested and charged with lying to a federal agent and gaining access to a restricted area.  According to Business Insider, Trump was reportedly hitting the links nearby at the time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 13:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/03/3807469/3807469_CDEDDE0E314B45DFADECFB70DBEFBA70_190403_3807469_Chinese_woman_with_malware_arrested_at_Trump_s_M_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2A7/67C/2A767CD53A67D3656F392F5B352891BF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Trump, Mar-a-Lago, Chinese woman Mar-a-Lago malware, China woman Mar-a-Lago arrested, thumb drive malware, Yujing Zhang, Yujing Zhang Mar-a-Lago]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3807261</guid>
      <title>Bodycam shows Willie McCoy sleeping before cops shot him</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VALLEJO, CALIFORNIA  Vallejo Police have released body cam footage of the fatal shooting of rapper Willie McCoy, following demands of transparency from his family and friends.According to the New York Times, the February 10 incident began with a 911 call from a Taco Bell employee, who reported an unresponsive man inside a silver Mercedes Benz stopped in the drive-thru.Bodycam video shows that officers who arrived at the scene found McCoy in his car, and spotted a gun in his lap. They soon realized that the gun did not have a magazine in it, with one officer noting that it would only fire a single bullet.Officers at one point hatched a plan to open the car, grab the gun, and pull McCoy out of the vehicle. But finding the doors locked, they instead moved their patrol cars to box in the Benz.According to the Guardian, they didn't attempt to wake him up or talk to him, and instead aimed their firearms outside the car as he slept.Eventually, McCoy began to stir, and can be seen in the video using a hand to scratch his left shoulder. Seconds after yelling at him to raise his arms, all six officers fired their weapons at him.According to USA Today, police had justified the incident in a February news release saying they were 'fearing for their safety.' But the body cam footage shows otherwise.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/03/3807261/3807261_D5C572E7C55547C5BC80D0980FE7F54D_190403_3807261_Bodycam_shows_Willie_McCoy_sleeping_before_cops__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F41/45C/F4145C92AAAE26F65980E022FE088772.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, willie mccoy, police body cam, body cam, taco bell shooting, sleeping while black, police brutality]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3807253</guid>
      <title>U.S. measles count is going to be really high this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, there have already been 387 cases of measles around the U.S. through March. Just for a comparison, there were ONLY 372 cases all of last year. According to the CDC, this year's numbers come from outbreaks in several states, including New York, California, Illinois, Texas and Washington. Here's a shockermost people who get measles have not been vaccinated. In the U.S., most outbreaks have been started by people traveling in countries where measles is more common. According to the WHO, a whopping 83,000 people in Europe had measles in 2018yikes.According to the CDC, the measles vaccine is 97 percent effective. Measles usually won't kill you, but you may feel pretty miserable. The most common symptoms include fever, runny nose, cough, and a rash all over the body for about 10-12 days.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/03/3807253/3807253_7858103CD86D48BABF734A320201AD6F_190403_3807253_U_S__measles_count_is_going_to_be_really_high_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/70B/333/70B333D7C8171B5115F7D0B0F6C27D68.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, measles, measles outbreak, US measles outbreak, CDC, measles vaccination, vaccination shots]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808065</guid>
      <title>New Denmark skyscraper will be the tallest in western Europe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRANDE, DENMARK  The Danish town of Brande [m] is to get a brand new skyscraper designed by architectural firm Dorte Mandrup[n][o][p], reports the Guardian.The project is being helmed by Bestseller, a fashion brand that was founded in the town of Brande.The Tower and Village skyscraper in Denmark will be the tallest building in western Europe once it is complete, The Guardian reports.The 320-meter skyscraper will be taller than London's Shard skyscraper by 10.4 meters. That building is currently western Europe's tallest building.The building will oversee the town, providing a view of the countryside.At the base of the skyscraper, low to mid rise buildings with green roofs will also be included. In a news release from Bestseller, the project's manager Anders Krogh said the skyscraper would "place Brande on the map."He added that the building would also serve as an architectural attraction.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 14:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/04/3808065/3808065_0A3F7AD529314D52A9F5898E0F509A61_190404_3808065_New_Denmark_skyscraper_will_be_the_tallest_in_we_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E90/A50/E90A50DE978258A0B32F255D4A1BECF7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, denmark, western europe, architecture, tiny Danish town, skyscraper denmark, brande denmark skyscraper, Bestseller Tower, bestseller tower denmark, bestseller tower brande, Dorte Mandrup, tallest building in western europe, tallest building in west europe, european architecture, skyscrapers in europe, Danish tower, Tower & Village project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808050</guid>
      <title>Denmark to convert excess renewable energy into gas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FREDERICIA, DENMARK  Denmark's biggest energy firm is planning on building wind farms that will convert their energy surplus into gas, reports The Scientific American. Orsted, Denmark's largest power company, announced it is planning to convert electricity from its wind farms into hydrogen fuel.They plan to achieve this by using electricity from wind farms to power electrolysis plants. These are capable of splitting water into oxygen and hydrogen that can be used as energy.The resulting hydrogen would be stored in a natural gas distribution system and used when there's a shortage of wind and sunlight powering the wind farms.Currently, there are 45 projects in Europe working on making power-to-gas conversion technologies more efficient and affordable. According to a study published in February in the journal Nature Energy, the cost of splitting water has lowered by 40 percent, suggesting the technology could become more accessible in the near future.According to Dutch energy consultancy, Navigant, using gas storage networks to support the European power system could help European consumers save up to $156 billion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 13:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/04/3808050/3808050_FC7A1E0795F240C689CE6CABC251E516_190404_3808050_Denmark_to_convert_excess_renewable_energy_into__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/780/76E/78076E03FF81CD15C10D3EA72B947152.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, renewable energy, alternative energy, growing source of energy, fastest growing source, denmark, europe, wind farm, fossil fuel, gas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808043</guid>
      <title>'It's Not Made in China' bottled water has angered Chinese people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURBAN, SOUTH AFRICA  A South African bottled water company with a hilarious nameIt's Not Made in Chinahas a lot of Chinese people seriously butthurt.According to ABC News, the company has been around since 2014, but only came to the attention of Chinese netizens in a post on their Twitter knockoff Weibo. The original post only got two comments, but started bunching some major panties after it was shared on the pro-CCP speakerbox Global Times and Guancha.cn. The hashtag #ThisWaterIsNotMadeinChina took off with more than 264,000 views on Weibo, while the company received typical lame Chinese backlash on their IG account. Some of the comments were really nasty like "I'm going to strongly boycott it."Another Weibo user said, "If it's not made in China, I won't drink it." Wonder how long that person is going to live for? The company told the SCMP it was surprised that so many Chinese people got angry and never planned to create a controversy. The company said it's now thinking about changing its name. That's unfortunate. It's Not Made in China has such a nice ring to it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 13:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/04/3808043/3808043_C29D5ECCCC534FE4B8514508B0C6353B_190404_3808043__It_s_Not_Made_in_China__bottled_water_has_anger_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE2/9C6/FE29C69DF49796EDF77B87923EA94261.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, It's Not Made in China, It's Not Made in China Still Water, Bottled Water, South African bottled water, It's Not Made In China water, Chinese netizens, Chinese netizens angry]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808504</guid>
      <title>Hybrid super plants could someday grow on Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, FLORIDA  Researchers have developed plants that can produce nanomaterials which then give them extraordinary abilities that could allow them to someday grow on Mars. The study, authored by a team from the University of Melbourne, was presented at an American Chemical Society meeting on April 3.According to the ACS, metal organic frameworks or MOFs consist of metal ions linked to organic molecules, which form highly porous crystals that can store and release chemicals. Potential applications for MOFs range from energy storage to drug delivery.While plants readily absorb water and molecules dissolved in it, MOFs are too big to go into the vascular system.Researchers added metal salts and organic linkers to water, and placed the plants in the solution. Once the MOF precursor molecules are absorbed, they are converted into finished nanomaterials inside the plant's tissue.In experiments, MOF precursor molecules in lotus plant clippings grew into fluorescent crystals that were able to detect concentrations of acetone in the water - fading slightly when it did so.Plant cuttings were also coated with luminescent MOFs and then exposed to UV light for three hours. Those with the coating had less wilting and bleaching.According to the researchers, the MOFs are also able to convert harmful UV into light that's useful for photosynthesis. This is useful for growing crops in space, especially on Mars, where ultraviolet radiation is abundant due to the lack of atmosphere.According to the ACS, the team has not noticed any toxicity in the nanomaterials, and is now working with plant biologists to study how MOFs affect plant growth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808504/3808504_5EBBF2386B314A64865CD50189B8A66C_190405_3808504_Hybrid_super_plants_could_someday_grow_on_Mars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/824/069/8240697AB9E479AE4232037940889B4A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cyborg plants, super plants, nanomaterials, MOFs, metal organic frameworks, plants on Mars, high tech plants, martian plants, martian crops]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808498</guid>
      <title>Man tries to retrieve Snoopy toy, gets arm stuck in claw machine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAINAN, TAIWAN  A man in Tainan grabbed the spotlight after finding himself in a pretty tight spot while attempting to retrieve his claw machine winnings.According to UDN, the man, surnamed Tu, got lucky with a claw machine and was about to be rewarded with a big old stuffed Snoopy. Unfortunately, Snoopy was too big to make it all the way down the chute.Tu called the arcade owner, and got him to agree to let him take matters into his own hands, literally, by reaching up into the hatch. It didn't go well.A couple of cops who happened to be nearby found him lying on the floor with his arm stuck in the machine.The cops had called firefighters to help extract Snoopy and friend, but the arcade owner soon arrived and unlocked the machine. Tu's arm had some contusions and redness, but it wasn't serious enough to warrant a hospital visit.The grabber machine owner also confirmed to police that he saw Tu's win on video, and got a call from him asking for permission to manually extract the toy, so no charges were filed.A grown man going through that much effort for a Snoopy doll may be kind of embarrassing, but hey, it could have been worse.At least the dude didn't get stuck in a machine that was giving out adult stuff, which apparently is pretty common in Taiwan.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 12:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808498/3808498_18DD9FB3F0964032B941462AB4E7248B_190405_3808498_Man_tries_to_retrieve_Snoopy_toy__gets_arm_stuck_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1C7/BE7/1C7BE752F7C40811ED6C5F117240AA83.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man stuck in claw machine, snoopy doll, snoopy stuffed toy, taiwan claw machines, arcade games, claw crane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808455</guid>
      <title>China to install AI surveillance in prison</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  One of China's largest prisons is almost finished installing an AI system that will keep prisoners in check 24/7, reports the South China Morning Post.China's Yancheng Prison will be using an AI system connected to a network of cameras and sensors that will track inmates' movements and behavior. The system will alarm guards if it detects unusual activities.The cameras and sensors will use facial recognition technology and movement analysis to monitor prisoners. Daily movements will be sent as a report and stored in the AI system.One of the developers of the system told the SCMP that it can track the activity of multiple individuals without the assistance of a human guard, no matter the size of the prison's population.Chinese experts think the AI network will make prison escapes harder because even if prisoners are able to bypass human guards, they will not be able to evade the AI surveillance system.Having prisoners in an AI-controlled panopticon may sound like a good idea but it also has some ethical downsides. According to Psychology Today, being under mass surveillance raises levels of anxiety and stress among those being observed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808455/3808455_00ABECA4331A443793459E3538F208A0_190405_3808455_China_to_install_AI_surveillance_in_prison_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/29D/FFE/29DFFE9BD0E7D64CD794F6C20B553F4B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china prison, china surveillance, china ai system, china ai, facial recognition, surveillance, surveillance state, china surveillance, police state, sharp eyes project, china surveillance system, total surveillance, social credit, sesame credit, china, beijing, china police, china prison]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808436</guid>
      <title>Chicago building the tallest and fastest elevator in North America</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Chicago is building North America's tallest and fastest elevator along with a glass cabin at the top of the Aon Center, reports Fast Company.Chicago's Aon Center will be featuring the fastest and tallest elevator in North America as well as a glass cab at the top of the building.The elevator will be built into the northwest corner of the building. It will be able to ascend 305 meters or 1,000 feet in roughly 60 seconds.The elevator takes visitors to the Aon Center Observatory which will feature a 360-degree observatory, a restaurant and an activity center.The glass cabin at the top of the building will be called 'Sky Summit'. The cabin unfolds and hangs passengers inside it over the edge of the tower.Developers claim both attractions could bring roughly 2 million annual visitors. According to Archinect News, construction of the elevator begins this spring.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808436/3808436_B08680D4412847088A4213726B3D23CF_190405_3808436_Chicago_building_the_tallest_and_fastest_elevato_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E2C/EDF/E2CEDF78AE0205D33077AF0D77AA45C7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fastest elevator, tallest elevator, fastest, tallest, chicago, aon center, chicago aon center, crazy buildings, buildings, sky summit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808420</guid>
      <title>Komodo Island closing so people can't keep stealing dragons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KOMODO ISLAND, INDONESIA  The Indonesian government is temporarily closing Komodo Island to tourist because idiots keep stealing komodo dragons off the island to sell them on the black market. According to Tempo, authorities announced the island would be temporarily off limits starting in January 2020. According to a government spokesperson, the ban is expected to stay in effect for at least a year. The decision comes in response to an alleged smuggling ring that was busted with 41 komodo dragons by the East Java Police. Apparently the smugglers were trying to sell the dragons on the black market for over $35,000 a piece. The East Java Police told the Jakarta Post that the suspects were intending to ship the komodo dragons to three countries in Southeast Asia via Singapore. Looks like the smugglers were selling the dragons over Facebook. And that's why people can't have nice things.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808420/3808420_D15BF5078DA14EBB8E6D4853C89346D5_190405_3808420_Komodo_Island_closing_so_people_can_t_keep_steal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4C8/1DE/4C81DEFFE366C9927A9D0BF59826DF22.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, komodo dragon, komodo island, komodo island closed to tourists, komodo island closed 2020, komodo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808416</guid>
      <title>Dutch container search stumbles on shipwreck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUTCH SEA  Dutch salvage teams looking for shipping containers that fell off a ship during a storm discovered a 16th Century shipwreck on the North Sea floor, according to the BBC. The ancient wreck was found during a search for missing cargo that fell from the ship MSC Zoe during a January 2 storm in the North Sea, when 345 containers fell off the vessel. According to the BBC, as salvage teams searched the Dutch North Sea, their sonar equipment discovered an unknown object on the seafloor a few miles to the north of Terschelling Island in the Wadden Sea. The salvage teams recovered some copper cargo, three wooden planks and 12 wooden ribs from the ship's frame. According to the BBC, experts believe the 30 meter by 7 meter ship could have been transporting as much as 5,000 kilograms of copper. According to the country's science and culture ministry, "it's the oldest sea-going ship ever found in Dutch waters.""An immediate archaeological survey was started and researchers determined the wood dated from 1536," the ministry said. It also added that the ship was built around 1540 during the reign of Charles V.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808416/3808416_5ABA2969EBA34C91AC6D8E6C5D9A376F_190405_3808416_Dutch_container_search_stumbles_on_shipwreck_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/907/B9D/907B9D31B5AEA086F6F2A07A77AA6723.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dutch shipwreck, shipwreck, Dutch sea shipwreck, MSC Zoe missing containers, container ship]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808353</guid>
      <title>Longer surveillance video shows Nipsey Hussle shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Grammy-nominated rapper and community advocate Nipsey Hussle was fatally shot on Sunday, in an incident that the Los Angeles Police Department says arose from a personal dispute.Hours after surveillance footage of the shooting made its way online, a longer version emerged that gave a clearer view of the shooter. Here, we recreate what went down based on that video.CBS reports that on March 31, rapper Nipsey Hussle and three other men were standing in front of his clothing store in L.A.'s Hyde Park.According to the LAPD, gang member Eric Holder approached the group several times, engaging them in conversation before leaving.According to CNN, Holder returned around 3:20 p.m. armed with a handgun and opened fire at the group. Surveillance video from an adjacent business shows Hussle and another man fall to the ground, as the others run from the gunfire.In the video, the shooter appears to walk away, before then coming back to shoot Hussle a second time, and then a third. He kicks the rapper after the third shot, then flees the scene. CNN reports that Hussle died from gunshots to the head and torso. Two others were wounded.According to the LAPD, Holder ran down an alley following the shooting, and got into a waiting car driven by a woman, which then sped away.The LA Times reports that the woman turned herself in after news of the shooting broke out, claiming she didn't know what Holder did when she picked him up. Holder was later arrested in the Bellflower area, after being spotted by a resident.TMZ, citing 'multiple sources,' says Holder and Hussle had a tense exchange before the shooting. Holder allegedly sought revenge after feeling disrespected when Nipsey asked him if he had snitched to the cops in the past.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808353/3808353_3D5707F7E3184280BBA4AB72C7B33EBC_190405_3808353_Longer_surveillance_video_shows_Nipsey_Hussle_sh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BB1/796/BB179614C0C930B2E6D55038FE4915DB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nipsey hussle, nipsey hussle shooting, surveillance video, surveillance footage, caught on camera, CCTV, CCTV footage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3808334</guid>
      <title>Mick Jagger to get heart valve replacement surgery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  Rolling Stones frontman Mick Jagger is set to undergo heart surgery, following the postponement of the band's North American tour.Reuters reports that according to U.S. website Drudge Report, the 75-year-old rock icon will be getting heart valve replacement surgery in New York this week. Here's what that entails.According to the British Heart Foundation, there are four valves in the heart that make sure blood flows through the heart in the correct direction.When a valve is damaged, it may need to be replaced when it either does not close properly and leaks blood, or has become narrowed and obstructs blood flow. Otherwise, it could get worse and may lead to heart failure."According to the NHS, valve replacement surgery is carried out under general anaesthetic.During the procedure, a 25-centimeter-long incision is made down the middle of the breastbone to access the heart. A heart-lung bypass machine is attached to take over pumping blood to the rest of the body, and the heart is stopped. Once the vessel is clamped and opened up, the damaged valve is removed and replaced with a new one that is either artificial or biological. The heart is then restarted using controlled electric shocks, and the new valve checked before the heart-lung bypass machine is removed and all incisions are closed."Patients who have had a valve replaced typically stay in the hospital for a week, and take two to three months to fully recover.According to the Telegraph, Jagger's doctors have said he is expected to make a complete recovery after his surgery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/05/3808334/3808334_AD7B41D935264D36A5A972F45C38A5B8_190405_3808334_Mick_Jagger_to_get_heart_valve_replacement_surge_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/496/A0C/496A0C231839462BDBDFC12DBF78CE9D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mick jagger, rolling stones, rolling stones tour, heart valve replacement surgery, heart surgery, heart valve replacement, aortic valve replacement]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810230</guid>
      <title>French fighter jet ejects passenger by accident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAINT DIZIER, FRANCE  A civilian flying in a French fighter was treated to something you don't experience every dayhe was accidentally ejected from the plane as it took off.  According to the Aviationist, a 64-year-old man got to test out the ejector seat first hand as the French Air Force twin-seat Rafale B fighter was taking off from Saint-Dizier 113 air base on Mar. 20. The aircraft was supposed to be going on a training mission. The pilot was able to land the aircraft safely with minor injuries to his hands caused by the broken canopy.  According to Aerotime, the unidentified human cannonball was hospitalized after he injured his back as he parachuted back down on to the runway.But according to a spokesperson for the French Air Force his health, "is not a cause for concern."Part of the French Rafale fleet was grounded as a precautionary measure for several days as the incident was investigated. The air force is still unclear what triggered the ejection. It may have been a voluntary ejection, an involuntary one or even a mechanical failure. According to the Aviationist, the Rafale is equipped with the MkF16F ejection seat, which features two rocket motors for double the fun.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 11:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/09/3810230/3810230_CB288A53E4354205B3BB5C7CEBEBDAFC_190409_3810230_French_fighter_jet_ejects_passenger_by_accident_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/224/572/22457200F96B5FB2C3B0B30136DFFF72.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ejector seat, ejector seat malfunction, passenger ejects on accident, passenger ejected accidentally, Rafale passenger ejected]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810204</guid>
      <title>Chinese students scam Apple out of $900,000 in iPhone scheme</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND  Two Chinese college students allegedly scammed Apple out of almost $900,000 by trading in fake iPhones for real ones, according to NPR. According to federal prosecutors, Yangyang Zhou and Quan Jiang, engineering students in their early 20s attending Oregon State University and Linn Benton Community College, took part in an elaborate scheme that involved friends and family, a whole mess of nonsensical pseudonyms and a ton of mailing addresses. According to a criminal complaint filed in Portland, the two men smuggled thousands of knockoff iPhones from China and then filed warranty complaints with Apple, saying the phones were busted and wouldn't turn on. Apple would then replace the fakes with brand new iPhones in most cases, which the duo would send back to China to be resold for a profit, of which they got a cut. According to court documents, Zhou and Jiang, who were both in the U.S. on F-1 student visas at the time, tried the scam with 3,069 iPhones from April 2017 through March 2018. Looks as if the two were successful half of the time. Apple told investigators that 1,493 warranty claims were linked to Jiang and/or Zhou were processed and replacement devices were issued at loss of $600 per iPhone. According to authorities, Jiang's mother collected his cut in China and then put the money into a U.S. account. The heat came down when Customs and Border Protection seized more than five shipments of fake iPhones addressed to them. Jiang has been charged with trafficking counterfeit goods and wire fraud. Zhou has been charged with submitting false or misleading information on export declaration and faces up to $10,000 and five years in the slammer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 10:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/09/3810204/3810204_DBB4BF7B88C54E20B22ABC22CE51CC08_190409_3810204_Chinese_students_scam_Apple_out_of__900_000_in_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/532/61B/53261BB8A219C04AEB309E04343DC831.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fake iPhone, fake iPhone China, college students iPhone scam, Chinese college students]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810172</guid>
      <title>CCTV shows vandal motorbike rider rammed by car in hit-and-run</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PINXTON, UNITED KINGDOM  Derbyshire police have released CCTV footage showing the moment a motorbike rider was rammed by a car into a parked van.According to the Derbyshire Constabulary, the incident, which happened a year ago on June 15, left rider Ashley Wood unconscious on the road with serious injuries.The footage not only captures Wood's accident, but also his shenanigans minutes before the collision.The 29-year-old had been wreaking havoc in Pinxton, kicking off car wing mirrors and speeding along the pavement. Police say he was also driving under the influence of alcohol and drugs, and with no license or insurance during his criminal spree.At some point, Wood is seen zipping past an orange Fiat Punto on the road, which promptly makes a U-ey.The Punto drives after him before eventually ramming him head-on into a parked van. It then backs up and mounts the pavement in a dramatic escape.Wood spent a week in the hospital as a result of the collision, and later charged for his offenses. He plead guilty to all charges and was recently sentenced to 8 months in the slammer, suspended for 18 months. He's also facing a 12-month driving ban.The orange Punto that hit Wood was later found burnt out in a layby, but police have yet to figure out who the driver was. They say the investigation is ongoing, and that the video was released as an appeal for information.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 10:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/09/3810172/3810172_7B0850994DA64844A6855516F8A4DEC0_190409_3810172_CCTV_shows_vandal_motorbike_rider_rammed_by_car__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8FF/D2A/8FFD2A92A9F58DF1BDF6F2374AB80817.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, CCTV caught on camera, car collision, drunk driving, car hits motorcycle, car hits biker, accident caught on cam, police CCTV, hit and run]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3809997</guid>
      <title>Arkansas men don bulletproof vest, hilariously shoot each other</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BENTONVILLE, ARKANSAS  According to the Northwest Arkansas Democrat Gazette, Charles Eugene Ferris, 50, and Christopher Hicks, 36, were arrested on Monday for aggravated assault. According to a probable cause affidavit, Benton County Sheriff's Deputy Dorian Hendrix was at Mercy Hospital around 11 p.m. on Sunday to investigate a man who had been shot while wearing a bulletproof vest. At first, Ferris told po po that he was protecting a man he called his "asset," but then his wife told them what actually happened. Turns out Ferris had been wearing a bulletproof vest for some reason while drinking on the outside deck with their neighbor Hicks. Ferris then told Hicks to shoot him, so Hicksbeing the good friend he isobliged by unloading a single shot from a .22 caliber semi-automatic rifle center mass.Hicks then put the vest on, but unbeknownst to him, Ferris was angry about getting shot, even though he had asked for it, so what did he do? He unloaded the remaining five rounds into Hicks' back. Luckily, none of the round penetrated the vest. Ferris was released from the hospital and arrested, while authorities went to Hicks' residence and busted him too. According to the affidavit, deputies also seized the rifle and vest. Tango and Cash are due back in court May 13.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 05:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/09/3809997/3809997_81A6E57FFF124C53A71DE8BCC05A752B_190409_3809997_Arkansas_men_don_bulletproof_vest__hilariously_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/212/F5E/212F5E25BDD461ED6A980754F5113A2E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bulletproof vest, bullet resistant vest, Arkansas men, Charles Eugene Ferris, Christopher Hicks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810916</guid>
      <title>U.S. sails amphibious assault ship in disputed South China Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST PHILIPPINE SEA  The U.S. sailed its USS Wasp amphibious assault ship near a strategic reef claimed by Manila and Beijing that lies 230 km off the Philippine coast, reports the Japan Times. According to ABS-CBN News, Filipino fishermen near the Scarborough Shoal spotted the U.S. ship on Tuesday. Fishermen said they saw U.S. aircraft landing and taking off from the ship, about 5 km away from the fishermen's boat. According to the Japan Times, a U.S. military spokeswoman would not confirm or deny  the Wasp's presence, but did confirm that the ship "has been training with Philippine Navy ships in Subic Bay and in international waters of the South China Sea … for several days."Scarborough Shoal, which is claimed by the Philippines, Taiwan, and China, was seized by Beijing in 2012 after an extended standoff with Manila. According to the Japan Times, the Wasp's presence in the South China Sea will likely draw attention from Beijing as it is paired with U.S. Marine Corp's F-35B Lightning II stealth fighters. The F-35B is the short takeoff and vertical landing variant of the fighter jet. Scarborough Shoal is of strategic significance to China in order to solidify its grip over the South China Sea. In an effort to push back against Chinese behavior near Scarborough, the U.S. Navy sent a guided-missile destroyer within 12 nautical miles (22 km) of the site in January of last year as part of its larger "freedom of navigation operations."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 13:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810916/3810916_53DFCABA9CFF4FA296AA286411C343E7_190410_3810916_U_S__sails_amphibious_assault_ship_in_disputed_S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6A4/193/6A419343D6EDD00429879D2687C93658.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, South China Sea, Scarborough Shoal, Philippines, USS Wasp, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810906</guid>
      <title>Man with stage 4 cancer wins $250,000 in North Carolina lottery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHARLOTTE, NORTH CAROLINA  A man who was recently diagnosed with stage 4 liver cancer has big plans after hitting the lottery jackpot.According to the Charlotte Observer, Richard Beare won $250,000 in the North Carolina Education Lottery two weeks ago, from a ticket he got at a QuikTrip store. The retired mechanic said in a state press release that he rarely plays, but stopped to get a Powerball ticket after his wife told him to, since the jackpot was pretty high.He ended up also getting four scratch-off Carolina Black tickets, and won the prize on the last ticket.Beare had to get the store clerk to explain the game to him, and when he told her he just won 250 grand, she was super shocked.The $250,000 prize money has whittled down to $176,876 after taxes, but it's still more than enough for Beare to take his wife on a dream vacation to Italy, since she's always wanted to visit.Who knew a random stop could lead to some incredibly good fortune?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810906/3810906_9F744D520F6F4BA9B5F9CB15E3945559_190410_3810906_Man_with_stage_4_cancer_wins__250_000_in_North_C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE7/06A/BE706A12F0DDFABF2C8A5E22451C209E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north carolina lottery, lottery winner, liver cancer, stage 4 cancer, stage 4 liver cancer, dream vacation, Italy vacation, scratch off lottery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810816</guid>
      <title>Timeline and aftermath of Christchurch shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHRISTCHURCH, NEW ZEALAND  The Australian man who carried out twin mosque attacks in Christchurch last month has been formally charged with 50 counts of murder.Here, we see how the deadliest mass shooting in modern New Zealand history unfolded, and what happened after. The New York Times reports that just after 1:30 p.m. on March 15, Brenton Tarrant emailed a 74-page manifesto filled with anti-immigrant and anti-Muslim ideas to 30 people, including New Zealand Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern.Minutes later, according to the BBC, Tarrant began live-streaming from a head-mounted camera. Footage shows him driving to the Al Noor mosque in Christchurch, and selecting a weapon from the boot of the car.At around 1:40 p.m., he walked into the mosque through the front entrance and opened fire at people inside, who were there for Friday prayers.Based on the footage, the BBC reports that Tarrant opened fire inside the women's prayer hall, and then the men's before changing weapons in his car. He then re-entered the mosque and shot at bodies in the men's hall before leaving.From Al Noor mosque, Tarrant drove five kilometers to another mosque in Linwood.Linwood's acting imam Latef Alabi told Stuff that he was leading prayers for a congregation of over 80 when he heard a voice outside at around 1:55 p.m.He looked out the window to find a man holding a large gun and bodies on the ground, and told everyone to get down.According to the New York Times, Tarrant was firing through a window when Abdul Aziz, a member of the congregation, ran out and threw a credit card machine at him.Aziz followed the attacker and picked up a discarded gun. He later threw the gun at Tarrant's windshield, prompting him to drive away.Stuff reports that police officers managed to force Tarrant's car from the road soon after. Video taken by a resident shows officers dragging the suspect out of the vehicle and taking him into custody.According to the BBC, a total of 42 casualties were reported in the Al Noor Mosque, while eight were killed at the Linwood mosque shooting.According to the New Zealand Police, Tarrant is facing 50 murder and 39 attempted murder charges, and is currently being held in a maximum security prison in Auckland.Tarrant will undergo routine mental health tests before his case proceeds. He is due back in court on June 14.CNN reports that in the aftermath of the attack, the New Zealand government has introduced a gun control bill that would ban military-style semi-automatic guns, assault rifles, and related components.Existing gun owners have until September to hand in their weapons and be compensated in a buyback scheme.The incident has highlighted the responsibility of social media platforms to stamp out online hate speech. Facebook announced in late March that it will ban all "praise, support, and representation" of white nationalism from its platform.Australia has also passed strict new laws that aim to stop the spread of violent content online, imposing fines and jail time if videos are not removed quickly.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 11:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810816/3810816_A2D3D0AD7C2C4F328D716FE2D7D16AEA_190410_3810816_Timeline_and_aftermath_of_Christchurch_shooting_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0CA/E6A/0CAE6A55FD4BC77571D9E9F0A3550883.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Christchurch shooting, Christchurch attack, mosque shooting, mosque attack, New Zealand, gun control, gun laws, social media]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810778</guid>
      <title>E-cigarette explosion tears chunk off Tennessee man's cheek</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CORDOVA, TENNESSEE  A Tennessee man is taking to court several companies involved in the selling and manufacturing of an e-cigarette that exploded in his mouth.According to a lawsuit cited by the Memphis Commercial Appeal, David Bishop had been using the device last May when the lithium battery inside blew up.The blast broke several of his teeth and tore a chunk of flesh from the upper lip to the lower cheek. He also got chemical burns to his face, mouth, tongue, and hands from battery acid. The 25-year-old survived but had to get 65 stitches in his face and missed weeks of work. In his lawsuit, he's seeking monetary damages against Create a Cig, where he bought the vape pen, Cali-based e-cigarette seller VGOD, and a U.S. affiliate of LG who supposedly made the batteries.Both Create a Cig and VGOD claim Bishop brought the explosion on himself, but didn't really specify how. LG USA, meanwhile, is asking to be dismissed from the suit saying it doesn't make batteries.Consumer Reports wrote in a 2016 article that lithium ion batteries are relatively safe, though in some cases a failure can cause the battery to heat up to 1,000 degrees and go kablam.And while flat lithium batteries just catch fire, the e-cig's cylindrical structure tends to propel exploding batteries across the room like bullets or small rockets.The report does say e-cigarette explosions are rare, but pretty deadly when they do happen, and have so far killed two people in the U.S.The U.S. Fire Administration recommends sticking to the vape pen charger instead of just plugging it into any old USB port, which could lead to disaster.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 10:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810778/3810778_CE2A6345CA2B4496B2856BC7F0B2C715_190410_3810778_E_cigarette_explosion_tears_chunk_off_Tennessee__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C4F/C1C/C4FC1CCEC3932583D0840ED153AFFEC7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, e-cigarette, e-cigarette blows up, vape pen blows up, vape pen, vaping, lithium battery, exploding battery, overheating battery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810749</guid>
      <title>Asian supermarkets using banana leaves instead of plastic bags</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THAILAND / VIETNAM  Supermarkets in Thailand and Vietnam are literally going green with their packaging, replacing plastic wrap with banana leaves. According to a Facebook post, Rimping supermarket in Chiang Mai, Thailand is at the front lines of the battle against plastic. The now viral photos show vegetables like chives, peppers and green peppers wrapped in banana leaves instead of some styrofoam and plastic wrap. According to VN Express, after seeing the Thailand post get so much traffic, supermarkets in Hanoi, Saigon and Ho Chi Minh City followed suit.According to a Lotte Market spokesperson in Ho Chi Minh City, the leaves are being used as a test, but if successful, it could be extended to other vegetables and meats. According the VN Express, every little bit helps, especially as Vietnam is currently fourth on the global list of ocean plastic polluting nations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 09:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810749/3810749_E1FC0E1407544B5DB4F60CC2E6EA64B0_190410_3810749_Asian_supermarkets_using_banana_leaves_instead_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/449/F55/449F5522BF0A5BC69874BA38A32069E1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, banana leaves, banana leaves packaging, plastic alternatives, green packaging alternatives, eco packing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810742</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong court finds 9 Umbrella Movement protesters guilty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  A Hong Kong Court has convicted nine prominent protesters over their role in the "Umbrella Movement" in 2014, The South China Morning Post reports.The democracy activists were charged with public nuisance and could face up to seven years in prison, The New York Times reports.The Umbrella Movement was a 79-day long democracy protest lasting from September to mid-December in 2014 against Hong Kong authorities and the Chinese government. Protestesters used yellow umbrellas during the movement and rallied against China's influence in the city. This was because the Chinese Communist Party decided to vet all potential leadership candidates in Hong Kong elections. As a result, thousands of activists occupied Hong Kong Central in protest.The New York Times reports the democracy activists were charged with public nuisance and could face up to seven years in prison.According to the South China Morning Post, Judge Johnny Chan said on the founders of the movement professors Benny Tai, Chan Kin-man and Pastor Chu Yiu-ming were found guilty of one count of conspiracy to create public nuisance.Judge Chan said the protesters had created a public nuisance by blocking roads and causing obstructions throughout the city.The two professors were also charged with instigating others to commit public nuisance.The BBC quotes Tai as telling reporters that "No matter what happens today… we will persist on and … not give up."Hong Kong Legislators Tanya Chan, Shiu Ka-chun along with student leaders of the movement Tommy Cheung, Eason Chung and Former Hong Kong Democratic Party lawmakers Lee Wing-tat were all convicted of one count of inciting others and one count of inciting protests themselves.In a statement by Chris Patten which was cited by the New York Times, the last governor of Hong Kong's colonial era, said the verdict was "appallingly divisive" and called it "vengeful."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 09:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810742/3810742_05E2C94B09E44EA8834B238C0D4A6D29_190410_3810742_Hong_Kong_court_finds_9_Umbrella_Movement_protes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7BE/990/7BE9903210EB9DF3E0093FFDBE1423B5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hong kong, hong kong umbrella protest, hong kong umbrella movement, yellow umbrella hong kong, hong kong yellow umbrella movement, umbrella riots hong kong, hong kong protests, umbrella movement, hong kong occupy central]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810735</guid>
      <title>European Parliament backs law banning single-use plastics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS  The European Parliament is set to implement a plastic ban that would restrict the use of single-use plastic items in the next two years, Reuters reports.Lawmakers voted last week in favor of banning a total of 10 single-use plastic items including cutlery, straws and balloon sticks.Disposable containers made out of expanded polystyrene as well as products made out of oxo-degradable plastic will also be banned in order to cut down on marine plastic pollution, according to a European Parliament news release.According to the European Commission,  80 percent of litter in the ocean was found to be plastic.By the year 2025, it will be mandatory for plastic bottles in Europe to contain at least 25 percent of recycled content.The legislation also set a target of collecting and recycling 90 percent of the single-use plastic bottles by 2029.Companies in Europe will be required to teach users how to correctly dispose of items such as tobacco filters, plastic cups and wet wipes, CNN reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 09:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810735/3810735_AE583C21E4BE48D9BE884EA446723EA4_190410_3810735_European_Parliament_backs_law_banning_single_use_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EA1/A1F/EA1A1FF81DAC33DED402B0C0B360CAE6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, banning plastic, EU, european union, european union plastic ban, plastic ban in Europe, banning plastic in europe, single-use plastic, eu bans single use plastic, eu parliament bans single use plastic, eu bans all single use plastic, plastic goods, disposable plastic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810516</guid>
      <title>Rhino poacher trampled by elephant, eaten by lions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH AFRICA  A poacher who snuck into a national park in South Africa probably won't be sneaking back out. That's because he was trampled by elephants, and then served as dinner to a pack of hungry lions, according to BBC. Apparently, police picked up four poachers running for their lives outside Kruger National Park, according to the Letaba Herald.  Looks as if five poachers were trying to hunt an endangered rhino, when an angry elephant charged and sent one of them six-feet under.When they learned of the elephant attack, rangers were sent out to search for the man. It took several days for them to finally locate his bodywell, what was left of it. A pride of lions had gotten to the body. The rangers were able to find some clothes and the guy's dismembered dome.  The Park's managing executive Glenn Phillips reminded people, "entering Kruger National Park illegally and on foot is not wise, it holds many dangers and this incident is evidence of that."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 03:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810516/3810516_AE3E5FBC722F4FEA83765E33639A511D_190410_3810516_Rhino_poacher_trampled_by_elephant__eaten_by_lio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/69F/BAF/69FBAF55E592694E9B50BB6FE5528DEF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, poacher, South Africa Kruger National Park, South Africa, Kruger National Park elephants, lions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810494</guid>
      <title>Massive alligator caught in South Florida</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JUPITER, FLORIDA  Police in Florida were called to remove a 750-pound alligator from Jupiter Commerce Park last week.A business owner near the park called on the authorities to get rid of the 12-foot long gator, The Associated Press reports.The gator was "carefully removed without harm," with the help of a trapper, according to a Facebook post by The Jupiter Police Department.The Sun Sentinel cites the trapper as saying to the authorities that the alligator was estimated to be around 100 years old. It was then relocated to a gator farm in South Florida, according to the Associated Press.The Florida police shared pictures of the gator on Facebook. Online commentators were quick to praise the police on taking swift action.Alligators are typically active when the weather is warm in South Florida, The Sun Sentinel reports.According to the Smithsonian's National Zoo & Conservation Biology Institute, male American alligators are typically 11.2 feet in length while female alligators are typically 8.2 feet in size.According to the Institute, "exceptionally large" male alligators can weigh as much as 1000 pounds.These alligators usually live to be around 50 years of age.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 02:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810494/3810494_B7B7E4081A4A4CBEA5E974E271768DA7_190410_3810494_Massive_alligator_caught_in_South_Florida_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E37/FE6/E37FE61E7DDEB5D91692AEF2C733E34E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, florida, florida gator, 750 pound gator, 12-foot 750-pound gator trapped in florida, alligator jupiter florida, 12 foot alligator caught in florida, jupiter commerce park, florida gator stories, gator stories, florida police gator]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810487</guid>
      <title>Nipsey Hussle: The rapper's last words, revealed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Rapper Nipsey Hussle's final words may have led to his death.On March 31, Grammy-nominated artist Nipsey Hussle was shot dead in front of his apparel store in Hyde Park, Los Angeles. Sources have told TMZ that Hussle's killer returned to shoot him again after hearing his final words.According to the LAPD, 29-year-old gang member Eric Holder approached a group of men outside Hussle's shop and conversed with them. He later returned at 3:20 p.m. and opened fire at the group. CCTV footage show Hussle and another man fall to the ground as the rest run away.Hussle allegedly raised his head off the ground and addressed the shooter saying, 'You shot me, you got me, I'm good.' Surveillance videos show the shooter then returning and firing additional shots at Hussle as he lay on the ground.The rapper ultimately died from gunshot injuries to the head and torso. According to TMZ, Hussle most likely died after the second round of shots.Holder is now in police custody and has been placed in solitary confinement to prevent inmates from attacking him.Sources have told Variety that Hussle's memorial service will be held this Thursday at the Staples Center.Apart from his music, Hussle was known for his work as a community advocate. According to LA Magazine, Hussle was scheduled to meet with the LAPD a day after his murder to discuss new ways to manage gang violence in the city.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 02:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810487/3810487_90741FE449A549819BC6CE0A411FEC2E_190410_3810487_Nipsey_Hussle__The_rapper_s_last_words__revealed_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15A/F85/15AF859F0D948FBE5B02D5AC76EA999D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Nipsey hussle death, nipsey hussle shot, nipsey hussle final words, rapper death, dead rapper, nipsey hussle, nipsey hussle shooting, surveillance video, surveillance footage, caught on camera, CCTV, CCTV footage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3810485</guid>
      <title>Drunk man climbs up a telephone pole then hangs upside down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HENAN, CHINA  A man in China man drank so much that he decided it was a great idea to climb up a telephone tower, according to Ladbible.Spectators spotted the man trying to drunkenly climb the pole for six hours in Henan province in China.The man eventually passed out and was seen hanging upside down off the 100 foot telephone pole.The police and the fire authorities were called on to help save the drunk man.Authorities struggled to reach the guy as they were trapped under a low gate and workers had to help dig up the road to allow the rescue trucks to go through.The authorities then tried to get the guy to climb down the pole and even set up inflatable cushions for him.They eventually reached the man on the pole and rescued him. The man was then taken to the hospital. He is not believed to have suffered from any serious injuries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 02:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/10/3810485/3810485_3581B416D861486785A03E82864F4766_190410_3810485_Drunk_man_climbs_up_a_telephone_pole_then_hangs__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DE7/0BC/DE70BC108645E93695170DBB867504A7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, drunk stories, man hangs upside off on phone mast, telephone pole, telephone tower, telephone tower china, henan, drunk man in China climbs telephone pole]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811478</guid>
      <title>Beijing may use facial recognition to ban people from parks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Feel like going to the park? Well, if you're in lovely Beijing, then you may need to get a facial recognition scan first. According to the ultra-CCP-friendly Global Times, Beijing park management d-bags said they may establish a blacklist using AI security cameras to ban uncivilized visitors from entering. Over the Tomb Sweeping Day holiday weekend, parks in Beijing saw a big uptick in visitors, which apparently led to a whole bunch of less than exemplary behaviour. Looks as if some Chinese people were seen climbing peach trees, picking flowers and damaging plants. There were also people fishing near a lake where it's prohibited, as well as people selling things in the park without the proper permits.  Officials think the facial recognition cameras will help detect all the detrimental behavior, so that it can be snuffed out. Good luck with that. China has placed itself at the forefront of super creepy facial recognition technology in order to keep its nose in everyone's business. So, if you're living in China, relax and rest assured, someone is watching.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 13:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811478/3811478_9BF3D6FCD10240D7ABA4138D6346431D_190411_3811478_Beijing_may_use_facial_recognition_to_ban_people_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/158/82C/15882C4AF143C6DC1D694C57F4B75FC7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China facial recognition, facial recognition, China AI security cameras, China unruly tourists, Chinese tourists]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811462</guid>
      <title>First ever black hole image released by scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHOENIX, ARIZONA  Scientists using a global network of telescopes released the first ever image of a black hole, an achievement that validates Albert Einstein's general theory of relativity. The details were announced in a series of six scientific papers published in Astrophysical Journal Letters. According to Reuters, the photo of the black hole at the center of Messier 87, or M87, a galaxy residing in the center of the Virgo galaxy cluster, shows a glowing ring of red, yellow and white surrounding a dark center. The image was captured by the Event Horizon Telescope, or EHT, a network of eight linked radio telescopes in six locations that acts as a planet-sized observational dish. The observations confirms the theory of general relativity proposed in 1915 by Einstein to explain the laws of gravity and their relation to other natural forces.Based on his equations, scientists predicted what a black hole would look like due to the immense gravitational pull, and what the light around it should look like.   According to University of Arizona astronomer Dimitrios Psaltis in a press release, "the Event Horizon Telescope allows us for the very first time to test the predictions of Einstein's General Theory of Relativity around supermassive black holes in the centers of galaxies." "The predicted size and shape of the shadow theory match our observations remarkably well, increasing our confidence in this century-old theory," he added. According to Reuters, the M87 black hole resides about 54 million light-years from Earth and has a mass of 6.5 billion times that of the sun.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 13:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811462/3811462_90C28FD6F5B9493EB1E194F5E8FE9440_190411_3811462_First_ever_black_hole_image_released_by_scientis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EF1/3DB/EF13DB85C1C118D3FAFE687034FA3FB3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, black hole, first ever black hole image, black hole photo, Event Horizon Telescope, M87 black hole]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811452</guid>
      <title>Doctor finds live 'sweat bees' in Taiwanese woman's eye</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAOHSIUNG, TAIWAN  A woman in Taiwan who went in for a swollen eye got the shock of her life after her infection turned out to be live bees.According to CTS, the whole thing began when the lady, surnamed He, felt something blow into her eye while visiting a relative's grave site with family in Kaohsiung. ________________She assumed it was just sand, and rinsed her eye out with water. According to Apple Daily, the time she got home, her eye was swollen, and tears were streaming out.He eventually ended up at the hospital, where a doctor checked her eyes out and found not one, not two, but four very much alive sweat bees under her left eyelid. According to CNN, sweat bees measure a miniscule three to four millimeters and nest near graves and fallen trees. They feed primarily off nectar and pollen, but are also drawn to the salt in human sweat and tears.They hardly ever charge into people's eyes though, and Fooyin University Hospital claims the operation to extract the little buggers out of Miss He's eye was the first in the world. Apple Daily reports that the bees were taken out of He's peepers alive and fully intact. Had she rubbed her eyes earlier and caused the bees to rupture, it would've been much more serious.As it is, the insects had given her cellulitis, a bacterial skin infection, and severe corneal erosion. Her eyesight is now the equivalent of 20-200 on the Snellen eye chart. But her central nervous system is thankfully unaffected, and she's expected to make a full recovery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 12:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811452/3811452_F6188F1A49764370954B92DD9641B6E6_190411_3811452_Doctor_finds_live__sweat_bees__in_Taiwanese_woma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/029/346/029346F6B84A5619A5B437A8316B28A4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, sweat bees, bees in eye, bees in eyelid, bees feeding on tears, eye irritation, eye infection, live bees in eye]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811337</guid>
      <title>Israel attempts moon landing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  An Israeli space probe, called the Beresheet, entered lunar orbit last week and is set to land on the moon's surface on Thursday, The Times of Israel reports.The spacecraft performed a maneuver to reduce its distance from the moon from 750 kilometers to 467 kilometers.According to Space.com, the probe will land on the Mare Serenitatis, which is on the northern hemisphere of the near side region of the moon. The spacecraft will focus on three possible landing sites in the area. These are  Posidonius 1, 2 or 3.Once the probe lands, it will use a magnetometer to measure the magnetism of moon rocks, according to an Israeli Ministry of Foreign Affairs news release This is to get a better understanding of how and when the lunar body acquired its magnetic field. If successful, Israel will become the fourth country to land a probe on the moon. Previously, nations such as the former Soviet Union, the United States and China have landed a spacecraft on the moon. The mission is a joint project between private Israeli company SpaceIL and Israel Aerospace Industries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 09:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811337/3811337_EE425808DE6740A2B0766C21F5687652_190411_3811337_Israel_attempts_moon_landing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE8/788/FE8788AC6F0B5BEEF5DA0B299BA43E99.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space exploration, israel, Israeli probe, israeli spacecraft, SpaceIL, first israeli lunar spacecraft, Beresheet, israeli spacecraft Beresheet, beresheet launch, beresheet lunar lander, beresheet moon lander, beresheet spacecraft, beresheet lander, beresheet israel moon, beresheet lunar orbit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811331</guid>
      <title>How whitening strips damage your teeth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, FLORIDA     New research on the effects of whitening products on our chompers shows that whitening strips containing hydrogen peroxide can be harmful to your teeth's dentin.According to research presented at the American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology's annual meeting, hydrogen peroxide, an ingredient present in over-the-counter whitening strips, may be damaging one of the layers of your teeth.Teeth have three layers  a thin outer layer called enamel, an underlying layer called dentin, and a connective tissue that binds the teeth's roots to the gum. Most of our teeth are made up of dentin which contains high levels of collagen protein.Researchers placed whitening strips on extracted human teeth coated with artificial saliva for about an hour or as instructed on the whitening product's description. After the strips were removed the teeth were washed for an hour and examined. Results showed that hydrogen peroxide in whitening strips can penetrate the enamel and break down the collagen protein present in dentin.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 09:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811331/3811331_44D275D5FE3F4695806F17FE874CBBBE_190411_3811331_How_whitening_strips_damage_your_teeth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C40/7B4/C407B4732E753936EF96BA84D9F5EBAB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, teeth whitening, teeth, how to whiten teeth, effects of whitening teeth, crest whitening strips professional effects, crest 3d whitestrips, whitening, crest whitestrips]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811325</guid>
      <title>Russia announces ambitious Arctic expansion plan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. PETERSBURG, RUSSIA  Russia has announced an ambitious expansion plan that will secure its foothold in the Arctic.The Associated Press reports that while at the Arctic forum in St. Petersburg, President Vladimir Putin revealed plans to increase cargo shipments on the Arctic sea route.From 20 million metric tons in 2018, the amount of cargo will reach 80 million by 2025.Russia, the only nation in the world with nuclear icebreakers, is also moving to expand its fleet.The country has four nuclear icebreakers and is currently in the process of constructing three new ones. By 2035, Russia wants to have a fleet of 13 heavy icebreakers, nine of which will be nuclear-powered. Ports on both sides of the Northern sea route, specifically Murmansk on the Kola Peninsula and Petropavlovsk-Kamchatsky on the Kamchatka Peninsula, are also set to be expanded.According to Putin, other ports and infrastructure facilities along the route will also be upgraded, and says foreign companies have been invited to invest in the reconstruction project.The Moscow Times reports that Russia is already expanding its military presence in the Arctic with new bases and increased air and naval activity.AP reports that with shrinking polar ice facilitating new opportunities for resource exploration and shipping in the Arctic, countries like Russia, the U.S., Canada, Denmark, and Norway are all trying to assert jurisdiction over the region.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811325/3811325_B4C4AF072AE747DCB0BD187FAFA38E35_190411_3811325_Russia_announces_ambitious_Arctic_expansion_plan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BCB/2DA/BCB2DAAB15435646C63556FFC17859F8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Russia, arctic expansion, arctic route, northern sea route, arctic shipping route, nuclear icebreakers, icebreaker, arctic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811182</guid>
      <title>China plans new Yangtze River nature preserve</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  Shanghai is set for a new nature preserve that will be used to conserve the natural ecology of the Yangtze River, according to Inhabitat.The preserve will consist of an aquarium and a research facility. The building will be 427,000 square-feet and will sit at the mouth of the Yangtze River, according to information from the project website.This is to boost public engagement and raise awareness of the importance of ecological conservation of the river, according to Ennead architects.The preserve will use Translucent PTFE panels and other sustainable technology methods such as geothermal heating and cooling loops.Visitors will be able to view the local flora and the aquarium while inside the building, according to the architects.Suspended walkways will also be incorporated into the building, allowing tourists to get a closeup view of shoreline ecosystems that are usually found under the sea.The project is expected to be completed by 2021.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 06:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811182/3811182_95855E09DE174607A14F337F2AA2A5F6_190411_3811182_China_plans_new_Yangtze_River_nature_preserve_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DAB/AA4/DABAA4E27870BB3E196376B3A0DE108E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, shanghai, nature preserve, yangtze river, Shanghai yangtze river, river estuary, chinese nature preserve, nature reserve in China, Shanghai Yangtze River Estuary Chinese Sturgeon Nature Preserve, nature, Shanghai Yangtze River Estuary, architecture, architecture in China, new architecture in China, modern architecture in China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811154</guid>
      <title>NASA to send flying robots to the International Space Station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON   Two special robots called 'Astrobees' will be sent to space to help astronauts carry out chores and experiments on board the International Space Station, according to NASA.Astrobees are cube-shaped robots that measure 1 square-foot. They are equipped with cameras, a touchscreen, speakers, a microphone and a mechanical arm. The Astrobees also come with special sensors used for navigation, crew monitoring, sampling, logistics, among other tasks. The robots are powered by onboard batteries and move around using a fan-based propulsion system. They can be controlled by NASA flight controllers in Houston and also have an automated mode. When the Astrobees' batteries begin to run low, they will automatically fly to a docking system in the ISS to recharge. The two Astrobees will be launched to space from the Wallops Flight Facility in Eastern Virginia at the end of this month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 05:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811154/3811154_A90CF12BA8D64E0281383445A0EF56F0_190411_3811154_NASA_to_send_flying_robots_to_the_International__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B2A/616/B2A6169F89A74FE66252A40FFCB8DA24.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa robots, nasa robot, nasa space, nasa science, nasa astrobees, nasa flying robots, nasa iss, international space station, nasa astronaut, nasa technology, nasa science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811091</guid>
      <title>Images show Chinese anti-satellite laser base</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA  Recent satellite images exposed a secret anti-satellite laser base and weapons facilities in Xinjiang, reports The Print.The images were provided by retired Indian Army Colonel and satellite imagery analyst Vinyak Bhat. The images show a base located near a lake 145 miles or roughly 233 kilometers south of the capital of Xinjiang.The pictures show a directed energy weapons facility, also known as a DEW.  According to Bhat, the facility is made up of four buildings with sliding roofs. Bhat believes that the buildings contain chemical lasers that can be used to disable satellites.Images also show an experimental electromagnetic pulse facility or EMP facility. When used as a weapon, EMPs can damage electronic devices and at high levels can generate a lightning strike that can destroy buildings or planes.According to The Print, this facility is being used for military research.Bhat also photographed a mobile pulse generator. This type of weapon uses non-nuclear pulses to create electromagnetic interference that can quickly disarm satellites.According to The Print, China also has space tracking stations across the country including in Tibet. These stations are believed to provide information on satellites they want to target.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 01:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/11/3811091/3811091_8A69B67C1B074348A401F48984DFB9E0_190411_3811091_Images_show_Chinese_anti_satellite_laser_base_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C3E/F0E/C3EF0E2BB574302C6FCB78D027A098B8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, anti satellite, china laser base, china satellite, china military, china secret base, china xinjiang, china secret base]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3812017</guid>
      <title>Idiot tosses coins at plane before flight for good luck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  A Chinese man has been arrested after chucking some coins before boarding a plane for a little bit of luck. According to the Chutian Metropolis Daily, the boneheaded incident happened on April 2 at the Wuhan Tianhe International Airport.Apparently a 31-year-old man, surnamed Xia, was traveling with his wife and 4-month-old daughter. Looks like his genius mother-in-law told him to throw coins at the plane while boarding for a safe and smooth journey.What's even funnier, when Xia got to the airport, he realized he only had one coin, so Einstein actually went to a shop to get even more change.Xia figured that if he chucked the coins in the terminal, he wouldn't be maximizing his good luck, so he waited until he was on the jetway to bless the plane. Xia then had the good fortune to get detained for 10 days, while his wife and kid flew to Urumqi without him. This is at least the sixth time this type of idiocy has happened in China over the last two yearsand thank god it won't be the last. At this point, Chinese airlines should just start leaving a big old container of coins for the passengers before each flight. Think of all that good luck.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 11:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/12/3812017/3812017_E104A85D264E4C8B866AA671E25B774E_190412_3812017_Idiot_tosses_coins_at_plane_before_flight_for_go_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1B6/0E0/1B60E01FE06242EAB35EC5ACD5D3CA74.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese passenger, Chinese airline passenger, Chinese good luck coins flying, China good luck flight coins, Chinese passenger throws coins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811969</guid>
      <title>Who are the people behind kid's YouTube channels?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE INTERWEBS  Kids' channels on YouTube are on the rise, but who are the people behind them? A report by the Wall Street Journal explored this issue.If you haven't accidentally stumbled upon an hour-long YouTube compilation comprised solely of variations of 'Mary Had A Little Lamb', consider yourself lucky. Kids channels on YouTube are becoming increasingly popular and they're making bank. According to Social Blade, CoCoMelon, one of the top kid channels on the platform, makes roughly $120 million a year in ad revenue.But who are the people behind these channels? And are there any guidelines ensuring the content is kid-friendly? YouTube doesn't monitor who uploads, it monitors what is uploaded. All you need to do to become a creator and collect revenue is provide a valid address and phone number. However, when it comes to channels directed at children, this can be risky. In 2015, YouTube launched the YouTube Kids app, in order to give parents more control of the content their children were consuming, but the app still does not provide any clarification as to who creates the content.Josh Golin, executive director of Campaign for a Commercial-Free Childhood, told the Wall Street Journal that this "adds to the lack of accountability," when it comes to the quality of the videos being created.Most of the top channels on the platform describe themselves as "educational" but whether or not that is true is questionable.Former research director for Sesame Street, Renée Chernow-O'Leary, mentioned a video in one of these channels where a kid dropped Mentos into a Coca-Cola bottle.  Chernow-O'Leary added, "I was waiting for the mother to say, 'Do you know why this happens?' But she didn't. What they lack is an intent to educate.'But if these videos are repetitive and non-educational, what makes them popular on YouTube? Well, the algorithm and parents. On one hand, YouTube promotes channels that prolong watch time, AKA long videos and content that is advertiser-friendly.On the other hand, parents see these hypnotic videos as the perfect nanny. According to a survey conducted by the Pew Research Center last November, 81 percent of parents with children under 11 let them watch YouTube and 34 percent said their children watch it regularly.But parents are catching up with the mind-numbing content. A mother told the Wall Street Journal that she stopped letting her 2-year-old-daughter watch YouTube videos after her daughter took a liking to a video of adults and kids opening plastic eggs with surprises inside.Peyton added, 'It was disturbing to me that somebody was working so hard on the videosintricately editing them and using so many eggs. I remember thinking, 'What was their agenda?'. That remains a mystery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 10:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/12/3811969/3811969_AAEB2AF373584F3C97B810854D71CE8A_190412_3811969_Who_are_the_people_behind_kid_s_YouTube_channels_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F43/EAE/F43EAE5F7D718AF68B998BDF6543C71F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, kids youtube channel, youtube channel, kids channels on youtube, kids channel tv, wall street journal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811962</guid>
      <title>Mom throws 7-year-old fast food feast for birthday party</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RATANA, NEW ZEALAND  A New Zealand mom is getting flack from concerned parents after she posted a photo of a cholesterol-filled banquet she threw for her daughter's seven-year-old birthday bash on a Facebook group.What was included in this nutrition-packed spread? Well, according to the Mirror, there were six buckets of Kentucky Fried Chicken, 10 pizzas, 20 McDonald's cheeseburgers as well as soda pops and candy. I can feel my cholesterol levels rising just by saying it.Now the Kiwi mom acknowledged in the post that this was, in fact, not a healthy diet. Perhaps hoping that netizens would appreciate her self-awareness. Not quite.One user commented, 'Happy birthday, we got you a heart attack.' Another was more critical, writing, 'New Zealand has a massive obesity problem and this is not helping. No seven year old needs food like this.' Yikes. Not everyone was up in arms over the fatty meal, some of them felt people were overreacting, writing, 'Some of you need to chill. I mean, it's one day? Not every single day of their entire lives.'  Isn't junk food what kids usually eat during birthday parties, though? I mean, how many parties have you seen happening in McDonald's Playplace? Last time we checked, they don't have vegan Buddha Bowls on the kid's menu.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 10:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/12/3811962/3811962_6085042F6FB44B28930C1A151F079112_190412_3811962_Mom_throws_7_year_old_fast_food_feast_for_birthd_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/182/34A/18234A0B07ED1E6A5C12A13B9D259EAE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, obesity, fast food, fast food party, diabetes, cholesterol, fast food feast, junk food]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811957</guid>
      <title>Cloning: Scientists want to clone an extinct horse species</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YAKUTSK, RUSSIA  Researchers found the body of a 42,000-year-old foal frozen in the Siberian permafrost. According to The Siberian Times, they are planning to bring its species back to life. A group of scientists from Russia and South Korea want to clone an extinct horse species by extracting DNA from the frozen remains of a foal that died 42,170 years ago in Siberia.The foal's body was found in the permafrost of a Siberian crater called Batagaika in Yakutia, Russia. It was found to be part of the Lenskaya breed which went extinct about 4,000 years ago.The team has attempted to extract cells from the foal to create a cloned embryo. The extracted cells are first cultivated in a growth medium, a substance that encourages the growth of microorganisms. They are then placed in a CO2 incubator.  If successful, the embryo would be implanted in a South Korean horse. Scientists are also considering using a Yakut horse, an Eastern Siberian breed, as a surrogate mother. According to Dr. Semyon Grigoryev, a leading researcher at the Mammoth Museum in Yakutsk, it is possible to successfully harvest DNA from the foal, stating, quote, "Fortunately, the animal's muscle tissues were undamaged and well preserved, so we managed to get samples of this unique find for biotechnology research.The Siberian Times reports that the team has attempted to obtain usable cells over 20 times in the last month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 10:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/12/3811957/3811957_10A6B39519114C10BEC9B205BA2BD99C_190412_3811957_Cloning__Scientists_want_to_clone_an_extinct_hor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/817/8E4/8178E4E0722D9EAAB870E83A2D9B029A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, extinct, cloning extinct species, cloning science, science behind cloning, jurassic park, russia, south korea, siberia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811931</guid>
      <title>Julian Assange arrested in London at Ecuadorian embassy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange was arrested at the Ecuadorian embassy on Thursday to face a charge in the U.S. of conspiring to hack into a Pentagon computer network in 2010, according to the New York Times. According to the BBC, Assange took refuge in the embassy in 2012 to avoid extradition to Sweden over a sexual assault case that has since been dropped.According to the New York Times, the Ecuadorian government suspended the citizenship it had granted Assange and evicted him on Thursday, clearing the path for his arrest. Apparently, Ecuador was growing impatient with Assange, after they say he interfered with other states' internal affairs and his personal habits of not cleaning the bathroom or looking after his cat.  At Westminster Magistrates' Court on Thursday he was found guilty of jumping bail.He is now looking at U.S. federal conspiracy charges related to one of the biggest ever leaks of government secrets. According to the BBC, the U.K. will decide whether to extradite Assange, in response to allegations by the Department of Justice that he conspired with Chelsea Manning to download classified databases. Assange is looking at up to five years in the slammer if convicted on the charges of conspiracy to commit computer intrusion. The WikiLeaks founder said he would fight extradition, and legal experts told the New York Times that the process could take years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 09:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/12/3811931/3811931_C1EC3683065F42A799A98DD02C090816_190412_3811931_Julian_Assange_arrested_in_London_at_Ecuadorian__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A4E/73C/A4E73CC2FB8105CD56571D7560AAA7BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Julian Assange, Julian Assange arrested, Assange arrested, Assange US extradition, WikiLeaks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3811843</guid>
      <title>China censors smoking, tattoos and bikinis online</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Content moderators in China have been tasked with the job of censoring unsuitable content such as smoking, tattoos and bikinis, the South China Morning Post reports.Popular live-streaming app Inke uses 1,200 staff members to selectively remove questionable content. The moderators have 15 seconds before a video goes live to decide whether a two-piece bathing suit is indecent or if it acceptable to show on screen depending on its context.The most censored activity on the platform is smoking, according to the South China Morning Post. The activity isn't allowed to be shown as it promotes an unhealthy lifestyle.Excessive tattoos on the body will also be blurred online, The New York Times reports.The team uses a training manual which is published by the China Association of Performing Arts to decide what is deemed as questionable content.Zhi Heng, the head of Inke's content safety team told The South China Morning Post that they "cannot let past anything that is against the law and regulations, against mainstream values and against the company's values".China is increasingly tightening control of content online to promote what it refers to as "core socialist values," according to the New York Times.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 07:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/12/3811843/3811843_1ECE42DDDCF740A6A79C234A4CFB2A45_190412_3811843_China_censors_smoking__tattoos_and_bikinis_onlin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/302/E73/302E73DB4A7FB2A269A2E2500CC0F6AB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, china censorship, china censorship internet, china internet restrictions, china internet clean up, chinese firewall, great chinese firewall, censorship in China, chinese censorship, China banned content, china censoring internet, what is china censoring online, content regulation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813424</guid>
      <title>Israel lunar probe crashes upon landing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Israel's lunar probe, the Beresheet, crashed while trying to land on the moon last Thursday due to an engine glitch, according to Space.com.Israel's Beresheet spacecraft crashed while attempting to land on the moon's surface due to a glitch that occurred just 14 kilometers from the moon.The Beresheet team explained that preliminary reports indicated that a malfunction in one of the probe's components caused the main engine to shut down. This flaw did not allow controllers to slow down the speed at which the Beresheet was descending, causing the crash. The engineers lost connection with the lunar probe when it was 150 meters away from the moon's surface. It was traveling at 500 kilometers per hour.The team succeeded in restarting the Beresheet's engine right before it crashed but it was already too close to the surface and traveling too quickly for them to control its landing.According to an Israeli Ministry of Foreign Affairs news release, the lander was equipped with a magnetometer that would measure the level of magnetism of moon rocks. Its main objective was to understand how and when the moon acquired its magnetic field.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/15/3813424/3813424_72219D643F8540E6BB1F6F27C63F92F6_190415_3813424_Israel_lunar_probe_crashes_upon_landing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4FF/AA6/4FFAA644B5F5FEAAD9CDDA6D637133BE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space exploration, israel, Israeli probe, israeli spacecraft, SpaceIL, first israeli lunar spacecraft, Beresheet, israeli spacecraft Beresheet, beresheet launch, beresheet lunar lander, beresheet moon lander, beresheet spacecraft, beresheet lander, beresheet israel moon, beresheet lunar orbit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813390</guid>
      <title>Singapore-based company has grand plans for cultured seafood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE , SINGAPORE   Singaporean-based company Shiok[w][x] Meats has plans to develop cultured meat from stem cells as a sustainable alternative to seafood, CleanTechnica reports.The word "Shiok" means "fantastic and delicious" in the Malay language, according to Shiok Meats website.Founders of the company Sandhya Sriram[y][z][aa] and Ka Yi Ling are looking to replicate seafood such as shrimp, lobster and crab, according to their website.However, the company is not actually looking to make seafood look like crustaceans from the sea.In an interview with Clean Technica, the two said they are instead looking to produce cell-based seafood that would consist of minced meat. The cell-based meat would consist of stem cells that are fed with a nutrient mix that would help the cells grow into meat tissues."The seafood meat can then be used inside dumplings or wantons.The company estimates it would be able to produce cultured shrimp meat for around $5,000 a kilo, according to Clean Technica.Shiok Meats plans to release its products over the next three to five years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 11:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/15/3813390/3813390_532EE1CB98A0422681A8769D33B7D21B_190415_3813390_Singapore_based_company_has_grand_plans_for_cult_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/77D/120/77D1202211F587735FC2BB06C72901ED.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, singapore, cell-based meat, shiok meats, shiok meats singapore, seafood, shrimp, replicating seafood, lobster, crab, artificial seafood, imitation seafood, cultured seafood, cultured shrimp, cultured lobster, cultured crab, clean meat, replicating seafood, alternatives to seafood, cell-based seafood]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813339</guid>
      <title>Chinese residents forced to 
install cameras at home</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Citizens in the cities of Hangzhou and Fujian province are being forced to install surveillance cameras in their homes, according to a report by Bitter Winter, a human rights magazine in China. Authorities in China are forcing landlords and homeowners in Hangzhou to install surveillance cameras in their houses living rooms. These cameras must be installed before the houses are registered for rent. Landlords are fined $74 if they do not comply.Another source told Bitter Winter that facial recognition software had been installed in their gated community forcing all residents and visitors to scan their faces before entering.In Fujian province, a new security policy is forcing residents to install surveillance cameras on top of their door locks in order to observe those who enter and leave the residency. It cost one neighbor $223 to install the system.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 10:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/15/3813339/3813339_80C40CBB3BC34EF69AD034C3BAA777C7_190415_3813339_Chinese_residents_forced_to__install_cameras_at__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9EB/BCD/9EBBCD3D33494BA6C2193FA81957D626.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china surveillance, China ai system, China ai, facial recognition, surveillance, surveillance state, China surveillance, police state, sharp eyes project, China surveillance system, total surveillance, social credit, sesame credit, China, Beijing, China police]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813309</guid>
      <title>Man smoking at gas station gets fire extinguisher to the face</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANGZHOU, CHINA  A really intelligent man who thought he'd start smoking at a gas station in Hangzhou last week was convinced to put it out by an attendantand his handy fire extinguisher.According to CTGN, surveillance cameras show Camel light up a cigarette as he starts to leave the pump.  As Newport stops at the gas station entrance continuing to puff away, an attendant comes over to tell him to stop smoking because apparently gas stations and fire we've been told don't mix well.But like a champ, Marlboro Man refuses to put it out, so the attendant hilariously returns with a fire extinguisher and sprays it directly into Parliament's face. Needless to saythe cigarette was put out, unfortunately Virginia Slims lit up with rage and tries throwing a punch only to get another big squirt of deja vu.After the po po arrived, they treated Lucky Strike to a three day stint in the slammer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 09:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/15/3813309/3813309_BA56AF6B369E4ED2A134DB0E4D1F57BF_190415_3813309_Man_smoking_at_gas_station_gets_fire_extinguishe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7E6/5B2/7E65B243BBB5A6051DA80C3C435553BF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fire extinguisher, fire extinguisher to face, Hangzhou gas station, Hangzhou gas station attendant, attenant fire extinguisher]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813136</guid>
      <title>CRISPR gene-editing activated by light</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANJING/XIAMEN, CHINA  Chinese scientists are using light as an alternative to viruses to deliver CRISPR-Cas9 gene editing tools into target cells.According to IEEE Spectrum, CRISPR-Cas9 is a genome editing tool that is used to cut and paste DNA sequences and modify gene function.CRISPR-Cas9 is typically delivered to the nucleus of a particular cell via a virus carrier system. Though it is effective, using viruses runs the risk of provoking an immune response or initiating tumors.Researchers from Nanjing University and Xiamen University have developed a light carrier system consisting of nanoparticles that absorb and convert low-energy near-infrared radiation to ultraviolet light.NIR light can penetrate human tissue to reach the nanoparticles deep in the body, while UV can cut light-sensitive molecules to untether the CRISPR-Cas9.To test the system, nanoparticles were injected directly into the tumors of mice. When researchers shone NIR toward the location of the growth, it was converted to UV, which then released the CRISPR package.The gene-editing tool stopped a protein associated with cancer cells like it was programmed to, resulting in a reduction in tumor growth.The research is published in Science Advances. According to author Yujun Song, the team is focused on nanomedicine and disease treatment. They hope to apply the tool not just to cancer, but also to Parkinson's and diabetes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 05:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/15/3813136/3813136_5CFB1DCDAE314061AB7F9D18E3FECFF2_190415_3813136_CRISPR_gene_editing_activated_by_light_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FDC/C84/FDCC84EAD62D22BF492D004C91379D2D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, gene editing, CRISPR, light activated gene editing, light activated CRISPR, CRISPR Cas9, virus, cancer growth, tumor, tumor growth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813098</guid>
      <title>New species of human found in Philippine cave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENABLANCA, PHILIPPINES  Ancient remains found in a cave in the Philippines have led to the discovery of a tiny hominin species previously unknown to science.According to an article published in Nature, researchers excavating Callao Cave uncovered bones and teeth with a mix of ancient and modern features. The fragments came from three individuals of a previously unknown species now named Homo luzonensis, after the Philippine island of Luzon on which it was found.The size of the bones suggest its owners may have only been about three feet tall, and possibly shorter than Homo Floresiensis, who inhabited the Indonesian island of Flores."Both were alive and present in eastern Asia 50,000 years ago, at the same time as the Homo sapiens, Neanderthals, and Denisovans.According to the New York Times, the tiny hominins on Luzon and Flores may be descended from Homo erectus.Nature reports that the species is known to have moved from Africa to Southeast Asia, and could have shrunk as it adapted to life on the islands.However, one toe bone discovered in the cave is curved, unlike that of a Homo erectus or Homo sapien. It is instead much more similar to that of the Australopithecus, which lived in Africa three million years ago and had curved toe bones that were good for climbing.According to CNN, more excavations are needed to answer questions about the characteristics of Homo luzonensis and how they evolved.But what's clear is that Southeast Asia was home to a much more diverse group of humans that first thought, so who knows what else archaeologists will find.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 03:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/15/3813098/3813098_9D6A84E5C49D4CED883C859A35CEA9CA_190415_3813098_New_species_of_human_found_in_Philippine_cave_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ECC/762/ECC762870AA1A5EC8720D2E4E2FA102A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, homo luzonensis, new species, new human species, undiscovered human, hominid, tiny human species, callao cave, homo floresiensis, homo erectus, australopithecus, neanderthal, denisovan, homo sapien]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813065</guid>
      <title>Chinese scientists add human brain genes into monkeys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Researchers from China have inserted human brain genes into monkeys, according to a new study published in the National Science Review.The scientists did this by injecting viruses with the human gene MCPH 1, a gene related to brain development and brain evolution, into the embryos of eleven monkeys. They then let the monkeys grow before further testing.Out of the eleven that were injected, only five survived. According to MIT Technology Review, the researchers found that the modified monkeys did better on memory tests involving colors and block pictures.They also noted the modified monkeys' brains took longer to develop, similar to human babies.None of the monkeys developed abnormally large brains.The Chinese scientists claim the modified monkeys have the potential to provide insight into understanding unique human traits.However, others such as James Sikela, from the University of Colorado who wasn't involved with the study, told MIT Technology Review, "the use of transgenic monkeys to study human genes linked to brain evolution is a very risky road to take." Adding that it could soon lead to extreme modifications.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 02:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/15/3813065/3813065_616A3E3729A7491EB6A038FE5A9A79A8_190415_3813065_Chinese_scientists_add_human_brain_genes_into_mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EAE/D85/EAED85B3743BD340FD0D5370F631A3E0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, gene editing, science, monkey, human brain genes, modified monkey, china gene editing, transgenic monkeys, transgenic animals, scientists modify monkey brains, MCPH 1, gene editing china, china gene editing monkey, gene editing china news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813982</guid>
      <title>Robbers use excavators to rob tons of ATM machines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COUNTY ATRIM, NORTHERN IRELAND    A group of robbers in Northern Ireland have been going all Fast & Furious with their ATM heists. Instead of stealing money from the ATM, they have been jacking the whole ATM  by ripping it out with excavators.According to The Guardian, the three bandits have been driving around in a black van, borrowing diggers and so far tearing 11 ATMs straight out of buildings.But how do they drive away with the ATMs they fish out? Well, they carefully dump them into their getaway van through its rooftop. Clever.You'd think that it would be pretty easy to catch robbers running around town on an excavator, but po-po has been having a hard time tracking them down. To be fair, even one of the shop owners whose ATM got snatched thought a call he received alerting him about an excavator-robbery was an April Fool's joke, can you blame him?But there's one thing we can learn from this: Next time you forget your PIN number, try using an excavator. Europeans definitely don't play around when it comes to robberies. They sure go hard.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/16/3813982/3813982_35E4BEEB8C04487BA422C686F4AD65C4_190416_3813982_Robbers_use_excavators_to_rob_tons_of_ATM_machin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, crazy robberies, crazy bank robberies, robbery, excavator robbery, digger robbery, robbery ireland, ATM robbery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813971</guid>
      <title>New oil-eating bacteria found beneath the Mariana Trench</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARIANA TRENCH  Micro-organisms that consume oil were found in the southern end of the Mariana Trench, according to a new study published in the journal Microbiome.Bacteria such as Oleibacter, Thalassolituss and Alcanivorax genera, were found in the depths of Challenger Deep.These bacteria are known to consume hydrocarbon molecules and are commonly found in crude oil and natural gas. The researchers analyzed samples of seawater taken from the surface of the trench and all the way down a column of water to the bottom of the trench, according to a University of East Anglia news release.The scientists found that the oil-consuming bacteria were in abundance at the bottom of the Mariana Trench.According to the researchers, these unique bacteria could one day be used to clean up oil spills on the surface of the ocean.The scientists also found hydrocarbons being produced at the bottom of the Mariana Trench, according to the news release.Dr David Lea-Smith explained in the news release that the hydrocarbons could help the oil-eating microbes survive the "crushing pressure" at the bottom of the trench as well as serve as a food source.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/16/3813971/3813971_CA3B65507CB94063BE70BAAA9BA1ABFD_190416_3813971_New_oil_eating_bacteria_found_beneath_the_Marian_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5BF/8D0/5BF8D0C8AEE7613D61CC82A2EC7CA679.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mariana trench, bacteria, oil-eating bacteria, deep sea microbes, oil-eating microbes, hydrocarbon molecules, challenger deep, oil-eating microorganisms, hydrocarbon eating bacteria, hydrocarbon nutrients, Alcanivorax borkumensis, hydrocarbon degrading bacteria, oleibacter, thalassolituus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813904</guid>
      <title>Fordham student dies falling from clock tower while taking a picture</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A Fordham University journalism student fell from the iconic campus clock tower while trying to get some shots of the city. According to police, 22-year-old Sydney Monfries and her friends snuck into the Keating Clock Tower around 3 a.m. on Sunday and were planning on climbing to the top. According to the New York Times, they scrambled up the steep staircase of the granite bell tower to get a view of the Bronx at nightand of course to send a Snapchat video. Unfortunately, Monfries fell through an opening in a landing, and plummeted down the inside of the clock bell tower one a few weeks before her graduation. According to the university, she was rushed to St. Barnabas Hospital, where she succumbed to her wounds on Sunday night. The police found the senior unconscious inside the tower at around 3 a.m., with trauma to her head and neck. According to the New York Times, the tower is off limits, but that has not stopped students from clambering to the top to catch a view.  The school said it is investigating how the students gained access to the tower.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 09:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/16/3813904/3813904_2FC2817532554433B5A88A5D86F53E28_190416_3813904_Fordham_student_dies_falling_from_clock_tower_wh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A03/3E0/A033E0E1C1FD6ED97EBF7F680C7B564C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Fordham University, Fordham University student clock tower, Fordham Keating Clock Tower, Sydney Monfries Fordham]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813900</guid>
      <title>Toddler hilariously locks father's iPad for 48 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  A D.C.-area father has become quite the internet sensation after his 3-year-old son hilariously locked his iPad for about 25 million minutes. That's only 48 years.Over the weekend, Evan Osnos, a staff writer at The New Yorker and fellow at the Brookings Institution posted a tweet of his locked iPad's screen and "try again in 25,536,422 minutes."Osnos added, "Uh, this looks fake but, alas, it's our iPad today after a 3-year-old tried (repeatedly) to unlock. Ideas?"According to CNN, the iPad lockout is a security feature of Apple devices that kicks in after the incorrect password is entered several times. The more the wrong password is typed, the longer the lockout time increases. The sure fire solution would obviously be to just enjoy password protection until 2067.    But luckily, Twitter was there to help. One user replied, "put it in a bag of rice," with another suggesting "reboot your 3 y.o."Another insightful netizen tweeted, "time travel seems to be your best bet."Later Osnos sent out an update saying they had managed to get the iPad into Device Firmware Update mode and was in the process of restoring the tablet.  Our advice would clearly be to immediately put the iPad directly back into the hands of the toddler once it's ready.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 09:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/16/3813900/3813900_2DD0EAE8465543A493619A1CF017714A_190416_3813900_Toddler_hilariously_locks_father_s_iPad_for_48_y_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C84/C8D/C84C8DB8035C2DE6BF2AD0F6CD5BB006.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, toddler locks iPad, toddler locks iPad 48 years, boy locks iPad 48 years, dad ipad locked 48 years, iPad locked 25 million minutes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813856</guid>
      <title>Trio of bald eagles seen raising young eaglets together</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FULTON, ILLINOIS  Three bald eagles, two males and one female, have been spotted living in one nest while raising three young eaglets in a tree on the Mississippi River in Illinois.According to a news release by the U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service, the two male eagles are named Valor I and Valor II, while the female eagle goes by Starr. In a livestream set up by non-profit Stewards of the Upper Mississippi River Refuge, the trio was seen taking care of the nest and feeding the baby eagles.Starr usually incubates the eggs, CNN reports. However, the two male eagles do step in and take turns sitting on the eggs whenever she gets tired.According to the same news release, the initial trio formed in 2013 and consisted of another female eagle named Hope. Unfortunately, Hope was killed by another eagle, which is when Starr came into the mix.She has since hatched multiple eggs with both Valor I and Valor II. It is rare for bald eagles to parent in threes, according to the National Audubon Society.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 08:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/16/3813856/3813856_DECD7078F2464644BC2F164BA44B4E99_190416_3813856_Trio_of_bald_eagles_seen_raising_young_eaglets_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2AC/C8B/2ACC8BD7B0248849955E3FC905EB60C8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bald eagles, bald eagles trio, bald eagles illinois, mississippi river bald eagles trio, cute animal stories 2019, Upper Mississippi River National Wildlife Refuge, bald eagle nest, bald eagle nest cam, bald eagle nest mississippi, trio of bald eagles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3813652</guid>
      <title>World's largest aircraft flies over California for the first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOJAVE DESERT, CALIFORNIA  The Stratolaunch aircraft flew over the Mojave Desert for more than two hours on Saturday for the first time, Reuters reports.The Stratolaunch plane is made up of two twin fuselages and massive wings. It is propelled by six Boeing 747 engines. The aircraft is wider than a football field due to its 117-meter wingspan.The plane reached speeds of up to 189 miles per hour and an altitude of 17,000 feet during its first flight, according to the New York Times.The aircraft is designed to carry rockets weighing up to 500,000 pounds into space and release them once it reaches 35,000 feet in altitude, Reuters reports.According to a Stratolaunch press release, the aircraft's reinforced center wing would be able to support multiple launch vehicles such as satellites and other payloads.According to the press release, the airplane would be an affordable alternative for deploying objects into space, with their mission to "make access to orbit as routine as catching a commercial airline flight."The company plans to launch its first rocket into space in 2020, at the earliest, according to Reuters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/16/3813652/3813652_713F2B1A6F0E45DEBC174E2462F0D54F_190416_3813652_World_s_largest_aircraft_flies_over_California_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E77/AD6/E77AD68ABD71806439AA61297E96BDA4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, world's largest plane, world's largest plane take off, world's largest plane makes first test flight, stratolaunch, stratolaunch takeoff, stratolaunch test flight, stratolaunch animation, stratolaunch systems corp, stratolaunch aircraft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3814682</guid>
      <title>Rich brat buys Bugatti with dad's money, complains about taxes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER  A Chinese tycoon's son thought it would be a good idea to complain about having to pay Canadian taxes after charging a Bugatti Chiron with daddy's credit card.  According to the SCMP, to show the world just how much of a self-made man he is, Ding Chen posted a copy of his father Chen Mailin's credit card bill on his Instagram stories with a Chinese message, "These taxes...my heart's tired."  Imagine how his heart would have felt if it had actually been his money. Chen apparently charged the $3.8 million custom Bugatti supercar on daddy's Union Pay credit card, incurring about $680,000 in taxes.  Unfortunately, Ding Dong's Instagram account was deleted soon after news broke.And It's a shame too, because Ding's IG was filled with super douchey pictures of him flaunting daddy's wealth like a true baller. It's smart to get your name on a $30 million Bombardier Challenger jetkind of like writing it down in your underwear.   An obviously a real man wouldn't be caught dead riding the HK subway without taking a picture of his AP watch.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/17/3814682/3814682_EFD55AAB93A6480DA442A3B7D37696D3_190417_3814682_Rich_brat_buys_Bugatti_with_dad_s_money__complai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8DE/785/8DE7859381CB611E326E3D474ECDEE5E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Bugatti Chiron, chinese guy buys bugatti, chinese son buys bugatti, chinese son complains taxes, chinese son charges bugatti]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3814675</guid>
      <title>Chinese electric workers take shocking power naps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENZHOU, CHINA  A bunch of Chinese electric workers in Hunan really take the expression power napping to heart.The shocking footage was uploaded to video app Kuaishou and shows workers cat napping while strapped in full-body safety harnesses 160 feet off the ground.The clip was uploaded by a worker named Xiao Jiang while he and his coworkers took a break from installing power lines.    Xiao Jiang told local media that he and his colleagues have to climb up the pylons every day.And since it's so tiring climbing up and down the towers, they only go down once for lunch. For short breaks, they just strap their safety harnesses to the tower and commence counting sheep right up in the sky.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 12:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/17/3814675/3814675_F2E3A7FDD52F4529A1227B51096D8FD1_190417_3814675_Chinese_electric_workers_take_shocking_power_nap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2D7/EB8/2D7EB8383977899193BABBC34FC9FD7E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, electric workers, electric workers power naps, electric workers nap on tower, electric workers napping on tower]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3814496</guid>
      <title>Stranded dog rescued by oil rig staff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BANGKOK  A dog was stranded in the Gulf of Thailand when an offshore drilling team spotted and saved the mammal on April 12, the Bangkok Post reports.Vitisak Payalaw[c][d] and his oil drilling team affiliated with Chevron noticed a dog's head sticking out of the water nearby their rig, CNN reports. The animal was trying to cling onto it."According to the Bangkok Post, they decided to throw a rope around the dog's neck and pulled him onto the oil rig.The team was worried that the waves could sweep him away, so they had to work fast.Payalaw told CNN that the dog's eyes looked sad and exhausted, as if it was pleading for the team to help him. He also shared images of the rescue mission on Facebook.According to Time magazine, the team named the dog "Boon Rod" which means "Survivor."The dog was then taken in by the animal protection group Watchdog Thailand.Payalaw has said that if no one takes the dog, he would be happy to adopt the dog and take it home.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 08:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/17/3814496/3814496_9276901947704E13B6EBCD27D43CA9BA_190417_3814496_Stranded_dog_rescued_by_oil_rig_staff_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6AC/62D/6AC62DD7DC687304C25C25658B324C0D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cute animal stories, thailand, dog rescue in thailand, dog rescue stories, offshore drilling team, dog rescue thailand, dog rescue videos, dog rescue bangkok, gulf of thailand, saving dog from the sea, rescuing dog from the sea, dog rescue, saving dog videos, saving dog from drowning, stranded dog]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3814481</guid>
      <title>Windbourne microplastics found in remote French mountains</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYRENEES MOUNTAINS, FRANCE  Scientists from the University of Strathclyde[g][h][i] have found tiny plastic particles falling from the sky in the Pyrenees Mountains of southern France.The researchers recorded a rate of 365 microplastic particles per square meter on a daily basis, according to the scientific study. They conducted the study by collecting samples from what they considered to be an "uncontaminated" area in the remote mountainous region.The Pyrenees Mountains are generally considered to be pristine due to a lack of development and their lack of cities and industrial centers, according to a University of Strathclyde[j][k][l] news release.Polystyrene and polyethylene were the most commonly found microplastics, The Guardian reports. These are widely used in single-use packaging and plastic bags.In the same news release, Steve Allen, lead author of the study said that it 'opens up the possibility' that plastic particles are able to travel significant distances from their original source."Adding that the particles are more than likely being transported by wind. He explained that it was "astounding and worrying" that so many microplastic particles were found in the remote region."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 08:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/17/3814481/3814481_267BA94470E74932839F0AF3516CF586_190417_3814481_Windbourne_microplastics_found_in_remote_French__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2CC/717/2CC7171D84849E68A99F7714821AB44B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, microplastics, pyrenees mountains, microplastics pyrenees, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, microplastics france, france, plastic bags, plastic pollution, plastic pollution pyrenees, pyrenees mountains pollution, pyrenees mountains plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, plastic litter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3814478</guid>
      <title>Chinese man throws coins at airplane engine for luck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOHHOT, CHINA  A 66-year-old Chinese man was removed from flight after being caught tossing coins at plane's engine, reports China Daily.Well, it's happened again, folks. Chinese people plus planes plus good luck coins equalsflight delay.This time around, a 66-year-old Chinese man surnamed Yang decided he'd take it upon himself to bless the flight for everyone on board by throwing coins at the plane's engine. How nice of him.The incident occurred on April 16. According to Tianjin Airlines, the flight was departing from Hohhot to Chifeng, two cities in Inner Mongolia, when one of the crew members noticed our hero in the passenger elevator, happily tossing coins at the engines.Po po, however, were not impressed at the man's incredible act of heroism. Even after Yang admitted that he was throwing coins for good luck, they took him away. He was trying to save everyone from impending doom, people! Unfortunately, the only thing Yang was keeping passengers from was their flight. After he was taken away, the flight was delayed for a security check. Yang and all the coins were removed from the plane. Well, there goes their luck.Good guy Yang has accepted to take whatever penalty is imposed by the civil aviation regulations.If you're wondering, didn't we see a similar story before? You're not wrong. This is the seventh time this has happened in China in just two years. Seventh. And it most certainly, won't be the last.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 08:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/17/3814478/3814478_3D5BE90964E346E682E2167A7857BB83_190417_3814478_Chinese_man_throws_coins_at_airplane_engine_for__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F77/B61/F77B61564A0A6FBB7F1FEBC084F21AE5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese passenger, Chinese airline passenger, Chinese good luck coins flying, China good luck flight coins, Chinese passenger throws coins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3814313</guid>
      <title>The meteor that killed all dinosaurs: Explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH DAKOTA, US  Fossils at an excavation site in North Dakota, called Tanis, show details of what happened moments after the deadly asteroid responsible for the extinction of dinosaurs hit Mexico's Yucatan Peninsula, according to a recent paper published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.According to National Geographic, the impact left a giant crater measuring 50 miles or roughly 80 kilometers wide, and 18 miles or roughly 30 kilometers deep. The collision catapulted tons of molten lava, vaporized rock and asteroid dust at high speeds.The fallout covered the entire planet and led to the extinction of  75 percent of life on Earth and the end of the Cretaceous period.In the recent study, paleontologists found fossils of fish, trees, terrestrial vertebrates, and marine creatures that had been flung to Tanis in the aftermath of the asteroid impact.These reveal that roughly an hour after the asteroid hit Earth, debris from the collision turned into particles of glass that rained down for roughly 20 minutes. These particles are called tektites and were found inside the gills of fossilized fish and captured in amber from fossilized tree resin.The deposits at Tanis are a result of magnitude 10 or 11 earthquakes caused by the asteroid crash that then triggered large waves, known as seiches, that sloshed water, sediments, and animals into areas now known as K-PG sites. Researchers believe these tsunamis reached Tanis roughly 17 hours after impact.K-PG sites are part of the K-PG boundary, which is a sedimentary layer that marks the end of the Cretaceous period and the beginning of the Tertiary period.According to the study's lead author Robert DePalma, these fossils are a window into the aftermath of one of the most impactful moments for life on Earth. As human beings, we descended from a lineage that literally survived in the ashes of what was once the glorious kingdom of the dinosaurs. And we're the only species on the planet that has ever been capable of learning from such an event to the benefit of ourselves and every other organism in our world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 04:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/17/3814313/3814313_4CB916959491476ABF20225AE41B0BF8_190417_3814313_The_meteor_that_killed_all_dinosaurs__Explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA4/FD3/BA4FD3643AC1BDA67183A99B2348C614.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  asteroid vs earth, dinosaur extinction, fossil, meteor, meteorite, dinosaurs, extinction north dakota]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3814279</guid>
      <title>America's nasty storms, explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Eastern U.S.  A number of tornadoes barreling through the Eastern U.S. have killed 23 people and wreaked havoc in cities and towns along their way, reports Reuters At least 23 people have died due to a string of tornadoes going through Eastern cities in the US. Currently, roughly 90 million people are at risk due to the massive storms.According to the National Weather Service, tornadoes are the roughest type storms. They are formed quickly and are on the ground for less than 15 minutes, however, they can reach speeds of 300 mile per hour, or roughly 483 kilometers per hour, making them extremely destructive.Tornadoes mostly occur during spring and summer in the United States. They form when cold and dry winds from Canada collide with warm and humid air coming from the Gulf of Mexico.According to the National Centers for Environmental Information, most tornadoes in America happen around Florida and in what is known as 'Tornado Alley', a region in the southern plains of the central United States.The Storm Prediction Center can forecast if tornadoes will form by observing weather conditions that could develop into storms. However, tornado warnings cannot be issued until the tornado is visible or detected by a weather radar.Tornadoes are measured using the Enhanced Fujita, or EF, scale which goes from 0 to 5. An EF level 0 is equal to gusts of wind that last three seconds and traveling at speeds of  from 65 to 85 miles per hour or 105 to 138 kilometers per hour.Tornadoes with an EF rating of 5 have winds reaching up to 200 miles per hour or 322 kilometers per hour.The recent string of tornadoes in Alabama have an EF rating of 3 with winds reaching  150 miles per hour or 241 kilometers per hour.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 03:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/17/3814279/3814279_A520DA69F7E04D44AE7FC69673DA5041_190417_3814279_America_s_nasty_storms__explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4EF/AA4/4EFAA4E7823C14B64F38A864D5E0D0CB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, us tornadoes, tornado, how are tornadoes formed, tornado forming, tornado formed, deadly tornado, tornado alley, enhanced fujita scale, ef scale, ef, enhanced fujita]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815385</guid>
      <title>Notre Dame Cathedral fire: Timeline</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  The iconic Notre-Dame Cathedral caught fire on Monday, destroying the landmark's roof and causing its famous steeple to collapse. Here is a timeline of how the fire occurred.According to The Guardian, smoke alarms sounded off during mass at 6:20 p.m. on April 15. The priest continued the service, believing it was a false alarm. Soon after, the building was evacuated as a precaution.By 6:43 p.m. a second alarm had gone off and firefighters had been called in as the flames were quickly spreading to the cathedral's roof. Fire chief Jean-Claude Gallet told the New York Times that the fire began in the cathedral's attic.According to Reuters, at 7:40 p.m. the fire had spread to the 850-year-old cathedral's famous spire. Minutes later, the spire collapsed in its entirety. By 8:07 p.m. the roof of the cathedral had also collapsed.According to Reuters, at 8:25 p.m. Parisian police had started to evacuate Paris' Ile de la Cité, the island where the cathedral was built. The Guardian reports that around 9 p.m. the fire had reached the north tower.By 9:40 p.m., Gallet told The Guardian there were 400 firefighters, two helicopters and two water tankers attempting to extinguish the fire.Fire services announced that the fire had been completely extinguished the next morning at around 9:30 a.m.According to Fortune, the following artifacts have been recovered from the fire so far: The Crown of Thorns, the Tunic of Saint Louis, the Rose Windows, the Great Organ, the Notre-Dame Bells, the bronze statues of the Twelve Apostles, and a few paintings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 14:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/18/3815385/3815385_E559C2D4D7F641469EFDB216D4B8C175_190418_3815385_Notre_Dame_Cathedral_fire__Timeline_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/749/EC6/749EC686CBDF942D94818094BF95A74D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, notre dame cathedral, notre dame cathedral fire, notre dame fire, notre dame, france, paris, fire in notre dame, notre dame fire collapse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815380</guid>
      <title>Chinese university bans female students from wearing skirts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JILIN, CHINA  Short skirts, nail polish, flip flops, and tank tops have all been banned from a Chinese university in China's Jilin province, according to Btime.com.All women studying at the International Business School of Jilin International Studies University, are now forbidden from wearing miniskirts, jewelry, sporting sleeveless tops, and even dying their hair.It's not just the ladies though, the gentlemen are banned from entering classrooms wearing flip flops, if they do, they will get points deducted from their 'moral education points', which we guess is the academic version of social credit points. The school claims that these measures are being taken to guarantee that the school is a, quote, 'civilized and cultured' institution, whatever that means.According to Global Times, netizens have taken issue with the lack of freedom of choice claiming that university students are adults and should be able to pick their outfits. But are we really surprised that a Chinese institution is doing this? I mean, we are talking about the same country that's forcing people to install cameras in their living rooms. The school might as well just slap some Mao suits on all the students.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 14:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/18/3815380/3815380_BDAA598F39D84F1C94373BE7EBC6F12F_190418_3815380_Chinese_university_bans_female_students_from_wea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/94B/45F/94B45FF89747BC8A71EB340F7D98E8DD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china bans short skirts,  china bans mini skirts, china bans nail polish, china ban, chinese university bans skirts, chinese university life, china college bans short skirts, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815374</guid>
      <title>Man plunges 4 stories after zip line breaks in Thailand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHIANG MAI, THAILAND  A 25-year-old Canadian tourist in Thailand suffered a fatal accident after his zip line snapped causing him to drop 12 meters and fall down a hill, according to The Bangkok Post.The man has been identified by local authorities as Spencer Charles. He was traveling around Thailand with a group of tourists and his girlfriend.The incident happened last Saturday morning in Chiang Mai at Mae Kampong village on a zip line operated by a company called the Flight of the Gibbon.This zip line is one of the longest in Asia, measuring roughly 5 kilometers and containing 33 platforms.Initial reports indicate that the cable snapped shortly after Charles, who weighed roughly 125 kilograms, was released from the start of the zip line.District chief, Suthep Saenmongkol, indicated that they were investigating what caused the cables to break-off adding that the zip line operator had taken full responsibility of the malfunction.The Canadian Consulate in Chiang Mai contacted Charles' family, who arrived the following Sunday.This is not the first time that people have been injured on a Flight of the Gibbon zip line. Back in 2016, the same zip line was shut down after 3 Isreali tourists crashed against each other and fell.In 2017, a similar incident occurred where a Chinese and American woman collided head first against each other while traveling down the line.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/18/3815374/3815374_06EBAA6E4E544D1DAEB3B4EE12A8C740_190418_3815374_Man_plunges_4_stories_after_zip_line_breaks_in_T_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7DA/9A6/7DA9A600F1D7D9A9A943EABD6C734E19.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man falls from zip line, Canadian man falls from zip line Thailand, chiang mai, zip line, zip line accidents, zip line accident, zipline breaks, zipline thailand, Flight of the Gibbon, canopy accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815347</guid>
      <title>Fortnite is making its way into the office</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LEHI, UTAH  A software startup in Utah has found that playing Fortnite has helped with office efficiency. According to Quartz, co-founder and CEO of Podium Eric Rea can often be found playing Fortnite on his iPad after putting the kids in bed or while waiting in an airport loungewith his employees.Rea told Quartz it's a good way to blow off stress, while at the same time helping the team develop stronger communication and collaboration, both in the game and at the office. According to Quartz, Podium has around 480 employees and has raised almost $100 million to date. More than 30,000 local businesses use Podium tools to get more personalized insight into customer feedback and online reviews. Fortnite lets workers bond with their coworkers without having to even leave the office. And since you can play it on mobile devices like your phone or tablet, colleagues can play anytime and anywhere. Studies have shown that video games that require teamwork can help with office productivity. A recent study from Brigham Young University found that newly formed teams were 20 percent more productive after playing video games together for just 45 minutes. So what's the takeaway here? People really like playing Fortnite.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 13:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/18/3815347/3815347_C7A7641113E74A83832C2CF4B05627E6_190418_3815347_Fortnite_is_making_its_way_into_the_office_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5F4/F4C/5F4F4C05390CCC7470063044D99C46A5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Fortnite, Fortnite office, Fortnite at work, Fortnite Podium startup, Fortnite promotes communication, Fortnite promotes collaboration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815299</guid>
      <title>France's Notre Dame Cathedral to be rebuilt in the coming years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  French president Emmanual Macron has said he wants the Notre Dame Cathedral to be rebuilt within five years, according to the Washington Post.Notre Dame's roof and spire as well as 13,000 beams in the church's ceiling were destroyed in a massive fire on Monday.Dr. Emily Guerry, a lecturer of Medieval European History at a British University, told CBS News that these were made of ancient oak and would require around 3000 trees to replace them.She explained that it is now rare to find oak forests across Europe due to deforestation, adding that they might still be found in the Baltic.A temporary roof will need to be installed onto the cathedral to avoid further damage to its interior, the Washington Post reports.The stone exterior may also need to be significantly repaired or replaced, CBS News reports. The limestone used originally was sourced from Normandy in the 12th Century.Some of the stained glass windows remained intact while the fire had melted others. These would also need to be reconstructed by glaziers.For now, investigators are assessing the extent of the damage caused by the fire. According to the Washington Post, this itself could take more than a year. The exact cause of the fire remains unknown.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/18/3815299/3815299_FA4F5ACCFFE4416D90623CF938D4C01B_190418_3815299_France_s_Notre_Dame_Cathedral_to_be_rebuilt_in_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/938/D7B/938D7B3D430FFEB203AFB4252098D85E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, notre dame, notre dame cathedral, notre dame fire, notre dame spire collapse, notre dame burning, notre dame fire collapse, notre dame cathedral fire, notre dame rebuild, notre dame rebuilding plans, notre dame reconstruction, notre dame restoration, notre dame remains]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815283</guid>
      <title>Samsung's foldable smartphones already breaking for some users</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  Samsung users are complaining that their brand new foldable smartphones are breaking after just a few days of use, The Verge reports.The company claims that its new smartphones are able to withstand 200,000 folds and unfolds.Four smartphone reviewers were using the phone when they realized that the screens were flashing on and off and seemed to be disconnecting, CNBC reports.Reviewers with The Verge and Bloomberg noted that they "accidentally" removed a protective film that was on the screen.Another youtube tech reviewer said he had the same issue after removing the protective layer.Samsung quickly released a statement urging users not to remove the protective film on the phone screen.Another reviewer with CNBC said that they didn't remove the layer but had the same problem, with the left screen continuing to flicker on and off.So far Samsung hasn't responded.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 11:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/18/3815283/3815283_A17ECE3A9DBF487A8756D69A6D7A7BC8_190418_3815283_Samsung_s_foldable_smartphones_already_breaking__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BC4/8AA/BC48AA5BB909125AD7D178DA79FC96AD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, samsung, samsung galaxy fold, samsung galaxy fold broken, samsung galaxy fold breaking, samsung galaxy foldable, samsung galaxy foldable phone, samsung galaxy fold screen broke, samsung folding phone, samsung foldable smartphones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815275</guid>
      <title>Israeli scientists produce the world's first 3D-printed heart</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEL AVIV, ISRAEL  Researchers at Tel Aviv University have produced a heart using 3D printing technology and human tissue, according to a study published in the journal Advanced Science.The scientists first took a fat sample from a participant and then separated it into cellular and non-cellular materials.The researchers then took the cellular material and turned them into stem cells. This would eventually become heart cells.  They also took the non-cellular material and converted it into a hydrogel.The cells and the hydrogel were used to create heart patches complete with blood vessels and heart chambers, according to CNN.The researchers then used a 3D bioprinter to build the 3D heart layer by layer.In a news release by Tel Aviv University, Professor Tal Dvir, who was involved with the study, said that the 3D heart is small and is only the size of a rabbit's heart.The 3D heart is able to contract however, it currently does not have the ability to pump, according to the study.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 11:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/18/3815275/3815275_7B99F389E2CB45699AFEBD3BDB2ACDFF_190418_3815275_Israeli_scientists_produce_the_world_s_first_3D__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/68B/9CF/68B9CFF03D3D9F153949FD814F3B6ED3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, science, medical breakthrough, 3D printing, 3D printing human heart, world's first 3D printed heart, israel, 3D printing heart model, 3D printing heart in israel, world's first 3D-printed vascularized heart, 3D printed heart, 3D printed human heart, human tissue, human tissue printing, 3D printing human tissue, human tissue organ printing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815857</guid>
      <title>McDonald's ditching its fancy burgers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  McDonald's has announced it is simplifying it's already simple menu and ditching its craft burgers to focus on revamping its Quarter Pounder. According to Nation's Restaurant News, following a recent announcement that it is trimming down its late-night menu, you can also say adios to its premium burger line. According to CNN, the Golden Arches said it is moving away from its Signature Crafted Recipes lineguess they're not so signature after all. Over the past few months, Mickey D's has introduced new versions of its classic Quarter Pounder. You can now get one with bacon, and a deluxe version with lettuce and tomato. Both are supposedly prepared with fresh beefwhatever that means in McDonald's terms.  The fast foot juggernauts CFO Kevin Ozan told analysts that McDonald's wants to reduce the "complexity" of menus and store operations. Complexity? We are talking about McDonald's here, right?Apparently...all the new additions to the menu like all day breakfast, fresh beef and premium sandwiches has slowed down drive-thru times. So, it's the Quarter Pounder to the rescue. But will it work?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 11:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/19/3815857/3815857_2B47A31CC33845B39BF03D60666F0C4A_190419_3815857_McDonald_s_ditching_its_fancy_burgers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4A1/522/4A152285194C6FB5ED8FC85C34012208.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, McDonald's, McDonald's ditches premium burgers, McDonald's ditches Signature Crafted Recipe, McDonald's ditches craft burgers, McDonald's quarter pounder]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815855</guid>
      <title>Taiwanese police finally rocking some new threads</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN  Po po from Taiwan's National Police Agency have finally gotten a uniform upgrade after wearing the old gray getup for over 30 years. According to the Central News Agency, Taiwan's finest are now rocking a new dark blue shirt with blue pants, that have been designed to be more durable and comfortableand also to less look like a crossing guard. The shirt pocket buttons have been tossed and replaced with velcro for easier access. Here's a question thoughwhen's the last time you actually saw a Taiwanese cop ever use his or her shirt pockets?And of course no new police uniform would be complete without a proper snapback made from breathable mesh to reduce sweating. But honestlyit's Taiwan, those guys will be sweating either way. The pants also have been equipped with more pockets as well as having the knees reinforced with two layers of fabric for extra durability. The old hall monitor gray uniforms have been in use since 1987. Apparently, the police have been experimenting with different uniforms since 2016, but recently decided on the blue ones.Guess they really are the boysand girlsin blue now.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 11:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/19/3815855/3815855_DF1E1C99BA3B41418AE7C964ED683BF9_190419_3815855_Taiwanese_police_finally_rocking_some_new_thread_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/17F/202/17F202B14D10AE1348AB99AD22DCAAE3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwan police, Taiwan National Police Agency, Taiwan new police uniforms, Taiwan new police outfits]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815654</guid>
      <title>Google removes popular Chinese apps for committing ad fraud</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  Google has removed six apps from China from the company's Play Store following a Buzzfeed News investigation. Buzzfeed reports that they found at least six Chinese apps committing ad fraud and abusing users' permissions on the Android-focused digital marketplace. These apps are part of the DU group, which is a spinoff from Chinese giant Baidu.All the apps concealed their real identity and were collecting vast amounts of user data then sending it back to China, Buzzfeed reports.Ad fraud researchers Check Point and Method Media Intelligence found that the apps used a code which allowed them to automatically click on ads without the user ever finding out. This is so that it would be able to generate more income.The apps were able to do this even when users' didn't open them. The six apps are: Selfie Camera, Total Cleaner, Smart Cooler, RAM Master, AIO Flashlight and Omni Cleaners.Google has since pulled the popular Chinese apps and released a statement indicating that they would hire more people to evaluate apps in order to "prevent prevent bad-faith developers from gaming our systems."Richard Kramer, a senior analyst with Arete Research told Buzzfeed News, "Ad fraud is simply the norm in China, and Google should be doing far more to prevent it. They cannot claim ignorance of, or deny the problem."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 07:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/19/3815654/3815654_032A97ACC8E6452CB14DFFF2849F620D_190419_3815654_Google_removes_popular_Chinese_apps_for_committi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9ED/31E/9ED31EE2EF67719355E66C0E700C5D12.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, google, android apps, chinese android apps, ad fraud, digital ad fraud, android ad fraud, ad fraud on google, chinese apps, chinese apps on google, chinese apps ad fraud, google play store,  popular chinese apps pulled from google play store, google play store, click fraud, clicking fraudulent apps, du group ad fraud]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815606</guid>
      <title>Data harvesting: Facebook copied contacts from 1.5 million users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook has admitted to 'unintentionally' harvesting the contact lists of more than 1.5 million of its users, according to Business Insider. The report states that the company has been collecting emails from its users since May 2016. Facebook has said the information was 'unintentionally uploaded' and that they were working on taking it down.Last Wednesday, the social media giant told Business Insider that the contacts were uploaded into their system and used to improve the company's ad targeting, developing friend recommendations, and building its social web. Business Insider noticed the breach when a Twitter user called e-sushi, posted a screenshot where Facebook asked new users to confirm their email address.In the tweet, e-sushi stated it was, 'a horrible idea from an #infosec point of view. By going down that road, you're practically fishing for passwords you are not supposed to know!'. Screenshots posted by Business Insider show Facebook asked users to confirm their email address and password by clicking on a blue 'connect' button. After clicking the button, users would see a pop-up where Facebook informed them that it was importing their contacts. This process could not be interrupted or canceled.Facebook is now looking to notify the users that were affected by the privacy breach and deleting all contacts that were harvested from the 1.5 million accounts, saying in a statement, 'We've fixed the underlying issue and are notifying people whose contacts were imported. People can also review and manage the contacts they share with Facebook in their settings.']]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 06:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/19/3815606/3815606_4492037E02CD4158A71FD1215E218491_190419_3815606_Data_harvesting__Facebook_copied_contacts_from_1_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AB/43B/1AB43B7715B730B344F8E41BAB5C70A8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, facebook data harvest, facebook data breach, facebook privacy scandals, usa, facebook, user data, mark zuckerberg, facebook ads, facebook targeting ads, selling data to advertisers, facebook data policies, data transparency, facebook data collection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3815531</guid>
      <title>First life forms on Earth may have formed in ponds not oceans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON   New research by MIT suggests that ancient ponds may have been a more suitable place for early life to develop, not oceans, according to a recent study by MIT published in the journal Geochemistry, Geophysics, Geosystems.Ponds roughly 10 to 100 centimeters deep may have provided better conditions for primitive life forms to develop due to their high levels of nitrogen in the form of nitrogenous oxides.Nitrogenous oxides are a result of lightning strikes splitting nitrogen bonds in the atmosphere and are hypothesized to be part of the creation of life. A hypothesis states that life was developed when nitrogenous oxides and primitive RNA mixed, creating amino acids that would later become living organisms.The study found that ultraviolet light from the Sun and dissolved iron from rocks could have diluted concentrations of nitrogenous oxides in the ocean due to its large volume.Shallow bodies of water like ponds and puddles, on the other hand, could have held higher concentrations of the nitrogenous oxides and RNA molecules, allowing them to mix more easily and develop into living organisms.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/19/3815531/3815531_690E4A8C028947B19876CB3844D70965_190419_3815531_First_life_forms_on_Earth_may_have_formed_in_pon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3E1/836/3E18363496D3A4995CFFB6A7242E80D3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, origin of life, how life started, how life began, life on earth,  life origins, chemical evolution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817152</guid>
      <title>Universe's first molecule sighted 3,000 light years from Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  NASA has detected the first-ever molecule that formed in the universe, according to a new study published in the journal Nature.Scientists discovered the molecule helium hydride 3,000 light-years from Earth near a nebula called NGC 7027 in the Milky Way Galaxy.This is the first time the molecule has been detected in space after scientists tried to create it in a lab almost a century ago, The Guardian reports.According to a NASA news release, the molecule was located using the Stratospheric Observatory for Infrared Astronomy or SOFIA.Researchers believe the molecule formed 100,000 years after the big bang. Helium and hydrogen merged together to form the helium hydride molecule. This molecule is believed to have a crucial role in the beginning of the universe, according to the Guardian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 12:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/22/3817152/3817152_34925B5FD3864B718565FB7ECE291181_190422_3817152_Universe_s_first_molecule_sighted_3_000_light_ye_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9D7/D2B/9D7D2BE7273ECB7AFC12A4746FAEAFCD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa, universe, space, molecule, earliest molecule in the universe, astronomy, universe's first molecule, Helium hydride, Stratospheric Observatory for Infrared Astronomy, HeH nasa, NGC 7027, ancient molecule, beginning of the universe, planetary nebula, first molecule to ever form in space, molecule in space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817146</guid>
      <title>Sri Lanka bombings: How the attacks unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SRI LANKA  A set of coordinated bomb explosions on Easter Sunday in churches and hotels in Sri Lanka killed 207 and injured 450. Here is a timeline of how the bombings occurred.According to Reuters, from 8:45 a.m. to 9:05 a.m. on Easter Sunday, six bombs went off at three luxury hotels and three Christian churches in three different cities in Sri Lanka: Colombo, Negombo, and Batticaloa. Officials say most of the bombs were set off by suicide bombers.The first string of explosions occurred in the following places: the Shangri La hotel in Colombo, St. Anthony's Church in Kochchikade, Kotahena, Colombo, St. Sebastian Catholic Church in Negombo, the Kingsbury Hotel in Colombo, the Cinnamon Grand Hotel in Colombo, and the Zion Roman Catholic Church in Batticaloa.At 1:45 p.m., a seventh explosion went off at an inn close to the national zoo in Dehiwela, Colombo. At 2:15 p.m. another explosion followed, this time during a police raid at a house in Dematagoda, Colombo. Three officers were killed in the attack.At 5:20 p.m., authorities announce 207 people had been killed and 450 were injured. At 9:30 p.m., police arrest 13 Sri Lankan suspects. Later that same day, at around 10:30 p.m., police report a bomb attack on a mosque and arson attacks on two shops owned by Muslims.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 12:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/22/3817146/3817146_888040871A0B4A4B9E029AA5D633D486_190422_3817146_Sri_Lanka_bombings__How_the_attacks_unfolded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CDC/511/CDC51154DDBB0CCC91B2EF74E7FC1C52.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, sri lanka, sri lanka attacks, sri lanka bomb, sri lanka bombings, sri lanka terrorism, how sri lanka bombings happened, sri lanka attacks unfolded, bombings, blasts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817045</guid>
      <title>Coast guard fires stun grenade at rock-throwing Chinese fishermen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MATSU, TAIWAN  A Taiwan Coast Guard ship had an encounter with a bunch of rock-throwing Chinese fishermen that hilariously ended with a stun grenade.According to the Central News Agency, at 10:50 a.m. last Thursday, Chinese fishing boats were spotted in Taiwanese waters near Matsu.Despite repeated warnings from the Taiwanese Coast Guard patrol vessel to get a move on, the Chinese fishing boats refused and apparently thought hurling rocks would help the situation. The Coast Guard returned the favor by firing a stun grenade at one of the Chinese fishing vessels. The explosion caused the fishermen to reassess the situation and immediately high tail it back to Chinese waters. According to CNA, Chinese fishing boats were seen in Matsu waters several times last week, with Chinese crews reportedly throwing rocks at Taiwanese fishing boats on April 17. The Coast Guard Administration said it has sent additional patrol ships to the outlying islands to stop future Chinese fishing boat incursions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 09:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/22/3817045/3817045_074E400B1A85450C97BA597FAEEE3911_190422_3817045_Coast_guard_fires_stun_grenade_at_rock_throwing__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5B5/44C/5B544C82238A62F9701073C62C42E69B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwan Coast Guard, Chinese fishing boats, Taiwanese waters, Taiwanese Coast Guard, Taiwanese fishing boats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817028</guid>
      <title>Human Moon village plans released by design firm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  American architecture firm, Skidmore, Owings & Merrill LLP, worked with the European Space Agency and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology to develop a concept for the first self-sufficient human lunar settlement which they are calling 'Moon Village'.According to a press release by SOM, the village would be built on the edge of the Shackleton Crater which is located near the Moon's South Pole and receives a consistent amount of sunlight throughout the lunar year. The settlements would be placed near the crater's water-ice deposits. This water would be used to make breathable air as well as rocket fuel for transportation and industrial activities within the modules.Each inflatable module would be interconnected by pressurized walkways and have up to four floors which include workspaces, residential areas as well as life support and environmental systems built inside a protective shell made of regolith. This base would be resistant to extreme temperatures, projectiles, lunar dust, and solar radiation.For all you space junkies out there, don't get too excited, this is a proposal for space exploration after the year 2050. Regardless, humans on the moon again, ain't that exciting?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 09:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/22/3817028/3817028_61D400E13C13449199FB11EC161BD2CB_190422_3817028_Human_Moon_village_plans_released_by_design_firm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5B2/C8A/5B2C8A330F08FFDE72549F2A497F537F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, moon village, lunar settlement, lunar exploration, space exploration, european space agency, human moon colony, moon exploration, moon, Massachusetts Institute of Technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3816957</guid>
      <title>Man has swum across Yangtze for 11 years to cut work commute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  To cut down on his work commute time, a man in Wuhan has been swimming across the Yangtze River every day for the past 11 years. According to China News, 53-year-old Zhu Biwu would normally have to burn an hour to get to work if he had to take the train like everybody else.Time is money for Zhu, so he swims 2,200 meters (7,200 feet) across the Yangtze River which shaves 30 minutes off his commute. To get to his job as a food market manager, Zhu slaps on some trunks around 7 a.m., while he puts his clothes and shoes in an inflatable bag, which also doubles as a floatation device. Zhu was diagnosed with type 2 diabetes in 1999, and started the swim in 2008 as a way to get in shape. The daily swim has allowed him to lose weight and get his blood sugar levels back to normal. He's become such a regular site in the water boats on the river recognize him and always let him pass.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 07:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/22/3816957/3816957_480B21D023724941A03CEE5315CCBBDA_190422_3816957_Man_has_swum_across_Yangtze_for_11_years_to_cut__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/805/870/805870C4A41F2AEC0752D7A5BEA4DE95.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man swims across yangtze, work commute, man swims cuts commute, Chinese man swims across yangtze river, yangtze river work commute]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817733</guid>
      <title>Samsung to delay Galaxy Fold launch due to folding issues</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  Samsung is delaying the launch of its newest device, the Galaxy Fold, just days before its intended release date after several reviewers reported issues with the phone's foldable screen.The company first announced the Galaxy Fold on February 21, stating in a press release that the internal screen of the device was made of a special polymer layer that made its screen capable of bending.However, technology reviewers from The Wall Street Journal, Bloomberg, CNBC and The Verge all reported that the devices they had been given broke after only a few days of use. Some of them removed a protective layer that Samsung later clarified should not be taken off as it is part of the display structure.In their latest statement, Samsung explained that the malfunctions could have been related to damage to the exposed areas of the screen at the hinge of the phone, adding that one phone had substances inside that had interfered with the screen's display performance.The tech giant stated it would be announcing a new release date in the coming weeks and will use this time to, quote, 'evaluate this feedback and run further internal tests.']]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 11:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/23/3817733/3817733_8BA0291024B94F57869AD9584C9D5D10_190423_3817733_Samsung_to_delay_Galaxy_Fold_launch_due_to_foldi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BAA/35F/BAA35FCF5989677E8578784C3EA8FD7E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  samsung, samsung galaxy fold, samsung galaxy fold broken, samsung galaxy fold breaking, samsung galaxy foldable, samsung galaxy foldable phone, samsung galaxy fold screen broke, samsung folding phone, samsung foldable smartphoneS, foldable phone, samsung review]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817728</guid>
      <title>World's first air-breathing rocket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUCKINGHAMSHIRE, ENGLAND  The European Space Agency is teaming up with the U.K. Space Agency and U.K. aerospace manufacturer, Reaction Engines, to build the first rocket engine capable of feeding on atmospheric oxygen.The European Space Agency has approved testing for the first partially oxygen fueled rocket called the Synergistic Air-Breathing Rocket Engine, or SABRE, according to a press release.Its design allows it to reach speeds of up to five times the speed of sound using atmospheric air as fuel. Once it reaches 25 kilometers in altitude it will switch to rocket fuel. Having the rocket partially rely on oxygen means it would be lighter and capable of delivering cargo that weighs half the mass of current launchers. It would also cut down on costs and potentially facilitate higher launch rates.Testing for the SABRE will begin within the next 18 months at a new facility that is currently being built by Reaction Engines in Westcott, Buckinghamshire.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 11:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/23/3817728/3817728_8772C96F0AF64E47B5DA6FF8510EAA2D_190423_3817728_World_s_first_air_breathing_rocket_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1FC/001/1FC0013E09A70C93B3CD8ECD8882E874.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, world first air breathing rocket, first rocket, European space agency, Reaction Engines, Synergistic Air Breathing Rocket Engine, SABRE, space, rocket]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817690</guid>
      <title>Social media influencer tried to hijack someone's domain name</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CEDAR RAPIDS, IOWA  A social media influencer from Iowa is looking at 20 years in the pen for a harebrained scheme to hijack someone's domain name.    According to a statement from the U.S. Attorney's Office Northern District of Iowa, Rossi Lorathio Adams II was convicted of conspiracy to interfere with commerce by force, threats and violence last Thursday. According to the statement, 26-year-old Adams founded a social media company "State Snaps" and at one point had over a million followers over the typical sites.  According to ABC News, the sites mostly had images and clips of young adults acting intelligently, booze and birthday suits, often with the tag "Do It For State!"The statement said when Adams tried to buy the internet domain "doitforstate.com", he found out someone in Cedar Rapids had already registered it on GoDaddy.com. After the owner turned down repeated offers from Adams between 2015 and 2017 to buy the domain, Adams took to sending gun emojis to one of the owner's friends who used the domain to promo a concert. The social media influencer then came up with a horrible plan to get his cousin to try and force the owner at gunpoint to give the domain to Adams. Let's just say THAT plan failed after his cousin ended up getting blasted in the chest by his own gun. The cousin was sentenced to 20 years in June 2018. Adams is now in custody and looking at 20 years in prison, a fine of $250,000 and three years of supervised release following any imprisonment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 10:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/23/3817690/3817690_33BC863C695D4B22B8CB11B31AB10863_190423_3817690_Social_media_influencer_tried_to_hijack_someone__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7AB/52A/7AB52AE7FB7073CE1A21616948C85812.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, social media influencer, influencer, domain name, rossi lothario adams II, rossi lothario convicted]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817606</guid>
      <title>NASA telescope sights Earth-sized exoplanet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  NASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, or TESS, has located its first Earth-sized exoplanet outside the solar system, according to the U.S. space agency.The planet is called HD 21749c and it orbits the star HD 21749, according to a NASA news release. This celestial body is located 52 light years from Earth.The exoplanet circles the star every 7.8 days, according to an MIT news release. This means the exoplanet could have surface temperatures of up to 427 degrees Celsius due to its proximity to the star.According to MIT, a second planet called HD21749b also orbits the star. It has a longer orbit of 36 days. Researchers described it as a warm "sub-neptune."The exoplanet's diameter is around 89% the size of Earth's. It is likely to be rocky and uninhabitable, according to MIT researchers.NASA's TESS has been searching for new planets outside the solar system since it launched in April 2018.For now, the satellite has identified 10 planets and aims to identify a total of 50 before the end of its mission next year, according to MIT.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 08:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/23/3817606/3817606_7D987C360D094970BC48A8652F599020_190423_3817606_NASA_telescope_sights_Earth_sized_exoplanet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E65/EA9/E65EA9AD17957BC55DDFC488CD34B982.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa, universe, space, astronomy, nasa exoplanets, TESS, transiting exoplanet survey satellite, nasa tess exoplanet, nasa tess telescope, HD 21749, HD 21749c, HD 21749b, sub-Neptune, smaller earth-size exoplanets, smaller planets, exoplanets like earth, exoplanets 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3817510</guid>
      <title>Kid makes emergency call for some Mickey' D's</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  A boy in Michigan last week had an emergency craving for some McDonalds' so he dialled 911, according to local news station WZZM 13.Izaiah Hall's grandma was asleep and he really wanted to eat some burgers from the fast food chain. The five-year old decided to make an emergency call via a deactivated phone to 911. When he got through, he asked if they could bring him some McDonalds.The dispatcher who picked up the call said no and instead reached out to a police officer in Wyoming. When Officer Dan Patterson heard the story he said he laughed but still decided to surprise the boy by picking up some McDonald's en-route to the kid's house.No one responded when he knocked on the door, so Patterson tried the window instead.When Izaiah saw the officer he told him, "My grandma's gonna be so mad, can you please go away?"But, according to ABC 13, Izaiah his grandma wasn't mad. The news station reports, she was just happy that he'd learned about what an emergency really is.Sara Kuberski, the dispatcher who picked up the call said it was "really cool" for Patterson to go with McDonald's. Adding that the story made their night.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 05:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/23/3817510/3817510_07F34935821645729E869B81A509560A_190423_3817510_Kid_makes_emergency_call_for_some_Mickey__D_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BD5/D94/BD5D947A12988006637891FEA55E4EB3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mcdonalds, 911, police, mcdonalds stories, funny mcdonalds stories, mcdonald's 911 calls, mcdonalds 911 funny calls, five yera old boy calls 911 to get mcdonalds,  mcdonald's michigan, cops get mcdonalds for five year old boy,  fast food, fast food craving]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818396</guid>
      <title>Vulture causes fatal motorcycle crash in Kansas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BARBER COUNTY, KANSAS  A married couple were riding on their motorcycle through south-central Kansas when a vulture popped out of a ditch. According to the Wichita Eagle, Army veteran Brandon Husband and his wife, Jennifer Husband, were cruising southeast on River Roadwithout helmetson Saturday around 3:16 p.m. in Barber County. According to a Kansas Highway Patrol crash report, the vulture flew out and struck 42-year-old Husband in the head, causing him to go off the road. According to the report, the couple then veered into the ditch and then ran into a barbed wire fence before they overturned. Brandon didn't survive the freak accident, while Jennifer was transported to a Wichita hospital where she later succumbed to her injuries Saturday night. Social media posts show the two were avid bikers, with Jennifer often accompanying her husband. According to his obituary, Brandon was a member of the 82nd Airborne Division, serving one year in Kosovo and three in Afghanistan.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 12:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/24/3818396/3818396_F625E6BBAA21406CBEC8CB1BC118176A_190424_3818396_Vulture_causes_fatal_motorcycle_crash_in_Kansas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9A5/DB7/9A5DB7262EEFE12228EC88C9524B9372.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, motorcycle, vulture motorcycle, vulture motorcycle Kansas, vulture hits rider]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818379</guid>
      <title>Flushable wipe fatbergs clogging up New York's sewers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  New York may be number one in a lot of areas, but it's their Number Twos that are now getting them into trouble. According to the New York Post, the Big Apple has a pretty stinky fatberg problem clogging up its sewers because New Yorkers keep flushing things down the can they shouldn't be. According to the Post, the city Department of Environmental Protection blew $19 million last year removing fatbergs from the city's underbelly, a cost that has doubled in the past decade. The DEP had to wipe up 2,100 fatbergs throughout the city's sewer system in 2018. And if you spread the cheeks a bit, it looks like flushable wipes are the main culprits, accounting for 90 percent of the solids captured at sorting screens at 14 treatment plants around the city. According to the paper, the DEP sent more than 53,000 tons of wet wipes and other junk to landfills. Giant industrial-sized dumpsters are jammed with wipes day after day, and then trucked away numerous times a week. One reason for the log jam is that most wipes marketed as "flushable" don't actually disintegrate and thus the costly back ups. There's nothing wrong with a squeaky clean backside, just remember to throw it in the trash. You'd be doing a real SOLID for your local sewage treatment plant worker.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 11:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/24/3818379/3818379_E3B618CB44154ECA8E55592D00DE0BE3_190424_3818379_Flushable_wipe_fatbergs_clogging_up_New_York_s_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AF7/3D3/AF73D34E2AA2622A49E5F18CB5598573.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fatberg, fatberg removal, fatberg costly removal, New York fatberg, New York City fatbergs, New York sewers, flushable wipes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818372</guid>
      <title>Man wants to sue ex for breaking his package</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAINAN, TAIWAN    A Taiwanese man surnamed Wang, is trying to sue his ex-partner for a mishap that occurred the last time they two were together, according to ET Today.Apparently, the two wanted to part ways by sharing a last dirty dance together, but Wang's ex decided to leave him with a rather painful parting gift.The dynamic duo ended up getting a little too Fifty Shades of Grey for Wang and by that we mean he ended up in the police station claiming his once sturdy clarinet now looked like a, quote, 'swollen saxophone'. Ouch.Wang told the police he suspected his ex purposely made his instrument out of tune. We're guessing so he wouldn't be able to perform for anyone else?"Unfortunately for Wang, police let him know that they would only be able to catch the  saxophone destroyer if he had caught the whole ordeal on video, which he didn't.Fortunately, Wang's wang might not actually be broken. A Taiwanese urologist told SET News that his trombone might have just gotten congested and swollen from the performance. Hooray!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 11:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/24/3818372/3818372_4B4CA4D874A542BE8822BCA848B3549E_190424_3818372_Man_wants_to_sue_ex_for_breaking_his_package_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/45E/4F0/45E4F01343DB1162EC685AE17A57AEDE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, breakups, relationships, man sues ex, accidents in the bedroom, man sues ex girlfriend, broken banana]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818343</guid>
      <title>NASA's Insight Lander detects first marsquake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE   NASA's Insight lander has sent back signals from the first ever marsquake, according to NASA. On April 6, scientists received data describing possible seismic waves in Mars detected by NASA's Insight lander. This was the first seismic recording that might have come from within the planet and not caused by exterior movement.The lander's seismometer detected three other seismic signals on March 14, April 10, and April 11. These waves were much smaller than the one detected on April 6 and their exact cause remains unknown.The marsquake was detected by the lander's Seismic Experiment for Interior Structure, or SEIS, which is designed to pick up seismic waves while at the same time insulating its sensors from wind and other external elements that might interfere with signals. "The weakest movements were detected by Insight's Very Broad Band sensors, an ultrasensitive instrument containing three pendulums that register movements on the Martian surface.The lander also carries a heat probe that can penetrate 5 meters into the surface of the planet to measure its heat flow and interior temperature and two antennas called RISE that will help determine the size and composition of the planet's core.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 10:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/24/3818343/3818343_7026A6320962438DB0C723E81D5B6113_190424_3818343_NASA_s_Insight_Lander_detects_first_marsquake_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AE8/418/AE8418AE4A9D6FCBB7DC694540503B92.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mars, space, NASA, insight, lander, insight lander, mars exploration, explore, can we live on mars, space travel, land on mars, spacecraft, astronaut, survive on mars, space exploration, NASA mission, 2018 launch, insight lander update]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818118</guid>
      <title>Washington state passes bill that would allow human composting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Washington state lawmakers have passed a bill to allow human composting, according to CNN.If Governor Jay Inslee decides to sign Senate Bill 5001 into law, it is to take effect on May 1, 2020.Recomposition is the process of turning bodies of deceased humans into soil.Katrina Spade, the CEO of Recompse, a company that wants to build a human composting facility, explained the process to KIRO 7. She said the body is covered in natural materials such as straw or wood chips. Microbes then break down the body into the soil over a period of three to seven weeks.Relatives can then choose to keep the soil in urns, use it to plant trees or spread it on public land in Washington state, according to the Associated Press.CNN quotes the bill's sponsor Senator Jamie Pederson as saying that, "People should have the freedom to determine for themselves how they'd like their body to be disposed of..."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 06:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/24/3818118/3818118_CBFC566E3740422895513E1F2284C01B_190424_3818118_Washington_state_passes_bill_that_would_allow_hu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC5/B6B/DC5B6BCBA0AA099E95B651171F4B41E1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, usa, washington DC, senate, bill, natural organic reduction, human composting, human remains, recomposition, Senate Bill 5001, senate bill 5001 washington state, legalizing human composting, natural organic reduction, concerning human remains, human composting bill, human composting bill washington, human composting burial, converting human remains to soil, disposing of human remains]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818082</guid>
      <title>Japan taxi ads use facial recognition to guess your gender</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Taxis in Japan are using facial recognition to record footage of passengers' faces for personalized advertising, reports technology news website Futurism.Google Privacy Engineer Rosa Golijan posted a photo of the tech on Twitter. The April 21 image shows a panel screen with text reading, "The image data is used to estimate gender in order to deliver the most optimized content." It further notes that "data is discarded immediately after the estimation processing. Neither the tablet nor the server records the data."Going deeper, Futurism reports that, another user called "@BenParker140" posted an image from Tokyo. His photo provides some context, saying the technology is called "Premium Taxi Vision." Futurism reports that a QR code in this photo connects to a website about the technology. Apparently it's from Japanese e-commerce giant and mobile provider DeNA.There, the company explains that the data gathered "would not allow an individual to be identified." It also says it shares the info with Genie Inc, an ad technology company, in order to get "optimal" ad content for riders.According to the website, the data snapped from your cab's backseat tablet cam includes video of your face. This is then computed to guess your age and sex, before hitting you with some tailored ads. There is an opt-out though and this can be disabled. As the DeNA website explains, you first tap on the menu button on the right of the screen, next tap about use of our camera footage and then disable content optimization.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/24/3818082/3818082_D05D0E7CD97E4D9681296FEED936BDA3_190424_3818082_Japan_taxi_ads_use_facial_recognition_to_guess_y_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C1B/A9D/C1BA9D2109F316CECB701A105A81DD10.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Japan taxi facial recognition, tablet cam tokyo cab, privacy, internet of things, dena facial recognition, Geniee Inc, technology news, transportation, personalized advertising, TomoNews, Satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818005</guid>
      <title>Boeing 787 Dreamliner plant hit by claims of poor production</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH CHARLESTON, SOUTH CAROLINA  Poor production and oversight at a Boeing factory may compromise the safety of the company's 787 Dreamliner jets, current and ex-staff of the plant have told the New York Times.Joseph Clayton, a technician at the plant, told the New York Times he frequently found debris close to the wiring underneath the cockpits.The New York Times cites former Boeing employees as saying that tools and metal shavings have repeatedly been left inside the planes and close to electrical systems. One anonymous source told the paper that test flights have been performed with debris in the plane's engine and tail.John Barnett, a former quality manager with Boeing said he noticed "clusters of metal slivers" hanging from wirings that direct flight control in several planes. He added that if the metal pieces were to go through the wires, it would be "catastrophic."A spokesman for the Federal Aviation Administration, told the New York Times that they had found those same metal slivers even though Boeing had said their planes did not contain such debris. He explained that these could cause electrical shortages and, potentially, a fire.Ex-staff were pressured by the company to not report violations, according to the New York Times. The newspaper reports that workers were told to keep on building Dreamliner jets regardless of any issues raised.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 03:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/24/3818005/3818005_CB22356249DC44C0ADD0DD11E83F5541_190424_3818005_Boeing_787_Dreamliner_plant_hit_by_claims_of_poo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6F5/0C6/6F50C63ADB196DE587BEDAAFFE3EC9F2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, boeing 787 dreamliner, boeing dreamliner factory, south carolina, boeing 787 dreamliner safety issues, boeing 787 dreamliner issues, dreamliner safety issues, boeing airplanes, boeing aircraft, boeing airplane factory, boeing airlines, boeing airline safety issues, boeing charleston]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818987</guid>
      <title>How do SpaceX and Boeing launch abort systems work?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA  Last Saturday, SpaceX's Crew Dragon capsule exploded after suffering what the company referred to as an 'anomaly' during engine tests in Cape Canaveral, Florida. Here is how the launch abort systems work in case of emergency.According to Space.com, crewed launch missions are usually aborted through either the 'pull' or 'push' method. The 'pull' method is the oldest abort mechanism. Capsules that use this method have rocket boosters on the tip of the capsule. These thrusters pull the capsule away from the rocket in the event of a mission abort.Newer capsules, such as SpaceX's Crew Dragon use the 'push' mechanism. The Crew Dragon has thrusters mounted on the exterior of the capsule's wall and eight SuperDraco engines installed in the hull. These engines help 'push' the capsule away from the rocket. According to SpaceX founder, Elon Musk, these thrusters and the parachutes installed in the Crew Dragon are designed to help secure a safe landing. Boeing's CST-100 Starliner also uses a 'push' mechanism similar to the one on the Crew Dragon, however, their capsules are equipped with four RS-88 engines built by Aerojet Rocketdyne.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 12:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/25/3818987/3818987_382B6A81E7384753A2E5CE541E8C3ED0_190425_3818987_How_do_SpaceX_and_Boeing_launch_abort_systems_wo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ED3/178/ED3178F0CA555F4B6C248DB811E7ABA3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, SpaceX, Boeing, Crew Dragon, Elon Musk, Cape Canaveral, launch abort system. Boeing Starliner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818978</guid>
      <title>Moving blobs in Earth's core may be linked to geomagnetic jerks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  The origin of geomagnetic jerks are unknown, but new research on the topic offers a possible explanation.Earth's magnetic field serves as a protection against solar and cosmic radiation. It originates in the Earth's core. Whenever there is movement in the core, Earth's magnetic field shifts. When these movements occur suddenly, they are called geomagnetic jerks.According to a new study published in the journal Nature Geoscience, Earth's sudden magnetic shifts may be caused by floating blobs of molten matter originating from the depths of the Earth's core.The team of researchers developed a computer simulation that mimics movements on the Earth's outer core over several decades, effectively recreating the conditions that take place right before a geomagnetic jerk will happen.Results showed that the sudden jerks happened when the Earth's inner core emitted hydromagnetic waves. As these waves move outwards and reach the surface of the Earth's core they become amplified and create movements that can be compared to geomagnetic jerks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 12:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/25/3818978/3818978_103484E6AA9B4A83AA95079F4DE910F9_190425_3818978_Moving_blobs_in_Earth_s_core_may_be_linked_to_ge_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A08/C58/A08C587AB1913DE1D95ECBEEA570C602.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, earth, earth core, geomagnetic wave, geomagnetic jerk, geomagnetic field, earth magnetic field]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818911</guid>
      <title>China bans blood, bodies, poker and more in video games</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Great news for gamers in China as the fun-loving Communist Party has released fresh guidelines to make video gaming enjoyable for everyoneexcept those playing them. According to Engadget, three types of games will now be sent to virtual concentration camps: Mahjong and poker, games based on China's imperial past, and games that have bodies or bloodof any color.Developers that went all in designing poker and Mahjong games made up a whopping 37 percent of the titles approved in 2017.According to Engadget, China's new super laid back gaming authority, the State Administration of Press and Publication, says it's worried about violence and gambling addiction in young people. Under the new rules, game makers must also introduce anti-addiction systems into their games, whatever that means. Other initiatives include asking publishers to change how their titles promote Chinese values and culture so that if the games go global, they'll put China in a good light. The new super fun regulations also require developers to give up information about a given title including detailed scripts and screenshots.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 10:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/25/3818911/3818911_403E231C214841C4B0F2FACECEF54301_190425_3818911_China_bans_blood__bodies__poker_and_more_in_vide_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A5B/5E3/A5B5E33485EA36FDDA79CC6D251CD033.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, China video games, China video game rules, China video game bans, China video game guidelines, China video game market]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818764</guid>
      <title>Malawi to begin test run of new  malaria vaccine for children</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LILONGWE, MALAWI  Malawi will begin a large-scale pilot of vaccinating children with the RTS,S vaccine to partially protect them from malaria, CNN reports.RTS,S is the first and only vaccine in the world that has been found to significantly reduce malaria in children, according to the World Health Organization.This new vaccine would teach the immune system to attack malaria parasites. These parasites are typically spread by mosquito bites.The vaccine would only be administered to children under the age of 2. According to the WHO, children under the age of five are the most vulnerable to malaria.The African nations of Ghana and Kenya will also start administering the vaccine in their countries in the next few weeks.An estimated 435,000 deaths worldwide were caused by malaria. Children accounted for 61 percent or 266,000 of malaria deaths worldwide in 2017, according to a report by the World Health Organization.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 08:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/25/3818764/3818764_E7519E173FBD473E85759B0DD10C828D_190425_3818764_Malawi_to_begin_test_run_of_new__malaria_vaccine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/869/728/869728DC038F47AC53AB1AAEA00665B9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, malawi, vaccine, malaria, malaria vaccine, malawi vaccine malaria, malaria vaccine 2019, malaria vaccine development, malaria vaccine child, rts s vaccine, rts s vaccine malawi, malaria cases, immunization, immunization for malaria, malaria shots, malaria shots africa, malaria parasite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818731</guid>
      <title>UK okays use of Huawei for 
'non-core' 5G network tech</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  The UK is to let Chinese telecoms giant Huawei build part of the country's 5G network despite security concerns from the U.S, reports the BBC.The British government has approved the use of Huawei technology in "non-core" telecommunications infrastructure, such as antennas. The U.S. suspects Huawei tech can be accessed by the Chinese government via backdoors and used for surveillance or sabotage. According to the BBC, Huawei denies this and allegations it is controlled by the Chinese authorities.   Citing a UK source, The Times reports the U.S. shared evidence with the UK that Huawei had received financing from Chinese military and intelligence bodies. The newspaper reports American intelligence also shared this with Canada, New Zealand and Australia. These countries, along with the U.S. and the UK, form an intelligence alliance called the Five Eyes. Explaining the U.S. stance on the use of Huawei tech in networks, Rob Joyce, a senior U.S. National Security Agency advisor, told the Financial Times, "We are not going to give them the loaded gun."The former advisor to U.S. President Donald Trump said, "What we will be insistent on is UK decisions can't put our information at risk but the good news is that the UK already understands that."The BBC reports Australia won't use Huawei technology, while Canada and New Zealand are still undecided. The UK's decision to allow Huawei into the fold may sway those on the fence.Information about the decision to allow the use of Huawei tech is believed to have been leaked from a UK National Security Council meeting on Tuesday.  The leak was described to the BBC by a senior UK minister as quote "extraordinary … the security council is the holy of holies."According to the Guardian, several UK ministers were said to have been opposed to the move and wanted a complete ban on the use of Huawei in the 5G network. The newspaper reports that top level officials including the UK defence and foreign secretaries have expressed concern over Huawei.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 07:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/25/3818731/3818731_A2C496D8B1FB48919E4A69B073CE2195_190425_3818731_UK_okays_use_of_Huawei_for___non_core__5G_networ_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/627/AFE/627AFE112707E9DCB261BCB34EE387F2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[UK Huawei 5G ban, spying, China, Huawei explainer, what is huawei, chinese government, 5g tech,  five eyes alliance, australia, US China cybersecurity, technology news, networking, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3818594</guid>
      <title>Japan's Hayabusa2 probe blasts crater into Asteroid Ryugu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN  The Hayabusa2 space probe ejected a small carry-on impactor or SCI onto the surface of Asteroid Ryugu a couple of weeks ago, according to NHK News.The impactor would analyze the asteroid's interior. The cone-shaped device was released as the spacecraft was 500 meters above the asteroid. The device is said to have exploded 40 minutes after the launch, NHK News reports.According to a JAXA press release, as soon as the impactor was launched, the Hayabusa2 space probe released a camera to capture images of the explosion.The crater is expected to be around 2 meters in diameter, according to the European Space Agency.The Hayabusa2 spacecraft had previously deployed two rovers that explored Ryugu's surface. They transmitted images and data of the asteroid back to Earth.The probe had also touched down on the asteroid in February to collect rock samples. Hayabusa2 is expected to return to Earth in 2020 with its cargo.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 03:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/25/3818594/3818594_6D434C261E9B42CD9FB7A5B7A3A66B16_190425_3818594_Japan_s_Hayabusa2_probe_blasts_crater_into_Aster_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ADC/3B2/ADC3B211AB7F1C751F682F6FF32CBEAF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space, japan, japanese asteroid mission, Ryugu, Hayabusa 2, jaxa, jaxa spacecraft, ryugu asteroid,  japanese spacecraft asteroid, Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency, Hayabusa 2 experiment, small carry-on impactor, Hayabusa 2 mission,  hayabusa 2 ryugu, hayabusa 2 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3819686</guid>
      <title>Man drives Mario Kart over Tokyo Highway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  A man went full Mario Kart on a Japanese highway crossing over to, get this, Rainbow Bridge. Nintendo vibes anyone?According to TBS News, a man boosted down a highway in Tokyo and went all Mario Kart, and by that we mean he literally raced through a highway and a bridge in a Go-Kart, making the hopes and dreams of all Mario fans a reality, what a hero.Mario was happily collecting coins down the Metropolitan Expressway in Odaiba, a man-made island in Tokyo Bay, around 9 p.m. on Sunday until a clerk at a toll gate called the po-po on our hero. Probably Wario.The po-po quickly joined the race, but sadly for them, Japanese Mario had some blue turtle shells under his sleeve. After bamboozling police, Mario quickly took a turn and drove away into Rainbow Bridge. Yes, that's the actual name of the bridge he took. Why Rainbow Bridge though?  That's like the hardest course. Hopefully, he didn't run into any banana peels on the way out.If you want to make your Mario dreams come true, you can! In Tokyo, Mario Kart enthusiasts can drive karts on designated roads without helmets and seat belts as long as they keep it under 60 kilometers, or 37.28 miles,  per hour. Just make sure you don't go on highwayunless you're going to make a video about it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 15:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/26/3819686/3819686_E2FD9959925E477DAF8AF978CFED0D02_190426_3819686_Man_drives_Mario_Kart_over_Tokyo_Highway_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8D9/D69/8D9D698A357D7D912F7E986C84B06C3E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mario kart, mario kart drifting, mario kart drift, mario kart driving, mario kart in real life, mario kart tokyo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3819466</guid>
      <title>11 workers die after elevator cable snaps in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HENGSHUI, CHINA  Eleven workers are no longer around and two seriously hurting after an elevator cable snapped at a construction site in northern China, state media reported.According to a local government statement, the accident happened on the Jade Huating development, a massive residential property being built. The Voice of China radio said the freak accident occurred around 8 a.m. in the city of Hengshui in Hebei province. Apparently, the elevator cable snapped, causing the construction site elevator to collapse. Local reports did not say how far the elevator fell. A witness told local media six or seven ambulances quickly arrived on scene.According to the statement, the two injured workers were being treated at a local hospital and appear to be in stable condition.  Authorities have begun investigations to determine the cause of the accident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 09:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/26/3819466/3819466_FDD331A232BE4AFDA6D7E62B640BD38F_190426_3819466_11_workers_die_after_elevator_cable_snaps_in_Chi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DDB/F40/DDBF40248C6035DFD1D369F02D6B1CAF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China elevator, China elevator malfunction, construction site elevator, China construction site accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3819344</guid>
      <title>China wants to build its own base on the moon in the next decade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Beijing plans to build a research station on the moon in the next 10 years, according to Chinese state media outlet China DailyThe facility is planned to be placed near the moon's south pole region where it will be used to conduct scientific research.Zhang Kejian, the head of the China National Space Administration, made the announcement on China's fourth annual Space Day, on April 24th. China's other space exploration plans include a mission to launch a Mars probe by 2020 and the lunar probe Chang'e-5 by the end of this year.China also announced that its space station, the Tiangong, is set to go into orbit in the year 2022.According to AFP, China now spends more on its space program than Russia and Japan, and is second only to the US.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 07:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/26/3819344/3819344_D6AE492DF3C343A99EAC1B5843B63C44_190426_3819344_China_wants_to_build_its_own_base_on_the_moon_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B10/42F/B1042FA7BA6D117C2B3D28D2D93502E1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, space, moon, moon south pole, moon mission, moon mission china, china manned mission to the moon,  moon south pole china, China National Space Administration, China space program, China space moon, china space agency, china space race, china moon station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3819329</guid>
      <title>Scientists create speech using brain recordings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO, CALIFORNIA  New research from the University of California San Francisco found that brain recordings can be converted into speech.According to a paper published in the journal Nature, neuroscientists from UC San Francisco have developed a technology that can convert brain recordings into synthetic speech using a computer simulation model with lips, jaw, tongue, and larynx. The team recorded brain signals of subjects that already had electrode arrays implanted in their brains for previous medical procedures. Subjects would read sentences out loud while the researchers captured the signals through the electrodes.They then analyzed the audio and observed which muscles were activated at different points during speech.Using this information, they developed  a simulation that would transform brain activity into muscle movements in a virtual vocal tract and in turn, turn the movements into a synthetic voice.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 07:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/26/3819329/3819329_1A4BDA85C8BD4D62B98FA30DC89F5EF4_190426_3819329_Scientists_create_speech_using_brain_recordings_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9AE/1CD/9AE1CDDB5379CBA19D08963AE7182CFB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, brain to speech, speech to brain, brain recordings, converting brain recordings to speech, changing brain recordings to speech, turning brain recordings to speech]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3819191</guid>
      <title>Delivery drones: FAA approves Alphabet-owned Wing for flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Alphabet-owned Wing has now become the first company in the US to get approved by the Federal Aviation Administration to use drones for delivering goods, Reuters reports.According to a Medium blog post by Wing, the delivery firm has officially become the first drone company to receive an Air Carrier Certification from the FAA.The blog post went on to explain that the certificate would allow them to start a commercial service of delivering goods to American homes.Each drone weighs about 5 kg and will be able to carry packages weighing up to 1.5 kg, according to Wing's website. The drones are able to fly roughly 20 km per round trip.While delivering, the drone hovers around 7 meters above the ground and slowly lowers the package. Delivery goods are attached to a line. The package automatically disconnects from the line when the goods touch the ground and then the drone flies away, allowing the customer to pick up the package.Wing has already begun its delivery service in the north of Canberra, Australia and is set to begin a trial in Helsinki, Finland, Reuters reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/26/3819191/3819191_32219C86056C4D38BE81B6312876A79F_190426_3819191_Delivery_drones__FAA_approves_Alphabet_owned_Win_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/438/2C9/4382C9AEA6A3D370F4D2EE707BBDF93E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Google, Alphabet, google alphabet project wing, Project Wing, self-flying vehicles, drone, drone delivery, packages, Wing, tech, technology, google wing drone, google wing drone delivery, google wing drone delivery usa, drone technology 2019, google drone technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3820855</guid>
      <title>Flesh-eating bacteria infects Florida fisherman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAMPA  A Florida fisherman will live to fish another day after contracting a scary flesh-eating bacteria while out fishing in the Gulf of Mexico. According to WFTS, Mike Walton was out fishing Saturday about 20 miles off the coast of Palm Harbor when he was struck by a fish hook. According to Walton, it was a small prick, something that has happened hundreds of times while fishing. According to WFTS, Walton stopped by a hospital to pick up some antibiotics for his hand that started to swell up.By Sunday morning, his hand had black blisters bubbling up all over his hand. He was immediately taken to Tampa General Hospital and put in the burn unit so he could be treated for necrotizing fasciitis. At one point, physicians had to consider amputating Walton's arm, but luckily they were able to get inside his arm and get all the bacteria out from his tissues. According to Walton, he received a skin graft going from his elbow to the palm of his hand. Doctors told Walton the infection is contained, but he'll have to be on antibiotics for about another month while he heals up.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 12:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/29/3820855/3820855_611B89C57C994595A37E1C51DFE2F5B9_190429_3820855_Flesh_eating_bacteria_infects_Florida_fisherman_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F7/93C/8F793C51065BFBDF26912EC24098681E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, flesh eating bacteria, fisherman flesh eating bacteria, necrotizing fasciitis, Florida man flesh eating bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3820844</guid>
      <title>"Kissing bug" identified in Delaware for the first time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENT COUNTY , DELAWARE  Triatomines, often called kissing bugs, are insects that suck blood and bite the faces of people, while they are asleep, according to the Center for Disease Control and Prevention.Some of these kissing bugs carry a parasite known as Trypanosoma cruzi. This is a parasite that could potentially cause Chagas disease. However, not all triatomine bugs carry the parasite.If the parasite is present, it will be in the insects' feces. The parasite is able to enter the skin of a person that is bitten if the insect's poop has accidentally been rubbed into the person's bite wound or into a mucous membrane such as the eyes or the mouth."Initial symptoms of Chagas disease include fever, body aches, headaches and rashes. According to the CDC, the disease may result in cardiac complications or intestinal complications for some. Anti-trypanosomal medication can be used to treat Chagas disease.In order to prevent the spread of the disease, the CDC recommends sealing gaps and cracks around windows and walls as well as repairing any holes and tears on screen doors.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 12:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/29/3820844/3820844_9B79F37949C2490180730F6F1848B155_190429_3820844__Kissing_bug__identified_in_Delaware_for_the_fir_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE1/A6C/EE1A6CF7A1EE8215168E1F456121D512.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Kissing bug disease, kissing bug, Triatomine bug, Chagas disease, Chagas disease symptoms, disease, infected animal, infected person, infected bug, Trypanosoma cruzi parasite, parasite, infection, illness, CDC, kissing bug delaware]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3820822</guid>
      <title>Five men trapped in Virginia cave rescued</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUSSELL COUNTY, VIRGINIA  Emergency crews pulled out five men from a cave in Virginia on Sunday night after heavy rains trapped them inside the cavern, according to CBS News.On Friday night, six men entered a cave located in southwest Virginia called Cyclops Cave. They intended to camp inside it until Sunday morning, but heavy downpour on Saturday trapped them inside.One of the men managed to get out on Sunday morning at around 2 a.m. and call 911. The temperature inside the cave was around 50 degrees Fahrenheit.Authorities stated that the remaining men, ranging in age from 34 to 59, were beginning to suffer from fatigue and hypothermia. They had no extra food or water with them and didn't have the proper gear to climb out of the cave.  The emergency team began work on Sunday at 10:30 a.m. and finished the rescue around 6:00 p.m. One of the men had to be taken to a health center via air transport.Frankie Smith, who owns the property where Cyclops Cave is located, told WJHL-TV that no one had been trapped in it before and that the men had not asked for permission to enter.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 11:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/29/3820822/3820822_D800D33A616B4767B5C74C42F2BC3009_190429_3820822_Five_men_trapped_in_Virginia_cave_rescued_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/351/717/35171725534D2A4462A6A71FDA7482A5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, virginia, virginia cave, cyclops cave, virginia cave rescue, cyclops save, cyclops cave rescue, men cave rescue, men trapped in cave]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3820784</guid>
      <title>Extreme ocean waves are getting more extreme</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE   A 33-year-old study led by the University of Melbourne shows ocean wind and waves are increasing in intensity and height.Researchers from the University of Melbourne studied wind speed and wave heights using roughly 4 billion observations from 31 different satellites that had been recorded between 1985 to 2018. The data extracted from the satellites was also compared to measurements from more than 80 ocean buoys around the world.Results from the study showed that strong winds in the Southern Ocean have increased by eight percent in the last 30 years. At the same time, extreme waves have increased by 5 percent, which equates to roughly 30 centimeters more in height.Extreme winds have also risen in the Pacific, Atlantic, and the North Atlantic by roughly 0.6 meters per second over the last 30 years.Changes in the Southern Ocean also affect wave climates in the South Pacific, South Atlantic and Indian Oceans, and determines the stability of beaches in the Southern Hemisphere.These fluctuations in wave and wind intensity can also increase the probability of coastal flooding and erosion which puts coastal communities at risk.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 10:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/29/3820784/3820784_A931608DE6A64F59B24ED831DD3FCD78_190429_3820784_Extreme_ocean_waves_are_getting_more_extreme_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/309/744/309744D5B02B18DE106496CC553B769D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, southern ocean, extreme waves, extreme winds, Pacific ocean, Atlantic ocean, north Atlantic ocean, ocean levels, extreme climate change, strong winds, big waves, huge waves, tall waves]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3820623</guid>
      <title>Robot spacecraft to clean up space debris surrounding Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TROY, NEW YORK  Researchers at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute are developing a new orbital device that would aid in cleaning up space debris surrounding the planet.There are around 128 million pieces of debris in space as of January 2019, according to a report by the European Space Agency.According to a news release by the institute, the spacecraft will be called OSCaR or Obsolete Spacecraft Capture and Removal. The space probe will be a CubeSat, a small, rectangular satellite, which will be made of up three 10 cm x 10 cm x 10 x cm units. The first CubeSat units will contain GPS, data storage and communication systems while the second will consist of a propulsion system. The third unit would contain nets and tethers which would be used to capture the space debris.The device will be sent to outer space aboard larger spacecrafts and then be released.OSCaR would use sensors such as thermal and RADAR imaging sensors to help locate and capture space debris.The spacecraft will automatically destroy itself and all the debris it has captured within five years, according to the Rensselaer Institute news release.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 05:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/29/3820623/3820623_C17B1BAD8128489D832E75D70BE72FA3_190429_3820623_Robot_spacecraft_to_clean_up_space_debris_surrou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/383/F58/383F58E51A5BFEADF721523AAC26A206.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space, orbital debris gathering spacecraft, OSCaR spacecraft, Obsolete spacecraft capture and removal, space junk, space debris, space debris cleanup, space debris around Earth, space junk around earth, cleaning up space debris, CubeSat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3820619</guid>
      <title>Chinese granny Spiderverses down high rise apartment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENGDU, CHINA  An 84-year-old Chinese granny with Alzheimer's went straight Spiderverse when she climbed down a high-rise building from her apartment on the 14th floor. According to the SCMP, Daredevil made it out onto the side of the building from her bathroom window.According to property management workers, the old lady was forced to spidey her way down after her family locked her in the bathroom. That's one way to respect your elders.    As Spider-Gran came down, neighbors unfolded a bedsheet to try and catch her in case she fell. Building workers unfortunately cut grandma's adventure short when they pulled her in from a 5th floor window. She was given something to eat and some water, while she waited around for relatives to come get her.   Granny will hopefully live to scale another day as reports said she escaped the escapade injury free.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 05:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/04/29/3820619/3820619_5A188A84102E41889D5BCEB3503C2EA1_190429_3820619_Chinese_granny_Spiderverses_down_high_rise_apart_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8C8/534/8C8534E8B57007A458D5CFA71F9B54BE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, grandma climbs down apartment building, grandma climbs down, old woman climbs down , China grandma climbs down]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
