<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 19:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3942899</guid>
      <title>Louisiana town crop-dusted with 100 gallons of holy water</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COW ISLAND, LOUISIANA  Hashtag blessed just took on a whole 'nother meaning. NPR reports that after church on the Saturday before Christmas, Catholic residents of Cow Island, Louisiana got over a hundred gallons of water blessed by their parish priest.He didn't do it at church though, but at an airstrip, where the newly holy H2O can go straight into a crop dusting plane and bless absolutely everyone – whether you like it or not.Word of the mass blessing got out fast enough that families who sauntered out of their houses got a big dose of holy from the heavens above.Rev. Fr. Matthew Barzare, who blessed the water, assured everyone there was no pesticide residue in the tank around this time of the year.Good to know we're not creating pesticide mutants in the image of God.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942899/3942899_16C578E6A49F4F579C5A970698869F45_191231_3942899_Louisiana_town_crop_dusted_with_100_gallons_of_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/934/7E1/9347E174BA038F08018088769A051F0D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Holy water, Crop duster, holy water crop duster, crop duster blessing, holy water spray, community blessing, christmas blessing, mass blessing, catholic blessing, cow island, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942862</guid>
      <title>North Korea 'ghost ship' washes up on Japanese island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SADO ISLAND, JAPAN  Japanese authorities discovered the bow of a wooden boat believed to be from North Korea on the coast of Japan's Sado Island in the Sea of Japan on December 27.Seven partially skeletonized remains were found inside the vessel, reports NHK World News. Three bodies were found with heads, two bodies were found without heads and two heads were found without bodies, the Associated Press reports, citing officials. All of the bodies were confirmed to be male, though officials said it is unclear whether or not the separate heads and the bodies came from the same people.According to NHK World News, the side of the boat bore Korean characters and numbers that were painted in red.The vessel's bow was measured to be roughly 7.6 meters long and 2 meters in height."These boats could have been involved in illegal fishing operations in the Sea of Japan, Nikkei Asian Review reports, citing authorities. Mitsuhiro Mimura, a researcher at Japan's Economic Research Institute for Northeast Asia, told the publication that this is partially due to the fact that North Korea sold fishing rights around its own coastal areas to China, forcing North Korea fishermen to go further out at sea in run down wooden boats.A number of wooden boats typically wash ashore during this time of the year after northwesterly winds blow the vessels off course, as reported by NHK World News.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 07:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942862/3942862_B097B63A64D64C36BA07EAF52C3E3FC3_191231_3942862_North_Korea__ghost_ship__washes_up_on_Japanese_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EF3/691/EF36918D054B3EC3DDF5061B331A8ED4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[north korea ghost ship, dprk ghost ship, ghosts ships, sea of japan ghost ships, north korea mysterious ships, north korean boats japan, north korean boats, north korean wooden boats, north korean fishing boats, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942825</guid>
      <title>China's very own navigation system, Beidou, near completion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China announced on December 27 that it is only a few months away from completing its own satellite-based position system called Beidou.China has already launched 53 satellites, including those that are longer in operation, for the navigational system since 2000, reports Nikkei Asian Review.  The final two satellites will be launched by June 2020. This will complete the network at 35 satellites. In comparison, the U.S.'s Global Positioning System, or GPS, uses approximately 30 satellites in space.China is developing a navigation system independent of the GPS in a bid to protect its own interests, Nikkei Asian Review reports. The satellite's level of location accuracy is currently within 5 meters, though Beidou Navigation Satellite System spokesperson Ran Chengqi said that the system's accuracy will improve to within centimeters by the end of next year.The company said this will help in search and rescue missions in the future.Beidou's navigation system will also be used to improve technology for self-driving vehicles and cell phones in China.According to the Nikkei Asian Review, Beidou will also include a text messaging service so that users can communicate with one another.Ran said that Beidou already has plans to export its products to roughly 120 trading partners through China's Belt and Road initiative.The country also plans to open up its navigational system to Southeast Asia, South Asia, Africa and eastern Europe.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 06:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942825/3942825_86CE274B119A495CBC34C574DEA032FE_191231_3942825_China_s_very_own_navigation_system__Beidou__near_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/87D/025/87D025329BB661D77DF88DF05337C7BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China beidou system, china gps system, chinese gps, china beidou, china beidou satellite navigation system, china beidou satellite, china beidou gps, china gps navigation, china navigation system, beidou navigation satellite system,TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942813</guid>
      <title>Mealworms can eat styrofoam without being poisoned</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA  Scientists say that plastic eating mealworms maybe even more useful than previously thought.Previous Stanford studies determined that mealworms' guts contain microbes that allow them to digest styrofoam."New research published in Environmental Science & Technology has found that mealworms can potentially consume toxic plastic additives in Styrofoam without any ill effects. These worms can then be used as a safe feed supplement.According to the university's news release, HBCD is a chemical added to styrofoam and other polymers as a flame retardant, but the substance is toxic.Mealworms in the experiment were able to excrete 90 percent of the HBCD they ingested 24 hours after eating the plastic and expel the remaining 10 percent within 48 hours.This means the mealworms are uncontaminated even if they substituted on styrofoam.Stanford University says that the results have significant implications, as the worms are used as feed for various livestock, including chickens.The experiment suggests worms used to consume plastic could still be used as a source of agricultural feed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 06:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942813/3942813_22F1012796BC48AFAC0AF9F545D57446_191231_3942813_Mealworms_can_eat_styrofoam_without_being_poison_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plastic pollution, plastic waste, styrofoam eating worms, styrofoam, styrofoam eating mealworms, toxins, toxin, HBCD, flame retard, livestock, livestock feed, feed supplements, livestock feed supplement, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942795</guid>
      <title>Geologists discover 'iron snow' in Earth's core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS It is snowing iron at the Earth's core because molten iron crystalizes in the outer core before the substance sinking downwards, a study published in JGR Solid Earth says.The University of Texas at Austin said in a press release that these iron particles form a 300 kilometer layer above the Earth's solid inner core.The study said that the team led by Sichuan University associate professor Zhang Youjun analyzed seismic wave signals to infer the composition of the Earth's core.The university says that scientists found seismic waves propagating slowly in the outer core's base, but quickly in the eastern hemisphere of the top inner core.The researchers believe that the varying thickness of the iron slurry layer is the cause of the speed difference.They theorize that the iron particles have the effect of slowing seismic wave travel and that the substance is thinner on the inner core's eastern hemisphere.According to the researchers, the Earth's core drives tectonic plate movement with its heat and generates the magnetic field around the planet.The researchers say that understanding the composition of the Earth's core may shed light on those larger processes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 05:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942795/3942795_4B285AFA4178413FBEC94D3423ECF6A9_191231_3942795_Geologists_discover__iron_snow__in_Earth_s_core_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/808/92F/80892F5944C31DAD37D60B798974B881.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Iron snow, earth's core, earth, core, inner core, outer core, seismic wave, University of Texas at Austin, Sichuan University, geology, science, technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942735</guid>
      <title>FAA proposes remote ID system to track drones across the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Federal Aviation Administration has proposed using remote identification for unmanned aircraft systems in the U.S.The agency proposes that drones in U.S. airspace would have to meet one of three remote identification requirements: the standard remote identification; limited remote identification; or those without any remote identification.The system would allow the government to track drones across the country and could also make it possible for third parties to track the vehicles as well, CNBC reports. The agency says that the remote ID of drones is necessary "to ensure public safety and the safety and efficiency of the airspace of the United States."A standard remote identification drone includes equipment that is able to connect to the internet and transmit remote identification messages to a Remote ID unmanned service supplier as well as broadcast these messages directly while in the sky.A limited remote identification drone is an unmanned vehicle that is capable of connecting to the internet and transmitting remote identification messages to a Remote ID USS, though it is unable to broadcast these messages directly. This type of drone is restricted in operating higher than 400 feet from its control station.According to an unpublished proposal by the FAA, the Remote ID USS would be required to have the ability to share these messages in near real-time with the FAA, and secure access to such information.Drones such as amateur built vehicles and previously manufactured aerial vehicles that may not have remote identification capabilities would be required to fly within the visual line of sight and only in FAA-recognized identification areas.The FAA states in the proposal that all drones in U.S. airspace would be required to comply with the new regulations within three years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942735/3942735_F95F2AF8D44245EA942EB449BCEADD37_191231_3942735_FAA_proposes_remote_ID_system_to_track_drones_ac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C7C/4BD/C7C4BDDFB594B53D05572E492B77558E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[FAA, remote ID drones, drone remote ID, remote ID for drones, standard remote identification UAS, limited remote identification UAS, drone regulation, remote identification of drones, Federal Aviation Administration, FAA drones, drone news, faa drone proposal, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942716</guid>
      <title>How predatory whales are able to hunt down tiny fish</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA  New research has found that the rorqual whale species, particularly humpback whales, are able to use stealth and deception to prey on tiny fish.In a Stanford University news release, scientists said they were curious as to why the small fish weren't able to escape from their predator.The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, suggests that the precise timing of the whale opening its mouth to engulf the fish allows it to avoid triggering an escape response in them.When researchers monitored anchovies' escape reaction to a virtual whale, they found that by the time the fish responded to the whale's predatory behavior, it had already expanded its jaw to capture them.The study suggests that humpback whales wait to open their jaws until they are extremely close to tiny fish in order to engulf them, a method called lunge-feeding.When whales lunge after tiny fish, their jaws expand to consume a volume of water larger than their own bodies. They then filter out the excess water before swallowing the fish they caught. This technique allows humpback whales to capture 30 to 60 percent of the school of fish at once.  Scientists did not see the whales doing the same when pursuing other prey such as krill. According to the news release, this is due to krill being less responsive to predators.David Cade, a researcher involved in the study, explained in the news release that in terms of evolution, lunge-feeding is a comparatively new eating technique for the whales.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 02:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942716/3942716_C4943570693F4515AFE3DB2B929D74B2_191231_3942716_How_predatory_whales_are_able_to_hunt_down_tiny__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BB8/BB7/BB8BB76315B4D80539833F0053EB22EB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Giant whales, giant whales stealth, sneaky whales, deceptive whales, whales use stealth, stealth whales, giant whale tiny prey, humpback whales, Rorqual whales, schooling fish, using stealth to hunt fish, Lunge-feeding whales, whales eating fish, how whales eat fish, how whales hunt down tiny fish, forage fish, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944108</guid>
      <title>Doctor rescues dog from choking to death on leash stuck in elevator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAMPA BAY, FLORIDA  Dog is sunny Florida will luckily live to bark another day all thanks to the quick actions of doctor Mohammad Awad. CNN reported that the Tampa Bay doctor had just gotten off a shift on Monday when he arrived back at his apartment building. Awad told CNN that as he walked up to the elevator, his neighbor had just gotten off with her dog, but the leash was still inside the elevator door. The doctor shared surveillance camera footage from his building's security camera on his Facebook page. Video footage shows the door shut on the leash, suddenly the dog is yanked up into the air. Awad instantly jumps into action, dropping his plate of food and dashing over to the doggo to try and break the leash. The doc's first attempt fails as he stumbled backwards. Awad told the least trusted name in news that he could hear the dog make whimpering and choking sounds. Luckily on Awad's second try, the leash snapped and the dog dropped safely to the floor. Doggy disaster averted.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 15:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3944108/3944108_92AF488A263C4AE8AAB0A1AB5ED8726F_200102_3944108_Doctor_rescues_dog_from_choking_to_death_on_leas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ABD/75B/ABD75B38B5A00C65A3C9D9370F6866EB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Doctor rescues dog, doctor rescues dog elevator, dog leash in elevator, dog rescued from elevator, man rescues dog, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944102</guid>
      <title>Man dies after falling into meat mincing machine in Malaysia.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MASJID TANAH, MALAYSIA  A man unfortunately had to meet his maker after having an accident at a meat factory in Malaysia. According to the Star, a 47-year-old Nepalese worker was involved in the incident at a meat processing facility near Masjid Tanah. An official from the Malacca fire department said that the man was doing maintenance with three other workers in the morning at the factory on December 30. For some reason during the check, the meat-mincing machine suddenly turned on and caught the man at his waist.The Star reported the other workers called for emergency crews at 7:45 a.m. and authorities arrived on the scene in under 10 minutes. He unfortunately succumbed to his injuries on the spot.  The Star also said that it took the Masjid Tanah Fire and Rescue Department around 30 minutes to extricate the guy.   An investigation is being launched into the incident. State news agency Bernama reported that around 360,000 Nepalese are working in Malaysia, with most of them doing security, construction or hospitality jobs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 15:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3944102/3944102_B0470EF927774CBA8A180306461C6B6B_200102_3944102_Man_dies_after_falling_into_meat_mincing_machine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9C9/AD0/9C9AD003F426C54EDD3299924377D756.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Malaysia Nepalese factory worker, Nepalese factory worker Malaysia, mincing machine, meat mincing, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944008</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong kicks off 2020 with mass anti-government protests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Hong Kong has welcomed the new year by continuing the anti-government protests that have rocked the city since June 2019.Tens of thousands of protesters took to the streets on New Year's Day in a peaceful march that soon turned violent, as reported by the South China Morning Post. According to Reuters, police began firing rounds of tear gas and water cannons at the activists as they started throwing petrol bombs and forming roadblocks across several districts in Hong Kong.Protesters were also seen spray painting graffiti, smashing ATM machines and setting fire to at least five different HSBC branches throughout the city.A bronze lion at the bank's headquarters was splattered with red paint and set ablaze.According to the South China Morning Post, the protesters turned against HSBC as they accuse the bank of having a hand in the recent police crackdown against a fundraising platform to support the activists. At least 400 people were arrested for illegally gathering and for possession of weapons, the South China Morning Post reports, citing Hong Kong police. Activists were seen holding signs that stated "Freedom is not free" and "Liberate Hong Kong, Revolution of our Times."The protesters have continued to pressure the Hong Kong government to meet their core demands which include universal suffrage, an independent inquiry into police brutality, amnesty for all the protesters arrested and for the Hong Kong government to stop referring to the protests as "riots."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3944008/3944008_64ACF2FD72AC477E8D445982C1706F6C_200102_3944008_Hong_Kong_kicks_off_2020_with_mass_anti_governme_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/737/407/737407955D4F722BEBFD0AAF6168A55E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong protests, hong kong protests new years day, HK protests, HK mass protest, Hong Kong mass protest, hong kong protesters, China extradition, China extradition protests, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong,  Hong Kong protest 2020,  hk protests latest news, hk protests new years day, hong kong police fire tear gas, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943916</guid>
      <title>U.S. to investigate nuclear waste site in Marshall Islands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUNIT DOME, MARSHALL ISLANDS  The U.S. Congress is demanding an investigation into the Runit Dome in the Marshall Islands, which contains radioactive waste and is being threatened by rising sea levels.The dome was built in the late 1970s during the Cold War era. It was originally built to contain radioactive waste from nuclear tests conducted by the U.S on the islands, according to CBS News.The U.S. conducted 64 nuclear weapons tests at Bikini and Enewetak atolls between 1946 to 1958.The tests included the "Bravo" hydrogen bomb, which was said to be 1,000 times more powerful than the atomic bomb the U.S. dropped on Hiroshima, Al Jazeera reports. According to the Los Angeles Times, the site holds more than 3.1 million cubic feet of radioactive ash and soil from the nuclear explosions, which was closed with a concrete dome that is 18 inches thick.This was originally meant to be a temporary solution since the bottom of the crater was never lined.As part of the National Defense Authorization Act, the Department of Energy must investigate the deteriorating concrete site and submit a report about the risks the dome poses to the people, wildlife, and surrounding environment by June 2020, the Los Angeles Times reports. The report must also assess how rising sea levels could affect the nuclear dome.In May 2019, UN Secretary General Antonio Guterres had raised concerns about the risk of the dome's radioactive material leaking into the sea, reports BBC News. According to the U.S. Department of Interior, the Marshall Islands was a UN trust territory that was administered by the U.S. from 1947 to 1978. It became a sovereign nation in 1979.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943916/3943916_D898DF4C63F34AC98667C48BD9951EEC_200102_3943916_U_S__to_investigate_nuclear_waste_site_in_Marsha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3EB/BBC/3EBBBCC7C2C6D0D047CE5E974843268A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Nuclear coffin, pacific, marshall islands, nuclear coffin in pacific, nuclear coffin leaking in pacific, nuclear coffin marshall islands, nuclear coffin leaking, nuclear coffin cold war, concrete dome, atomic bomb tests, radioactive material, radioactive material leaking, radioactive material leaking into the pacific, enewetak atoll, nuclear explosions,  runit dome, cold war era nuclear tests, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943882</guid>
      <title>Microsoft sues North Korean hackers for stealing user info</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REDMOND, WASHINGTON  Microsoft has filed a lawsuit against two anonymous North Korean hackers for stealing user information in a hacking operation called Thallium.The hackers were using 50 domains as part of their cyber operation, according to ZDNet. In the court documents for the lawsuit, which was filed on December 18, Microsoft explained that hackers would send spear phishing emails to users that pretended to be from a Microsoft Account Team.The emails would include a link to a host phishing page that would encourage users to enter their account credentials. Once hackers gained access gained access to a users' account, they would be able to review user emails, contact lists and other information.In addition, Microsoft said the hackers were able to use misleading domains to trick users into clicking links that would result in malware such as KimJongRAT and BabyShark, which are remote access trojans, being installed on a user's computer.This type of malware is able to exfiltrate information and wait to receive additional commands from the hackers who installed it, ZDNet reports. Most targeted users were based in the U.S., Japan and South Korea.According to ZDNet, Microsoft has since been granted a court order by U.S. authorities to take over the 50 domains used by the North Korean hackers. The tech company has since taken those websites down.Microsoft had previously notified 10,000 users in July that their accounts had been targeted by hackers from North Korea, Russia and Iran over the past 12 months, CBS News reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 07:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943882/3943882_024C232861AA4ACD9100E7A19EFFF07A_200102_3943882_Microsoft_sues_North_Korean_hackers_for_stealing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F2/868/8F2868DA30F9400AE54B64BB3FF8202B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[north korea, cyber attacks, north korea cyber attacks, north korean cyber attacks, north korea microsoft, microsoft suing north korean hacking group, microsoft vs north korean hackers, north korea 2019, kim jong un, pyongyang cyber space, north korea cyber attack microsoft users, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943853</guid>
      <title>CDC links Vitamin E additives  to vaping related lung injuries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA  U.S. health officials have linked vitamin E acetate additives to a "vast majority" of vaping illness cases.The CDC made those remarks in a news conference on December 20, citing the latest papers in a series of studies the agency carried out. The agency says it has been tracking the vaping cases since July and confirmed that incidents of illnesses have declined.According to a study in the New England Journal of Medicine, the CDC took bronchus and lung fluid samples from a large number of vaping illness patients across 16 states.Analysis found vitamin E, a substance identified in e-cigarette product samples, in 48 out of 51 patients, but not in healthy people. According to the Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, the CDC studied 38 vaping illness patients who died or were rehospitalized after hospital discharge.The median time for patients to go back to the hospital was three days, and the median time from hospital discharge to death was four days.The CDC advises doctors to follow up on patients soon after hospital discharge.According to the same report, vaping illness patients over 50 years of age are more likely to die than other patients.The CDC says that vaping illness patients with heart diseases and diabetes are significantly more likely to be readmitted after their initial hospitalization.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 06:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943853/3943853_944D63BB2201423E977BA3EE694D67EE_200102_3943853_CDC_links_Vitamin_E_additives__to_vaping_related_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, vape, vaping, lung injury, lung injuries, evali, vaping illness, vitamin e, e-cigarette, e-cigarettes, e-cigs, cdc, centers for disease control and prevention, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943792</guid>
      <title>Sriracha hot sauce recalled over fears of  'exploding' bottles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA/NEW ZEALAND The BBC reports that bottles of Sriracha hot sauce have been recalled in Australia and New Zealand over fears they might go kaboom.According to Food Standards Australia New Zealand, lactic acid build-up is causing certain bottles to bloat and continue to ferment. That means if you try and open one, it could very well blow up in your face.According to the website, customers should watch out for bloated 17 and 28-ounce bottles with a March 2021 expiration date and take them back for a full refund. Seems Sriracha's been exploding everywhere lately. The BBC reports that just last month, Irish officials have had to impose a recall on similar grounds.Hipster Tabasco also made headlines in the outback last October, after 400 kilos of speed were found hidden inside the imported sauce bottles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 04:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943792/3943792_3118F5EBBD7A4C01BB2577B07B4CBDBF_200102_3943792_Sriracha_hot_sauce_recalled_over_fears_of___expl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EEA/4AC/EEA4AC950F5437E8D1E0C6C5932ED004.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sriracha, hot sauce, exploding hot sauce, exploding sriracha, exploding hot sauce bottles, asian hot sauce, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943710</guid>
      <title>China opens up knockoff Charles &amp; Keith stores called Cherlss &amp; Keich</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Few civilizations throughout the course of history have impacted the world as much as glorious China.  Beijing has always been the global leader when it comes to innovation and trademark protection, which is why it makes this next story so outrageous. According to Business Insider, Singapore fashion brand Charles & Keith has 95 stores in Chinathat is, as long as you don't count the knockoff stores as well. According to Hong Kong news site hk101.com, apparently some Chinese consumers have been duped by copycat stores called Cherlss & Keich. The fake stores are owned by a Chinese company called Guangzhou Yuantai Leather and opened last year. You can find Cherlss & Keich stores in Guangdong, Sichuan, Hunan and Shanghai. And if you take a look at their website, it bears a striking resemblance to the actual Charles & Keith site. It looks like quite a few Chinese shoppers thought they were buying the real thing, only to be tricked. Wellthis is most likely a one off as the Chinese have nothing but the utmost respect for trademarks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 01:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943710/3943710_5B0A3FBB37B742AAB9882925C892CAB9_200102_3943710_China_opens_up_knockoff_Charles___Keith_stores_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B0C/E28/B0CE283A087DA174D2F6B5B02FD5091B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China knockoff, China counterfeits, China counterfeit goods, fake Charles & Keith store, fake Charles & Keith bags, China Cherlss & Keich, Cherlss & Keich, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944763</guid>
      <title>Tesla ready to start delivering made in China Model 3s</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  The first deliveries of Tesla Model 3 sedans made in lovely China for Chinese consumers are all set to go.Reuters reports that the company delivered its first Chinese made cars on Monday to 15 employees. The U.S. electric car company will start making deliveries to the public at its Shanghai factory at an event on Jan. 7.  According to the NY Post, this comes exactly a year after CEO Elon Musk broke ground on the US$2 billion "Gigafactory."According to Reuters, the China-made Model 3s are $50,000 before subsidies. Imported Model 3s start at $63,000 for the longer-range version, while the same model in the U.S. costs under $40,000. The fun-loving Chinese government has been ultra supportive of the Tesla factory, the first wholly foreign-owned car plant in the country. Guess that will make it a tad easier for China to get its grubby little hands on Tesla's trade secrets. Tesla has said its Shanghai factory will have a production capacity of 150,000 vehicles annually. So what are you waiting for China? Go get your shiny new Tesla today!!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 18:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/04/3944763/3944763_AA150A13A7B94B71BAEE9836AAB36944_200104_3944763_Tesla_ready_to_start_delivering_made_in_China_Mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tesla, Tesla Model 3, Tesla Model 3 Shanghai, China made Tesla, China made Tesla Model 3, Made in China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944758</guid>
      <title>Four Amish men were arrested for driving a horse and buggy drunk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEAVERTON, MICHIGAN  Four Amish bros were busted in Michigan for being tipsy while operating a horse and buggy. MLive reported that around 4 p.m. on Sunday, Dec. 29, Gladwin County Sheriff's deputies got a call from a motorist notifying them about a horse and buggy that was acting kind of buggy. The driver said the men were apparently tossing empty cans onto the street. After police located the buggy in question, they pulled the guys over and asked them to cough up their IDs. Police said the group first gave the cops bogus ages and refused to give them their names.  Upon further investigation, deputies discovered several more cans of beer inside the buggy. They also added that all four were obviously loaded. Levei Mast, 20, Andrew Zook, 19, Joseph Miller, 20 and Joseph Troyer, 19, were all charged with felony obstruction of justice and disorderly conduct. They were also hit with civil infractions for being minors in possession of booze. Each was released on Monday on $3,500 bond.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 18:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/04/3944758/3944758_0D969AAD1B7C4A9DB248D3F6A87F47E8_200104_3944758_Four_Amish_men_were_arrested_for_driving_a_horse_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Amish, Amish horse and buggy, Amish men arrested, Amish men arrested Michigan, Amish horse and buggy Beaverton, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944583</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's top general killed in Blackhawk helicopter crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW TAIPEI CITY, TAIWAN  Taiwan's Chief of General Staff, General Shen Yi-ming, was en route to visit troops at a military base in Yilan when the Blackhawk helicopter he was traveling in crashed on Thursday, killing him and seven other officers.Citing a military spokesman, the Liberty Times reports that the reason for the incident is unknown as visibility was good that day. According to the United Daily News, the pilots reported favorable conditions for landing in their last communication at 8:07 p.m.Shortly afterward, the military lost contact with the helicopter as the radar signature disappeared over a naval base in Yilan.Citing first responders, the Liberty Times reports that the helicopter crashed to the west of its last reported location in the mountains between New Taipei City and Yilan.Eight high-ranking officers and aircrew were killed, including Sheng. Five other passengers were rescued.The United Daily News reports that a Military News Agency journalist, who was pinned by the wreckage, was able to call for help with her cellphone. She was rescued with injuries.Another wounded officer helped guide rescuers to the crash site through heavy mist by blowing a rescue whistle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944583/3944583_23EB7C9A3F1F46689A251CD57622E040_200103_3944583_Taiwan_s_top_general_killed_in_Blackhawk_helicop_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Blackhawk crash, helicopter crash, crash, UH-60, Blackhawk, helicopter, top general, chief of general staff, Taiwan, defense, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944521</guid>
      <title>India announces plans for third lunar mission, Chandrayaan-3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BENGALURU, INDIA  The Indian Space Research Organization on Tuesday announced plans for a third lunar mission called Chandrayaan-3 and said it is most likely to be launched later this year, according to the Times of India.Speaking at a press conference, the space agency's chairperson K Sivan explained that the spacecraft's configuration will be similar to its predecessor, Chandrayaan-2.According to AFP, he said the agency will build a new propulsion module, lander and surface rover for the mission.Sivan told the Times of India the mission will cut costs by reusing the same orbiter from India's second lunar mission as it is already orbiting the moon.The aim is to land the spacecraft on the moon's south pole, the same area that the Chandrayaan-2 tried to land in but failed to do so in September of 2019.If the mission is successful, this would make India the fourth nation to achieve a soft landing on the lunar surface.India's second moon mission failed as the Chandrayaan-2 spacecraft had a hard landing on the moon's south pole and lost communication with Indian spacecraft operators.The mission was aimed at searching for water and minerals on the moon as well as measuring moonquakes.Sivan said the Indian space agency plans to launch at least 25 space missions this year as part of India's plans to become a low-cost space power.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 10:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944521/3944521_F647E9799D664472824AE8AF2AB4B055_200103_3944521_India_announces_plans_for_third_lunar_mission__C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3D9/04C/3D904C70087684543F25A96519F1875E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Space, space exploration, india, moon, Chandrayaan-3 , Chandrayaan-3  spacecraft, Chandrayaan-3 mission, Chandrayaan-3 lunar mission,india's third lunar mission, india lunar mission,  india moon mission, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944497</guid>
      <title>Giant fish chows down on whole shark</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE DEEP SEA  The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration captured rare footage of a wreckfish trying to gobble up an entire shark while swimming in the deep sea. The video also shows a bunch of sharks swimming towards a dead swordfish and feasting on the creature's skin and muscle tissue as it lies still on the seafloor.On their website, NOAA explains that deep-sea sharks aren't usually seen gathering together like unless there is food available in the surrounding area. The footage was captured by the remotely operated vehicle Deep Discoverer during the NOAA's Windows to the Deep expedition last year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944497/3944497_234A64358E1E4AE9BAD8F55F93EDDABE_200103_3944497_Giant_fish_chows_down_on_whole_shark_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/239/C8B/239C8BB19D93497044480ECEDD9A195C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Giant fish eats shark, fish eat shark video, wreckfish eats shark, shark deep sea, NOAA fish eat shark, fish gobbles on shark, big fish eat shark, giant fish eat shark, small shark eaten, shark attacked by giant fish, giant fish vs shark, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944435</guid>
      <title>Global warming could force the North Atlantic Current to halt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRONINGEN, NETHERLANDS  The North Atlantic Current is a vast flow of warm seawater from the Gulf of Mexico that makes northwestern Europe's mild climate possible.According to a study in Science Reports, Netherlands-based scientists warn that global warming might temporarily halt this important current in the next century.According to the British Meteorological Office, the North Atlantic Current is driven by differentials in salinity and temperature levels in the sea.As the hot current flows north, the water loses salinity and heat. This cold, dense water then sinks deep into the ocean and flows back to tropical waters.According to the researchers' news release, climate change-related ice melt in Greenland and excessive rains over the seas are adding freshwater to the North Atlantic.The scientists say the new study's mathematical model has bolstered previous theories that freshwater inclusions would slow the current or even interrupt it.A study co-author says that their simulations predict a 15 percent chance that the current would seize up temporarily in the next 100 years.The scientists say that such a disruption might lead to cold spells in the northern Atlantic region.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 08:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[North Atlantic Current, Atlantic Ocean Circulation, climate change, global warming, Greenland, ice melt, melting glaciers, Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944400</guid>
      <title>Protesters storm on U.S. embassy in Baghdad</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAGHDAD, IRAQ  The U.S. embassy in Iraq was hit with attacks during violent protests, an action which has been condemned by President Donald Trump. He has since called on Iraq to use its forces to protect the embassy.According to CBS News, an estimated 6000 protesters, including Iraqi Shiite militiamen gathered outside the American embassy in Baghdad on Tuesday during a hostile protest. Several dozen managed to break into the compound and were heard shouting, 'down, down, USA!', whilst they smashed a main door and set fire to a reception area.Protesters also threw stones over the walls, pulled down security cameras, stormed empty guard posts and were seen hanging yellow flags belonging to the Kataeb Hezbollah militia on the walls of the embassy. U.S. soldiers watched from the roof and used a loudspeaker to urge the crowd to stay away.Videos posted to social media captured smoke funneling out from one guard checkpoint on the perimeter of the compound. Iraqi special forces responded by firing tear gas to try and disperse the protesters. According to the New York Times, the demonstration was in retaliation to U.S. airstrikes that killed 25 Iran-backed Kataeb Hezbollah, an Iraqi Shia paramilitary group just two days earlier. The Pentagon, however, says their airstrikes were in retaliation to an attack consisting of more than 30 rockets on an Iraqi military base near Kirkuk, northern Iraq. The attack killed an American defense contractor and injured four U.S. service members.A U.S. defense official told CBS News that the military is sending reinforcements to the embassy from units already within the country, adding, "there are no plans to evacuate Embassy Baghdad."President Trump accused Iran of "orchestrating" the break-in, adding that "they will be held fully responsible."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 07:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944400/3944400_095D842F89BD437C9FFA329A43DA1886_200103_3944400_Protesters_storm_on_U_S__embassy_in_Baghdad_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F7A/5BF/F7A5BF28DB053547A315296351415CDF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, protests, Iraq, Baghdad, Iran, Baghdad embassy protests, protesters break into U.S. embassy, tear gas protesters]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944253</guid>
      <title>A designer rolled out 3D printed synthetic fruits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Jerusalem  An Israel-based designer has invented 3D printed synthetic fruits that are edible and contain essential minerals and vitamins.According to Dezeen, Meydan Levy created five types of artificial "neo fruits."The neo fruits' structure is made of cellulose, an organic compound that forms the structure of living plants.The artificial fruits' cellulose microtubes also contain the liquid mixture that gives the fruit nutrients and flavor.  Citing Levy, the online outlet says the artificial fruits do not take up their final shape until liquid is injected. Levy says that without the liquids, the artificial fruits could be stored for long periods and transported easily until the injections are added before consumption.According to Levy, industrial agriculture will not be able to meet the nutritional needs that coincide with a global population increase.  Dezeen reports that nutritionists helped Levy to create different ingredients for each type of neo fruit in order to meet the wide range of nutrition the human body requires.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 03:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944253/3944253_C3B94ADBC2EC4412BFE4E674B8D720BC_200103_3944253_A_designer_rolled_out_3D_printed_synthetic_fruit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/523/426/523426B9D9D26E1DE8E2AD1792B5204D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Neo Fruit, fake fruit, synthetic fruit, artificial fruit, imitation fruit, 3d printed, 3d printing, 3d printed food, 3d printed fruit, Meydan Levy, dezeen, science, sustainability, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944246</guid>
      <title>U.S. sends paratroopers to Kuwait after Baghdad embassy riot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Washington  The U.S. Army's 82nd Airborne Division is deploying paratroopers to Kuwait, after Iran-affiliated rioters swarmed the U.S. embassy in Baghdad.U.S. Secretary of Defense Mark Esper said in a written statement on Tuesday that Air Force C-17s were already flying in 750 paratroopers of the division's Immediate Response Force.The Military Times reports that the 750 paratroopers will be joined by an additional 4,000 U.S. soldiers from the division's IRF in the following week.The 82 Airborne Division said in a statement that the 1st Brigade Combat Team is currently assigned to the IRF role. According to Fox News, the alert sequence for the Division Ready Brigade is to have one rifle battalion ready in 18 hours, another rifle battalion in 36 hours and a third in 54 hours.The alert brigade should be ready to deploy for operations within a 96-hour alert window. Fox reports that the aircraft carrier USS Harry S. Truman has been in the Gulf of Oman with its carrier strike group, armed with F-18 fighters and Tomahawk cruise missiles.Citing the Pentagon, Fox reports that there are 60,000 US troops in the Middle East, including the 14,000 reinforcements added since May in response to Iran's rising threat.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 03:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944246/3944246_6F41EC4436564385B09B49A127EE1FAF_200103_3944246_U_S__sends_paratroopers_to_Kuwait_after_Baghdad__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C6C/DA2/C6CDA2737A7656B7903CB85C98606F28.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[82nd Airborne Division, 82nd Airborne, 82nd division, Airborne Infantry Brigade, U.S., US, Kuwait, Iran, Iraq, ambassy, Baghdad, ambassy, riot, riots, demonstration, defenes, security, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945807</guid>
      <title>Hackers from Iran target U.S. government website</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  A U.S. government website was targeted by a group of Iranian hackers on Saturday January 4, amid ongoing tensions between Iran and the U.S. over the killing of Qassim Suleimani, a high ranking Iranian commander. According to AFP, the Federal Depository Library Program's website was replaced with a page called "Iranian Hackers!"As soon as the site was opened, visitors were shown a picture of U.S. President Donald Trump bleeding through the mouth and being punched in the face by what seems to be the fist of an Iranian Revolutionary Guard.The website also showcased images of Iran's leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, the flag of Iran and a message from the country's leader which expresses support for the oppressed people in the Middle East.In a statement, a spokesperson from the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency told CNN that the site has since been taken offline and is no longer accessible.The official said that there is no confirmation of whether or not the hacking operation was part of Iran's state-sponsored activities.Suleimani was killed on January 3 by a U.S. airstrike ordered by President Trump after the U.S. Department of Defense accused him of developing plans to attack American military personnel and diplomats in Iraq and the Middle Eastern region, as reported by CNN. The Pentagon also says he was responsible for the deaths of hundreds of Americans and wounding thousands more.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945807/3945807_419DF1D55DAE445EAFEB35E3B249C747_200106_3945807_Hackers_from_Iran_target_U_S__government_website_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[usa vs Iran, iranian hackers, iran vs usa latest news, iranian hackers US government website,  us govt website, us gov hacked by iran, qassem soleimani, qassem soleimani iran usa, donald trump iran, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945800</guid>
      <title>Vietnamese influencer dumps on makeup in hospital for boyfriend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VIETNAM  A so-called social media influencer in Vietnam found herself on the wrong end of some online backlash for dumping mountain loads of makeup on while in the hospital.According to China Press, the influencer of all influencers was recovering in the hospital back in October when she decided to encase herself in some cosmetics.Apparently she found out that her boyfriend was on the way over and shared a Facebook post saying, "My boyfriend is coming to see me!"The ultra influencer then posted a crap ton of pictures of herself hooked up to a respirator wearing a truckload of foundation on as well as fake eyelashes, blush, eye shadow, eyeliner, nail polish and jewelry. And of course you can't be a real deal influencer if you don't take selfies of yourself pretending to sleep. Isn't it about time they have selfies drones that can do that kind of thing for you? Just think of all the influencing an influencer could influence. Well, we here at TomoNews wish nothing but the best for this woman and hope that she gets back up on her feet as quickly as possible because the world surely isn't going to influence itself.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945800/3945800_29975D3FF80040EC9E35FE53056D809C_200106_3945800_Vietnamese_influencer_dumps_on_makeup_in_hospita_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Influencer, vietnam influencer, vietnam influencer makeup, makeup in hospital, fake selfie, makeup selfie, social media influencer, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945795</guid>
      <title>Brit man gets 5-inch dragon horn removed from back</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LIVERPOOL, UNITED KINGDOM  If you ever thought it was a good idea to ignore whatever that thing is that's growing on your skin, don't  or else you could end up dragon horned like this guy. According to the British Medical Journal, doctors were surprised to discover a 5-inch long "dragon horn" growing out of a 50-year-old man's back.But no, he wasn't turning into a scaly fire-breather. In reality, the "dragon horn" was a cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma, a fairly common type of skin cancer. What's unusual is how massive it got  which is what happens when you neglect that cancerous skin lesion for 3 whole years!SCC cases are usually seen in older people with light skin with a weak immune system and lots of sun exposure.In this case, the patient was a low-risk manual laborer, who wasn't immunosuppressed and had no significant sun exposure or family history of skin cancer.  And unlike most folks battling skin cancer, there wasn't anything abnormal with his lymph nodes either. To treat the man, doctors had to surgically remove the horn along with a good chunk of healthy skin to make sure no cancer got left behind. They then took a skin graft from his thigh to patch up the deep wound.What's mind-boggling is that healthcare in the UK is free. So everyone who has to deal with America's crappy system probably wants to know why the dude didn't just go to a doctor? Treatment would've been a lot less gnarly.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945795/3945795_1915512C42164D85A88E366D158666DE_200106_3945795_Brit_man_gets_5_inch_dragon_horn_removed_from_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dragon horn, dragon horn on back, skin cancer, horn on back, skin cancer horn, squamous cell carcinoma, scc, dragon horn scc, horn scc, horn shaped growth, bizarre medical case, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945789</guid>
      <title>Almost the whole US military has gone to war against TikTok</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  When the U.S. Army, Navy and Marines recently went into battle against Chinese video sharing app TikTok, it was only a matter of time before reinforcements were sent in.Now according to the Wall Street Journal, the Air Force and Coast Guard have also said they are no longer allowing TikTok on government-issued devices. According to Engadget, it's unclear if the ban will also extend to the Super Space Force. Apparently there are no restrictions of the app on personal devices, but officials have encouraged personnel and their kids to ditch it. The recent bans come amid U.S. concerns that the Chinese government could pressure TikTok to hand over sensitive data.   Spokeswoman Major Malinda Singleton told the Wall Street Journal, some of the issues are "not unique" to any one social media platform. Bad guys could possibly recruit people through social networks, and there's a chance that personnel could inadvertently reveal military secrets or expose themselves to attack. But if anything, the TikTok ban has to make you think. U.S. soldiers are damn young.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945789/3945789_FD6AD764B0424D918926295BF96A96B4_200106_3945789_Almost_the_whole_US_military_has_gone_to_war_aga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[US military TikTok, US military TikTok ban, TikTok ban, Air Force bans TikTok, Coast Guard bans TikTok, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945634</guid>
      <title>First human composting facility to open in Seattle next year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  US-based company Recompose will start the first ever funeral service that turns human bodies into compost soil next year.Citing architects involved in the project, Dezeen reports that the flagship facility in Seattle will be capable of housing 75 bodies in its compost vessels.According to Recompose, prosthetics and pacemakers will be removed from the cadaver to prepare the body for the natural organic reduction process.Citing company founder Katrina Spade, the Washington Post reports that the vessels accelerate natural decomposition.According to Recompose, the company's technology is designed for urban areas that do not have space for burials.The body is interred in a vessel 4 feet wide and 8 feet tall with alfalfa, wood chips and straw and then heated to a temperature of 150 degrees Fahrenheit.After 30 days, the microbes will have decomposed the body and eliminated most pathogens and residual pharmaceuticals.The process creates about a cubic yard of soil from each person and the decedent's friends and family may take part of the soil for their garden.Recompose claims their services save one tonne of carbon emissions per person when compared to conventional burial or cremation, which increases sustainability.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 09:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945634/3945634_525950EA241D471398DB896F62B96279_200106_3945634_First_human_composting_facility_to_open_in_Seatt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Human compost, human composting, green burial, recompose, recomposelife, sustainability, Seattle, U.S., TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945623</guid>
      <title>This is the amount of plastic particles ingested by humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWCASTLE, AUSTRALIA  New research from the World Wide Fund for Nature and the University of Newcastle, Australia suggests that humans consume roughly 2,000 pieces of microplastics, or five grams of plastic, a week. This is equivalent to eating a credit card a week.Microplastic particles are less than five millimeters in length and are approximately the size of a sesame seed.The study found that the number increases to 21 grams of plastic pieces a month, which is equivalent to the weight of a hanger or the amount of microplastics needed to fill half a rice bowl.Every six months we consume 125 grams of plastic, which is enough plastic to fill an entire cereal bowl. According to the study, this turns into roughly 250 grams of microplastics in a year, or a dinner plate full of plastic.The study found that we consume approximately 20 kilograms of microplastics in our lifetime, or roughly the weight of two mobile recycling bins, according to Reuters.The study notes that the largest source of plastic ingestion around the world is through water consumption, either ground water, surface water, tap water or bottled water.The study also estimates that a small number of microplastics may enter the body through inhalation.Researchers mentioned that the long term effect of microplastics on our health is unclear and that additional studies are still needed to understand the effect of plastic on human health.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 09:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945623/3945623_54E893A398E341C281FF2234820E5E7A_200106_3945623_This_is_the_amount_of_plastic_particles_ingested_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[microplastics, microplastic pollution,  plastic pollution, microplastic particles, microplastics in human body, humans ingesting plastic, humans ingesting microplastics,  how much plastic do we eat, the problem with microplastics, microplastics animation, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945481</guid>
      <title>Australia's bushfires are creating freak thunderstorms</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VICTORIA, AUSTRALIA  CBS News reports that bushfires in Australia are burning so fiercely that they are creating pyrocumulonimbus clouds which are then creating thunderstorms.  The Bureau of Meteorology in Victoria tweeted that the bushfires in East Grippland had triggered one such storm in a warning issued on Thursday last week. CBS News meteorologists say that bushfires heat the air so intensely that they could send ash upwards at a speed of 100 miles an hour or more.The updrafts can then cause ash and smoke to rise miles up into the atmosphere where cooler temperature causes water to condense into clouds.According to CBS News,  freak storms like this could increase as our planet continues to heat up. According to CBS News, the more violent the bushfire, the faster the updraft and the more likely the clouds will form thunderstorms.Unlike normal storms, bushfire-caused storms do not result in much rain since the falling raindrops are evaporated by the heat from the fires raging below.CBS News warns that lightning strikes from these storms are far more likely to cause further bushfires due to the lack of rain.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 04:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945481/3945481_2663BECF5AD349588E017A7FECD9301E_200106_3945481_Australia_s_bushfires_are_creating_freak_thunder_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bushfire, new weather system, weather system, storm, thunderstorm, pyrocumulonimbus, lightening, Australia, climate change, global warming, science, climate TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945409</guid>
      <title>$17,000 fine for passenger who threw coins at plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANQING, CHINA  A Chinese passenger has been fined $17,000 for throwing coins at a plane. 28-year-old, Lu was boarding a flight from Anqing to Kunming in February last year and told staff he threw the coins to ensure the plane avoid hazards.'Lucky Air' the carrier, pursued the case and sued Mr. Lu for his actions, actions that caused significant delays to all 163 passengers including Mr. Lu who was initially detained for ten days. On Wednesday, a court in Anqing ruled that he must pay a $17,000 fine. Mr. Lu then attempted to shift blame by saying the airline failed to tell him that he couldn't throw coins at the plane.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 02:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945409/3945409_4C9925C66E7140B0B8E0F82BC4358FEB_200106_3945409__17_000_fine_for_passenger_who_threw_coins_at_pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese tourists behaving badly, Tourists behaving bad, Chinese passenger throws coins, coins at plane, coins in plane engine, Chinese passenger, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946361</guid>
      <title>Chinese man climbs into X-ray scanner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  A man was caught climbing into the security scanner at the Beijing West Railway Station, but why?Accompanied by his wife, the couple was traveling home when security checks required them to place their coats and bags through the X-ray machine. Suddenly, the man climbed onto the conveyor belt and went through the machine, appearing out the other side before being detained. On questioning, the man explained that he felt it was too much hassle to remove all of his belongings, so opted to scan himself instead.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 23:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946361/3946361_497D65781C9E4054BACEB63BB3B916B0_200108_3946361_Chinese_man_climbs_into_X_ray_scanner_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese tourists, Chinese man climbs into scanner, tourist behaving badly, Chinese tourist behaving badly, security fails, security check fail, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946122</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's endangered leopard cats saved by road culverts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAOLI, TAIWAN  Taiwan is making a push to save its leopard cats.Taiwan's Miaoli County passed an ordinance to protect leopard cats by rewarding eco-friendly farming and mandating impact studies for some construction projects on December 28.Liberty Times reports that Miaoli is an important breeding ground for leopard cats, an endangered species in Taiwan. The busy traffic on Taiwan's freeways poses a significant danger to the leopard cats and at least 21 cats were killed by cars in 2019.Taiwan's government has been trying to address the problem by building culverts to help leopard cats safely cross roads.Citing the Forestry Bureau, United Daily News reports that its camera detected 39 leopard cats at one culvert.Last year, the government and the National Chung Hsing University unveiled a safe crossing system.The system features a speedometer linked traffic sign, fences, light sound emitters to slow down cats, animal biometrics, and a safe passage culvert.The Forestry Bureau says that cats have learned to use those systems and that a combination of LED lights, fences and speeding enforcement may help save the cats.Liberty Times reports that Miaoli's laws would require construction of a certain size--such as roads over 1 km long--to pass an environmental impact study before they are built.According to the Liberty Times, there are less than 1,000 living leopard cats in Taiwan. The government has issued repeated calls for motorists to slow down in areas that the cats inhabit.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3946122/3946122_6A1931EBEF584B88AAA2489B3ED29535_200107_3946122_Taiwan_s_endangered_leopard_cats_saved_by_road_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taiwan, Taiwan leopard cat, Taiwan leopard cats road culverts, Taiwan leopard cat endangered, leopard cats, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946057</guid>
      <title>How a U.S. drone strike killed Iran's Quds Force commander</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAGHDAD, IRAQ  General Qassim Soleimani, head of Iran's expeditionary Quds Force, was killed early Friday by a U.S. drone that fired missiles into his convoy near Baghdad International Airport. The U.S. military has confirmed that it carried out the attack. The Times of Israel reports that a MQ-9 Reaper drone fired four missiles into two cars and destroyed the vehicles on the airport's access road.Citing local media sources, the paper reports that the blast tore Soleimani apart and the general was later identified by the ring he wore on his hand.The strike killed Soleimani, his son-in-law and five Iranian Revolutionary Guards members.According to the New York Times, several Tehran-backed Iraqi militia leaders in the convoy were also killed.The Times of Israel reported 10 fatalities for the airstrike.The Washington Examiner reports that the MQ-9 drone was favored for its quiet propellers and loitering capabilities.Citing debris analysis by independent observers, Forbes reports that the missiles utilized could be the JAGM, a missile type that adds advanced sensors to the Hellfire missile.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 08:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3946057/3946057_E1B26C9277404D03B529A8BD2A04CB8C_200107_3946057_How_a_U_S__drone_strike_killed_Iran_s_Quds_Force_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Qassim Soleimani, drone, drone strike, airstrike, killed, MQ-9, MQ-9 Reaper, Reaper, Baghdad, JAGM, Hellfire missile, Baghdad International Airport, Iraq, Iran, US, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946041</guid>
      <title>How to protect yourself from SIM swapping</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  SIM swapping occurs when scammers gain access to your sim card number, usually by telling the cell phone service provider that the device has been lost or damaged, according to the Federal Trade Commission.Once the same number is activated on a new device, the hacker receives all your text messages, calls and data.According to the agency, scammers may log into your email accounts, social media accounts and change your passwords to potentially lock you out of your own accounts.They could also use your login credentials to access money in your bank account. This is because once hackers have gained access to your phone number, they can receive verification codes through SMS and bypass two-factor authentication.The agency urges users to limit the amount of personal information shared online, and in emails and text messages, in order to prevent becoming a victim of SIM swapping.Users are also advised to set a password or a PIN on their cellular account in order to better protect their phone numbers.Those who have fallen victim to SIM swapping are urged to contact their cell service provider to gain back access to their account. Once access has been restored, users should change their account passwords.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 07:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3946041/3946041_FECD74FFCF5841C498CD74327D71AD90_200107_3946041_How_to_protect_yourself_from_SIM_swapping_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sim card, sim jacking, sim swapping, sim swap attack, sim card swap scam, sim swapping news, sim swap hack, sim hack, sim hacking technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945910</guid>
      <title>Carlos Ghosn's escape: How it happened</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN  According to Turkish private jet firm, MNG, two of their aircraft were used to facilitate ex-Nissan boss, Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan. MNG state that two separate private jets to two different clients were leased using faked documents forged by an employee of the company who acted within "his own capacity."According to Business Insider, Ghosn was seen fleeing his home in Tokyo on the 29th of December. MNG state that the first private jet used in his escape flew from Osaka's Kansai Airport at 11 p.m. and landed in Istanbul the following day. At 6 a.m. just forty-five minutes after landing, Ghosn then took a second MNG flight bound for his home in Beirut, Lebanon.65-year-old Ghosn, who holds Brazilian, French and Lebanese nationalities, reportedly entered Beirut legally using his French passport and his Lebanese identification despite Japanese lawyers stating they had possession of all three of his passports. Japanese outlet, NHK, however, reported that Mr. Ghosn had a duplicate French passport.On Wednesday the 1st of January 2020, Turkish private jet firm, MNG filed a criminal complaint concerning the illegal use of its aircraft in relation to Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan.Mr. Ghosn is now a fugitive in Lebanon, which has no extradition treaty with Japan. Interpol has since filed a "red notice" for his arrest with authorities there.Carlos Ghosn released a statement saying, "I am now in Lebanon and will no longer be held hostage by a rigged Japanese justice system where guilt is presumed, discrimination is rampant, and basic human rights are denied.""I have not fled justice  I have escaped injustice and political persecution."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 03:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3945910/3945910_D38055E34A134C6D9F5AEA8E9B5896CA_200107_3945910_Carlos_Ghosn_s_escape__How_it_happened_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Carlos Ghosn, Ghosn escape from Japan, how did Ghosn escape, Ghosn escape explained, Nissan boss, Ghosn escapes Japan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946758</guid>
      <title>Ukrainian Airlines plane crashes in Tehran, killing all aboard</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN  A Ukrainian passenger plane crashed in Iran shortly after takeoff on Wednesday, allegedly due to technical issues.According to FlightRadar24, Ukraine International Airlines Flight 752 took off from Tehran's Imam Khomeini airport at 6:12 a.m. on Wednesday. It was bound for Kiev.Al Jazeera reports that the Boeing 737-800 jet had been carrying 176 passengers and crew members.According to Iranian State TV, the aircraft is suspected to have experienced mechanical issues, and stopped sending flight data just minutes after takeoff.The plane crashed in a field in between the cities of Parand and Shariar. All 176 passengers on board were killed.An Iranian emergency official told state TV that emergency crews were trying to collect the bodies, which lay among shattered parts of the aircraft.The Associated Press reports that according to a civil aviation spokesman, an investigation team has also been dispatched to the crash site.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 14:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946758/3946758_8D0FE5FCB71F40E18476067FE2F5EC50_200108_3946758_Ukrainian_Airlines_plane_crashes_in_Tehran__kill_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ukrainian airlines crash, Boeing crash, Boeing 737 crash, Iran plane crash, Tehran plane crash, Boeing 737-800 crash, Ukrainian airlines, Boeing 737-800, Ukraine International Airlines, UIA, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946734</guid>
      <title>Plastic ban causes Thai shoppers to think outside the bag</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BANGKOK  Thai shoppers are having to think outside the bag after a single-use plastic bag ban went into effect at the start of the year. According to a viral Facebook post with more than 70 pictures, a number of shoppers have decided to get creative with their reusable shopping containers. Thai citizens are hopping on board the environmental push by using earth-friendly reusable tote bags as well as some more unconventional carriers.  From buckets and baskets to rice sacks, shoppers at major stores, supermarkets and convenience stores have taken to social media to post snaps of themselves going green. Other methods of carting off purchases that deserve a hat tip include a wheelbarrow and a fishing net. Oh, there were also vases, pots, people using their own shirts and some random dude on his scooter. According to Reuters, Thailand was ranked sixth in the world's top countries that dump plastic garbage into the sea. However, over the past five months, they've dropped down to the 10th.  Hopefully after the initial excitement of going green just for likes on social media wears off, consumers can stick to permanently cutting down plastics use.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 13:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946734/3946734_DF5BA83F49C4432F872C89014EFE5C21_200108_3946734_Plastic_ban_causes_Thai_shoppers_to_think_outsid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Thailand plastics ban, Thailand single use plastics ban, Thailand plastic bag ban, Thailand creative reusable bag, environmentally friendly, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946728</guid>
      <title>Can Impossible dumplings and Beyond buns make it in China?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  Impossible Foods and Beyond Meat want to tackle the Chinese market but face an uphill battle getting through governmental and cultural hoops. According to the failing New York Times, both Impossible Foods and Beyond Meat have both turned from niche start-ups into major food companies. They have made deals with fast-food giants like Mickey D's and Burger King, and have gained recognition for introducing plant-based products that are healthier and less harmful to the environment. Okaymaybe not SO healthy.But can both companies find a foothold in China? Because there are so many damn people in China, it makes them the world's largest consumer of meat.Unfortunately, as the demand in China for pork and beef continues to rise, so will the temperature of the planet.    According to the New York Times, the two companies could find it difficult to get through China's complex regulatory process that involves a ton of Red China tape. Impossible and Beyond Meats could also face cultural challenges like making sure their faux meats meet Buddhist vegetarian laws and Chinese aversion to genetically modified foods. But let's be realistic, it's only really Americans that have such an aversion to veggies and fruit. Getting the rest of the world, especially Asia, to get on board with plant-based alternatives shouldn't be BEYOND IMPOSSIBLE.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 13:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946728/3946728_E1D2B6A9F5D9438980E57C7D28D72632_200108_3946728_Can_Impossible_dumplings_and_Beyond_buns_make_it_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Impossible Foods, Impossible Foods China, Beyond Meat, Beyond Meat China, Impossible dumplings, Beyond Buns, faux meat, plant-based meat, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946695</guid>
      <title>Deepfake videos banned on Facebook</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook has put forth a new policy that would ban all videos that are "edited or synthesized" using AI technology in a way that would be difficult for average Facebook users to spot, reports the Washington Post. This would include a ban on videos that use techniques to make a subject say words that he or she never said.Though the company said in a news release that they will allow manipulated videos as long as they are for satire or parody purposes.In this case, the Washington Post points out that under the policy, a doctored video showing Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi drunkenly giving a speech last year would still be allowed on Facebook.Last year, the company declined to remove the video even though fact-checkers had determined that the video was fake. A Facebook spokesperson explained to the Washington Post that this is because the company doesn't have a policy that says that the information you post on their platform must be true.Facebook's new policy would also not restrict simpler forms of video deception. This includes mislabeled footage, or trimming a video to make something a person says sound out of context.Another Facebook spokesperson said in a statement that the company would remove political ads if they include highly manipulated videos.A digital forensics expert from UC Berkeley told the Washington Post in an email that the social media giant should focus on the issue of removing misleading videos in general instead of just deepfake videos.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946695/3946695_DA12A5AC75DF4AC79C8C5FFFCA16DED9_200108_3946695_Deepfake_videos_banned_on_Facebook_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Facebook, facebook scandals, facebook bans deepfake videos, facebook bans deepfake, facebook AI, facebook artificial intelligence, mark zuckerberg, facebook deepfake tech, facebook threatened with deepfakes, deepfake videos on facebook, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946656</guid>
      <title>How the moon lost its magnetic field one billion years ago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  Billions of years ago, the ancient moon had a powerful dynamo at its core that produced a strong global magnetic field.Scientists at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology say that they have pinned down when that dynamo stopped, leading to the field's dissipation.In a study published in Science Advances, researchers say that the Apollo mission collected lunar rocks that preserve a record of the moon's ancient magnetic field.However, most of these rocks dated to between 3 and 4 billion years, or too long ago for studying the end of the moon's internal dynamo. To research the moon's later magnetic history, the scientists tested two samples that were 1 billion years old and found them to record a weak lunar magnetic field. As the rocks were left by a meteor impact, scientists reheated the rocks and obtained the same readings to make sure the impact's heat did not interfere with the rocks' magnetic records.According to the MIT news release, the moon used to be much closer to earth, and the gravitational effect caused the liquid lunar core to wobble, which created the magnetic field.The weak magnetism recorded by the two rocks suggests the gravitational effects had begun to seize up one billion years ago.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 10:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946656/3946656_A62F51F7F75541D1A2EF25EF40E40FCA_200108_3946656_How_the_moon_lost_its_magnetic_field_one_billion_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Moon, magnetic field, dynamo, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, MIT, core, Apollo, lunar rocks, lunar rock, science, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946538</guid>
      <title>Mysterious virus sickens dozens in central China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  A mysterious strain of viral pneumonia has affected 59 people in Wuhan, China since mid-December 2019, China Daily reports. The cause of the infection has yet to be determined.According to the Wuhan Municipal Health Commission, some of the victims were sellers at a local seafood market, sparking fear that the virus may have been transmitted from animals to humans. The market has since been temporarily shut down for disinfection, and patients placed in quarantine.Symptoms of the virus include fever, with a few of the patients having breathing difficulties. Chest X-rays from the victims show invasive lesions on both lungs.Wuhan's health commission said that they have eliminated the possibility of the virus being SARS, MERS or bird flu.Although a preliminary analysis found no clear evidence of the virus being transmitted from one human to another, at least 163 others were placed under medical observation for coming into close contact with the infected.Asian nations such as Singapore and Hong Kong have taken precautionary measures to prevent the spread of the virus by conducting temperature screenings at airports for visitors from China, as reported by BBC News. The World Health Organization said on its website that it "does not recommend any specific measure for travelers." They said that they are closely monitoring the situation and are in close contact with authorities in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 07:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946538/3946538_07DEB296BB5A44E3AC477D058897D84A_200108_3946538_Mysterious_virus_sickens_dozens_in_central_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china pneumonia, mystery pneumonia, pneumonia, mysterious virus in china, china pneumonia outbreak, wuhan pneumonia outbreak, mystery illness, mystery illness china, unknown pneumonia strain, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946392</guid>
      <title>Someone released bedbugs inside a Pennsylvania Walmart</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EDINBORO, PENNSYLVANIA  Someone in Pennsylvania apparently hates Walmart so much they deliberately tried to cause a bedbug infestation.[CUT 1]According to CNN, a manager at an Edinboro Walmart found a closed pill bottle filled with live bed bugs inside a boy's jacket that was for sale.The next day, an employee from health safety company Ecolab visited the store and spotted the little parasitic critters crawling all over the men's changing room. After a second closed bottle with dead bed bugs inside was found later in the men's department, Walmart staff finally reported the incident to the cops.NBC reports that state police are now investigating the incident, and itching to find whoever's responsible.Itching is right. Bed bugs may not spread disease, but they're definitely a pain to deal with.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 03:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946392/3946392_1E799E34471940A4B6210FF332E91275_200108_3946392_Someone_released_bedbugs_inside_a_Pennsylvania_W_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bedbugs, bedbug infestation, Walmart bedbugs, bed bugs, bed bug infestation, insects, parasite, parasitic insects, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946383</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show the scale of Australia's wildfires</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  Australia's wildfires are so big now that satellites in space are able to spot the fires.Footage captured from Japan's Himawari-8 satellite shows plumes of smoke covering eastern Australia on January 2. Another image from the same satellite pinpoints the exact location of the burning fires using near infrared light.NASA released images from the International Space Station that show smoke from the fires around the Sydney area on January 3.The European Space Agency's Sentinel-2 satellite also captured images of the growing wildfires in New South Wales on New Year's Eve. Images captured by the Japanese satellite in the past few days show the smoke from the fires gradually drifting and slowly making its way toward New Zealand.These bushfires have been fuelled by record high temperatures and severe drought over the past few months, BBC News reports. The state of New South Wales has been the worst hit, with the fires destroying more than 1,300 homes and forcing thousands of people to evacuate.According to the BBC, the fires have been worse than usual. Since July 1, roughly 5 million hectares have already been burned down in New South Wales. In comparison, the Amazon rainforest fires in 2019 burned down approximately 900,000 hectares of land.According to CNN, the fires aren't likely to end anytime soon as it is just the beginning of summer in Australia, and temperatures tend to soar in the months of January and February.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 02:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946383/3946383_EA6249915D8A4AA3BA966993A2C08A68_200108_3946383_Satellite_images_show_the_scale_of_Australia_s_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Australia wildfires, australia wildfires space, australia fire, australia fire from space, australia news, australia wildfires 2020, australia wildfires 2020 from space, NASA australia fires, fires in australia, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947135</guid>
      <title>SpaceX just put 60 satellites in orbit with one rocket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA    SpaceX launched its third batch of Starlink satellites into orbit from a U.S. Air Force base in Florida on Monday evening.Space.com reports that a Falcon 9 rocket carried the satellites in its first stage and that the launch marked the second time SpaceX reused a booster four times.Citing SpaceX, AFP reports that after deployment, the satellites would utilize ion thrusters to reach an orbit of 550 km to avoid collisions at higher, more congested space.MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX now operates 180 Starlinks, making the company the owner of the world's largest constellation of commercial satellites.According to the publication, the reusable first stage booster was successfully recovered by a drone ship in the Atlantic Ocean, but not the payload fairing.The lost component is worth an estimated US$3 million.However, the program has come under criticism because the satellites reflect glare that interferes with astronomical observatories.The MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX has applied a light absorbing coating to the new satellites to address those concerns.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 11:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947135/3947135_92C9C1CA406B410DA7698CA373989AB8_200109_3947135_SpaceX_just_put_60_satellites_in_orbit_with_one__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Starlink, Falcon 9, SpaceX, Elon Musk, satellite, commercial satellite constellation, drone ship, U.S., space, science, technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947126</guid>
      <title>Chinese jaywalkers cross six-lane road by squeezing through crack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINING, CHINA  Why did the pedestrians cross the road? So they could use a tiny hole in the middle of a median barrier that wasn't meant for people. Pedestrians from the city of Xining located in fabulous Qinghai province have found themselves between a concrete median and some metal fencing. According to Pear Video, people having to hoof it along a massively long, six-lane street with few crosswalks have been forced to take matters into their own hands. People have been forced to squeeze themselves through a tiny opening in the middle of the busy street because walking down to actual crosswalks could take as long as 20 minutes, according to one person interviewed by Pear Video. The tiny crack definitely saves people a lot of time, but it also depends on how low you can go.  And then there's the whole risking your life trying to get across the road part that people also need to deal with. Either way, this is a clear cut example of some top notch civil engineering.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 11:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947126/3947126_69E527595042456FBAF54EC70026CAD8_200109_3947126_Chinese_jaywalkers_cross_six_lane_road_by_squeez_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Pedestrian crossing, China pedestrian crossing, China makeshift crosswalk, China traffic, China civil engineering, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947121</guid>
      <title>Misleading images of Aussie fires make their way to social media</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  As Australia's fires burn at an unprecedented rate, social media activists have been quick to share maps and images of the wildfires  though not all of them are accurate.One example is of a map that was widely shared on social media as it seemed to show the live extent of the spread of fires across Australia. In reality, it was a visualization created by artist Anthony Hearsey which showed where fires were detected across Australia from December 2019 to January 2020.In response to the criticism, Hearsey admitted in an Instagram post that the scale was a bit exaggerated and said that some of the fires depicted may not be burning anymore but said it was "generally" true as he had obtained data about the fires from NASA's website.Another misleading map claimed to show all the wildfires burning across the country and used data from an Australian government website called MyFireWatch. It was later discovered that the map was inaccurate as the data gathered included any heat source including gas flares and refinery furnaces.Social media users have also been spreading old photographs or fake images to show the extent of destruction caused by the fires, Australia's SBS News reports. One photograph shows a family hiding under a pier with the atmosphere turned orange in color due to the flames. The image was taken in 2013, not during the recent wildfire outbreak.  Another photo shows a girl holding a koala and wearing what seems to be an oxygen mask while a forest in the backdrop is caught in flames. A Twitter user pointed out that the image could easily have been photoshopped to show the girl holding the koala with the fires burning in the background.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 10:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947121/3947121_65B24283ACE046BDB9E53BB1433F41CF_200109_3947121_Misleading_images_of_Aussie_fires_make_their_way_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Australia wildfires, australia fire, australia bushfires, australia fires misleading maps, australia news, australia wildfires 2020, australia bushfire 2020, fires in australia, australia misinformation, australia bushfire misleading photos, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947105</guid>
      <title>Starbucks introduces new nondairy drinks, tests oat milk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  Good new overpriced coffee lovers, Starbucks unveiled two new dairy-free coffee drinks and announced it would be testing oat milk in select markets.  For those prone to the squirts when downing dairy, the Seattle coffee juggernaut has got your bowels covered with their new Almondmilk Honey Flat White and Coconutmilk Latte. In a Jan. 7 press release, the coffee chain said their new minus-the-moo drinks will be available at all locations in the U.S. and Oh Canada. Starbucks describes the Almondmilk Honey Flat White concoction as a "coffee-forward beverage with real honey to complement the almond flavor with a touch of sweetness." That's a lot of words for a coffee with almond milk. If you're wondering how they came up with the Coconutmilk LatteHINT, it's in the nameproduct developers slapped shots of Starbucks Blonde Espresso with steamed coconut milk and sugar, aka Starbucks secret ingredient.    Customers at 1,300 participating stores in Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Michigan, Minnesota, Missouri and Wisconsin will also get the chance to be lab rats as Starbucks tests out oat milk as another non-dairy option. Here's a question...if you live in the Midwest, can you order an Almond Coconut Oat Milk super triple threat combo latte?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947105/3947105_D5AA5A1709574C1DBD567245E9F05C58_200109_3947105_Starbucks_introduces_new_nondairy_drinks__tests__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Starbucks non-dairy drinks, Starbucks Almondmilk Honey Flat White, Starbucks Coconutmilk Latte, Starbucks oat milk, Starbucks oat milk latte, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947004</guid>
      <title>NASA finds Earth-size world in habitable-zone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON    NASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, or 'TESS' mission, devised to specifically find Earth-sized planets orbiting nearby stars has identified TOI 700 d as a potential candidate occupying a star's habitable zone where conditions may be just right to allow the presence of liquid water on the surface.NASA explains that TESS observes large regions of the sky known as sectors for 27 days at a time. TESS identifies and tracks changes in stellar brightness caused by an orbiting planet passing in front of its star.During recent observations, TESS tracked a total of three planets.The closest to the star, TOI 700 b is Earth-sized, rocky and has an orbit of ten days. The middle planet, TOI 700 c, is 2.6 times larger than Earth, likely gas-dominated and orbits every 16 days. TOI 700 d, the only one in the habitable zone, measures 20 percent larger than Earth and orbits every 37 days.While the exact conditions on TOI 700 d are unknown, researchers at NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center created models to explore its potential conditions to help narrow future predictions of the planet's atmosphere. One model showed a water-covered world and the other, a completely dry version of today's earth. NASA says that future missions, "may be able to identify whether the planets have atmospheres and, if so, even determine their compositions."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 07:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947004/3947004_03B7BD50AE614C91AB9FBCB5B4D8BA79_200109_3947004_NASA_finds_Earth_size_world_in_habitable_zone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA, NASA finds planet, Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, TESS, planet hunter, TOI 700 b explainer, TOI 700 b, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946976</guid>
      <title>What we now know about Ghosn's daring escape from Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  On December 29, former Nissan, Renault boss Carlos Ghosn, who was under house arrest facing charges of diverting millions in company funds for his personal use, walked out of his house in Tokyo wearing a hat and a surgical mask in plain view of security cameras.Bloomberg reports that police surveillance was lax during the holidays and that Ghosn's lawyers had filed a legal complaint that prevented Nissan's hired agents from following him.Ghosn claims he would not have received a fair trial in Japan, where 99 percent of those accused of a crime are convicted.Citing Japan's NTV, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn boarded a bullet train in Tokyo and arrived at Osaka at about 4:30 pm. He then called a cab to a hotel near Kansai International Airport.Citing sources familiar with the matter, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn apparently evaded security by hiding in a case that was too big to be scanned by the airport's X-ray machines.Earlier, Ghosn's alleged accomplices had flown in on a Bombardier Global Express Jet with the case. Ghosn would use both in his escape.According to Bloomberg, Ghosn was aided by U.S. contractor and ex-Special Forces veteran Michael Taylor in his flight.At 11 p.m., the Bombardier Global Express took off and headed for Istanbul with Ghosn on board.Bloomberg reports that Ghosn's alleged rescuers carefully plotted the flight to avoid countries with extradition treaties with Japan such as South Korea and instead flew through Russian airspace.Russia was viewed as more friendly territory as Ghosn is credited with saving the ailing automaker AvtoVAZ, which he brought in to the Renault-Nissan Alliance's fold.The jet landed at Istanbul's Ataturk Airport at around 5:00 a.m.After that, Ghosn would again secrete himself as cargo in the box before boarding a smaller Bombardier that would take him to Beirut.In addition to Brazlian and Lebanese passports, Ghosn has two French passports. One was taken by the Japanese authorities and another kept by his lawyer as a condition of his bail but stored in a flimsy box that could be broken easily with a tool. However Reuters reports the French government denies Ghosn used the nation's passport.Citing a Lebanese judiciary official, Reuters reports that Lebanon has received a request to extradite Ghosn from Japan, not Interpol.Bloomberg reports that Ghosn entered Lebanon legally, where extradition of citizens is denied as a matter of policy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 06:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3946976/3946976_F228312BAED24490A2F92505B3733B0B_200109_3946976_What_we_now_know_about_Ghosn_s_daring_escape_fro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Carlos Ghosn, Ghosn escape from Japan, how did Ghosn escape, Ghosn escape explained, Nissan boss, Ghosn escapes Japan, Bombardier, case, box, hid in a box, hid in a case, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947759</guid>
      <title>Mystery pneumonia virus identified in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  Scientists have identified a new virus as a possible cause for the mysterious pneumonia outbreak in China's Wuhan.Citing researchers, China's Central Television reports that the pathogen is a coronavirus in the same family with the deadly MERS and SARS viruses.Citing experts involved in the effort, the channel reports tests showed that an isolated sample to have appearances similar to the coronavirus.The lab was also able to reconstruct the virus's genome sequence from 15 patient samples.CNN reports that the symptoms of the mystery pneumonia include having difficulty breathing and fever, adding that the condition does not appear to be deadly.According to CCTV, eight patients have been discharged from hospitals as of Thursday.The pneumonia outbreak occurred in December and some of the patients were employed at a local seafood market.According to Chinese authorities, there has been no clear evidence of a human to human infection and no fatalities have been reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 14:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947759/3947759_B653121606B74A2A951915E5A31A6B5F_200110_3947759_Mystery_pneumonia_virus_identified_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China virus outbreak 2020, China virus outbreak, Chinese virus outbreak 2020, Chinese virus, pneumonia, MERS, SARS, coronavirus, mystery virus, Chinese disease, epidemic, China, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947741</guid>
      <title>Sky Green towers built in Taichung, Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAICHUNG, TAIWAN  Singaporean architectural firm WOHA has designed a sustainable, mixed-use building called Sky Green, in Taichung, Taiwan.According to the company's project website, the development features two towers with sky gardens and terraces filled with lush greenery.One of the tower's facades is lined with mesh screens with vegetation on it, while the other consists of balconies with plants and other flora.The first three floors of the structure includes retail stores, while the rest of the building consists of residential apartments stacked on top of one another.The tower's interior offers open spaces with green vegetation for residents to relax in.According to Arch Daily, the design of the structure was chosen to adapt to Taiwan's local culture and climate.Construction on the building was completed in November of 2019.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 13:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947741/3947741_7400DFD523F8433896C18AE9E5F752A9_200110_3947741_Sky_Green_towers_built_in_Taichung__Taiwan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Lush Sky Green towers, sustainable buildings, green buildings, taiwanese architecture,  WOHA architecture firm, taichung architecture, green buildings, green development, sky green development, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947734</guid>
      <title>Iran may have shot down the Ukrainian commercial jet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN  The BBC reports that Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau says intelligence shows that Iran had shot down the Ukrainian passenger plane with a missile, possibly in error.According to CNN, U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson states that British intelligence has reached the same conclusion.CNN reports that the plane had crashed shortly after it took off from Tehran airport on Wednesday.The Boeing 737 was carrying 176 passengers and aircrew, all killed in the crash.On Thursday, CNN aired a video it obtained that apparently shows a missile striking an object over Tehran's skies at the time of the commercial jet's crash.CNN states that it cannot independently verify the video.Citing U.S. officials, CBS News reports that a satellite detected infrared blips of two missile launches, then another of an explosion. The network states that officials were confident the plane was shot down by a missile.Newsweek quotes three US and Iraqi officials as saying they believe a Russian-made Tor M1 surface to air missile had struck the plane.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947734/3947734_6F8E64EF62B54958A1CB87B448CB183A_200110_3947734_Iran_may_have_shot_down_the_Ukrainian_commercial_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Iranian missiles, Iranian missile, shoot down, shot down, missile fire, missiles, Trudeau, Johnson, Ukranian jet, Ukranian Boeing, jet crash, Ukrainian jet crash, Ukraine, Iran, accident, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947575</guid>
      <title>Israel claims breakthrough in anti-missile laser weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEL AVIV, ISRAEL  Israel's Defense Ministry says in a news release that it made a technological breakthrough in a defensive laser weapon that intercepts aerial threats.Israel-based Defense Update reports that the laser can shoot down range rockets fired at close range and other threats that are too costly for the Iron Dome to engage.Defense Update reports that Israeli air defense batteries, armored vehicles and aerial drones will be outfitted with the lasers to bolster defense systems already in use.The Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon is electrically powered and that it combines multiple beams into one beam capable of overcoming atmospheric conditions. The active defense system is precise and the laser has successfully intercepted various projectiles in tests, including mortar shells and anti-tank missiles.Citing a military researcher, the Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon could fire a beam the diameter of a coin from Tel Aviv to Herzliya, which "provides a dramatic solution to rocket fire."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 09:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947575/3947575_9FD81847F7004CAC8669A5ECAF2A744A_200110_3947575_Israel_claims_breakthrough_in_anti_missile_laser_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Lasers, laser, directed energy weapon, missile, missiles, aerial threats, anti-missile, antitank guided missile, active defense system, active defense systems, Israel, defense, technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947345</guid>
      <title>Toyota to transform site at Mt. Fuji base into a futuristic city</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Danish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group has been commissioned by Toyota to build a prototype futuristic city called Woven City at the base of Mt. Fuji in Japan.In a press release, Toyota said the city will be built on a 175-acre site and will be used to test futuristic vehicles, AI robots and smart homes in a "real-world environment."Designs of the city were unveiled at the Consumer Electronic Show in Las Vegas on January 7.Woven City will include buildings made mostly of wood for sustainability, with its rooftops covered with solar panels to produce energy. In addition to solar power, the city will also be powered by hydrogen fuel cells.Homes will be equipped with AI robots and sensors to take care of residents' basic needs and to monitor their health.The futuristic city's main roads will only allow fully-autonomous vehicles, such as the Toyota e-Palettes, to operate. There will be separate roads for pedestrians and those using personal mobility vehicles such as bicycles.A central plaza, neighborhood parks and a large central park will be included for social gatherings among residents.Toyota explained in its press release that it plans to populate the city with company employees, families, retired couples, visiting scientists and others.The city will initially be populated with 2,000 people. The company plans to break ground by early 2021.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 02:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947345/3947345_B4556CFCD5DC4F1384B00F27E40362FB_200110_3947345_Toyota_to_transform_site_at_Mt__Fuji_base_into_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Futuristic cities, toyota futuristic city, japanese futuristic city, Woven City, Toyota Woven city, city of the future, toyota city of the future, futuristic toyota city, futuristic cities in the world, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947332</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman rams into illegally parked car eleven times</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHEJIANG, CHINA  A Chinese woman turned herself in to police after a spot of parking rage. The woman known only as Yang had difficulties leaving her parking space Saturday night after a black vehicle illegally parked in front of her. She tried to contact the owner of the car and waited for 10 minutes; with no response, she took matters into her own hands and rammed into the car a total of 11 times.  The surveillance footage went viral with some people empathizing with her whilst others claimed that she could have pulled out of the space had she been more careful.Yang turned herself in to police the following day in Tonglu county in Zhejiang. They said that despite the fact the other vehicle was parked illegally she could still be charged with various crimes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947332/3947332_BFF7182652744AD48C52702036EB0538_200110_3947332_Chinese_woman_rams_into_illegally_parked_car_ele_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Road rage, Chinese woman rams into car, illegal parking, Chinese driving, driving in China, parking fails, bad parking, funny parking fails, driving fails, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948923</guid>
      <title>U.S. Army is retooling to fight in the Indo-Pacific Region</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. Army will deploy two task forces with the ability to fight across the information, electronic, cyber and missile domains in the Pacific to counter China.Reuters reports that Army Secretary Ryan McCarthy said at a Brookings Institute event on Friday that the multi-domain task forces will be established in two years.Although McCarthy did not specify any locations, Bloomberg News speculates that those units will likely be based on islands east of Taiwan and the Philippines.Citing McCarthy, Reuters reports the U.S. Army intends to "neutralize all the investments China and Russia have made."China's military strategy calls for blocking U.S. naval forces from entering the Pacific through the first and second island chains.The People's Liberation Army intends to achieve this by utilizing surveillance satellites and building up its arsenal of anti-ship ballistic missiles.The task forces would potentially be armed with hypersonic missiles and other weapons capable of attacking land and sea based targets.Reuters reports that these units will help neutralize the capabilities China and Russia now possess.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948923/3948923_E43ACBACC8CE4A508C5278116E70CEB4_200113_3948923_U_S__Army_is_retooling_to_fight_in_the_Indo_Paci_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[U.S. Army, US Army, multi-domain task forces, multi-domain task force, cyber warfare, long-range missiles, hypersonic missiles, electronic warfare, information warfare, China, Beijing, Pacific, Indo-Pacific, U.S., Brookings Institute, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948902</guid>
      <title>NASA completes the booster for its 'mega-rocket'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS  NASA rolled out the core stage of the Space Launch System 'mega-rocket' from a New Orleans factory on Wednesday.BBC reports that the core stage was loaded onto the Pegasus barge to sail down the Mississippi River for testing at the Stennis Space Center.According to NASA, the SLS rocket is the backbone of U.S. plans to land on the moon again by 2024 and to explore Mars. It has a top speed of Mach 23.NASA states that the rocket's core stage is 212 feet tall and 27.6 feet wide, making it the largest booster ever built.The core stage features a forward skirt for housing avionics, a liquid oxygen fuel tank, an intertank that joins the boosters' tanks, a liquid hydrogen fuel tank and quadruple RS-24 engines.The four engines create more than 2 million pounds of combined thrust.The BBC reports that the SLS will deliver the Orion spacecraftwhich is undergoing testingto Luna for the uncrewed Artemis 1 mission planned for the next year.According to European Space Agency, the Orion spacecraft will feature foldable solar panels and it will orbit the moon for the Artemis 1 mission.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948902/3948902_55C0B65D79264A84A2F3FE9B2BAFEC05_200113_3948902_NASA_completes_the_booster_for_its__mega_rocket__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mega-rocket, megarocket, core stage, space launch system, sls, giant rocket, huge rocket, Artemis, Orion, booster, space, spacecraft, barge, New Orleans, NASA, Mississippi, US, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948877</guid>
      <title>Taiwan President Tsai wins 2nd term in massive landslide</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN  Taiwanese voters young and old hit the polls en masse on Saturday, voting President Tsai Ing-wen to a second term and giving the Democratic Progressive Party control of the legislature once again.According to Focus Taiwan, Tsai received 57 percent of the voteearning a record 8,170,231 votesin a three-way race against panda hugging KMT candidate Han Kuo-yu with 38 percent and PFP candidate James Soong with only 4 percent.Focus Taiwan reports that voter turnout hit a whopping 74 percent, higher than 2016's 66.38 percent turnout. The DPP importantly retains control of the Legislative Yuan, which will allow Tsai to continue with her reform agenda. According to the failing New York Times, Tsai's incredible victory highlighted how effectively her campaign tapped into an electorate that isn't fooled at all by China's intentions. Another factor influencing the vote were months of protests in Hong Kong against Beijing's strong arm tactics and encroachment into the city.But by far, the biggest deciding factor in the historic election was the younger generation, who consider themselves Taiwanese, hitting the polls in force. The people have spoken and the message is clear, Taiwan and the Taiwanese people are here to stay.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 10:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948877/3948877_1BB1F1E0613E4D1D9297151EB156C524_200113_3948877_Taiwan_President_Tsai_wins_2nd_term_in_massive_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taiwan elections 2020, President Tsai wins 2nd term, Taiwan Tsai Ing-wen, Taiwan Han Kuo-yu, Tsai vs Han, Tsai wins landslide victory, Taiwanese voters, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948780</guid>
      <title>Iran admits downing Ukranian aircraft, but calls it an accident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN  Iran has admitted to accidently shooting down a Ukranian airplane on January 8, killing all 176 passengers and crew members onboard.According to the Guardian, Ukraine International Airlines flight PS752 took off from Tehran's Imam Khomeini International Airport at 6:12 a.m., and reached roughly 8,000 feet in altitude before the plane exploded and came crashing down at 6:18 a.m. The flight was en route to Kiev, Ukraine.Iran had previously denied shooting down the plane for three days, before issuing a statement on Iranian state TV in which the country took responsibility for the incident, reports BBC News. The country said the plane was hit due to "human error" and said the flight was hit by a missile unintentionally.An Iranian Revolutionary Guard airspace commander said that the plane was downed by a short-range missile that exploded beside the aircraft, though he did not specify which missile system was used during the incident.Images shared on social media appears to show the remains of a missile believed to be from Iran's Tor-M1 system near the site of the plane crash.Iran said its military was at its "highest level of readiness" due to heightened tensions with the U.S.The incident occurred just hours after Iran carried out missile strikes on two Iraqi air bases housing U.S. soldiers.Iran's military apologized and said that they would work to upgrade their systems to prevent these types of mistakes in the future.Iranian citizens have since taken to the streets condemning their government and even chanting for their Supreme Leader Ayatollah Khamenei to step down in the aftermath of the downing of the Ukranian jet, CNN reports. Demonstrators say they want those responsible for the mishap to be prosecuted.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948780/3948780_360B191B5FDA4A1683E6A03E9BB4980F_200113_3948780_Iran_admits_downing_Ukranian_aircraft__but_calls_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Iran news today, iran downs ukraine plane, ukraine plane crash, ukraine international airlines, flight PS752, flight ps 752 crash, flight ps752 missile strike, iran plane crash, tehran plane crash, iran plane crash site, iran accidentally shot down plane, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948777</guid>
      <title>The Chinese paddlefish is extinct</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANGTZE, CHINA  The Chinese paddlefish has been declared extinct. But what was it and why has this happened?The Chinese paddlefish was thought to be the world's largest freshwater fish with an average length of 10 feet. Some reports recorded them reaching 23 feet and weighing half a ton.The Chinese paddlefish had a long, silver-gray body and their name derived from their protruding snout that resembled a paddle.The fish were prominent in many parts of the Yangtze, Asia's largest river flowing 3914 miles from the Tibetan Plateau to the East China Sea.They used their special sword-like snout to sense electrical activity to find prey, such as crustaceans and fish, however, they haven't been spotted since 2003.In the journal Science of The Total Environment, a team of researchers at the Chinese Academy of Fishery Sciences in Wuhan declared the paddlefish as extinct. They believe overfishing in the 1970s, which harvested 25 tons of paddlefish per year on average was the root cause of the gradual decline in paddlefish.However, the main contributor which led to extinction was the loss of habitat through the construction of the Gezhouba Dam, built on the main stem of the Yangtze.The dam was constructed without a fish ladder or bypass, cutting off the paddlefish from their only spawning grounds upstream.The team tried to locate the paddlefish at hundreds of locations along the Yangtze using nets, sonar and electro-fishing gear.Researchers even monitored fish markets around the country but found nothing.Based on the previous population size and the intervals between sightings, the researchers used a mathematical model to determine the likelihood that the species is, in fact, extinct and most likely went extinct between 2005 and 2010.The researchers believe that this is a hard lesson in conservation. Sadly, efforts to save the paddlefish did not begin until the fish had already gone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948777/3948777_BEE653C905874F2481A0E87663FCA42E_200113_3948777_The_Chinese_paddlefish_is_extinct_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Chinese paddlefish, Chinese paddlefish extinct, Yangtze river, Yangtze paddlefish, conservation, world's largest fish extinct, Chinese fish extinct]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948711</guid>
      <title>Vulnerabilities found in video-sharing app TikTok</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN CARLOS, CALIFORNIA  Cybersecurity firm Check Point has conducted an investigation into video-sharing app TikTok and found major vulnerabilities within the app.In a report, researchers from the company explained that hackers could access a person's account by using a function on TikTok's website that allows users to enter their phone number, which will text them a link to download the app.Hackers could use this flaw to change the download url and send a fraudulent SMS link containing a malicious link created by the attacker. This allowed attackers to access a user's account and to send requests on their behalf.Attackers could use this to manipulate a user's content feed by deleting videos from their feed and uploading unauthorized videos onto their feed instead. Hackers would also have the authority to change a user's video privacy settings from hidden, or private, to public.Researchers found that attackers could also execute JavaScript code in order to retrieve sensitive information about the user. This includes emails, payment information or birthdates.According to the BBC, Check Point said they informed TikTok's parent company ByteDance about the vulnerabilities in November.TikTok says the security flaws have since been fixed in their latest app version.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 04:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948711/3948711_C335D815DCF940CCA8D0DF01CA17FF2C_200113_3948711_Vulnerabilities_found_in_video_sharing_app_TikTo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TikTok, Tik tok vulnerabilities, tiktok security flaws, tik tok security, tik tok security breach, checkpoint tik tok, tik tok news, is Tik Tok secure, tik tok social media, tik tok major security flaws, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948647</guid>
      <title>Taco Bell robber makes himself a meal and has a nap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAWRENCEVILLE, GEORGIA  A burglar who broke into a Taco Bell in Georgia made the opposite of a quick getaway after he made himself a snack and then had a nap. According to ABC News, the Gwinnett County Police Department released photos and surveillance video of a guy who broke into the Taco Hell on Dec. 25, because they need help locating him. Surveillance footage shows the man crawl through the drive-thru window around 12:15 a.m.  After getting in, he then makes a run for the  fryers, which he proceeds to turn on. The taco thief then walks into the cooler and comes out with a whole mess of food, which he then whips up and scarfs down like a champ.  That's apparently when he gets hit with a serious case of the itis, which knocks him out for a good couple of hours right on the floor.  Sleepy head finally wakes up from his slumber around 3 a.m. He then five finger discounts a laptop and a tablet, before making his way out the back door, which triggers an alarm.  When the cops showed up on scene, the burrito bandito was nowhere to be seen. Officers were called back to the fine dining establishment when it opened because a manager found the suspect's headphones and black beanie cap.The manager told police that the suspect might have worked at Taco Bell before as he knew how to use the fryer and where all the fine quality food was located.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 03:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948647/3948647_F9B604126A6A42DC8A1FAF18BB6E9B5F_200113_3948647_Taco_Bell_robber_makes_himself_a_meal_and_has_a__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taco Bell burglar, Taco Bell burglar takes nap, Taco Bell burglar makes meal, Taco Bell burglar Georgia, burglar takes nap, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948642</guid>
      <title>Taco Bell robber makes himself a meal and has a nap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAWRENCEVILLE, GEORGIA  A burglar who broke into a Taco Bell in Georgia made the opposite of a quick getaway after he made himself a snack and then had a nap. According to ABC News, the Gwinnett County Police Department released photos and surveillance video of a guy who broke into the Taco Hell on Dec. 25, because they need help locating him. Surveillance footage shows the man crawl through the drive-thru window around 12:15 a.m.  After getting in, he then makes a run for the  fryers, which he proceeds to turn on. The taco thief then walks into the cooler and comes out with a whole mess of food, which he then whips up and scarfs down like a champ.  That's apparently when he gets hit with a serious case of the itis, which knocks him out for a good couple of hours right on the floor.  Sleepy head finally wakes up from his slumber around 3 a.m. He then five finger discounts a laptop and a tablet, before making his way out the back door, which triggers an alarm.  When the cops showed up on scene, the burrito bandito was nowhere to be seen. Officers were called back to the fine dining establishment when it opened because a manager found the suspect's headphones and black beanie cap.The manager told police that the suspect might have worked at Taco Bell before as he knew how to use the fryer and where all the fine quality food was located.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 02:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948642/3948642_49A5D0033CF44E90A5AE4FB2E5C5133C_200113_3948642_Taco_Bell_robber_makes_himself_a_meal_and_has_a__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taco Bell burglar, Taco Bell burglar takes nap, Taco Bell burglar makes meal, Taco Bell burglar Georgia, burglar takes nap, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948637</guid>
      <title>Supermarket offers cheap TVs on accident, kicks out shoppers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTPELLIER, FRANCE  French supermarket Géant Casino accidentally advertised TVs that cost over $440 for only $35. According to the BBC, this caused a whole bunch of shoppers to rush over and grab a TV, or twoor five. The Beebs says the mix-up occurred because the televisions were tagged at 30.99 euros instead of 399 euros. Unfortunately for shoppers, the store refused to sell the TVs at the bargain basement price, but the people weren't having it. The customers then blocked the checkout area demanding that they be allowed their flatscreens. So Géant did the reasonable thing and called the police. BBC reports that dozens of police officers had to be sent to help clear the store out.   Images and video posted to social media show angry customers with a mountain load of TVs refusing to leave the store empty handed. The police were finally successful in getting everyone out, although it did take over an hour after the store's closing time. The BBC reports that French retailers are required to sell items at the listed price under the consumer code, however exceptions are allowed for obvious mistakes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 02:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948637/3948637_504FAA6054174731B591BC19EAD9F537_200113_3948637_Supermarket_offers_cheap_TVs_on_accident__kicks__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[French supermarket, French supermarket TV deal, French supermarket TV price accident, French supermarket TV incident, TV price mistake, price error, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949556</guid>
      <title>Woman gets caught lying about why she's late to work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In an epic photoshop fail, a woman was caught lying to her boss about why she was late to work.In an attempt to get a day off, the unnamed woman sent an image of a punctured tire with a nail in it to her boss and apologized for not being able to make it in.However, on zooming into the image it's clear that the image has been photoshopped.The boss shared the epic fail with her coworker, Sydney Whitson who shared it via Twitter in a post that has since gone viral with over 45,000 retweets and counting. In an unsurprising twist, if you google 'nail in tire', it's the first image that comes up.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949556/3949556_5AFFB030697E4EB39849B37290AED9CF_200115_3949556_Woman_gets_caught_lying_about_why_she_s_late_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Epic fail, photoshop fail, funny photoshop fail, woman photoshop fail, nail in tire, nail in tire fail, woman caught lying about nail, boss catches employ lying, boss catches employee, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949414</guid>
      <title>Carrots and sweet potatoes airdropped to hungry animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW SOUTH WALES  As Australia continues to struggle with bushfires, brush-tailed rock-wallabies are getting a helping hand via air.  According to Global News, the New South Wales government is airdropping thousands of kilograms of carrots and sweet potatoes to starving animals in a mission called "Operation Wallaby."  In a statement released on Sunday by NSW environment minister Matt Kean, "initial fire assessments indicate the habitat of several important brush-tailed rock-wallaby populations was burnt in the recent bushfires. The wallabies typically survive the fire itself, but are then left stranded with limited natural food as the fire takes out the vegetation around their rocky habitat." He continued, "the wallabies were already under stress from the ongoing drought, making survival challenging for the wallabies without assistance."Global News reports that the aerial food deliveries are expected to help endangered species like wallabies amid larger wildlife recovery efforts across the country in the aftermath of bushfires. According to a government media release, nearly 2,000 kilograms of veggies were dropped to 11 different rock-wallaby colonies. The drops will continue, and will be accompanied by feral predator control as the little critters recover.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949414/3949414_BE9A4C7194D54645B33B81FED3BC475B_200114_3949414_Carrots_and_sweet_potatoes_airdropped_to_hungry__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Australia wallaby, Australia Operation Wallaby, carrot airdrop, sweet potato airdrop, Australia brush-tail rock-wallaby, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949364</guid>
      <title>Japan will upgrade air defense missiles to counter North Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Japan's Type-03 Air Defense System is a surface to air missile system that utilizes a truck-mounted launcher to shoot interceptor missiles, according to Missile Advocacy.Citing unnamed defense officials, Japan Forward reports the Japanese military will give the missile an anti-ballistic capability to respond to the North Korean threat.According to Global Security, the Chu-SAM is 490 cm long, 30 cm wide, and weighs 580 kg.Missile Advocacy states that the current version of the missile has a top speed of Mach 2.5.According to Global Defense, the rocket uses a single stage solid fuel design and includes an active radar homing system.Japan Forward reports that the Defense Agency is testing technologies that will improve both components of the projectile.North Korea's new ballistic missile, which was tested last year and is based on Russia's Iskander missile, flies in an erratic trajectory that Japan's other air defense missiles cannot track.According to Japan Forward, the upgraded the Chu-SAM will be able to predict the irregular trajectory and achieve a shootdown of the enemy missile.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 11:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949364/3949364_EEA2985530AF4A4F81E88C94353E11BB_200114_3949364_Japan_will_upgrade_air_defense_missiles_to_count_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Japan upgrades anti-ballistic missiles, Japan upgrades anti-ballistic missile, Japan upgrades SAMs, erratic trajectory, ballistic missile, ballistic missiles, North Korea, Chu-SAM, Type-03 Air Defense System, Type-03, Iskander, Chu-SAM, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949347</guid>
      <title>Philippines Taal volcano could be about ready to blow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANILA, PHILIPPINES  Philippine officials have urged a "total evacuation" of millions of people close to Manila, after a volcano spewed ash up to nine miles into the air on Sunday, prompting warnings of a possible "explosive eruption," CNN reports. The BBC reports that early Monday, a weak flow of lava began seeping out of Taal volcano, which is located around 45 miles south of Manila. According to the BBC, Taal had earlier emitted a huge plume of ash, triggering the mass evacuation of 8,000 people from the immediate area. The BBC cites that Taal is the country's second most active volcano, located in the middle of a lake. CNN reports that the Philippine Institute of Volcanology and SeismologyPHIVOLCShas raised the alert lever to four, meaning an "explosive eruption" could happen in the coming hours or days. The highest alert level is five, indicating that an eruption is taking place. According to CNN, in explosive eruptions, magma is fragmented and violently released from the volcano as opposed to thick lava flowing out. PHIVOLCS has requested a "total evacuation" of citizens within a 10.5 mile radius around the volcano.    The BBC reports that Taal is also one of the world's smallest volcanoes and has recorded at least 34 eruptions in the past 450 years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949347/3949347_8B27B8FFF9A54326905289AA91A8FF42_200114_3949347_Philippines_Taal_volcano_could_be_about_ready_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taal volcano, Taal volcano eruption, Taal volcano lava flows, Philippines Taal volcano, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949343</guid>
      <title>How Iran accidentally killed 176 people on Flight PS 752</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN  Iran's military on Saturday admitted that its air defense system had shot down Ukraine's Flight 752 by mistake.Citing Iranian official statements, the New York Times said the passenger jet had been misidentified as a U.S. cruise missile.The New York Times reports that the Tor is a mobile system carrying eight missiles, that can be operated without input from other air defense infrastructure.Citing defense analyst Steven Zaloga, Bloomberg reports that the missile's guidance system is unable to distinguish cruise missiles from military aircraft or civilian airplanes.Citing FlightRadar24, Bloomberg reports that the Boeing 737 made a slight right turn two minutes after its takeoff from Tehran International Airport, which was normal.The plane was clearly transmitting its identity and position until it climbed to about 7,900 feet of altitude, presumably because it was hit by missile fire."The plane plunged into a field in between the cities of Parand and Shariar. All 176 passengers and crew were killed.Due to the Tor's indiscriminate guidance system, most nations do not operate the weapon without connecting it into a command structure.Bloomberg reports that according to Zaloga, SA-15 operators were not supposed to fire without authorization.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949343/3949343_B6D435F9383243209E49625242050F72_200114_3949343_How_Iran_accidentally_killed_176_people_on_Fligh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Iran shoots down plane, Iran accidentally shoots down plane, Iran shoots down Ukrainian plane, Tor, Tor SA-15, surface to air missile, SAM, missile, missiles, Iranian missile, Iranian missiles, Flight PS 752, Flight 752, Boeing 737, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949278</guid>
      <title>Sinkhole swallows up public bus in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINING, CHINA  Anyone else getting a sinking feeling in your stomach? Oh that's just the entire road collapsing. On January 13, a road in Xining, China suddenly opened up and swallowed half of a public bus while waiting for passengers to get on.Footage from Chinese social media shows people fleeing the scene as soon as the road begins to give way.  Some bystanders tried to help passengers escape, but as the sinkhole got bigger they all said screw it and just ran away instead. After that, an explosion is seen occurring at the front of the bus. It's unclear what caused the blast. According to Sina News, 15 people are injured while 10 are missing. Authorities say they will continue searching for those missing and will investigate the cause of the incident.Just last month, two giant sinkholes, one in Guangzhou and the other in Xiamen, appeared over underground railways that were under construction in China. For the Guangzhou subway, three people actually went missing while in Xiamen the sinkhole gobbled up passing vehicles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 08:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949278/3949278_4B023587483844C89BB61EF1D06C980C_200114_3949278_Sinkhole_swallows_up_public_bus_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Giant sinkhole, chinese sinkhole, chinese sinkhole 2020, sinkhole caught on tape, xining sinkhole china, road collapse, road collapse china, sinkhole swallows bus in china, china bus sinkhole, sinkhole swallows bus, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949152</guid>
      <title>Water on Mars is evaporating faster than expected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  New research by France's National Center for Scientific Research suggests that water on Mars is evaporating faster than previously thought.Scientists analyzed data from the Trace Gas Orbiter, which orbits around Mars, and found seasonal changes affect how water vapor is distributed around the atmosphere.As the sun warms up the red planet's ice poles, water molecules, in the form of water vapor, are released into the atmosphere. The molecules are then carried by the wind to higher altitudes.During the warmest parts of the year, Mars' atmosphere becomes "supersaturated" with 10 to 100 times more water vapor than its frigid cold temperatures typically allow. This allows the water to reach the planet's upper atmosphere.As water molecules make their way to Mars' upper atmosphere, ultraviolet rays from the sun breaks them down into hydrogen and oxygen atoms where the atoms are able to escape into space.The researchers were surprised at their findings, as they expected that the water vapor would be limited by Mars' cold temperatures and would condense into clouds, according to Space.com.Franck Montmessin, one of the scientists involved with the study, told the publication that further research would be needed to find out how much water exactly is making its way to Mars' upper atmosphere and escaping so that scientists can get a better understanding of the process.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949152/3949152_2D49B0F5DAF8449AB1818AEC15B36F6A_200114_3949152_Water_on_Mars_is_evaporating_faster_than_expecte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mars water, mars, martian atmosphere, mars is losing water, mars water evaporating, mars water disappearing, water on mars, mars water vapor, water vapor on mars, martian water disappearing, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949118</guid>
      <title>Tortoise's 'libido' saves his species</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA CRUZ ISLAND, CALIFORNIA  A 100-year-old tortoise named, 'Diego' has been credited with saving his species after he was enlisted to help boost species numbers as part of a conservation program. Set up in 1965 the program has produced more than 2,000 giant tortoises and this time around, Diego is said to have fathered 800 offspring. Diego was requested from California's San Diego Zoo, however, the Galapagos National Park believes that he was originally from there and was taken during a scientific expedition 80 years ago.He will be released back to Ecuador's Galapagos Islands, located in the Pacific Ocean for a well-deserved retirement where he will join a 1,800 strong tortoise population, with park rangers there crediting him with fathering 40% of them.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 02:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949118/3949118_B94B56D721EC4D209E6F304E2D2FF89A_200114_3949118_Tortoise_s__libido__saves_his_species_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Diego the tortoise, tortoise saves species, Galapagos tortoise, tortoise species saving, tortoise sex drive, species saving sex drive, tortoise sex drive, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949112</guid>
      <title>Man finds cigarette butt in his fancy Haidilao hot pot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAOJI, CHINA  A Chinese man enjoying some hot pot at China's most popular chain was lucky enough to find a cigarette butt in his yummy-for-the-tummy broth. According to Pear Video, a customer surnamed Liu was eating at a Haidilao location in the Shaanxi city of Baoji. Unfortunately for Liu, lurking inside his delicious broth was a nastly old cigarette butt. Either that, or he was eating tobacco flavored hot pot. Anyways, it looks like Liu called up the chain's headquarters and demanded 14 cents in compensation and that the location be shut down for one week. Haidilao refused to close the location in question, but they did offer the man $144 instead. Too bad Liu turned them down. Guess we'll have to wait and see what happens. According to the Shanghaiist, Haidilao now has more than 190 stores through fun-loving China and in cities like L.A., Singapore, Seoul and Tokyo.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 02:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949112/3949112_C5F430A496A84036B727491D89333E66_200114_3949112_Man_finds_cigarette_butt_in_his_fancy_Haidilao_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China hot pot, China Haidilao hotpot, customer finds cigarette in hot pot, hot pot mistake, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949941</guid>
      <title>British tourist dies falling off Australian cliff taking selfie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  A British woman is sadly no longer around after taking a plunge off a cliff in Australiawhile trying to selfie. News Corp Australia reports that 21-year-old Madalyn Davis was at Diamond Bay Reserve on Sunday with some friends.  According to reports, Davis had been at a party in a rich suburb east of Sydney, when they decided to watch the sunrise from the cliffs, which also happen to be a popular selfie spot. According to Marine Rescue New South Wales, Davis and her friends split up when they got to the cliffs. BBC reports that signs are placed to warn people to stay away from the cliff edge and the local mayor said the height of the fences in the area had been increased. It appears that Davis was attempting to take a selfie when she somehow fell off and was fatally injured. When everyone regrouped, Davis was nowhere to be found, so they called rescue services. Emergency crews responded to the scene around 6:30 a.m. local time. Her body was located and retrieved from the water about four hours later.   According to her social media accounts, Davis was an eyelash beautician and had recently been to Thailand and Bali before making her way Down Under.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949941/3949941_CC29B381F753448D84907FD3F942DC27_200115_3949941_British_tourist_dies_falling_off_Australian_clif_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[British tourist, British tourist falls, British tourist selfie Sydney, Madylin Davis, Madylin Davis selfie, Madylin Davis selfie Sydney, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949937</guid>
      <title>Dog-walking app Wag loses another doggo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN ANTONIO  It appears that the dog-walking app Wag is really great at walking your dog, however it's the returning your pet part that has them perplexed.According to the New York Post, Wag has already been accused of losing more than a dozen doggos across the countrywell, it looks like they can add another one to the list. San Antonio resident Cody Martinez told the Post that he travels a lot for work and used the app to take care of his two huskies Sozin and Ozai while he was out of town. Martinez said that on Oct. 4 while he was working in Philadelphia, he got a call from a Wag representative saying Sozin had gotten loose from his collar during a walk and was missing.The rep told him to relax, and said the company would be putting up flyers in the area and that it was opening up a tip line so people could call in sightings. Guess what? The flyers didn't work, but Wag kept giving Martinez the run around and failed to take other actions like dispatching dog trackers. Even though he repeatedly asked for more help besides flyers, he wasn't offered a tracker until 10 days after Sozin went missing. By the time the tracker was actually sent, three weeks had passed. The tracker then told Martinez that if she would have gotten there earlier, they might have had a better shot.  Wag was then kind enough to call Martinez last Friday, more than three months after Sozin went missing, to say they were cutting ties and giving up the search. A Wag spokesperson said it had suspended the walker who lost Sozin and that it continues to monitor the tip line for any Sozin sightings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949937/3949937_B7E1FE96621C4952A92A7A03D3971B55_200115_3949937_Dog_walking_app_Wag_loses_another_doggo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Wag app, dog walking app, wag dog walking app, wag loses dog, wag app loses dog, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949906</guid>
      <title>Delta aircraft dumps fuel on school before landing at LAX</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Delta Airlines Flight 89 was enroute to Shanghai from Los Angeles International Airport on Tuesday when the plane experienced an engine issue shortly after takeoff. The plane then proceeded to return to the airport and release jet fuel before conducting an emergency landing. The jet fuel was dumped over a Los Angeles schoolyard and school buildings, reports NBC News. According to the Los Angeles County Fire Department, at least 20 children and 11 adults are being treated for minor injuries for fuel exposure. Those affected were being treated by firefighters on the scene for skin irritation and breathing problems.The fire department said none of the injured needed to be hospitalized.The airline explained the release of fuel is required as part of standard procedure to reach a safe landing weight, Reuters reports, citing a statement from Delta Airlines.In a statement on Twitter, the Federal Aviation Administration explained that there are special fuel-dumping procedures which require airplanes to release jet fuel over designated unpopulated areas. The agency said that the fuel is typically released at higher altitudes so that it dissolves before reaching the ground.The FAA said in the same statement that it is "thoroughly investigating" the circumstances around the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949906/3949906_E9A1A5EF689846FAB0A92D1B7F3BEC5A_200115_3949906_Delta_aircraft_dumps_fuel_on_school_before_landi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Delta jet, delta jet dumps fuel, delta plane, delta emergency, delta jet fuel release, delta fuel release,  LAX, delta jet dumps fuel over school yard, airplane dumps fuel over school, jet release, airplane fuel release, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949809</guid>
      <title>EU, Russia to launch ExoMars mission in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZURICH, SWITZERLAND  The EU and Russia are collaborating on a mission to Mars to try and answer the question of whether life has ever existed on the Red Planet.According to the European Space Agency, the ExoMars programme is comprised of two missions. The first  the Trace Gas Orbiter  launched in 2016 to orbit Mars and examined its atmosphere.The Schiaparelli lander had been deployed with the Trace Gas Orbiter to the surface but crashed during a touchdown attempt.The second mission, slated for July 2020, will launch Roscosmos' Kazachok surface platform and the ESA's Rosalind Franklin rover to Mars via a Proton rocket.After a nine-month journey, a descent module will separate from the carrier and perform a controlled landing on the surface of the Red Planet, at a site called the Oxia Planum.Space reports that the Oxia Planum is a plain in the planet's northern hemisphere that is rich in clay deposits, indicating ancient water activity.After touchdown, the Kazachok platform will remain at the landing site to study the surface environment. Instruments on board will be used to take images of the landing point, study subsurface water distribution, as well as the planet's atmosphere and internal structure.The rover, meanwhile, will travel across the planet's surface, using stereo cameras to build navigation maps and collision avoidance cameras to navigate the terrain. It will drill up to 2 meters down to retrieve underground samples that may contain preserved biomarkers, which will be subject to chemical, physical, and spectral analysis.New Atlas reports that the mission has had trouble in the past with the parachutes, which tore in high-altitude tests.The team has since worked with NASA to iron out the issues, and have announced that the previous problems have been eliminated. But to be sure, further tests will be conducted ahead of the official launch later in the year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 10:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949809/3949809_F798EF2EB06445038E23332BBFAB685F_200115_3949809_EU__Russia_to_launch_ExoMars_mission_in_2020_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[exomars 2020, exomars, mars mission, mission to mars, esa, roscosmos, mars rover, exomars rover, exomars 2020 rover, Rosalind Franklin rover, Kazachok surface platform, Oxia Planum, mars, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949580</guid>
      <title>New artificial trees to absorb pollution in London</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  German startup Green City Solutions has installed artificial trees called CityTrees across London to absorb urban pollution.According to the company's website, the CityTree is the world's first bio-tech filter that has been able to considerably improve air quality.The CityTree is a tower filled with different types of moss which collect toxins such as particulate matters such as PM 10 and nitrogen dioxide from the air while giving off oxygen. Each artificial tree is able to produce as much clean air as 275 real trees, according to Dezeen.The structure is powered by solar panels and collects rainwater which is evenly distributed using a fully automated irrigation system.Green City Solutions explains on their website that the CityTrees also contain Internet-of-Things technology to gather environmental data about the trees' surrounding as well as data about its own performance. The artificial trees also have the ability to create an immense cooling effect in its surrounding atmosphere as mosses can store large amounts of moisture.CityTrees were previously trialled in London in 2018 as a trial. The current project is a permanent installation.The structures have previously been installed in Oslo, Paris, Brussels and Hong Kong,  according to CNN.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 02:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949580/3949580_312EEF18DFAC405B99858A11C3566630_200115_3949580_New_artificial_trees_to_absorb_pollution_in_Lond_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[CityTree bench, artificial trees, london artificial trees, london smart bench, mossy living wall, london CityTree, Green City Solutions, Green City Solutions CityTrees, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950538</guid>
      <title>Villagers in India flee after being terrorized by army of monkeys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NARASAPURAM VILLAGE, INDIA  In a plot straight out of the Planet of the Apes films, villagers in India were forced to flee their homes after being menaced by a crazed army of over 400 monkeys.According to the Daily Star, the whole thing started 15 years ago, when a troop of mischievous macaques were kicked out of Hyderabad and abandoned near the village of Narasapuram.They were a nuisance, but it wasn't until they bred and multiplied into an army of over 400 that they REALLY became a problem.Village chief Srivarama Krishna told the Daily Star that the pesky primates became more brazen and opportunistic, stealing snacks and groceries out of people's hands, and even sneaking into houses to grab pots of food.They also turned more aggressive, and started attacking people, which in turn led to  about 20 families packing their bags and fleeing the village.According to the New Indian Express, village chief Krishna asked expert monkey catchers to help nab the macaques in exchange for money from the villagers.Over 100 monkeys were caught and released deep in the forest, prompting old residents to come back now that the village's primate population has gone down.Here's hoping Planet of the Apes doesn't rise again anytime soon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950538/3950538_3889C82A802B4674A807F2A649D7B7B8_200117_3950538_Villagers_in_India_flee_after_being_terrorized_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Planet of the apes, monkeys, gang of monkeys, monkey gang, monkey army, monkeys terrorizing people, monkeys india, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950372</guid>
      <title>Domino's wants to open more than 800 shops in Italy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ITALY  Pizza giant Domino's is clearly overestimating the world's love for crappy American pizza with its latest announcement that it will open 880 locations in Italy. That's right folks. According to the New York Daily News, Domino's for some reason thinks that it can get a piece of the pie in the land where actual pizza was invented. According to the CEO of Domino's Italy Alessandro Lazzaroni, the new stores would join the 16,000 other locations the pizza juggernaut has in 85 other countries. Lazzaroni said the new locations would center on north and central Italy and focus on home delivery as their selling point. Domino's for some reason actually thinks it can become the biggest food delivery outlet in the country.  Domino's apparently already has 29 stores in Italy, mostly around Rome, Milan and Turin. The announcement sparked hilarious reactions online with some making comparing the move to "selling ice to Eskimos" or "bringing sand to the beach."Perhaps Taco Bell should think about a move to Mexico? Or maybe Panda Express should think about a hard China push? Don't listen to the haters Domino's. You guys will crush it in Italy. With pizza products like hot dog stuffed crust, how could you possibly go wrong?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950372/3950372_4DD8E7A1A16E40C58259788892F40086_200116_3950372_Domino_s_wants_to_open_more_than_800_shops_in_It_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Domino's, Domino's Pizza, Domino's Pizza Italy, Domino's Italy expansion, Domino's Italy plans, Italians mad Domino's, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950368</guid>
      <title>Distracted dad almost puts son through X-ray scanner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUIGANG, CHINA  Who hasn't been there before? Running late for a flight or the train with a little one in tow and a boatload of luggage for extra fun. A father at a train station in the Guangxi city of Guigang clearly had some other things on his mind when he almost sent his son through a security checkpoint X-ray scanner by accident. According to video posted to Miaopai, the distracted daddy was pushing his luggage, which was also doubling as a ride for his 3-year-old son on January 12.  Security camera footage shows dad of the decade approach the security check and get in line.   When it's his turn, he just starts going through the motions and grabs his son and puts him right onto the conveyor belt.It isn't until security and another traveler point at that lil man isn't baggage that the dad jumps into action and rescues him from a free X-ray.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950368/3950368_890265BE221F4A8297D2D124845E4A21_200116_3950368_Distracted_dad_almost_puts_son_through_X_ray_sca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, china x ray machine, China dad x ray machine, China distracted dad, x ray machine train station, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950362</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show Philippines Taal volcano erupting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TALISAY, PHILIPPINES  The eruption of Taal volcano in the Philippines was so big that it was visible from space.Japanese satellite Himawari-8 captured a series of images from space showing plumes of smoke from the volcano that erupted on January 12, according to Live Science. The images were put together to create an animation and were released by NASA's Earth Observatory. In the satellite images, the volcano is seen spreading its volcanic plumes across the surrounding area from January 12 to 13.On Sunday, ash spewed out of the volcano as high as nine miles up into the air, CNN reports. Taal continues to create dark gray plumes that rise up to 0.6 miles high since the eruption began a couple of days ago. The Philippine Institute of Volcanology and Seismology has said that the volcano may continue to erupt in the next few days.Authorities ordered a total evacuation for those who live within 8.7 miles of the volcano, while those who live within 10.6 miles were advised to leave. Images show houses near the volcano buried in volcanic ash while animals that were left behind were captured with their fur and feathers covered with ash, according to CNN. Philippine's Institute of Volcanology and Seismology has raised the alert level for Taal volcano to a level 4. This means that the volcano may have an "explosive eruption" very soon, either in a few hours or in the coming days.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950362/3950362_B2F65B3B50DB4B428BF05B52C240E09C_200116_3950362_Satellite_images_show_Philippines_Taal_volcano_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taal volcano, Taal volcano eruption, Taal volcano eruption 2020, filipino volcano eruption, taal volcano eruption seen from space, taal volcano space, taal volcano eruption captured, taal volcano eruption captured from space, volcano eruption seen from space, Himawari-8 satellite taal volcano, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950341</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy's new missiles will be strike anyway in an hour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARLINGTON, VIRGINIA  The U.S. Navy plans to arm the fleet's newest destroyers with a classified hypersonic missile.Citing a naval officer's remarks at the Surface Naval Association's annual symposium, Fox News reports that the Zumwalt class may obtain the Conventional Prompt Strike weapon.The Zumwalts are stealthy warships that feature two advanced 155mm guns, vertical launching systems, advanced radars in the deckhouse, and electric drive propulsion. No details about the prompt strike weapons are available, but Fox reports that the missile combines a conventional warhead with a ballistic missile.This allows the U.S. to launch conventional strikes with the speed and range of nuclear weapons.According to Fox, the stealthy warships will be able to deliver missiles to any target in the world in an hour and some targets could be struck within minutes.The outlet reports that the missiles will potentially allow the U.S. to launch attacks rapidly and without giving away time or the element of surprise.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950341/3950341_8CAC082E99784027BF9A2DC558403653_200116_3950341_U_S__Navy_s_new_missiles_will_be_strike_anyway_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[US Navy, U.S. Navy, USN, Zumwalt, Zumwalt-class, destroyer, destroyers, missile, missiles, hypersonic missiles, hypersonic missile, Prompt Strike, Conventional Prompt Strike, anywhere on Earth in an hour, anywhere in the world in an hour, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950335</guid>
      <title>The solar system's 'Great Divide' explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO   A separation known as the Great Divide splits the rocky planets and the gas planets in our solar system.According to the latest paper published in Nature Astronomy, researchers can now explain how the divide came to exist.Citing the researchers, University of Colorado's news release says that rocky planets in the sunward side of the divide are poor in carbon and other organic materials.The opposite is true for the gas planets beyond the divide, such as Jupiter, which is rich in carbon.The paper theorizes that billions of years ago, the sun may have once had a massive ring structure with alternating high and low pressure bands.Those bands would separate matter into distinct sinks, one forming Jupiter and Saturn, and another Earth and Mars. This results in the Great Divide.A paper co-author says that the pressure barrier was not impenetrable, as enough materials from outer space have likely crossed over.The carbon rich material that had climbed the divide would then play a role in the evolution of life on Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950335/3950335_1C629C1431834449B4A64A11D28973F4_200116_3950335_The_solar_system_s__Great_Divide__explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[The solar system's great divide, the great divide, solar system, the sun had a ring, ring structure, ring around the sun, solar system had a ring, stellar system ring, young sun, rocky planets, gas planets, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950324</guid>
      <title>NASA's Journey to Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  NASA's road to Mars is via the moon.NASA's Moon to Mars exploration program first proposed in 2015 consists of three phases.The first, called 'Earth Reliant', involves using the International Space Station until 2024 to research deep space technologies, and study the effects of long-term space missions on the human body.It also covers the development of the Orion spacecraft and the Space Launch System super heavy lift launch vehicle, or SLS.The second phase, 'Proving Grounds', involves the creation of infrastructure in cislunar space such as the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway, to help the agency learn how to conduct operations in a deep space environment.The Gateway space station is slated for completion in the mid-2020s. According to Space.com, NASA's 2019 fiscal budget request calls for a 2022 launch of the power and propulsion module. Two additional launches by 2025 will add habitation, logistics, and airlock functions.According to the ESA, Gateway will serve as a staging post where astronauts can dock and leave their spacecraft, then travel to the lunar surface in a lander.It will also provide them shelter, a place to stock up on fuel and supplies and relay communications, and a base to dispatch crew and robots to the moon.Missions to Mars and its moons would begin during 'Earth Independent', the third and final phase, which could see NASA using the Lunar Gateway and a spacecraft such as the Deep Space Transport.According to Universe Today, a station in the Red Planet's orbit, like Lockheed Martin's proposed Mars Base Camp, could also be built to allow crewed missions to journey to the Martian surface.Based on a White House directive, NASA will be aiming to land astronauts on the moon by 2024, and then on Mars by the 2030s.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950324/3950324_685084D0601C47FDB1478429F352CEC3_200116_3950324_NASA_s_Journey_to_Mars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mars mission, moon to mars, Nasa moon to mars, moon mission, lunar mission, NASA moon mission, NASA lunar mission, gateway space station, lunar orbital platform gateway, deep space transport, Orion, SLS, Mars base camp, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950079</guid>
      <title>Man challenges ex-wife to 'trial by combat' to settle legal dispute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHELBY, IOWA  A man has filed a plea to challenge his ex-wife to 'trial by combat' after claiming that along with her attorney, have both "destroyed him legally."40-year-old David Ostrom, from Kansas, appealed to a judge in Iowa that he should be granted the right to 'trial by combat' to end his ongoing dispute with his ex-wife, Bridgette Ostrom and her attorney, Mr. Hudson. He claimed that trial by combat has "never been explicitly banned or restricted as a right in these United States." He then went on to ask the judge for 12 weeks, so he could either "source" or "forge" Japanese samurai swords.Ostrom said his ex-wife could nominate her attorney as "her champion," however, faced with the prospect of death, her attorney argued the possibility of loss of life outweighed the ramifications of property tax and custody issues. Mr. Hudson also asked the court to suspend Ostrom's visitation rights and order him to undergo a court-ordered psychological evaluation. The judge, Craig Dreismeier said that he won't be issuing a decision anytime soon and that no further action would be taken at this time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 02:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950079/3950079_8E338E45638A41E49A8D22EE4B817621_200116_3950079_Man_challenges_ex_wife_to__trial_by_combat__to_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man challenges wife to trial by combat, trial by combat samurai swords, trial by combat court, trial by combat game of thrones, funny trial by combat, trial by combat man vs woman, man challenges wife to sword fight, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950962</guid>
      <title>Sepsis causes one in five deaths around the world: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  A study in The Lancet estimates that sepsis is associated with one in five deaths around the world, or more deaths than cancer.Citing the authors, the University of Washington says in a news release that the study's figure doubled the previous estimates of global sepsis deaths.Sepsis is triggered by diarrhoeal infections or lung diseases that cause the immune system to overreact.The immune cells attack the patient's own body and can lead to organ failure followed by death. In adults, sepsis symptoms include passing little urine, shivering, extreme shivering or muscle pain, and mottled or discolored skin.According to the paper, low and middle income countries are overwhelmingly more affected by sepsis cases.Those deaths could have been prevented by better sanitation, clean water, and access to vaccines.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 12:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950962/3950962_6ABFD04EF5F642AEBE8B5601A812DE4B_200117_3950962_Sepsis_causes_one_in_five_deaths_around_the_worl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sepsis, sepsis symptoms, sepsis deaths, sepsis mortality rate, sepsis death stats, university of washington, lancet, the lancet, university of Pittsburgh, health, science, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950838</guid>
      <title>Scientists found weird celestial objects near the galactic core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Scientists identified a new class of celestial bodies near the Sagittarius A, the Milky Way Galaxy's supermassive black hole.According to the paper in Nature Astronomy, the six strange objects, named G1 through G6, orbit around Sagittarius A in circuits that range from 100 to 1,000 years.Citing the authors, the University of California Los Angeles says that as the objects are close to Sagittarius A, the black hole stretches them out of shape and strip away their outer gas shell.Observing one of the objects G2, the researchers found that even after the black hole dramatically elongates its gas shell, the object retains a relatively coherent dust core.This suggests G2--and by inference, the rest of the G-class objects--had stellar objects inside the core.Co-author and UCLA professor Andrea Ghez speculates that all six G objects were formerly binary stars that fell under the black hole's influence.Ghez says that Sagittarius A's powerful gravity may have caused the binary stars to merge and to give rise to the weird G-class objects.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950838/3950838_AC11AF0DC35F4E04A2B2F595BFC49188_200117_3950838_Scientists_found_weird_celestial_objects_near_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Weird objects, binary stars, bizarre objects, black hole, center of the galaxy, galactic core, supermassive black hole, Sagittarius A, the milky way galaxy, the galaxy, star, gas, UCLA, Galactic Center, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950821</guid>
      <title>This skyscraper is set to become the tallest building in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TORONTO  Supertall skyscraper "The One" is set to become the tallest building in Canada at 309 meters once it is completed in Toronto later this year.The mixed-use development is designed by British architecture firm Foster + Partners and Canadian design firm Core Architects.The skyscraper's exterior consists of multiple champagne-hued rectangular blocks stacked on top of one another. The tower's facade has two diagonal columns with diagonal bracing on each side of the building.Residents will be able to see the diagonal bracing through their window as they look out to the city.The top of the skyscraper will feature a green space with trees, according to Urban Toronto. The 85-story tower will include retail stores, restaurants, hotels and apartments.Toronto currently has 67 skyscrapers and is set to add 31 more to its skyline. An additional 59 skyscrapers have been proposed by architects and design firms. According to data from the Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitat, this will make Toronto home to the second highest number of skyscrapers in North America.Chicago currently has 126 skyscrapers while 19 other skyscrapers are either under construction or have been proposed for the city.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950821/3950821_A34EC53EC0394B08A447D1FE3B137124_200117_3950821_This_skyscraper_is_set_to_become_the_tallest_bui_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Canada skyscrapers, toronto the one, toronto the one skyscraper, toronto buildings, toronto skyscrapers, toronto skyline, skyscrapers in toronto, canada's tallest building, canada's tallest skyscraper, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950813</guid>
      <title>Chinese 'quantum' speed reading institutes ordered to shut down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING Remember those "quantum" speed reading classes in China? Turns out it was a total scam.In a video from last year, kids at a "quantum" speed reading competition were seen flipping pages at superspeed, staring as the pages went by.One teacher actually claimed that this technique allows children to read 100,000 characters in a span of one to five minutes. According to the Shanghaiist, this speed reading technique was developed by Japanese teacher Yumiko Tobitani who claimed that as a person flips the pages, images start appearing in your head which helps a person to understand the content of the book.Tobitani even went so far as to claim that the technique works on foreign text as it will be translated to your native language through images as you flip the pages.According to the Shanghaiist, parents have shelled out as much as US$7,000 for their kids to pick up "quantum" speed reading.On Thursday, China's Ministry of Education released a statement saying that at least five institutes with "quantum" speed reading courses have been ordered to shut down for operating without proper licenses required for teaching or running a business.The ministry also called on local governments to launch an investigation into other institutions to prevent false advertising.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950813/3950813_02DECB20706B42189070E016FC1DCABE_200117_3950813_Chinese__quantum__speed_reading_institutes_order_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China speed reading contest, China quantum speed reading contest, quantum speed reading, quantum speed reading hoax, quantum speed reading scam,  quantum speed reading training centers china, quantum speed reading technique, speed reading,  strange speed reading techniques, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950810</guid>
      <title>Chinese man pays $21,000 for ant-sized parking space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIAN, CHINA  A massive baller in China dropped over $21,000 on a money parking space. Unfortunately, it looks like it was made for ants. According to Pear Video, the man surnamed Yu showed local media his unbelievable awesome space in the Shaanxi city of Xi'an.The man told reporters that he moved into the building in 2008, but didn't spring for a parking space until 2019. Unfortunately for the man, when he actually saw the space, he realized that there was a massive slab of concrete blocking him from actually opening his door. What's even more money is that if the a car is parked in the parking spot next to him, the only way he can get in and out of his vehicle is through the sunroof. Yu then measured the space himself and found it to only be 1.9 meters wide and 4 meters long. The funny thing is that when Yu told building management about his crappy space, they told him that he would need to blow even more money in order to get a new spot.  Guess Yu better get used to using that sunroof, or maybe we should call it a sundoor.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950810/3950810_F5E4E6B5D42E415B8A755A69C34A9156_200117_3950810_Chinese_man_pays__21_000_for_ant_sized_parking_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China parking space, China small parking space, China parking space fail, man climbs through sunroof, man uses sunroof as door, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950604</guid>
      <title>Golden tower planned for Toronto</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TORONTO  Canadian architectural firm Giannone Petricone Associates has unveiled plans to build a 79-story golden tower in Toronto. The skyscraper would be 266 meters in height.The building's exterior resembles a pleated curtain which reflects sunlight from different angles to create a sense of movement, according to Urban Toronto. The development would cover a gross floor area of roughly 121,965 square meters.It would include three levels of retail space at the bottom of the building, while the rest of the tower would be residential.The building's main lobby would include escalators to the tower's shopping areas, while elevators would be available for residents looking to return home or visit the building's sky lobby.Architects have also proposed a five-level underground garage and 500 bicycle parking spaces, reports Urban Toronto.  Once completed, the building would be connected to Toronto's Bay subway station.According to Urban Toronto, if the building was completed today, it would be the fifth tallest building in the city.Toronto is expected to surpass Chicago as home to the second highest number of skyscrapers in North America, Bloomberg reports , citing data from the Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitat. The city is currently home to 67 skyscrapers. Toronto currently has 31 skyscrapers under construction and has proposed an additional 59 towers.Chicago now has 126 skyscrapers and 19 other skyscrapers that are either under construction or have been proposed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950604/3950604_29EEBC7893D44633B566A14DA3777134_200117_3950604_Golden_tower_planned_for_Toronto_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Toronto skyscraper, toronto golden skyscraper, toronto architecture, Giannone Petricone Associates,  toronto golden building, golden skyscraper, toronto skyline, toronto high rise, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950582</guid>
      <title>Indian restaurant found to have moldy food and a bug in mayo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUTHIN, UNITED KINGDOM  An Indian restaurant in Ruthin, Wales was found to be home to moldy lamb chops, moldy cheese, moldy red peppers and a tub of mayonnaise with an insect inside. The restaurant, which had been inspected before, tried to fool its customers by flipping its zero-rating hygiene sticker upside down, to give the impression it had a top mark of five.  Magistrates were told by Julia Longworth, prosecuting for the local council that, "significant improvement was required."The owner of the restaurant, 41-year-old Mohammed Chowdhury was fined a total of £1,260. He admitted to seven offenses of failing to comply with food hygiene regulations and his chef, now unemployed, Hanna Ali pleaded guilty to five food hygiene offenses and was also fined. Court chairwoman Ann Dickinson said, "We found the photographs of the kitchen quite shocking."In the owner's defense, the court heard that Mr. Chowdhury hadn't spent enough time at the restaurant to make the necessary improvements from previous inspections because he also worked at Manchester airport.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950582/3950582_2A95E66D080A4076BEAF9F18FD2C0404_200117_3950582_Indian_restaurant_found_to_have_moldy_food_and_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Kitchen nightmares, disgusting kitchen, dirty kitchen, disgusting restaurant, dirty restaurant, Indian restaurant dirty, Kitchen nightmares UK,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952314</guid>
      <title>ISIS preacher dubbed "Jabba the Jihadi" captured in Iraq</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSUL, IRAQ  An overweight ISIS zealot dubbed "Jabba the Jihadi" was caught by an Iraqi SWAT team in Mosul last week, but as his name suggests, the known gang leader was too large to get into a police car, so instead, they loaded him onto a flatbed truck.That's according to the military newspaper, Stars and Stripes who say the man, Abu Abdul Bari, a known preacher of provocative speeches, ordered the execution of scholars and clerics who refused to pledge allegiance to ISIS when it occupied the area.In July 2014, 'Jabba' also ordered the destruction of a mosque believed to be built on the burial place of Jonah, the biblical prophet who once had a renowned encounter with a whale.Maajid Nawaz, founder of the London-based counter-extremist organization Quilliam, took to Facebook to say that the images held a significant "psychological blow" to ISIS as gluttony is frowned upon by jihadists, yet this, "walrus was their top religious cleric."British anti-ISIS activist, Macer Gifford who fought with a U.S. backed Kurdish militia in Syria, applauded the arrest in a Twitter post, saying,  "Good luck hanging him in Iraq." He added, "he literally looks like the world's biggest chicken."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 23:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952314/3952314_2FCC89C416E744ECB38CA0DE3BC5008C_200121_3952314_ISIS_preacher_dubbed__Jabba_the_Jihadi__captured_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Jabba the Jihadi, Jabba the Jihadi captured, ISIS fat preacher, fat ISIS loaded onto flatbed, fat man flatbed truck, Iraq ISIS, Macer Gifford, Maajid Nawaz, Quilliam, Abu Abdul Bari, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952169</guid>
      <title>Rich woman angers China with Forbidden City photoshoot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  A very intelligent woman decided to brag over Chinese censored social media about being in the Forbidden City on a day it was closed to the publicwhich for a country that gets its feelings hurt REAL easilyprobably wasn't the best idea. According to the BBC, the woman, who calls herself Lu Xiaobao on China's Twitter knockoff Weibo, decided to flaunt her high level commie connections by posting snaps of herself, some other spoiled brat and a Mercedes SUV in a completely empty Forbidden City in lovely Beijing.  She was also kind enough to include the caption saying, "On Monday the Palace Museum is closed, so I hurried over, hid from the crowds, and went to play in the Forbidden City."The BBC reports that the old palace complex usually closes on Monday to allow for maintenance and renovation work. Wellcue the outrage. The incredibly douchey photos instantly went viral. Lu then realized she had made a mistake and deleted the pictures.  One user left a comment that has been shared more than 400,000 times saying, "deleting the pictures is useless; the entire Chinese nation has seen them." According to the Shanghaiist, the Palace Museum had to issue an apology Friday night saying they would increase security and not let something like this happen again. But let's be honest, in a country where people connected to the CCP can do whatever they want, stuff like this will clearly happen again. Long live China!!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952169/3952169_06089F0C2E2F4110A95DB976EAC6CE1C_200120_3952169_Rich_woman_angers_China_with_Forbidden_City_phot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China Forbidden City, Forbidden City photoshoot, Lu Xiaobao Forbidden City, Lu Xiaobao SUV Forbidden City, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952163</guid>
      <title>China teen gets intestinal bubble tea blockage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINXIANG, CHINA  A teen from Henan had to make a trip to the emergency room after experiencing some severely unpleasant abdominal pain. Turns out the culprit was bubble tea. According to Pear Video, he was sent for a checkup and an X-ray at the First Affiliated Hospital of Xinxiang Medical University, which showed signs of intestinal blockage. In strict medical terms, the pipes were all backed up. It appears the boy had drunk two bubble teas one week before he started feeling abdominal discomfort. Unfortunately, rather than chew the bubble tea pearls, he pretty much just swallowed them.Bubble tea pearls are made out of tapioca starch and corn flour which could take a while to digest. Some places may also add thickening agents to the pearls which make them even harder to get rid off. And then let's not forget the whole made in China factor. Doctors had to go in and remove the two bubble tea blockages through surgery. Nature then took its course for the remaining pearls over the next couple of days after the operation. Lesson of the day? Maybe add some chewing into the inhaling process.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 12:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952163/3952163_FE7981E60E4A469FA3BE5CB9EC7F0889_200120_3952163_China_teen_gets_intestinal_bubble_tea_blockage_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bubble tea, Bubble tea pearls, bubble tea blockage, bubble tea causes blockage, bubble tea surgery, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952136</guid>
      <title>China's virus outbreak may be a lot worse than Beijing reported</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Citing Chinese officials, the BBC reports that the coronavirus outbreak in China's city of Wuhan has killed three people and infected over 200 as of Monday.The news comes days after researchers at London Imperial College's MRC Centre for Global Infectious Disease Analysis warned that there may be far more infection cases than what Beijing had reported.Citing the MRC GIDA, the BBC reports that the China-based virus outbreak has infected two people in Thailand and one in Japan.The researchers say that their model, based on the virus, Wuhan's population and flight data, estimates that more than 1,700 people have been infected.Chinese authorities speculate that the virus likely crossed the species barrier from infected animals to people at a seafood and wildlife market in Wuhan.Citing an MRC-GIDA researcher, the BBC says that the authorities should seriously consider the possibility of "substantial human-to-human transmission."According to the BBC, the new coronavirus more closely resembles SARs than any other viral strain.Coronavirus is a large family of viruses and only seven are known to infect humans, including the new one discovered in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952136/3952136_1CF60CABF68F4976930718A7029DF9B1_200120_3952136_China_s_virus_outbreak_may_be_a_lot_worse_than_B_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China virus outbreak 2020, China virus outbreak, Chinese virus outbreak 2020, Chinese virus, pneumonia, SARS, coronavirus, mystery virus, Chinese disease, epidemic, China's virus, China's new virus, Wuhan pneumonia, coronavirus, new coronavirus, Wuhan, China, MRC Centre for Global Infectious Disease, Imperial College London, UK, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952093</guid>
      <title>British fish species projected to decline over the next 30 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  A new report by the Marine Climate Change Impacts Partnership has predicted that cold-water fish species in British waters may be replaced with warm-water species as sea temperatures continue to rise in the next 30 years.Researchers explained that local fish such as cod may decline and be replaced with fish that are typically found in warmer waters, such as the European anchovy.The study also pointed out that the number of Atlantic bluefin tuna has been increasing in British waters, and that this may be partially related to rising temperatures.Likewise, warming waters has caused mackerel to become the dominant fish off of Scotland's west coast over the past 30 years, while the Northern hake has repopulated in the northern part of the North Sea after being largely absent for more than 50 years.The study also predicts that fish may evolve to have smaller bodies as oxygen levels decrease in the warming waters, and fish have to swim farther to find food.Researchers involved in the study explained that this could be bad news for the British fishing industry, which could face a limited quota allocation, and may have to make their livelihood with tinier fish.They projected the net value of the British fishing industry to decrease by 10 percent by 2050 under a "high-emissions scenario."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952093/3952093_8E1E3198A8ED4544941D78D743757046_200120_3952093_British_fish_species_projected_to_decline_over_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tuna, anchovies, codfish, UK seas, global warming, climate change, warm oceans, acidic ocean, coldwater fish, shellfish, Marine Climate Change Impacts Partnership, effects of climate change, climate change fish, UK water fisheries,TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952076</guid>
      <title>France is deploying its sole aircraft carrier to fight ISIS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS   France is deploying its sole aircraft carrier Charles de Gaulle to the Middle East.Citing President Emmanuel Macron's speech to the military, Reuters reports that the carrier and its battle group will support counterterrorism operations from January to April.According to Naval Technology, Charles de Gaulle is a 261.5 m long nuclear powered carrier with a displacement of 38,000 tonnes.The de Gaulle's air group includes up to 40 Rafale M fighters, E-2C early warning aircraft, and various helicopters, including the Dauphin PEDRO.The carrier's deck load is supplemented by an internal hanger equipped with two lifts for aircraft.The ship is also armed with the Aster and Mistral air to air missiles and 20mm guns for close range defense.Citing Macron, Reuters reports that after its deployment in the Middle East, the carrier will proceed to the Atlantic Ocean and the North Sea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952076/3952076_672F6E175CA742D38E753E8E02E2746E_200120_3952076_France_is_deploying_its_sole_aircraft_carrier_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Charles de Gaulle, de Gaulle, aircraft carrier, carrier, French aircraft carrier, French carrier, R91, deploy, deploying, middle east, Emanneul Macron, Macron, ISIS, ISIL, Middle East, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3951939</guid>
      <title>How sugar addiction impacts the brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AARHUS, DENMARK  New research from the journal Scientific Reports has found that sugar has the ability to transform our brain chemistry.Scientists from Denmark's Aarhus University performed their experiment on seven pigs to test out their theory. These pigs were fed two liters of sugar water on a daily basis over a 12-day period.The pigs' brains were imaged using a brain scanner prior to the experiment, after the first day of the experiment and after the last day of the experiment.Researchers found significant changes in the pigs' brains' dopamine and opioid systems.Michael Witherdahl, one the researchers involved in the study, said in a Aarhus University press release that the pigs' opioid system, which is associated with well-being and pleasure, had been activated after the pig's first sugar intake.Witherdahl explained both natural stimuli and artificial stimuli have the ability to activate the brain to release dopamine and opioids.He said humans may end up replacing natural stimuli, such as socializing, with artificial stimuli, such as sugar, in order to get a rush of dopamine and opioids to the brain.As part of the bigger picture, the study was looking to see how palatable food, such as sugar, is addicting and how it affects the human body.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 07:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3951939/3951939_7441A7CF7B934E8ABCA5A9BD5AD037D0_200120_3951939_How_sugar_addiction_impacts_the_brain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sugar, impact of sugar, addictive impacts of sugar on the brain, sugar brain effects, sugar intake, sugar intake health effects, sugar artificial stimuli, sugar brain,  how sugar influences the brain, Aarhus University, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3951850</guid>
      <title>Burger King offers Prince Harry a job</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BURGER KINGDOM  As Prince Harry and Meghan Markle prepare to step back as senior members of the British royal family, future employment will most definitely be an issue. Thank the Queen, okay, more like the king in this case, Burger King to be exact. According to Fox News, Burger King Argentina kicked things off by offering Harry and Meghan a spot in their royal family as the couple say they want to be financially independent of the monarchy. Amid all the Megxit madness, the fast food chain with royal roots decided to weigh in with an ad reading, "If you're looking for a job, we have a new crown for you." "We have a proposition for you: do as thousands of people and take your first steps in the world of work with us," it goes on to say. "You know that the crown will suit you perfectly." "Also, after so many years of living as dukes, it is time for you to start eating like kings." The message ends with a link to apply for a job at B.K.Burger King U.S.A., then followed Argentina's lead with a tweet a few days later saying, "you always have a job in our kingdom."And then another a few days later to Harry with the message, "this royal family offers part-time positions."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 04:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3951850/3951850_4BF17D88F6CD49E3AB505EBF59DF4C76_200120_3951850_Burger_King_offers_Prince_Harry_a_job_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Megxit, Prince Harry Meghan Markle, Prince Harry stepping back, Burger King Prince Harry, Burger King offers Harry job, BK offers Prince Harry, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3951759</guid>
      <title>Missing 3-year-old girl found with her trusty dog by her side</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PILBARA, AUSTRALIA   It's good news down under after a three-year-old girl was found safe and sound after going missing in Western Australia's flood-hit Pilbara region.On Wednesday at around 2:30 p.m, three-year-old Matilda, accompanied by her pet Jack Russell, wandered off from her home in Noreena Downs Homestead, an area that has recently been flooded with heavy rain.The Western Australia Police Force said the floods lead to a number of creeks surrounding the property to be full of water. After the water level receded a bit, Matilda was able to make her way across one of these creeks. However, when it started to rain again, the creek quickly filled, thus trapping her and her dog.Around 4 p.m the alarm was raised that Matilda was missing. Police said they were throwing every resource they had to locate her.Three helicopters searched from the skies, whilst mounted police teamed with State Emergency Service searched from the ground. Matilda, with her faithful dog at her side, was alone for nearly 24 hours without shelter before being spotted wandering around 3.5km south of the homestead. She was rescued and happily reunited with her family.Pilbara's police superintendent, Kim Massam praised the girl's dog who, "stayed with her that whole time."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3951759/3951759_4239969A602D43D1975C1658846F6527_200120_3951759_Missing_3_year_old_girl_found_with_her_trusty_do_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Missing girl found, missing Australian girl found, Matilda found, girl found with dog, Australian floods, girl missing 24 hours, 3km from home, missing persons found, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952833</guid>
      <title>Chinese school rewards top students with bags of pork</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FUYANG, CHINA  A middle school in Fuyang City rewarded its top students with a choice of either bags of pork weighing 2.5kg or two large carps. In an interview with Pear Video, the principal told reporters that this was the second year his school rewarded its students with food; going on to say that a rough 5500kg of pork had been distributed to 2200 students.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 23:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3952833/3952833_73B681E8689A4ED795AEE16532855DA3_200122_3952833_Chinese_school_rewards_top_students_with_bags_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese school rewards students pork, pork prize, pork gift, pork present, Chinese students, Chinese pupils, Chinese students get pork, funny Chinese news, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952703</guid>
      <title>Bow-tie wearing rabbit flies business-class to Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN  A bunny with some pretty incredible fashion sense named Coco lives better than you do.Photos recently went viral of the bowtie-wearing rabbit flying business class from San Francisco to Japan onboard a United Airlines flight with her owner, who was starting a new job there a couple of years ago. According to Insider, the bougie bunny incident took place in late 2018, but the pictures are just going viral now after recently appearing on sites like Metro. Owner Takako Ogawa was moving back to Japan, but was worried Coco might not make the trip back in the hold, so she registered it as an emotional support animal and only had to pay $100 to let Coco join her in the cabin in a carry case. After the flight took off, flight attendants let Ogawa know the seat next to her was empty, so they let Coco have it. How considerate of United to let a rabbit use the seat rather than some unlucky person jammed in crappy economy.  People will be happy to hear that when it was time for ice cream, Coco wasn't left out. She was given her own plate of almonds and nuts to munch on.  Ogawa said she also remembers being prepared if Coco had any accidents, but apparently the rabbit didn't make a mess. So just remember next time you hop on board your next flight, this bad & bougie bunny has you beat.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 13:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952703/3952703_103554728D284C08916B5F2E64120F54_200121_3952703_Bow_tie_wearing_rabbit_flies_business_class_to_J_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Rabbit flies business, rabbit flies business class, emotional support rabbit, rabbit flies to Japan, Coco the Rabbit airplane, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952618</guid>
      <title>Novel coronavirus infection just tripled in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  Cases of novel coronavirus infection in China have tripled over the weekend, sparking global concerns about an outbreak.China's state-run Xinhua News reports that there are 218 confirmed cases, mostly in the city of Wuhan. The BBC reports that three have died and nine are in critical condition.China Daily yesterday reported that a fourth fatality occurred in Wuhan, where 15 medical workers have caught the disease as they try to help the patients.Millions of Chinese are traveling in the country to celebrate the Lunar New Year vacation, which will begin on Friday.The BBC reports that the virus has spread, with five cases in Beijing, one in Shanghai and one in Shenzhen.Outside of China, four cases have been confirmed, two in Thailand, one in Japan and a new case in South Korea.The BBC reports that in each case, the infected person had recently visited Wuhan before falling ill.Scientists believe the infection's main source is animal-based and have advised people not to handle live chickens without protection and to thoroughly cook meat and eggs.However, China's state-run Xinhua News Agency reports that health officials have confirmed that human to human transmission has occurred in two cases.According to the BBC, genetic analysis has identified the pathogen as a SARS-like coronavirus strain and one of the seven coronaviruses capable of infecting humans.According to the WHO, scientists are calling the pathogen 2019-nCoV.The pneumonia-like infection causes coughing, shortness of breath, breathing difficulties and fever.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 11:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952618/3952618_D294583881D54B25A8D3AF5A4C2D8B13_200121_3952618_Novel_coronavirus_infection_just_tripled_in_Chin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China virus outbreak 2020, China virus outbreak, Chinese virus outbreak 2020, Chinese virus, pneumonia, SARS, coronavirus, mystery virus, Chinese disease, epidemic, China's virus, China's new virus, Wuhan pneumonia, coronavirus, new coronavirus, infection, surge, surged, tripled, triple, Wuhan, China, Lunar New Year, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952386</guid>
      <title>Pig forced to bungee jump in China for LNY theme park stunt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA  As African Swine Flu continues to decimate China's oink oink population and a new SARS cousin spreading like mad within the country, it's good to see people are still in the Lunar New Year's spirit. According to the SCMP, workers from some two-bit theme park in the Sichuan city of Chongqing decided to celebrate the opening of a bungee jump attraction by hurling an animal off of it. Footage shows the animal-loving employees haul the 200-pound unwilling participant pig up the 70-meter tall tower. The pig clearly isn't having any of it, but that doesn't stop park staff from suiting it up. Porky then gets launched off the 20-story tower squealing like mad the entire way down. And of course because the video was shared online it caused instant and massive backlash. And by massive backlash we mean some netizens leaving some comments online. The theme park owner told local media that since it was the opening day, they wanted to, "let the pig make the first jump because pork prices have been very high this year and recently they dropped a bit." The owner also said the cruel stunt was planned to mark the end of the Year of the Pig and the beginning of the Year of the Rat, which begins Saturday.The theme park owner kind of sounds like a rat. As for the hog, when asked for a quote about the whole incident it said...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 05:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952386/3952386_8BB08FA5D8734F2AB48FAC550494EDFB_200121_3952386_Pig_forced_to_bungee_jump_in_China_for_LNY_theme_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China pig bungee jump, pig bungee jump, China pig bungee jump stunt, China Lunar New Year's pig bungee, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952376</guid>
      <title>Man hiding for weeks in grocery store ceiling still at large</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUBURN, WASHINGTON  You've heard of people living in airports, attics, even in cupboards under the stairs. But living in a store ceiling  that might be a first.Cops in Auburn, Washington released surveillance footage of a man they say has been living in the rafters of a grocery store for weeks and emerging only to pilfer goods.King5 News reports that on Christmas Day, police were called to Haggen Northwest Fresh Market for what was initially thought to be a burglary. They found evidence that someone had accessed a vent in the roof, including jackets, gloves, tools, debris, and even a length of rope.The cops only realized someone was living inside the store after Haggen employees heard footsteps overhead and saw someone's legs dangling out of the storage closet ceiling.When they pulled surveillance footage, they saw a perp wearing a face mask and an all-black ensemble, walking the aisles with thousands of dollars worth of cigarettes in a bag.Police spent about four and a half hours up in the rafters trying to hunt the thief, but no dice. Even heat-mapping infrared technology and K9 units were no use.So basically, the perp managed to outsmart and out-hide the po-po and is still somewhere in there, living off the store. Gotta give him props though. What better place to squat in that inside a grocery store.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 04:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952376/3952376_7EFAFCCB825949E8B9ED8F94DF958024_200121_3952376_Man_hiding_for_weeks_in_grocery_store_ceiling_st_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man living in ceiling, man living in store ceiling, man in grocery rafters, store squatter, caught on cam, surveillance footage, grocery store squatter, mystery in the rafters, haggen, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953234</guid>
      <title>A huge 'ghost net' is haunting Hawaii's seas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WAILUKU, HAWAII  Ghost nets are commercial fishing nets discarded by fishers or lost in the ocean.The Maui News reports that local authorities are asking for the public's help to recover a very large ghost net floating in Hawaii's near seas.According to the paper, the giant net is 50 feet long, 70 feet wide and drifting at a depth of about 50 feet. It is also believed to have a yellow floater bucket.The massive net could ensnare whales and potentially inflict serious damage to boats.According to CNN, the net has not been found as of January 18, although the debris is possibly in the area of Maui, Kahoolawe, Lanai, and Molokai.According to the institute, the ghost net may have collected up to 18 tons of plastic trash.The network reports that ocean nonprofits are hoping to retrieve the ghost net before it sank, or rescuers would have to remove net carefully to avoid harming the reefs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 13:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953234/3953234_B198DD7FA5064A2395916188D7580469_200122_3953234_A_huge__ghost_net__is_haunting_Hawaii_s_seas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ghost net, huge net, ocean debris, marine debris ghost fishing, plastics, pollution, ocean, environment, Hawaii, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953221</guid>
      <title>Scientists found clues for making universal cancer cure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARDIFF, BRITAIN  Cardiff University researchers have identified a mechanism in our immune system that could be utilized to treat most cancers.According to the study published in Nature Immunology, certain T-cells can be engineered to kill prostate, breast, lung and other cancers, albeit only in lab settings."T-cells are a type of lymphocytes found in the blood that searches and destroys threats to the body that include infections to cancers.Cardiff University says in a press statement that one type of T-cells was found to possess a unique receptor that allows them to detect almost all cancer cells.The BBC reports that scientists may be able to take blood from a cancer patient and isolate their T-cells.The T-cells could then be reprogrammed by a harmless virus to grow the special receptor and cultured before the immune cells are reintroduced to fight the patient's cancer cells.T-cells with the special receptors are able to ignore healthy cells and attack the cancerous tissue, including tumors, which normal T-cells cannot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 13:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953221/3953221_8123C5D985DD4EC28176323BE2E4BFC2_200122_3953221_Scientists_found_clues_for_making_universal_canc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[cancer research, cancer treatment, cancer t cells, t cell receptors, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953201</guid>
      <title>Update: Wuhuan virus is spreading fast out of China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  A new virus from the Chinese city of Wuhan has made 440 people sick, at least nine of whom have died, as of Wednesday, Reuters reports, citing China's National Health Commission.The state-run Xinhua news agency on Monday reported that the commission confirmed the virus is capable of human-to-human transmission.According to NBC, a man who recently visited Wuhan and lives alone near Seattle became the first case of the virus in the U.S.The man fell ill and read about the outbreak online before he contacted his doctor.Citing U.S. officials, the network reports that he was sequestered but is doing well.Taiwan's Liberty Times reports that a Taiwanese woman working in Wuhan got sick and decided to return to Taiwan because she did not trust Chinese hospitals.The woman informed the flight crew of her condition and was sent to a hospital upon landing. She is confirmed to have been infected.The novel coronavirus's rapid spread from across China to Thailand, Japan, South Korea and Taiwan has sparked fears of a larger epidemic.The Wuhan Municipal Health Commission states that the novel coronavirus' symptoms include fever, respiratory difficulties, coughing and invasive lesions on both lungs."China's state-run CCTV reports that scientists identified the pathogen as a coronavirus by its microscopic appearance and its novel strain by genetic analysis.According to the BBC, the new virus resembles SARS and is one of the seven coronaviruses that prey on humans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/763/20/01/22/3953199/3953199_481C526CB6314ABDAC3516D1E14345BF_200122_3953199_Update__Wuhuan_virus_is_spreading_fast_out_of_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China virus outbreak 2020,China virus outbreak,Chinese virus outbreak 2020,Chinese virus,pneumonia,SARS,coronavirus,mystery virus,Chinese disease,epidemic,China's virus,China's new virus,Wuhan pneumonia,coronavirus,new coronavirus,Wuhan,China,TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953082</guid>
      <title>Chinese teen with grandmother face gets brand new mug</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENYANG, CHINA  A teenage Chinese girl with a medical condition that gave her the face of a grandmother finally has something to smile abouta brand new mug. According to Chinese Twitter knockoff Weibo, 15-year-old Xiao Feng from Heishan County in Liaoning province suffers from Hutchinson-Gilford Progeria syndrome.One of the more noticeable symptoms is premature aging. Unfortunately, there is currently no cure for the condition. Things had gotten so bad for Feng that she had to drop out of school because she was getting made fun of so much. But then it all turned around after she wrote a letter to Chinese philanthropist Guo Mingyi asking for a helping hand. After a few weeks of back and forth, Sunline Plastic Surgery Hospital said it would waive 70 percent of the $72,000 surgery, while Guo picked up the rest of the tab. A team of plastic surgeons then went to work on building a new face for Xiao in a three-part operation. Physicians first had to get rid of all the wrinkles in her skin, which took a bit more time because it was so loose and lacking elasticity.After that was taken care of, doctors then went about reconstructing her nose and lips. And only three weeks after going under the knife, Xiao was able to show off her brand new face to a backed house on January 20. For now, Xiao said she plans to go back to school and in the future hopes to become a doctor or nurse someday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 09:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953082/3953082_B8C3AAEBCFA141198977DB8D38AFB44A_200122_3953082_Chinese_teen_with_grandmother_face_gets_brand_ne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Premature aging, Hutchinson-Gilford Progeria, Hutchinson-Gilford Progeria symptoms, girl with grandmother face gets surgery, girl with grandmother face gets surgery, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953049</guid>
      <title>Amtrak quotes two wheelchair users $25K for train ride</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  You're charging HOW MUCH for a train ticket?!For normal people, hopping on an Amtrak to go from Chicago to Bloomington costs all of 16 bucks. But for two disabled riders using power wheelchairs, Amtrak quoted a whopping $25,000 for the same two-hour train ride.NPR reports that the two are part of a group from the disability service and advocacy organization Access Living, and had reached out to Amtrak for travel arrangements to go to a conference in Bloomington.The group's transportation policy director Adam Ballard says they've been booking train trips with Amtrak for years.In the past, larger groups with 10 to 15 wheelchair users have been accommodated on the trains. Amtrak simply took out seats to fit in more wheelchairs, for only a couple hundred dollars extra.But Amtrak agents cited a new policy for reconfiguring a train car, saying taking out extra seats would now cost over 25 Gs, as it means taking a car out of service.For that price, Ballard and company might as well just buy themselves a car.Unsurprisingly, Amtrak received serious backlash when news of the sky-high ticket prices got out.Senator Tammy Duckworth, a veteran who lost both legs in the Iraq War, called the price quote "outrageous" and said Amtrak "must do better moving forward." Fortunately, the PR folks at Amtrak realized how hot of a mess they were in and quickly backpedaled. NPR reports they told Access Living on Monday that they would accommodate all the wheelchairs onboard for the price of a regular ticket.It only took a crap ton of media and public criticism but hey, all's well that ends well.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 09:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953049/3953049_648C2AF6ECAA450D844CF740C9711F67_200122_3953049_Amtrak_quotes_two_wheelchair_users__25K_for_trai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Amtrak, Amtrak wheelchair access, Amtrak train ticket, Amtrak prices, expensive train ticket, disabilities access, wheelchair users, American disability act, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953015</guid>
      <title>Malaysia ships back containers of 'illegal' plastic waste to the West</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR  Malaysia announced that it has returned 150 shipping containers filled with plastic waste to their country of origin after they were found to be contaminated and mixed in with other trash.Malaysia has sent back 3,737 metric tons of plastic waste to a total of 13 countries, including France, the United Kingdom, the United States and Canada, according to the BBC. France received 43 containers, while the United Kingdom received 42 containers. The United States and Canada received 17 and 11 containers, respectively.Malaysian authorities said that they hope to send back another 110 containers by mid-2020. Sixty of the containers are from the U.S., 15 from Canada and 14 from Japan.Malaysia's environmental minister Yeo Bee Yin said the shipping companies and the countries that shipped out the containers will be responsible for the cost of the returns, CNN reports. Many countries export recyclable waste abroad as this reduces domestic landfill, helps them meet recycling targets and is also inexpensive.In a Facebook post, Yeo said that their government will ensure that Malaysia does not become the "garbage dump of the world."Malaysia is not the only country in Southeast Asia facing this problem. According to the BBC, Indonesia and the Philippines have all sent back unwanted plastic waste to developed countries over the past year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 08:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953015/3953015_A0DA5D56A3CA4359AF000B82E58D41E3_200122_3953015_Malaysia_ships_back_containers_of__illegal__plas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Malaysia plastic waste, malaysia sending plastic waste back, sending trash back, sending plastic waste back, malaysia returns plastic waste, imported plastic waste, plastic pollution, plastic waste, importing plastic waste, illegal plastic waste, illegal plastic waste Malaysia, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952917</guid>
      <title>China to implement single-use plastic ban over 5 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China will be implementing a ban on single-use plastics over the next five years.A new policy will ban plastic bags in all major Chinese cities, such as Shanghai and Beijing, by the end of 2020 and in all Chinese towns by 2022, Reuters reports, citing China's National Development and Reform Commission. Markets that sell fresh produce will be exempt until 2025.Restaurants will be banned from providing single-use straws by the end of this year, while takeaway food services will not be allowed to provide single-use utensils by 2025. China aims to reduce single-use plastic consumption in its restaurant industry by 30 percent in the next five years.Other plastic items such as plastic courier packaging will be phased out by the end of 2025.China also stated that the production and sale of plastic bags thinner than 0.025 millimeters, as well as plastic film for agricultural use that is less than 0.01 millimeters thick, would be banned.According to the online publication Our World in Data based at the University of Oxford, China produced nearly 60 million tons of plastic waste in 2010. The research noted that the projections are expected to be similar up to the year 2025.The research also said that mismanaged plastic waste around the world is at "significant risk" of leaking and impacting our environment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 05:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3952917/3952917_DDF5E5D8DABA47F9B71C722CEDD07122_200122_3952917_China_to_implement_single_use_plastic_ban_over_5_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plastic pollution, plastic problem, china plastic pollution, china single-use plastic, single-use plastics, china plastic ban, plastic ban, plastic contamination, plastic waste china, china bans plastic bags, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953756</guid>
      <title>Wuhan suspends public transport amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  Authorities in the Chinese city of Wuhan have shut down public transport to stop the spread of a new strain of coronavirus.All flight and passenger train services in and out of Wuhan have temporarily been stopped as of Thursday, January 23, BBC News reports. Public buses, subways and ferry services have also been shut down starting from Thursday, 10:00 a.m. local time.In addition, those residing in Wuhan have already been advised to avoid crowds and to minimize public gatherings. Large-scale activities that were planned at tourist attractions throughout the city have also been suspended ahead of the Lunar New Year holidays.According to CNN, Wuhan has already made it mandatory for everyone in the city to wear face masks in public after the city confirmed more than 500 coronavirus cases.The virus is now known as 2019-nCOV and is believed to be a new strain of coronavirus that had not been previously identified in humans, reports BBC News. Chinese officials believe that the virus was spread from a local seafood market in Wuhan. The coronavirus originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there is now evidence that the virus can be transmitted between people.The seafood market has since been closed for disinfection.Symptoms of the virus include fever, with some experiencing difficulty breathing. Chest X-rays from the victims show invasive lesions on both lungs.According to CNN, there have already been 555 confirmed cases of the Wuhan coronavirus, out of which there have been 17 deaths.The virus has since spread to countries such as Thailand, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan and the United States.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 10:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953756/3953756_9399DDDC88684A0B8B30CC2D1A1531F5_200123_3953756_Wuhan_suspends_public_transport_amid_virus_outbr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china virus outbreak 2020, china virus outbreak, chinese virus, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953708</guid>
      <title>Man buys stolen bike so he can return it to the owner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  26-year-old Ste Burke bought an expensive stolen bicycle just so he could return it to the original owner.Speaking to Metro.co.uk, Ste said that he was outside his house getting his gym bag from the back of his car when he was approached by three men carrying the bike; he said he spotted a lock around the back wheel and knew it was stolen. According to Ste, they tried to sell the £1350 bike for £100; he instead offered £80 which they happily accepted. He said, "as soon as they left I put it on Twitter because I knew it wouldn't have been stolen far away as it was locked."A few hours later a man carrying paperwork, receipts and the key for the lock met Ste. He told him that his home was "recently burgled" and that he'd pay him back the £80. Ste respectfully declined and insisted he didn't do it for a reward.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 09:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953708/3953708_DFCD27EF414340889440F5DCDB6B9776_200123_3953708_Man_buys_stolen_bike_so_he_can_return_it_to_the__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Stormzy, Man buys back stolen bike, Liverpool bike theft, Ste Burke, Ste Burke bike theft, Man buys stolen £1,300 bike for £80, man buys back stolen bike]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953639</guid>
      <title>Scientists use x-ray 'light echoes' to scope out black holes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, BRITAIN  Astronomers have found a novel way to explore the regions around a black hole.In a paper published in Nature Astronomy, researchers say that they were able to use x-ray echoes around a black hole to map the celestial body's surroundings.According to the University of Cambridge's news release that black hole's gravitational force is extremely powerful and causes massive spatial distortions around itself.As objects caught in the black hole pull are drawn to the event horizon, they heat up and radiate x-rays that "echo and reverberate" against nearby gas.Using the European Space Agency's XMM x-ray observatory, the team was able to observe x-ray echoes of a black hole at the heart of a distant galaxy.The echoes allowed the team to determine the spin and mass of the black hole.The team also made the unexpected discovery that a black hole's the corona--or hot electrons above the accretion disk--changed its size often and quickly.By raising and lowering the roof of the comic echo chamber, the corona's shift in size affected the light echoes and changed their quality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 08:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953639/3953639_441CA66447C84328A753A9357E53AE1B_200123_3953639_Scientists_use_x_ray__light_echoes__to_scope_out_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Black hole, black holes, x-ray, xray, light echoes, light echo, x-ray echoes, x-ray echo, University of Cambridge, space, European Space Agency, ESA, XMM, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953634</guid>
      <title>Feral cats break into body farm to eat cadavers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WHITEWATER, COLORADO  Feral cats broke into a Colorado body farm to munch on some choice cadavers. But scientists don't mind – it's all in the name of science!For the uninitiated, body farms aren't as gruesome as the name implies. It's simply a facility where scientists observe and record how the body decomposes over time. So less horror flick and more CSI.At this farm – Colorado Mesa University's Forensic Investigation Research Station – there were fences both above and below ground as well as infrared cameras. Newsweek reports that donor bodies were placed three meters apart and checked weekly for decomp.The cadavers of man and a woman in their 70s had been placed five or six days earlier when a pair of feral cats broke in and started scavenging the bodies.Like bobcats, their favorite bits were soft tissues in the shoulder and arms. Housecats, when they do munch on cadavers, tend to go for facial tissue.The felines came by for a snack twice, but stopped coming when the bodies began going into moist decomposition. Clearly, it doesn't matter whether cats are feral or domesticated – they're still finicky!Scientists weren't really upset about the break-in – they actually thought it helped them learn how to distinguish cause-of-death injuries from damage inflicted postmortem. Guess it's a win-win situation for man and cat!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 08:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953634/3953634_EC9F6AE27B264C7FBDD0A537C1E25996_200123_3953634_Feral_cats_break_into_body_farm_to_eat_cadavers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Feral cats, scavenger cats, body farm, cats eating corpses, cats eating cadavers, human research facility, decomposition research, forensic research, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953494</guid>
      <title>Chinese city apologizes for pajama shaming its residents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SUZHOU, CHINA  Officials in the city of Suzhou in China's Anhui province got all the hate for shaming residents who go out and about in their nightwear.According to the New York Times, wearing pajamas in public is a thing in China. And honestly, can you blame them? Those things are comfy!But government officials in Suzhou don't like the practice, so they used facial recognition tech to police folks strutting the streets in their sleepwear.The party poopers posted the surveillance photos online and outed the identities of the pajama wearers to shame them for their "uncivilized behavior."Suzhou officials claimed they were trying to win a national "civilized city" competition and banned residents from wearing their PJs out on the street. Not cool!Spitting in the streets, cutting lines, throwing wild public tantrums - that's uncivilized. But what the heck is wrong with pajamas?! Chinese netizens are asking the same thing. Many online are pissed at the pajama shaming and are calling the city government out for infringing on its citizens' privacy.Suzhou officials later apologized and said they'd blur the photos in the future.Hey geniuses, maybe try focusing on legit public matters instead of policing people's clothing choices.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953494/3953494_2D21C30C86CA4534BA00AD46B128D099_200123_3953494_Chinese_city_apologizes_for_pajama_shaming_its_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Pajama shaming, pyjama shaming, pajamas in public, public pajama wearing, facial recognition tech, pyjamas in public, uncivilized behavior, uncivilized Chinese, civilized city, Suzhou, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954293</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus spreads amid Lunar New Years celebrations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  Lunar New Years' festivities pose a great challenge for the Chinese government as it tries to contain the Wuhan coronavirus. According to Reuters, the coronavirus death toll has now risen to 18, after the death of an 80-year-old victim in Hebei province. The South China Morning Post, citing Hebei Daily, reported the victim had spent more than two months in Wuhan visiting relatives.This is the first death due to coronavirus infection outside of Hubei province. The number of infected individuals has risen to 650 worldwide.So far, the virus has been detected in 23 Chinese provinces, four municipalities, Hong Kong, Macau, Thailand, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, Singapore, Vietnam and the United States. According to the South China Morning Post, local governments have issued travel bans in eight cities in Hubei which include Wuhan, Huanggang, Ezhou, Chibi, Xiantao, Qianjiang, Zhijiang and Lichuan.BBC News reports, the city of Wuhan has halted all flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city as of Thursday, January 23. The travel ban includes ride-sharing services. Wuhan authorities asked Didi, a Chinese company similar to Uber or Lyft, to stop all ride services starting Friday at noon. The coronavirus originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there is now evidence that human to human transmission of the virus is possible.Chinese officials believe that the virus originated from a local seafood market in Wuhan. The market has since been closed for disinfection.The virus has an incubation period of 5 days.Symptoms of the virus include fever, with some experiencing difficulty breathing. Chest x-rays from infected patients show invasive lesions on both lungs.However, despite the virus's spread and rising death toll, the World Health Organization said on Thursday that the coronavirus is not an international public health emergency.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 11:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954293/3954293_6BD609FD610841D2B966246D3ABCBFD0_200124_3954293_Wuhan_virus_spreads_amid_Lunar_New_Years_celebra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china virus outbreak 2020, china virus outbreak, chinese virus, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954258</guid>
      <title>A Harry day in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANADA  Now with Prince Harry and Meghan Markle taking a step back from the spotlight, how will they adjust to life in Canada, eh?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 10:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954258/3954258_C8171755559540098204A31195F8B581_200124_3954258_A_Harry_day_in_Canada_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Megxit, Prince Harry, Harry and Meghan, Prince Harry Meghan Markle, Prince Harry leaves U.K., Canada Prince Harry, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954224</guid>
      <title>Rise in greenhouse gas emissions linked to China, India: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA / INDIA  New research from the University of Bristol has found that atmospheric levels of hydrofluorocarbon gas, or HFC-23, have continued to rise despite China and India saying they had stopped emissions.Scientists involved with the study said they expected to find a roughly 90 percent decline in greenhouse gas emissions as part of the Montreal Protocol, an international treaty signed by countries around the world to protect the ozone layer from greenhouse gas emissions.Researchers gathered data from the Advanced Global Atmospheric Gas Experiment network baseline stations and created model simulations for data between 2015 to 2018. Their research linked HFC-23 emissions to China and India, even though both countries were said to have almost completely halted emissions in 2017.According to a news release from the University of Bristol, HFC-23 is an extremely potent greenhouse gas, with one ton of HFC-23 emissions being equivalent to more than 12,000 tons of carbon dioxide emissions.HFC-23 is typically used in cooling systems such as refrigerators and air conditioners, the Guardian reports.Lead author of the study Kieran Stanley explained in the news release that it is very likely that China wasn't as successful in its endeavor to reduce HFC-23 emissions as was previously reported.As for India, Stanley said that without additional measurements, the team can't be sure whether or not India was able to implement an emissions reduction program.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 09:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954224/3954224_231546DB8D6D4AB2899C798F40053ECC_200124_3954224_Rise_in_greenhouse_gas_emissions_linked_to_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Greenhouse gases, potent greenhouse gases, greenhouse gas emissions, carbon emissions, greenhouse gases and global warming, greenhouse gas emissions by country, greenhouse gas emissions rise, china and india greenhouse gas emissions, global warming, climate change, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954151</guid>
      <title>Personal trainer says he's too muscley for parking spaces</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  A personal trainer, known as the 'Greek Stallion' claims he has "no option" but to use designated parent and child parking spaces because he's too muscular.Chris Goodwin, who claims he's a "muscle-model champion" and "a beast" says he always picks the wider parking spaces to permit his 20-stone frame to get out of his car; saying "I'll just go and park in the same parent-and-child bay, even if I'm on my own – I always do it." Adding, "I don't give a c**p what people think of me. I'll do what I want. I can't fit out of my car – I'm too big."According to Metro.co.uk, Chris was filmed trying to get out of his car in a normal spot, where he claimed, "I'm stuck! I'm actually stuck!"He added, "I don't think it is selfish, I really don't.""People take it way over the top because you're parking in a bloody parent-and-child bay. They want to bloody fight you like Mike Tyson would.""I still think anybody should be able to park there and that's not being selfish. I think I should have my own bay saying, 'The Greek Stallion's Bay.'"]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 07:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954151/3954151_A7502337EA514A6BAEB64EE44BFBCD59_200124_3954151_Personal_trainer_says_he_s_too_muscley_for_parki_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Britain's parking hell 2020, Chris Goodwin, personal trainer parking, Greek Stallion, parking fails, parking videos, bad parking, funny bad parking, bodybuilder fail]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954143</guid>
      <title>Four leaks found in Japan's Fukushima Nuclear Plant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FUKUSHIMA, JAPAN  After surviving a massive earthquake, tsunami and nuclear meltdowns in 2011, Japan's Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Plant is now dealing with four different leaks in its walls. According to NHK Japan, there are four coolant leaks at four different locations of the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Station. According to Tokyo Electric Power Company Holdings, also known as TEPCO, the coolant has been found seeping through pipes located in the nuclear station's underground wall of frozen soil. This wall surrounds the facility's reactor and turbine buildings.The leaks are specifically located in the pipes between the plant's No. 2 and 3 reactor buildings.TEPCO found the leaks in late 2019 after noticing a reduction in coolant liquids in its tanks. The company estimates it has lost a total of 20 cubic meters of coolant due to the leak.The cooling liquid is an important tool in disaster prevention for the plant. As it circulates through the underground pipes, it freezes the soil surrounding the reactor buildings, this keeps groundwater from flowing into the nuclear station.Although a leak at a major nuclear station sounds alarming, TEPCO assures that the chemical composition of the cooling liquid is commonly found in snow-melting agents and therefore is not harmful to the environment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 07:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954143/3954143_90A4C8CD24F74CF29914A1007460F646_200124_3954143_Four_leaks_found_in_Japan_s_Fukushima_Nuclear_Pl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tomonews, fukushima, fukushima nuclear reactor, fukushima power plant, fukushima leak, fukushima problems, japan fukushima reactor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955202</guid>
      <title>Wuhan coronavirus contagious even during incubation period</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA   Chinese authorities believe the coronavirus is contagious even when symptoms are not visible.  Citing China's National Health Commission, the South China Morning Post reports that the new strain of coronavirus is contagious during its incubation period, that is before patients start showing visible symptoms. The incubation period of the coronavirus lasts up to 14 days.Symptoms of the virus include fever and cough with some experiencing difficulty breathing.National Health Commission Minister Ma Xiaowei, told media during a press conference on January 26 that 1,350 doctors had been sent to Hubei province with 1,000 more to come in the following days.According to the South China Morning Post, so far there are 2,510 cases of coronavirus infections around the world. The death toll has risen to 80.The virus is believed to have originated from a wet market in Wuhan.In an effort to contain the virus, the city of Wuhan has halted all flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city as of Thursday, January 23. Other transportation systems have been curtailed.According to Reuters, China announced it was temporarily banning the sale of wildlife in markets, restaurants, and online retailers throughout the whole country.The best way to prevent the spread of the virus is to compound wearing masks with other sanitary measures such as washing hands thoroughly and frequently as well as avoiding hand to mouth and eye contact.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 13:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955202/3955202_8313607AB275487A9565192C93454FFE_200127_3955202_Wuhan_coronavirus_contagious_even_during_incubat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china virus outbreak 2020, china virus outbreak, chinese virus, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955123</guid>
      <title>Do masks prevent the spread of the coronavirus outbreak?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD  The rapid spread of the Coronavirus in cities in China has everyone wearing surgical masks out on the streets. But does wearing surgical masks actually protect us from catching deadly diseases?According to BBC News, more than 80 million masks were sold on Chinese online retailer, Taobao, on January 20 and 21 following the outbreak of the deadly coronavirus.However, wearing facemasks alone is not the most efficient way to avoid transmission of viruses or prevent the contraction of them.Talking to BBC News, Dr. David Carrington of St George's, University of London explained that surgical masks do not provide sufficient protection from airborne viruses as they have no filter and do not shield the wearer's eyes.They do however protect against and prevent the spray of coughing and sneezing. They also provide limited protection against hand-to-mouth viral transmission.According to the Centers for Disease Control, the best way to prevent the current coronavirus outbreak is to compound wearing a facemask with the following actions:covering your mouth when coughing or sneezing, washing hands often for at least 20 seconds, avoid touching eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands, avoid sharing items that could be infected and consistently monitoring for coronavirus symptoms.So far there have been 18 deaths in China and over 600 cases of coronaviruses detected globally. So mask up and wash up people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955123/3955123_76C88C3FCE9746EF94B2374794EAFEC0_200127_3955123_Do_masks_prevent_the_spread_of_the_coronavirus_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[do masks work, how to prevent viral spreading, how to not catch virus, do surgical masks work, china virus outbreak 2020, china virus outbreak, chinese virus, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955119</guid>
      <title>Woman waiting for call from God drives into oncoming traffic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEATHERLY, PENNSYLVANIA  Oh lord. A woman who has somehow managed to survive more than 31 years on this planet actually drove into oncoming traffic as a way to test out her faith. According to Lehigh Valley Live, Nedejda Reilly is charged with aggravated assault and other offenses over allegations she purposely caused an accident on Jan. 7 on Route 93 close to Weatherly, about 45 miles north of Allentown.Reilly told state troopers she had been driving around for a few hours waiting for a calling from God. After driving with traffic got her nowhere, she decided to drive straight toward an oncoming vehicle instead. Trooper Bruce Balliet said in an arrest affidavit that, "Reilly related God took care of her by not having her injured.""Reilly expressed no concerns or remorse for the victims. Reilly also stated she did not care if the other people were injured because God would have taken care of them."Well God must have been busy because the two other people in the other car had to be taken to the hospital and treated for injuries. The online court docket indicated Reilly's $50,000 bail was revoked last week.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955119/3955119_2C14534BEB1F4D81848AEEF6A60266C3_200127_3955119_Woman_waiting_for_call_from_God_drives_into_onco_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Woman tests faith, woman tests faith drives, woman drives into oncoming traffic, woman drives into traffic, test of faith, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955101</guid>
      <title>Kobe Bryant, daughter die in helicopter crash in California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALABASAS, CALIFORNIA  One of the greatest athletes to ever play the game of basketball Kobe Bryanthas died in a helicopter crash in California. The New York Times reports that the 41-year-old retired NBA player and his 13-year-old daughter Gianna tragically lost their lives in the crash in Calabasas on Sunday. CNN reports that Bryant and Gianna were supposed to be at the Mamba Sports Academy in Thousand Oaks for a basketball game on Sunday. According to CNN, there was extremely low visibility at the time of the crash and conditions were foggy and cloudy with drizzle. LA County Fire Department Capt. Tony Imbredna said he didn't immediately know whether the Sikorsky S-76B helicopter radioed a distress signal. He told reporters, "individuals that saw the aircraft said it was coming down at a fairly significant rate of speed and impacted the ground on the hillside."According to Los Angeles County sheriff Alex Villanueva at a press conference, Kobe was among 8 passengers traveling aboard the aircraft along with one pilot. All nine people were killed in the accident. According to Los Angeles County Fire Department Chief Daryl Osby, the chopper crashed about 30 miles northwest of downtown L.A. and caused a brush fire. Bryant leaves behind his wife and three daughters. His passing has sent shockwaves across the NBA and around the world. Rest in peace Mamba.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955101/3955101_DC619715E978466E9C55F1BEC103E4F6_200127_3955101_Kobe_Bryant__daughter_die_in_helicopter_crash_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Kobe Bryant, Kobe Bryant helicopter, Kobe Bryant helicopter crash, Kobe Bryant dies helicopter crash, Kobe Bryant crash, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955501</guid>
      <title>College student returns to China, gets jailed over US tweets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  Beijing got its feelings so hurt over some tweets posted by a Chinese student studying at the University of Minnesota, they actually threw him in jail the first chance they got.According to a Chinese court document viewed by Axios, some of the tweets contained images deemed to be unflattering portrayals of a "national leader."Now what national leader could they possibly be talking about in China? Axios reports the document says that in September and October 2018, while 20-year-old Luo Daiqing was a Golden Gopher, he used Twitter to post more than 40 comments "denigrating a national leader's image and indecent pictures," which "created a negative social impact." Some of the images which got some panties in a serious ruffle where Chinese propaganda slogans pasted over images of cartoon bad guy Lawrence Limburger. Other pictures that helped land him behind bars were those of Winnie the Pooh, a cartoon that is off limits because Xi Jinping looks like the fat cartoon bearexcept just more dictatory. Chinese police snatched Luo in his hometown of Wuhan in July 2019 when he went back for summer break. After months of just waiting in a fun-loving Chinese jail, he was sentenced in November 2019 to six months in prison for "provocation."  According to Axios, the case represents a dramatic escalation of Beijing's efforts to shut down free speech abroad and a global expansion of a Chinese police campaign to hunt down Twitter users in China critical of the douchey government.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 11:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955501/3955501_E97F649D3A2249FDA03CE7F8E3D43E0F_200128_3955501_College_student_returns_to_China__gets_jailed_ov_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China jails student over tweets, jailed over tweets, Chinese college student jailed tweets, University of Minnesota student jailed tweets, China freedom of speech, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955497</guid>
      <title>Chinese media uses stock image to show hospital building progress</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  As the Wuhan novel coronavirus continues to spread like wildfire throughout China, it's nice to see Beijing still using good old propaganda to deal with the situation. To handle the exponentially increasing number of patients infected with this latest coronavirus, officials in Wuhan announced last week that they would build a 1,000-bed hospital in just six days. Hey, God created Earth in just seven, so six days should be more than ample time for a hospitalespecially a prefabricated one.  On Monday, the Hubei Daily bragged that the first building of the Huoshenshan Hospital being completed in only 16 hours. They were then kind enough to attach a stock photo to prove the pop-up hospital was almost ready to receive the walking dead. By using the latest technologya reverse image searchit was quickly discovered the photo was in fact nothing but a stock photo from a Chinese construction company. The Hubei Daily has since deleted the post, but luckily one of the CCP's official speaker boxesthe People's Dailyis still trying to pass it off as real. The Huoshenshan Hospital is supposed to be up and running by February 2. What could possibly go wrong?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 11:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955497/3955497_B7CC3DE96EB04B3CA2BE0DD8A3EBD428_200128_3955497_Chinese_media_uses_stock_image_to_show_hospital__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China Huoshenshan Hospital, China 6 days hospital, China Wuhan virus, China fake hospital photo, China hospital stock photo, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955448</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus continues to spread, its origins are still being debated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  The number of confirmed cases and deaths from the novel coronavirus infection continues to rise with more than 4,000 confirmed cases in China and a death toll of 106 as of January 28, according to Al Jazeera. The death toll includes its first fatality in Beijing.The virus was believed to have originated from a seafood market in Wuhan, however, according to a report published in The Lancet by a group of Chinese researchers, the earliest patient that contracted the virus had not visited the seafood market.The report also notes that the first cases of coronavirus occurred on December 1, 2019. This means the viral disease first began spreading in November 2019, during its incubation period.According to Deutsche Welle, the virus has now reached Germany. The Bavarian Health Ministry reported its first case of coronavirus in Starnberg, a town located 30 kilometers southwest of Munich.The man is in medical isolation and, according to the Bavarian Health Ministry, there is a low risk of infection.The symptoms of the novel coronavirus include severe coughing, fever, and difficulty breathing. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.The city of Wuhan's transportation has been on lockdown since January 27. All flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city have been canceled.In an effort to aid overcrowded hospitals in Wuhan, National Health Commission Minister Ma Xiaowei told media during a press conference on January 26 that 1,350 doctors had been sent to Hubei province with 1,000 more to come in the following days.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955448/3955448_B1143E722E3C4847BA446617A0D906B6_200128_3955448_Wuhan_virus_continues_to_spread__its_origins_are_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, coronavirus, beijing virus, corona virus explained, what is coronavirus, china outbreak, china virus, wuhan virus, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955442</guid>
      <title>Rolls-Royce unveils plans to build mini nuclear reactors in the U.K.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Rolls-Royce has announced that it plans to build small modular reactors, or SMRs, and install them in old nuclear sites across the United Kingdom by 2029.The company said they will build approximately 10 to 15 mini nuclear stations. These are expected to last for 60 years.Rolls-Royce explained that these modular reactors will be mass produced while prefabricated components will be delivered onsite in order to reduce costs.Chief technology officer at Rolls-Royce, Paul Stein, told the BBC that lower reactor building costs would eventually lead to cheaper electricity for the public.These nuclear reactors will be roughly 1.5 acres in size, BBC News reports. This is 16 times smaller than the size of Hinkley Point, a major nuclear power station in the United Kingdom.A press release by the company states that one reactor will be able to provide roughly 220 to 440 megawatts of energy which is equivalent to up to 150 onshore wind turbines.Roll-Royce said that it also plans to sell these tiny modular reactors to other foreign countries such as Canada, the U.S. and China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955442/3955442_9C619001F855435EB8E6EBC23494F60B_200128_3955442_Rolls_Royce_unveils_plans_to_build_mini_nuclear__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Rolls-royce, rolls-royce nuclear reactors, rolls-royce nuclear reactors UK, mini nuclear reactors, rolls-royce nuclear power, rolls-royce nuclear power plant, rolls-royce nuclear energy, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955323</guid>
      <title>US Space Force logo boldly goes when others have gone before</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  President Donald Trump officially dropped the brand spanking new U.S. Space Force logo on January 24, and it boldly went where no man has gone beforeexcept maybe Star Trek. Space reports that Donald unveiled the new Space Force logo over Twitter, his unofficial spokesman. According to Space, Trump has been using social media recently to announce news for the newest branch of the U.S. military that included the service's new threads and the swearing in of Gen. John W. Raymond as Chief of Space Operations. Trump tweeted, "After consultation with our Great Military Leaders, designers, and others, I am pleased to present the new logo for the United States Space Force, the Sixth Branch of our Magnificent Military!"Twitter users being Twitter users couldn't help but point out the striking resemblance to the Star Trek logo. Set phasers to copy. However, others pointed out that the new logo got its inspiration from the existing Air Force Command logo.That being saidit still kind of looks like a close Trekky cousin.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 03:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955323/3955323_337CA34C8C1F4F0694B4D9DD8F4EC265_200128_3955323_US_Space_Force_logo_boldly_goes_when_others_have_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[US Space Force, US Space Force logo, US Space Force logo Star Trek logo, Star Trek logo Space Force, President Trump, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955893</guid>
      <title>Woman dies during cake-eating contest on Australia Day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HERVEY BAY, AUSTRALIA  A woman inhaling cakes during a contest commemorating Australia Day is unfortunately no longer around after eating it.  According to the New York Daily News, the idea was to cram as many small cakes known as lamingtonstraditional sponge cake covered in coconut-dusted chocolatedown as possible in an allotted time. News.com.au reports that the unidentified 60-year-old woman was among a whole bunch of contestants at the Beach House Hotel in Hervey Bay, Queensland on Sunday, January 26. Local news showed cell phone video of rows and rows of people ramming down pies and lamingtons as fast as humanly possible. Glasses of agua are next to each person to help wash down the desserts. According to witnesses, the woman was inhaling the cakes at breakneck speed around 2 p.m. That's when some people in attendance said she looked like she choked on some cake, which caused her to have a seizure. According to News.com.au, pub workers immediately jumped in and started giving the woman CPR. Paramedics arrived shortly after and took over. This went on for about 30 minutes. She was then taken to the hospital where she was later pronounced not living.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 11:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/29/3955893/3955893_BED78C2A9CDC4BD693F3CFE67A732E9A_200129_3955893_Woman_dies_during_cake_eating_contest_on_Austral_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Australia Day, Australia Day Lamington eating contest, cake eating contest, woman cake eating contest, Australia woman cake eating, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955867</guid>
      <title>Japan and U.S. evacuate citizens in Wuhan amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  According to Bloomberg, China has confirmed over 5,900 cases of coronavirus nationwide and at least 132 deaths.About 60 thousand patients are being monitored. The number of confirmed cases now surpasses the number of SARS epidemic in China in 2003.Channel News Asia reports, Japan successfully evacuated 206 of its citizens from Wuhan on Wednesday. All passengers will be tested for the virus and will be asked to stay home until test results are ready.According to CNN, the U.S. has also evacuated 240 American citizens from Wuhan on a flight chartered by the U.S. State Department. There are roughly 1,000 Americans currently trapped in the city of Wuhan.BBC News reports Chinese authorities in Beijing and Shanghai are implementing a 14-day monitoring period for individuals entering the cities from Hubei province, where Wuhan is located.A report published in The Lancet by a group of Chinese researchers states that the earliest patient that contracted the virus had not visited Wuhan's seafood market.The symptoms of the novel coronavirus include severe coughing, fever, and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.According to the Centers for Disease Control, the best way to prevent spreading or catching the virus is to wear a facemask, cover your mouth when coughing or sneezing, washing your hands often for at least 20 seconds, avoid touching eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands, avoid sharing items that could be infected and consistently monitoring for coronavirus symptoms.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 10:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/29/3955867/3955867_FB6335129E5A4B18AC9BC4F15D383C99_200129_3955867_Japan_and_U_S__evacuate_citizens_in_Wuhan_amid_v_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, coronavirus, beijing virus, corona virus explained, what is coronavirus, china outbreak, china virus, wuhan virus, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956367</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus vaccine might take months to create</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AN ARBOR, MICHIGAN  Researchers say previous work on the closely related MERS and SARS could benefit the vaccine development strategy to fight the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak.The University of Michigan's Aubree Gordon and Icahn School of Medicine's Florian Kramer say that nucleic acid vaccine technology, which utilizes viral DNA or RNA material, might lead to a viable vaccine.Writing in an op-ed published in Live Science, the authors explain that making a vaccine involves creating a construct, such as an antigen, that the body's immune system could use to target and attack the virus.A vaccine has to be tested in animal and human trials before it is judged safe and effective.According to the authors, scientists do not have isolated virus samples or enough antibodies for testing the vaccine, and they have not established the animal species suitable for animal trials.The vaccine development process will likely take months to complete.The authors state that better global surveillance of viruses would be important to mitigate future epidemics, as coronavirus, Zika, Ebola and influenza outbreaks have shown.They say novel vaccine technologies that could be quickly adapted to different strains are needed as part of a proactive approach to combating pathogens.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956367/3956367_FC7429089DBC4E7BA3822F90AE3C2C65_200130_3956367_Wuhan_virus_vaccine_might_take_months_to_create_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Wuhan virus vaccine, Wuhan virus, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, coronavirus, beijing virus, corona virus explained, what is coronavirus, china outbreak, china virus, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956300</guid>
      <title>French firefighters set themselves on fire in protest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  A violent clash between police and firefighters broke out in the streets of Paris on Tuesday, during a protest over working conditions and pay. French police attempted to control the situation by firing water cannons and tear gas at the firemen, some of which had even set fire to themselves.The Fire brigade unions want a pay raise of 25% and argued that their work is made increasingly difficult due to staff cuts and attacks against them.Paris police said firefighters who tried to break down or scale fencing near the Nation area of the city were dispersed by water cannon.France24 explains how firefighters have demonstrated before, back in October one protester in the southern city of Dijon was seriously hit in the eye and has not recovered his vision.Videos showing baton-wielding officers struggling against the forces of protesting firefighters made their way online.The news outlet, Metro claims France has seen widespread labor unrest since December, with unions mobilizing against President Emmanuel Macron's plans to reform the pension system.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 10:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956300/3956300_E00BA04285CD4003B7451668F293A8C9_200130_3956300_French_firefighters_set_themselves_on_fire_in_pr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, firefighters Paris protest, firefighters vs police, Paris protests, french firefighters protest, police fight firefighter, firemen protest, Paris firemen protest, firefighters set themselves on fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956272</guid>
      <title>Chinese villagers build wall to keep coronavirus out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  The Wuhan coronavirus is spreading in China like wildfire and with it the paranoia of Chinese citizens. Aaaand they've gotten quite creative with their viral contention methods.According to Skynews, villagers from different towns in China's Hebei province have taken the viral battle into their own hands. Some have built DIY brick walls to keep out coronavirus zombies from infecting their people.Others have written eery warning signs on street entrances that read: "No outsiders allowed in." Heard that coronavirus? Ya can't come in!UK's Daily Star reports poor hotel staffers in a quarantined hotel in Hangzhou China have had to deal with waves of passengers being screened for the virus.They've taken a more… technological approach by sending robots to feed and sing? For the possibly infected guests.Hopefully the robot doesn't go all terminator on them.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 09:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956272/3956272_2B2E0F67A5C240CE8A2EB5DBC76E333A_200130_3956272_Chinese_villagers_build_wall_to_keep_coronavirus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak, wuhan on lockdown, wuhan shuts down public transport, coronavirus, beijing virus, corona virus explained, what is coronavirus, china outbreak, china virus, wuhan virus, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956247</guid>
      <title>China demands apology from Danish paper over virus cartoon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK  As China continues to struggle containing the massive outbreak of the Wuhan coronavirus, luckily it's still finding time to get its feelings hurt and wasting time asking for apologies. Reuters reports that the Chinese embassy in Denmark has DEMANDED an apology from newspaper Jyllands-Posten after it published a cartoon of the Chinese flag with its five yellow stars replaced with coronavirus particles insteadNAILED IT.In a statement, the embassy said the paper and Danish artist Niels Bo Bojesen should apologize to the Chinese people for publishing the image, captioned "Coronavirus" in their Monday paper edition. The statement whined that "without any sympathy and empathy, it has crossed the bottom line of civilized society and the ethical boundary of free speech and offends human conscience."What exactly does China know about the ethical boundaries of free speech? Anyways, editor-in-chief Jacob Nybroe said the paper had not intended to make fun of the grave situation in China, but refused to apologize. Nybroe told Danish media that, "we cannot apologize for something that we don't believe is wrong." And to be honest...shouldn't the WORLD be one asking for an apology from China for giving us this latest coronavirus epidemic?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956247/3956247_67ACCA3D6B3643FC96EC9E1F36EF7E1C_200130_3956247_China_demands_apology_from_Danish_paper_over_vir_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China coronavirus, China novel coronavirus, China mad Denmark, China mad Danish coronavirus cartoon, China mad at cartoon, China demands apology, China feelings hurt, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956124</guid>
      <title>Monster mosquito found in Argentina</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CORDOBA, ARGENTINA  A young muchacho named Ezequiel Lobo from Cordoba, Argentina was just going about his day like any other young Argentinian would when he and his mother got a visit from what can only be described as a monster mosquito.Lobo and his mom battled it out with the gigantic bug in the family's kitchen. The battle lasted until, in the words of Lobo himself, his mom then "panicked and attacked it with a can of Raid.In a tweet, Lobo shared a photo of the enormous bugger and added, "This is either some sort of Chernobyl-mutation or I've just realized I am in Jumanji.Well, Lobo, we're happy to say that lucky for you, you're wrong and wrong. Turns out this is not a murderous bloodsucking insect that's here to terminate humanity. On the contrary, it's a species of friendly bugs called assassin flies that eat other pesky insects like well... flies.Lobo wasn't alone in his confusion though, many others in the Twitterverse replied with photos of their own encounters with assassin flies. And although they've been proven to be harmless for humans, they're still pretty darn scary to look at.A user called @PatricioLupich took a video of his own murderous visitor and captioned it: "I crossed paths with this yesterday, I ended up sleeping outside." Yep. We would be setting up camp outside too, buddy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 05:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956124/3956124_4AB45DE9B6A245C8934CC5162DBD7D98_200130_3956124_Monster_mosquito_found_in_Argentina_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Giant mosquito, giant insect, big mosquito, massive mosquito, huge bug, weird bugs, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956066</guid>
      <title>Rescued turtle found pooping out a ton of plastic particles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA  A green sea turtle was rescued off the coast of Buenos Aires after it was entangled in a fishing net at the end of last month, according to the Mundo Marino Foundation, an Argentinian conservation organization. Researchers took X-rays of the turtle's belly and found that its digestive tract was clogged up with a bunch of plastic trash such as nylon bags and netting.The turtle was promptly treated with medication to get everything flowing smoothly again. It then spent the next month pooping out over 13 grams of plastic waste. The organization said in a statement that this is the equivalent of 26 plastic straws or 2.5 credit cards.Researchers said the turtle is healthy now and has been feasting on greens such as lettuce and seaweed instead of abandoned plastic waste.The Argentinian organization explained that they previously found two other green turtles with plastic in their digestive tracts.One of the turtles was found dead with plastic waste in its belly while the other was taken in by the organization after which it dumped out a fragment of a plastic bag.The green turtle has been listed as an endangered species on the International Union for Conservation of Nature Red List, mainly due to the threat of plastic pollution and habitat degradation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 02:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956066/3956066_DE9ADF62355E42F5BA3A0686DC741862_200130_3956066_Rescued_turtle_found_pooping_out_a_ton_of_plasti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plastic pollution, plastic waste, turtle plastic, plastic found in turtle, plastic in turtle feces, plastic in turtle, turtle poops out plastic trash, plastic in turtle poop, plastic waste marine life, plastic waste affecting marine life, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956062</guid>
      <title>Smart campus conceptualized for new Tencent headquarters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA  Dutch architectural firm MVRDV has proposed a smart green campus for Tencent's next headquarters in Shenzhen, China.The campus is expected to have a total floor space of 2 million square meters. Sloped buildings throughout the campus will be topped with solar panel roofs, while green terraces would also be present around the smart campus, according to a news release by the architectural firm. The campus' primary means of transport will include autonomous cars and a shuttle bus loop.The smart campus will also feature a conference center in the shape of a rock as well as a spherical information plaza that would display messages for Tencent employees.The futuristic campus is expected to include office space for 80,000 to 100,000 employees and houses for up to 19,000 Tencent employees. The campus will also include amenities such as schools, sports centers and a waterfront park.Designers explained that there would also be metro lines and bus lines that connect the Tencent campus to the rest of Shenzhen.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 02:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956062/3956062_47A881E32B7A494C84B7C475CE649336_200130_3956062_Smart_campus_conceptualized_for_new_Tencent_head_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tencent, tencent, MVRDV, tencent green smart city, tencent campus, tencent futuristic campus, futuristic cities,  MVRDV shenzhen, MVRDV green smart cities, futuristic cities shenzhen, tencent enormous smart city district, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
