<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 19:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3899073</guid>
      <title>Skydiver dies after hitting big rig trailer on California highway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LODI, CALIFORNIA  A 28-year-old woman is sadly no longer around after a skydiving accident involving a big rig trailer on a busy Northern California highway. According to California Highway Patrol, Maria Vallejo, of Colombia, was skydiving with a group of seven people last Thursday around 2 p.m.Authorities say conditions were windy when the group took off from the Lodi Parachute Center at the Lodi Airport.  As the group was descending, Vallejo was unfortunately caught up in a large gust of wind. A witness told KCRA, that a big gust of wind pushed Vallejo away from the landing zone, and sent her careening toward heavy traffic on California Highway 99 in Acampo. The wind pushed Vallejo until she slammed into a big rig trailer that was driving down the highway. After hitting the trailer, she bounced off and then crashed into the shoulder of the highway. CHP said she was pronounced dead at the scene. According to the owner of the Lodi Parachute Center, Vallejo was an experienced skydiver with 155 jumps. According to CNN, the CHP is now investigating the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 10:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/09/30/3899073/3899073_C15488534E664BF2A945B81BD70AE3D7_190930_3899073_Skydiver_dies_after_hitting_big_rig_trailer_on_C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/43F/784/43F7840EAF78F209029C8AF5EB826B7F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, skydiving, skydiver, skydiver accident, woman skydiving, woman skydiver, Lodi skydiving, Lodi skydiving accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899018</guid>
      <title>NJ clerk arrested for making shoplifter strip at gunpoint</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SALEM, NEW JERSEY  A New Jersey clerk has been arrested for making a suspected shoplifter strip at fake gunpoint. WPVI reports that the incident happened Monday night at a Sunoco Gas Station in Salem. According to store personnel, clerk Amit Saraswat had spotted a man he believed had stolen from the store over the past few days.Usually, you call the cops and get to the bottom of it, but Captain Justice had other ideas, and instead took out a gun.Surveillance video shows him aiming the firearm at the suspected pilferer from behind the counter and then forcing him to strip all the way down to his birthday suit.The nekkid man left the store but came back later after realizing the weapon wasn't real. Investigators later said it was an Airsoft gun.WCAU reports that after the incident was reported to police, they came and arrested Saraswat.He's been charged with aggravated assault by pointing a firearm, unlawful possession of a firearm, possession of a firearm for unlawful purpose and terroristic threats.Meanwhile, the customer he branded as a shoplifter hasn't been charged, and no one knows if he even actually stole anything from the store.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 08:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/09/30/3899018/3899018_5C052AE55FAA4CD0BBBDD2C182BDEF2C_190930_3899018_NJ_clerk_arrested_for_making_shoplifter_strip_at_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9F3/633/9F36335B5A040326B877C3CD90774683.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, shoplifter, suspected shoplifter, New Jersey, airsoft gun, fake gun, gunpoint, shoplifting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3898849</guid>
      <title>Washing machine's delicate cycle releases a ton of microplastics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWCASTLE UPON TYNE, UNITED KINGDOM  New research from Newcastle University has found that a washing machine's delicate wash cycles release more microplastic fibers in comparison to other wash cycles.The scientists used a tergotometer to simulate a washing machine to test for different washing cycles, different water temperatures and different water volumes using polyester clothing.They used a digital color imaging system called DigiEye camera to accurately measure the amount of microplastics released from the wash.A delicate wash cycle released approximately 1.4 million microplastics, the Irish Times reports, citing the study. This is 800,000 more plastic fibers than a standard wash. In comparison, the washing machine's standard washing cycle released around 600,000 fibers.Lead author of the study Max Kelly, a PhD student at the university's School of Natural and Environmental Science, explained in a Newcastle University news release that even with a slower spin speed, the delicate wash cycle is able to "pluck" away extra fibers from clothing material due to its larger water volume.These microplastics are so tiny that they are able to drain out of the washing machine and enter the oceans to harm the marine environment, according to the news release.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/09/30/3898849/3898849_00260129D45C442882207ACFDF1E52D2_190930_3898849_Washing_machine_s_delicate_cycle_releases_a_ton__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5FD/6FA/5FD6FA4A89CC1F737BB8B46401370868.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, microplastics,  plastic pollution, plastic particles, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, microplastics washing machine, washing machine delicate cycle, washing machine delicate mode, washing machine delicate cycle microplastics, washing machine delicate mode microplastics, microplastic fibers, microplastic fibers washing machine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3898824</guid>
      <title>Cold weather causes woman to break out in spidery purple rash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COOPERSTOWN, NEW YORK  A 70-year-old New Yorker developed a strange spidery rash after cold weather triggered a rare blood condition.In a case published in the New England Journal of Medicine, a woman from upstate New York sought medical attention for dizziness and a purple rash.Doctors noted that the rash was consistent with livedo reticularis, which is caused by blood vessel spasms or abnormal circulation beneath the skin, according to the Mayo Clinic.But after blood samples revealed an almost clear fluid with red clumps instead of a deep crimson fluid, doctors diagnosed the woman with a rare autoimmune condition called cold agglutinin disease.According to the Genetic and Rare Diseases Information Center, the disease causes antibodies that normally attack bacteria to attach to red blood cells when triggered by cold temperatures. The cells end up in clumps through a process known as agglutination, eventually getting destroyed and resulting in a drastic decrease in blood oxygen.Doctors believe the woman's condition was exacerbated by a recent viral infection, as well as the below freezing weather at the time.Fox News reports that the woman was kept warm and treated with blood transfusions and medication. After a week, the ratio of red blood cells to total blood volume doubled, indicating the anemia had disappeared. Dizziness also subsided, but the rash persisted.Good thing it's easy to cover up in winter.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 03:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/09/30/3898824/3898824_7C5CD90CDEB946109B66CC1ACC8C80AA_190930_3898824_Cold_weather_causes_woman_to_break_out_in_spider_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E4A/913/E4A913B092BF9E58990FDBDA86E9A446.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, purple rash, purple skin rash, skin rash, cold weather rash, cold agglutinin disease, rare disease, rare medical condition, blood disease, autoimmune disease, anemia, livedo reticularis, abnormal blood]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3898819</guid>
      <title>Central Park's North End to be redesigned by 2024</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  The Central Park Conservancy and the City of New York have announced plans to revamp Central Park's northern end by 2024.The project aims to restore the area's ecosystem and improve the landscape around the Harlem Meer, according to Central Park Conservancy's website. The project will remove Lasker Rink and Pool and connect the Harlem Meer with the Ravine stream valley in Central Park.A boardwalk will be constructed across a new freshwater marsh for the public to observe wildlife. The boardwalk can be converted into a skating ribbon during winter.A new indoor facility with a glass facade will be built onto the landscape of the park's north end and will oversee a pool, which will turn into a skating rink during winter.The building will use a green roof that absorbs stormwater. It will also reduce the urban heat effect by making use of natural locally sourced materials such as stone, wood and glass. The structure aims to achieve LEED Gold certification.According to the park's project page, recreational activities such as boating, fishing and wildlife observation will be introduced to the area once renovations are complete.Construction on the project is to begin in the spring of 2021.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 02:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/09/30/3898819/3898819_32A4DB3F73F6457FAA10666B7BBF1755_190930_3898819_Central_Park_s_North_End_to_be_redesigned_by_202_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/68A/122/68A122021862EBF16802C243176FCF23.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, central park, central park renovation, central park redesign, central park redesign revamped, Central Park Conservancy, Lasker Rink and Pool, harlem meer, ravine, central park harlem meer, central park north end, central park north end renovation, central park north end revamped]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899834</guid>
      <title>Man pops pimple only to find out it was actually a tumor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGDONG, CHINA  A 51-year-old man tried to get rid of what he thought was a forehead spot, only for it to return as a black mass, more menacingly than he could have possibly imagined. After visiting the hospital, the man learned that he hadn't tried to eliminate a pimple, but instead squeezed a tumor; he was diagnosed with squamous cell carcinoma.The location of the malignant tumor left the hospital in a difficult spot, but doctors opted to tackle the situation through careful surgery and luckily for Xie, grafted skin from his forearm to replace the skin removed during the pimple extraction]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 23:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/02/3899834/3899834_9A652C8FEED34519B6AD20FB17C256F2_191002_3899834_Man_pops_pimple_only_to_find_out_it_was_actually_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9B8/289/9B8289CBEC1CB5F2EEC702D049D30B4D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, spot squeezing, pimple squeezing, pimple popper. Pimple removal, spot removal, pimple extraction, face pimple, pimple patch, pimple is tumor, pimple popper blackhead, spot popping, spot pop, spot popping video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899708</guid>
      <title>Fugitive on the lam for 17 years caught living in cave by drone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YONGSHAN, CHINA  A Chinese fugitive who had been on the lam for 17 years was finally captured after he was caught on camera by a drone living in a cave. According to Yongshan police in a statement on WeChat last Friday, authorities had tried multiple times to recapture 63-year-old Song Mou Jiang but failed. The cops were tipped off that Song may have been living in the mountains behind his hometown in Yunnan province in southern China. After searches for Song came up empty due to the difficult terrain and thick vegetation in the mountains, police requested drones to help with the search. With the eye in the sky, police spotted blue metal siding being used as a roof on a steep cliff. They also saw a bunch of garbage outside a tiny cave. According to NBC News, search teams then went to check out the cave on foot and discovered the elusive Song, who was sent to a prison camp in 2002 for human trafficking. Police said Song had been living in the tiny cave for several years. Photos of the cave show a makeshift bed and blackened pots used for cooking. Song apparently had been living off the grid for so long he had trouble communicating with the police. He has since been sent back to China's wonderful prisons.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 14:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/01/3899708/3899708_AF57A21A33A643528C16F70E4D24FF55_191001_3899708_Fugitive_on_the_lam_for_17_years_caught_living_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7D4/A6F/7D4A6FCA3D7CFB055B940AD944ABEEAE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese fugitive living in cave, fugitive living in cave, fugitive living in cave 17 years, fugitive caught by drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899575</guid>
      <title>Woman found dead in exploded porta potty in Florida</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. AUGUSTINE, FLORIDA  Authorities say they discovered a woman in a portable toilet that caught fire and went boom at a construction site in north Florida.  According to Fox 13, the St. Johns County Sheriff's Office said investigators weren't able to ID the person but they believe it was a white female. According to Action News Jax, the porta-potty was located in front of a home under construction. Neighbors say the portable can had been in front of the home for at least 5 months. The homeowner told local media that no one had been scheduled to show up and work on the house. According to the New York Daily News, an official at the sheriff's office hypothesized that the woman may have been smoking inside the porta-potty and ignited the gas fumes inside. Fox 13 reported that neighbors reported hearing a loud boom early Saturday morning around 7 a.m and then seeing a fire. Police say firefighters responded to the scene at 7:30 a.m. Authorities are now asking the public for help in identifying the woman.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 10:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/01/3899575/3899575_EC64E9BF2E364166A6BC23F5B870E941_191001_3899575_Woman_found_dead_in_exploded_porta_potty_in_Flor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/511/657/51165714D4D9E62CA89B7DBB0F47F33C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, porta potty, port-a-potty, portable toilet, florida porta potty, florida porta potty accident, porta potty fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899418</guid>
      <title>Yilan bridge collapses
in northeast Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YILAN, TAIWAN  At around nine o'clock this morning, Taiwan's Nanfang'ao Bridge in Yilan, suddenly collapsed injuring more than 20 people. According to Taiwan News, a fuel truck was almost done crossing the 140-meter long bridge when the entire structure collapsed and fell into the water, causing a fire and sending plumes of smoke into the air.Witness said they heard a loud noise before seeing the bridge, which stands 18 meters above seawater, crumble. Former town mayor and Yilan county councilor, Chi-Shan Lin told reporters during a press conference that officials believe excessive weight may have caused the collapse.    He added that maintenance on the Nanfang'ao Bridge is conducted every two years with previous results checking in as good. At around 11 o'clock, ten individuals were rescued and sent to the Taipei Veterans General Hospital in Su'ao.Citing the Yilan County Fire Bureau, Taiwan News reports that 10 fishermen have been rescued, six have suffered serious injuries, and four have sustained minor injuries.Su'ao Township Mayor Lee Ming-che told the media that five fishermen are still believed to be trapped under the bridge.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 06:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/01/3899418/3899418_55141A8F47C747BFB86C45D81CB716C1_191001_3899418_Yilan_bridge_collapses_in_northeast_Taiwan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FCD/863/FCD863091DA1DCB485EFAE74161F60C4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bridge collapses in Taiwan, Yilan bridge collapse, bridge falls down, bridge fails,  bridge collapse Taiwan, Taiwan bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899347</guid>
      <title>Japan Airlines unveils seat map to avoid annoying crying babies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  Japan Airlines has announced a new online booking option that everyone can get onboard witha tool that lets you see where the little screaming ones will be seated. According to the Guardian, when passengers with mini-mees between eight days and two years old reserve seats, a child icon automatically shows up on the seat plan. This allows people that would rather not have to listen to the oh-so-pleasant sounds of a crying kid blasting into their ear for an entire long-haul flight the option to get as far away as possible. The Guardian reported that JAL was also quick to mention that the new god-sent option did not guarantee passengers would be totally out of earshot. Japan Airlines website also said the icon won't show for customers that book their flight through a third party or if they are part of a tour group, or if there's a last-minute change of aircraft.   All Nippon Airways has also been offering the whaling wee ones seating plan for a while now. Reaction on social media was predictable from those praising the move to others outraged and shocked. Anyways, when are they going to release the seating plan to see where all the large people are sitting?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 03:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/01/3899347/3899347_A654EC6E28294052B7D6AECFCC489C2F_191001_3899347_Japan_Airlines_unveils_seat_map_to_avoid_annoyin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BAF/8D4/BAF8D426F5A7E36FA5F9E6D2150D6359.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, airplane, Japan Airlines, Japan Airlines new seat map, Japan Airlines unveils seat map, Japan Airlines seat map tool]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899325</guid>
      <title>Plastic tea bags release billions of microplastics, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTREAL  New research from McGill University has found that plastic tea bags leak plastic particles such as microparticles and nanoparticles into brewed tea.Researchers conducted tests by removing tea leaves and then dipping the plastic tea bags into 95 degree Celsius water for five minutes, according to the study published in the journal Environmental Science and Technology. Scientists tested tea bags from four different companies. The researchers did not name the tea brands they tested.Researchers analyzed the tea brewed from the plastic tea bags using an electron microscope and found that roughly 11.6 billion microplastic particles and 3.1 billion nanoplastic particles were released into a single cup of brewed tea.Further testing revealed that the plastic particles were made of nylon and polyethylene terephthalate, or PET, which is the same material used to make the tea bags.According to the study, the amount of plastic particles released from the tea bags are "several orders of magnitude higher" than the amount of plastics previously found in other foods.Laura Hernandez, a researcher involved with the study, explained to the BBC that this could also be due to the fact that a piece of plastic, referring to the tea bag, is exposed to boiling hot water.The study did not look into the health implications of plastic consumption, though Hernandez said in a McGill University news release that more research is needed to find out the effects of plastic on human health.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/01/3899325/3899325_F312036652CD4BADBE66D6019499371E_191001_3899325_Plastic_tea_bags_release_billions_of_microplasti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD2/B2E/FD2B2ED4A99AA03AA95C5EB340BAE5A9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, microplastics, nanoplastics, plastic pollution, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, plastic litter, microparticles, tea bags microplastics, tea bags plastic, tea bags releasing billions of plastic particles, plastic particles tea bags, tea bags release plastic particles, tea bags release microplastics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900310</guid>
      <title>Bridge collapse in Taiwan: what caused it?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YILAN, TAIWAN  Taiwanese authorities are looking into what may have caused the sudden collapse of a bridge in northeastern Taiwan.CNA reports that an oil tanker truck had been driving over the Nanfangao Bridge in Taiwan's Yilan County when the structure abruptly gave way.The collapse caused the oil truck to plunge six stories down and catch fire. Three fishing vessels beneath the bridge were crushed, with at least 9 people falling overboard.The Taiwanese truck driver was rescued from the cab of the truck, and taken to the hospital. Liberty Times reports that he sustained multiple fractured ribs, head trauma, a damaged kidney, a ruptured spleen, and a broken leg.He regained consciousness Tuesday afternoon, and is slated for an operation on Friday. Doctors say they are optimistic about his condition.At least 11 Indonesian and Filipino fishermen were also injured in the incident but have been rescued. According to Apple Daily, four fishermen were found dead, while two more remain missing.Focus Taiwan reports that the cause of the collapse is still being investigated, there is speculation that the cables holding the structure up had rusted from exposure to the ocean air, rain, and wind.Yilan County had been besieged by heavy rain and strong winds from Typhoon Mitag a day earlier, and been hit by a 3.8-magnitude earthquake early Tuesday. Officials have yet to determine whether either of these was a factor in the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 16:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900310/3900310_121A4E08994E40E68AF03F29DA557B1C_191003_3900310_Bridge_collapse_in_Taiwan__what_caused_it__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/095/BFE/095BFEC0E1411773042EF0CE21E7A5B4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, taiwan bridge collapse, bridge collapse, nanfangao bridge collapse, nanfangao bridge, taiwan bridge, suspension bridge, oil tanker truck]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900306</guid>
      <title>Elon Musk unveils first full Starship prototype</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOCA CHICA, TEXAS  Elon Musk has mighty big plans for SpaceX's Starship spacecraft that he says will "make life as we know interplanetary.Space.com reports that during an annual update in Boca Chica, Texas, Elon Musk displayed the 160-foot tall Starship MK1, the first full-size Starship prototype, which contains three methane-fueled Raptor engines.The final Starship vehicle will be mounted atop the Super Heavy booster. The entire stack will be 387 feet tall and contain six Raptor engines, with space for up to 37.According to Musk, this new version will be able to carry up to 100 people to destinations in space like the Moon or  Mars, or around Earth.Instead of carbon fiber, the Starship spacecraft will be made of 301 stainless steel, which gets stronger as the temperature drops.The material's higher melting point also makes the vehicle more resilient during reentry into the Earth's atmosphere.According to Space.com, the Starship rocket will be the same one to launch Japanese billionaire Yusaku Maezwa and others on a lunar tourism mission in the 2020s."Musk plans to launch the MK1 on an uncrewed 20-kilometer test flight in the next month or so. MK2 is already under construction at the company's Cape Canaveral facility, while building plans MK3 and MK4 will be underway shortly after.The short-term goal, according to Musk, is to reach orbit in less than six months. The long-term goal, as we all know, is Mars.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 16:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900306/3900306_284529DF768840A2B2B9C0FCD07B4B13_191003_3900306_Elon_Musk_unveils_first_full_Starship_prototype_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/766/470/766470C2DFB2740EEC9A295F9E325374.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, SpaceX, Starship, Starship MK1, MK1, Starship spacecraft, Elon Musk, spaceflight, Mars rocket, moon rocket, space rocket]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900246</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protester shot in the chest by police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  A high school student involved in anti-government protests in Hong Kong was shot in the chest by police during clashes with authorities. The BBC reports that the incident came as thousands of people demonstrated in defiance of a protest ban for the 70th anniversary of Communist rule in China. According to the BBC, although people have been shot with rubber bullets in previous protests, this marks the first time live ammunition has been used.Reuters reports that Hong Kong police confirmed that an officer opened fire at a protester, saying he was acting in self-defense. A police statement said, "a large group of rioters was attacking police officers in Tsuen Wan.""Police officers warned them, but they were still attacking police. A police officer's life was seriously endangered. In order to save his and other officers' lives, they fired at the attacker."According to Reuters, a clip posted to social media shows the 18-year-old protester swing a baton at a policeman, brushing his right arm. The officer then fires a round into the protester's chest as he stumbles over another policeman and falls on his back. According to the BBC, the man has been undergoing surgery and his condition is not known. Police say he was hit "near his left shoulder."According to Hong Kong police, in addition to the bullet fired at the young protester,  five other live rounds were fired at various locations on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 14:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/02/3900246/3900246_A620A2CF79B649E5BD7B273B750627C2_191002_3900246_Hong_Kong_protester_shot_in_the_chest_by_police_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/893/796/893796089430ADD8A718900B6B511751.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong protester shot, Hong Kong protester shot live round, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899974</guid>
      <title>Officials look for causes in Yilan
bridge collapse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YILAN, TAIWAN  Following the sudden collapse of Nanfang'ao Bridge in Yilan on Tuesday, its steel cables are currently at the heart of the investigation. According to Taiwan News, the structures vertical suspension cables, known as "hangers" snapped.Speaking to the Liberty Times, Sung Yu-chi of the School of Engineering at National Taipei University of Technology believes that the ocean salt could be a factor. The high levels of salt content in the air could result in rusting, thus weakening the cables.Another theory is that long-term vibration caused by wind may have loosened cable anchors. Yilan county also had experienced a magnitude 3.8 earthquake at 1:54 a.m on the morning of the collapse. It was also hit by Typhoon Mitag on Monday, which brought heavy rain and strong winds.Officials have yet to indicate whether either was a factor in the collapse. Citing the Yilan County Fire Bureau, Taiwan News reports that 10 fishermen have been rescued, six of whom have suffered serious injuries, and four having sustained minor injuries.The Ministry of the Interior's National Fire Agency said of the 10 people requiring hospitalization, that six were Filipinos and three were Indonesians.Up to six fishermen are still believed to be trapped under the bridge inside their fishing boats with divers hearing knocking sounds coming from them.Since the incident, a total of 214 first responders, 32 disaster rescue vehicles, 14 ambulances, and 11 boats have been dispatched to the scene.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/02/3899974/3899974_C8EC95708BAF4CEC8D65D9383856D41E_191002_3899974_Officials_look_for_causes_in_Yilan_bridge_collap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E02/50D/E0250D7541AE841C48F6ABF69494A52D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bridge collapses in Taiwan, Yilan bridge collapse, bridge falls down, bridge fails,  bridge collapse Taiwan, Taiwan bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899964</guid>
      <title>Internet of Things devices may soon use light-powered RFID tags</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  Researchers from Massachusetts Institute of Technology have published a study detailing the use of photovoltaic powered sensors on radio-frequency identification, or RFID tags, to power internet of things devices.Thin film perovskite cells were added onto the RFID tags to function as energy harvesters, according to an MIT news release. These cells are able to power sensors in the RFID tag in sunny and dimmer indoor light conditions.MIT researchers say the sensors could potentially function for months or even years at a time, depending on the environment's moisture and heat condition.The scientists explained in the news release that their goal was to create inexpensive internet sensors that would not require the use of batteries or any other outside power source.The study, published in the journals Advanced Functional Materials and IEEE Sensors, found that the sensors were able to transmit data for extended amounts of time at five times the distance of traditional RFID tags.This technology could be used to track cargo in supply chains, monitor soil and monitor the amount of energy used by building equipment.Researcher Ian Matthew from the university's Department of Mechanical Engineering said in the news release that RFID tag prototype was only able to monitor the temperature.He explained that researchers plan to add more sensors integrated with perovskite cells  to the RFID tag to monitor humidity, pressure, vibration and even pollution levels.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 05:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/02/3899964/3899964_11422A402437446E8E46005661E77ECB_191002_3899964_Internet_of_Things_devices_may_soon_use_light_po_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D29/71B/D2971B946897833298F823607105AE0A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, RFID, RFID tag, light-powered RFID, RFID technology, MIT RFID technology, internet of things, RFID internet of things, light-powered sensor for  internet of things, perovskite cells, internet-connected sensors, internet of things devices, photovoltaic RFID tag, Photovoltaic-powered sensors, RFID-based devices]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899864</guid>
      <title>Exposure to air pollution lowers students' test results, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  New research from the London School of Economics has found that students exposed to polluted air before taking their exams end up receiving lower scores.For the study, 2,418 students in the Greater London urban area were tested taking a total of 11,443 exams over a period of several weeks. Researchers found that a one unit increase of PM 10 levels indoors resulted in a 0.055 to 2.230 percentage point decrease in student test scores.The study explained that particle pollution is classified as "inhalable coarse particles" or PM 10, and "fine particles," or PM 2.5, on the basis of their size.Particles larger than 2.5 micrometers and smaller than 10 micrometers in diameter are referred to as PM, 10 while particles that are 2.5 micrometers or smaller in diameter are called PM 2.5.The study tested indoor air pollution levels in exam rooms and found PM 10 levels above 75 micrograms per cubic meter. This was able to reduce a student's test score by 3.41 percentage points.The World Health Organization's limit for PM 10 is 50 micrograms per cubic meter.Sefi Roth, a researcher from the London School of Economics who was involved with the study, told the Times of London that students should limit their outdoor activity on polluted days and try to take the less polluted route to school, the Irish Post reports. A separate study examining the impact of PM 2.5 on Israeli students also found a significant decline in student performance.The study found that a one standard deviation increase of PM 2.5 resulted in students' performance declining by 0.93 percentage points.The researchers also showed that 10 additional units of PM 2.5 is associated with a 1.5 percentage point decline.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 02:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/02/3899864/3899864_3BE08A5CECD742D7BBDAFBFB314818A3_191002_3899864_Exposure_to_air_pollution_lowers_students__test__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pollution, air pollution, air pollution UK, pollution linked to grades, pollution grades, pollution academics, pollution linked to getting worse grades, getting bad grades in college, reasons for getting bad grades, A level exams, students exposed to pollution perform worse in exams, students exposed to pollution, students pollution school, students pollution grades]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3899858</guid>
      <title>Manhattan's supertall skyscraper to open in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  The One Vanderbilt tower is set to become the tallest office tower in Midtown, Manhattan with a height of 1,401 feet once it completes construction and opens in 2020.The project is being helmed by American architectural firm Kohn Pedersen Fox Associates.The skyscraper will include a total of 1.7 million square feet of office space which spreads across 58 floors, according to the architectural firm's website. The building will consist of 42 elevators and 5 escalators.The tower's exterior will be lined with a glass facade while the building's top part will be made of four interlocking volumes that rise towards the sky.The overall shape of the tower is meant to complement the Empire State and Chrysler buildings in the area, according to Kohn Pedersen Fox Associates. The skyscraper will include a 30,000 square-foot amenity floor complete with outdoor garden terraces as well as a dining area. A pedestrian plaza will also be added to the bottom of the skyscraper.The architectural firm stated on its website that the building is aiming for LEED certification of sustainability as well as WELL certification for a building's health and well-being.The company did not detail which sustainable features the tower would include.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 02:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/02/3899858/3899858_C496FF8228754B039150B2473F65BB8D_191002_3899858_Manhattan_s_supertall_skyscraper_to_open_in_2020_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/96C/890/96C89065F94743CB3DAEC7DA740F2A73.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, new york architecture, manhattan architecture, crystalline skyscraper, One Vanderbilt skyscraper, crystalline skyscraper new york, one vanderbilt tower, one vanderbilt nyc, one vanderbilt 2019,  one vanderbilt spire, one vanderbilt manhattan, one vanderbilt new york, new york skyscrapers, manhattan skyscrapers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900741</guid>
      <title>Smart woman climbs into zoo enclosure to taunt lion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  The U.S. seems to have a never ending supply of dumb people, but this woman looks as if she's vying for the top spot. Several videos posted to IDIOT-gram over the weekend show the woman visiting the Bronx Zoo and actually climbing into a lion enclosure, so she could taunt the massive carnivore.According to the New York Post, the genius has been identified as 32-year-old Myah Autry. Anyways, Myah had the fabulous idea of climbing into the African lion exhibit, so she could torment a male lion by dancing and waving at him. According to NBC News, the lion didn't really move and just stared at the Israelite. It was probably wondering how Autry made it into adulthood. NBC News reported that the zoo confirmed the boneheaded incident occurred on Saturday. A zoo spokesperson said on Wednesday that a concrete trench was between Israelite and the lion. Good thing lions can't jumpuhhh, wait a second.Luckily the lion decided against pouncing on Myah, because it would have been put down if it did.The zoo also said in a statement, "this action was a serious violation and unlawful trespass that could have resulted in serious injury or death. Barriers and rules are in place to keep both visitors, staff and animals safe. We have a zero tolerance policy on trespass and violation of barriers." Police are now hunting for Autry to slap her with a trespassing citation. Maybe they should just introduce her to some more lions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 12:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900741/3900741_4C4B1810B64D4C4C855F4AA6572A38AF_191003_3900741_Smart_woman_climbs_into_zoo_enclosure_to_taunt_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0B5/51E/0B551EC0E612F715817CE59CB6EEFF91.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Bronx Zoo lion enclosure, woman taunts lion, woman taunts lion Bronx Zoo, woman climbs into lion enclosure, Myah Autry, Myah Autry Bronx Zoo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900733</guid>
      <title>Plastic waste in remote Atlantic island comes from ships: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INACCESSIBLE ISLAND  A new report has found a 15 percent increase of plastic waste on a remote Atlantic island called Inaccessible Island, and it's likely being dumped by Chinese merchant ships.The researchers examined plastic bottles that washed ashore on the island in 1984, 2009 and in 2018. Most of the plastic waste that drifted to the island during the 1980s was from South America, according to their findings. In 2009, plastic debris from Asia surpassed the amount of plastic waste from South America, and by the year 2018, researchers said, 75 percent of the plastic debris originated from Asia, with most made in China.Around 90 percent of the bottles discovered by researchers had been manufactured in the past two years. This means the plastic could not have been carried by ocean currents from Asia as that would take roughly three to five years to wash ashore.This indicates that marine merchant ships dispose of plastic bottles into the ocean rather than disposing it at trash cans at ports, AFP reports, citing the study. The authors noted that the number of Chinese marine ships has steadily increased in the Atlantic Ocean since the 1990s.Peter Ryan, one of the authors involved with the study, told AFP that the plastic waste is not coming from land, adding that, "It's inescapable that it's from ships."More than eight million tons of plastic are dumped into the oceans every single year, 50 percent of which are single use plastics, according to non-profit organization Plastic Oceans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 12:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900733/3900733_488B57A3CB81491A8ADDEA8D5FB06B7E_191003_3900733_Plastic_waste_in_remote_Atlantic_island_comes_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0E0/B72/0E0B721015FFB908C133BB733A55C355.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic pollution, plastic waste, plastic waste in oceans, ocean plastic pollution, plastic waste in the ocean, south atlantic ocean plastic waste, plastic pollution from ships, plastic polluting the oceans, plastic waste ships, plastic debris from ship, Inaccessible Island, inaccessible island plastic trash, inaccessible island plastic waste, plastic in Inaccessible Island, plastic from ships in Inaccessible Island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900701</guid>
      <title>North Korea says it tested a new submarine-launched missile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WONSAN, NORTH KOREA  Pyongyang successfully test-launched a new type of submarine missile...or so they claim.North Korea's state news agency KCNA has released images of what it says is a new type of submarine-launched missile.According to the agency, the projectile was fired in vertical mode in the waters near Wonsan Bay on Wednesday.The SLBM, or submarine-launched ballistic missile, is called Pukguksong-3. Reuters reports that it uses solid fuel and is nuclear-capable missile to be tested since November 2017. According to the BBC, it is capable of flying up to 1,900 kilometers.South Korean officials say that during the Wednesday test, the missile flew 450 kilometers before landing in the East Sea.The Pukguksong-3 also reached an altitude of 910 kilometers before landing  nearly twice as high as the International Space Station.The BBC reports that Pyongyang has carried out 10 missile tests this year, but have only fired short range projectiles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 11:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900701/3900701_590516C37C524424911D2F9586D7CF17_191003_3900701_North_Korea_says_it_tested_a_new_submarine_launc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/022/280/022280832799E1CBAA6E282D69798801.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north korea missile, submarine launched missile, north korea submarine missile, submarine ballistic launch missile, SLBM, ballistic missile, Pukguksong-3, Pukguksong 3, Pukguksong missile, pyongyang, kim jong un]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900674</guid>
      <title>Guy gets crazy sausage lip after basketball pick up game in Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAOHSIUNG, TAIWAN  If you play basketball long enough, you've probably injured nearly every part of your bodyat least a few times. According to Apple Daily, a 20-year-old guy in college playing some pickup with his friends down in Kaohsiung ended up with an upper lip close to the size of a basketball.  Apple Daily reported that the man was running pickup when he took an inadvertent elbow to the face. Like a true baller, he just shook it off and kept on playing. He then went home and went to bed without icing it. In the morning when he woke up, his upper lip had swollen to the size of a Taiwanese sausage and was looking A TAD on the bruised side. He got himself to the hospital where doctors had a look and found that he had suffered a hematoma where several of the smaller blood vessels in his upper lip were damaged.  With a quick visit to the OR, physicians were able to relieve the swelling.Dude's lip is now back to its regular size and seems to be no worse for wear.  He'll no doubt be back out on the courts in no time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 10:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900674/3900674_0A8A5F9DC740475BA4A3E7246B6BC6AF_191003_3900674_Guy_gets_crazy_sausage_lip_after_basketball_pick_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/093/094/0930947520F637881BCABBB2C8AB641B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, basketball, basketball pickup game, basketball injury, swollen lip, basketball swollen lip, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900672</guid>
      <title>Man gets burned after falling into Old Faithful thermal water</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YELLOWSTONE NATIONAL PARK  A 48-year-old man got a bit overly toasted after he fell into thermal water near Old Faithful. The National Park Service said in a statement that Cade Edmond Siemers went out for a little leisurely stroll Sunday night. The NPS statement said, Cade told park rangers that he wandered off the boardwalk without a flashlight and tripped into the thermal water near Old Faithful cone.  According to CNN, Yellowstone clearly states on their website that visitors are to always remain on the boardwalks. The statement went on to say, "the ground in hydrothermal areas is fragile and thin, and there is scalding water just below the surface."Siemers, who currently lives in India, was able to make it back to Old Faithful Inn, where he was staying to call for help around midnight. According to the statement, park rangers thought there were signs he had been drinking. Park authorities later discovered a beer can near the geyser, one of Cade's shoes, and footprints going back and forth from the geyser. According to NBC News, he was transported to the Burn Center at Eastern Idaho Regional Medical Center. The AP reports he was in critical condition on Monday.  Park officials said the water at the pool where Siemers took a dip measured around 150 degrees Fahrenheit when they tested it in August. Leaving the boardwalk around Old Faithful is punishable to up to six months in prison and a $5000 fine.  Park officials are now assessing any damage to the geyser cone. These results will then be given to the U.S. Attorney's Office to see if any criminal charges will be filed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 10:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900672/3900672_B86503BAB1DD47AE8CF85F3388B25728_191003_3900672_Man_gets_burned_after_falling_into_Old_Faithful__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4DD/0CD/4DD0CD24B6CB742D114028B7C9C5DAD2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Yellowstone, Yellowstone Old Faithful, Old Faithful geyser, Old Faithful thermal water, Yellowstone thermal water, Old Faithful boardwalk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900643</guid>
      <title>Woman flipped by bison at same park her date was gored at months earlier</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANTELOPE ISLAND, UTAH  A man and a woman went out on a friendly date to Antelope Island State Park only for the woman to be attacked by a bison just months after her partner was attacked by one at the same location.Kayleigh Davis was walking on a trail in the park with her date Kyler Bourgeous when Kayleigh decided to run ahead. It was then that she spotted the bison. She turned around and tried to make her way back to Kyler.Kayleigh told the BBC that the bison then started charging towards her and lifted her roughly 15 feet into the sky. She then landed on her back and stayed still as the bison sniffed her.Kayleigh had broken her right ankle and wounded her leg.Eventually the bison wandered away and she was airlifted to a hospital in Utah after receiving help from people passing by.At the hospital the 22-year-old had learned that the bison's horn had actually pierced through her ankle. Her partner, Kyler Bourgeous, went through a similar ordeal in June.Kyler told the BBC that the bison had ended up goring his hip and armpit, before stomping and kicking his head.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900643/3900643_59032E44FB794724B29A55AF53BDD77D_191003_3900643_Bisons_in_state_park_attack_man_and_date_in_a_ga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E7D/324/E7D3249F18DCFC1B94E659010968D75E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,bison utah,bison attack,bison charges woman,bison charges man and man's date,bison tosses woman at the same park her date was tossed,antelope island state park,antelope island state park bison attack,bison gores man's date,bison gores woman,bison attacks woman in antelope island state park]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900565</guid>
      <title>$637m in gold found stashed
in Chinese mayor's home</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HAIKOU, CHINA  Chinese officials have discovered an eyewatering stash of gold and cash valued in the billions, in the basement of an allegedly corrupt Chinese ex-mayor in Hainan province.Former mayor of Haikou 58-year-old Zhang Qi was being investigated by the National Supervisory Commission when they found his basement treasure of supposed bribes.The video evidence from the raid shows investigators sorting through the mass heap of gold bullion after they fell from the shelf.The Sun reports that piles of cash singing to the value of $36.7 billion took the form in various currencies such as dollars, euros, and Chinese yuan. If true, this stash alone would make him the richest man in China.The former mayor allegedly has a portfolio of perks, including multiple luxurious villas and will face the death penalty if he is found guilty of "economic crimes."The exposed former mayor has since been stripped of his titles as Xi cracks down on "corruption." The clip and related news have since been censored in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 08:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/03/3900565/3900565_093A5274DB3D4E7E999BD2ECBB5FE3E2_191003_3900565__637m_in_gold_found_stashed_in_Chinese_mayor_s_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/52C/DEC/52CDEC3FA7DD8993A073E6C1A9E0BEA6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese mayor gold, corrupt Chinese mayor, richest Chinese mayor, Chinese mayor has billions, billions found in mayors home, gold and cash in mayors home, Zhang Qi]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3901389</guid>
      <title>Huge 6.5-meter python captured in southern Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAOHSIUNG, TAIWAN  Firefighters in southern Taiwan have just captured a massive snake that's so ginormous you kinda wonder what it's been eating.Liberty Times reports that while clearing weeds near a roadside ditch in Kaohsiung on Thursday, a worker had spotted the Burmese python wriggling in the grass and immediately notified authorities.Firefighters soon arrived to nab slithers, who was 6.5 meters long and weighed about 100 kilos. But it soon became apparent that their puny snake catchers were no match for the huge snake, which kept hissing and lunging at the men. They eventually subdued the serpent by using a crowbar to press its head down, and tape to seal its big mouth shut. It took more than a few firefighters to load the python into a water barrel  part of it anyway  and then onto a borrowed delivery truck.At the fire station, the brave snake nabbers had a bit of light fun with slithers with a Tetris Challenge photo.The giant python stayed at the station for a bit before being handed over to animal control.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 15:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/04/3901389/3901389_9037C78E266141098EF5FCDCE28E6450_191004_3901389_Huge_6_5_meter_python_captured_in_southern_Taiwa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/73F/5B7/73F5B7F9C514264271041CDD5F3A6253.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, python, burmese python, giant snake, massive snake, giant python, massive python, Taiwan python, snake catchers, Kaohsiung, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3901262</guid>
      <title>Deputy pulls car over for speeding, ends up delivering a baby</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NAPLES, FLORIDA  It's not everyday a traffic stop leaves you with a smile on your face, but this one from Florida most likely will. According to AP, officials say a Florida deputy who pulled a couple over for speeding ended up delivering a baby instead of writing a ticket. The Collier County Sheriff's posted the traffic cam footage on its Facebook Page where Deputy Robert Pounds helped deliver a baby girl Tuesday morning on the side of the road. The AP reported that Pounds spotted a car going 63 mph in a 45 mph zone and pulled the car over. Deputy Pounds approached the vehicle, and the driver told him his wife was in labor. Pounds then sprung into action, called an ambulance and popped over to the passenger side after grabbing a blanket from his patrol car. The ambulance showed up minutes after Pounds delivered the baby, and rescue workers cut the umbilical cord. The mother and her new daughter looked to be in good health and were transported to the hospital.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 11:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/04/3901262/3901262_EF2CFF7EF9B24A77AE6E838CA1584CE2_191004_3901262_Deputy_pulls_car_over_for_speeding__ends_up_deli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DCD/D82/DCDD82A4FD2B87DFDD0F03AB5C527BC1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cop delivers baby traffic stop, Florida deputy delivers baby, police officer delivers baby, traffic stop delivers baby, baby born traffic stop]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3901259</guid>
      <title>Chinese must pass facial-rec test to use internet or get smartphone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Beijing is actually planning to get even more annoying and up in people's business by forcing all Chinese citizens to undergo a facial-recognition scan just to get the internet installed or to get a smartphone. According to LifeSiteNews, the new nanny rules issued by the Chinese Ministry of Industry and Information Technology will go into effect on December 1. The new super fun regulations are all part of China's ultra awesome social credit system. First off, China doesn't even have the real internet, and now you're going to need a facial-rec scan to just get some third-rate INTRANET service?? That's cutting edge. Winnie the Xi and his goons are also planning on forcing facial-recognition scans on its 850 million mobile phone users as well. According to Quartz, after December 1, people applying for new mobile and data services will have to have their mugs scanned by telecom providers. The Commies claim that these absurd new rules will help China's internet security and combat terrorism. Combat terrorism?? Yeah okay.Perhaps Beijing should just start considering electronic dog collars for all 1.3 billion of its lucky citizens.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 11:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/04/3901259/3901259_7A8E42F86A9941658A10C858C9D2959E_191004_3901259_Chinese_must_pass_facial_rec_test_to_use_interne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EDB/5C0/EDB5C039A9257D4D681D5FB5ABEB2760.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, China facial-recognition scan, China facial-recognition internet, China facial-recognition smartphone, China social credit system, China 1984]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3901167</guid>
      <title>More than half of Europe's native trees are in danger of extinction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EUROPE  A new report published by the International Union for Conservation of Nature has found that approximately 58 percent of Europe's native trees are at risk of going extinct.The report said trees such as crimean rowan and the mountain ash has been assessed as threatened, while the horse chestnut tree species is deemed to be vulnerable due to the leaf-miner moth, an invasive species from the Balkans, which is causing a decline. Other species facing extinction in the European continent includes terrestrial molluscs, bryophytes and shrubs. These are threatened by the loss of agriculture, a reduction of wildlife area, climate change and invasive species.A news release by the International Union for Conservation of Nature explains that a decline in terrestrial molluscs species would be dire as they are vital for soil regeneration, nutrient recycling and producing oxygen. The report says 2,469 species of terrestrial molluscs, which are endemic to the European continent, risk extinction.A decline in Europe's ecosystem is due to a number of factors including forest fires, logging and urban development.Luc Bas, director of the organization's European regional office, said in a statement that the report shows the alarming plight of the "overlooked, undervalued species that form the backbone of Europe's ecosystems and contribute to a healthy planet."He went on to say that humans need to lessen their impact on the ecosystem and prioritize these species.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 09:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/04/3901167/3901167_70119685D986427BB4B640BF177F50CE_191004_3901167_More_than_half_of_Europe_s_native_trees_are_in_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F0/203/1F0203CA84B78AF7F933E4E89785E6EF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, europe, trees extinction europe, endemic trees europe, native european tree species, europe's endemic tree species threatened with extinction, tree species in europe, native european trees face extinction, ash tree, elm tree, rowan tree, european trees face extinction, european trees could go extinct]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3901005</guid>
      <title>New bionic prosthetic allows amputees to feel their leg</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZURICH  Researchers from the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology Zurich, or ETH Zurich, and several other European universities collaborated to create a leg neuroprosthesis that sends sensory information to nerves in amputees' leg stump.A study published in Science Translational Medicine detailed the researchers' findings.The sensorized prosthetic was tested on three different amputees as they conducted different activities such as walking up and down the stairs with and without the neuroprosthesis. The study found that the sensorized bionic prosthetic allowed the participants to successfully feel obstacles underneath their foot, prevented them from falling and allowed them to walk faster.Scientists implanted tiny electrodes into the amputees' residual nerves and placed an insole with sensors under the bionic foot as well as sensors above the prosthetic knee. Signals were then sent to the residual nerves as the person walked. The nerves were able to send sensory information to the amputees' brain, allowing them to feel their knee, heel and the rest of their foot as they walked.In a press release from ETH Zurich, researchers explained that this technology improves the health of amputees as it would reduce phantom pain in their limb and improve their walking ability.The scientists noted that the study was limited as there were only three participants and said that more volunteers as well as in-home assessments were needed to provide a stronger assessment to the study's findings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 04:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/04/3901005/3901005_2481440E586C4C04A0FB2C11FC9EC9B4_191004_3901005_New_bionic_prosthetic_allows_amputees_to_feel_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1E4/6D0/1E46D02BD50BB18A8927D7BF3C7526F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, prosthetic leg, prosthetic limb, prosthetic limb sensation, bionic limb, bionic leg sensation, nerve-stimulating leg prosthesis,  nerve-stimulating prosthetic limb,  Neuroprosthetic Leg, feeling prosthetic limb, prosthetic limb technology, prosthetic limb 2019, prosthetic limb with feeling, bionic leg with feeling, prosthetic leg with feeling]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3900995</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong to announce new law banning masks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  In what can only be seen as a massive leap toward an even more authoritarian society, struggling Chief Executive Carrie Lam plans to announce a new law that would ban face masks during public assemblies.The anti-mask consideration comes after mounting pressure from Beijing to curb the continued anti-government protests which began in March, protests which Carrie Lam has been failing miserably at suppressing.The law itself will be forced through legislation by invoking a colonial-era emergency law, which was introduced in 1922.The draconian-type legislation permits the city's leader the power to "make any regulations whatsoever which he or she may consider desirable in the public interest" in the face of "emergency or public danger."According to The South China Morning Post, if the Executive Council approves the anti-mask law, the government will make the announcement today, with the ban taking effect "within a short time." A quick-fire warning from legal experts advises that utilizing the undemocratic emergency law would be another step toward an authoritarian society, thus making way for further tyrannical regulations.The Junior Police Officer's Association, which is the largest police group in Hong Kong, pleaded with the government to impose the repressive emergency law or to enforce a curfew. The chairman of the police group, Lam Chi-wai said that implementing the mask ban would be challenging, however, he added that it would be, "irresponsible not to introduce the law just because the police might experience difficulties while on duty."Ronny Tong Ka-wah, an adviser to Carrie Lam said, "If we do nothing, some would think the government is incapable and has no will to solve the crisis."The mask ban hopes to prevent mass protests from breaking out, but Jimmy Sham Tsz-kit, convenor of the Civil Human Rights Front believes, "repression will only make people more flexible and unpredictable when they protest."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 04:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/04/3900995/3900995_7A4AFD66D62C43A19294E0B5E3DBB694_191004_3900995_Hong_Kong_to_announce_new_law_banning_masks_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/31F/636/31F636ED00FF7FDECC0EA0EAED7D0207.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong mask ban, Hong Kong bans masks, Hong Kong anti-mask, Carrie Lam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902720</guid>
      <title>Giant iceberg breaks off from eastern Antarctica</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA  An iceberg has just broken off from Antarctica and is the biggest to do so in decades  but it's not caused by climate change.USA Today reports that a huge iceberg broke off from the Amery Ice Shelf in Eastern Antarctica on September 26.The iceberg, named D-28, has an area of over 1,636 square kilometers  bigger than Greater London or Los Angeles.According to USA Today, scientists working with the Australian Arctic Division said they first discovered a rift in the early 2000s and have been observing it because they expected the ice to calve.They said the calving is part of the ice shelf's normal cycle and not due to atmospheric warming, which mostly affects Western Antarctica, and not the east where D-28 is. Since the ice shelf was already floating, the calving has no direct impact on sea levels. However, the loss of ice may influence melting under the remaining ice shelf.Maritime authorities will now be tracking the iceberg, according to CNN, for the potential hazard it poses to shipping.We don't want another Titanic do we?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 16:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/08/3902720/3902720_201131654A3E4A2CAB274602D56100E5_191008_3902720_Giant_iceberg_breaks_off_from_eastern_Antarctica_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5C7/616/5C761610C0A856E9F413D47B1CDBE5CB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Iceberg, d-28, antarctica, arctic, east antarctic ice sheet, amery ice shelf, ice sheet, ice shelf, calving, los angeles, london, australian arctic division, maritime, global warming, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902676</guid>
      <title>Tomcat on glucose drip after five females in one night</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGDONG, CHINA  A tomcat in China is making quite a name for himself.The New Zealand Herald details that Mr. and Mrs. Zhao, owners of a Russian Blue named Xiaopi, left him at a pet hotel in Guangdong Province in southern China and made it very clear the stud wasn't neutered. Mr. Zhao took to social media to say, "between 10:40 p.m. and 5 a.m., my cat mated with five female cats. And those are only the ones I could see in the CCTV footage."Defending his fluffy Lothario he added, "that's right, all the cats were free to walk around the shop and then the employee went home."Zhao claims the staff had the audacity to blame him for the night's events and explained that some of the cat owners didn't even want kittens.In an attempt to avoid liability, the staff demanded Mr. Zhao explain the situation to the other owners.The disagreement came to a close when the pet hotel apologized and offered to pay for Xiaopi's fluid therapy.Zhao has since confirmed that Xiaopi has since regained his feistiness and is in stable condition.Music: Bensound: http://www.bensound.com/]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 14:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/07/3902676/3902676_D190FADF34034FF6A5E87623A693EA2A_191007_3902676_Tomcat_on_glucose_drip_after_five_females_in_one_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/195/2F4/1952F40A6879D9A9AE62DB6F16629268.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cat on drip after mating, mating cat on drip, cat on glucose drip, cat on drip after mating with 5 other cats, cat on drip, Tomcat five females, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902522</guid>
      <title>Makeshift hot air balloon explodes 10,000 feet up in China killing two</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANTAI, CHINA  A hot air balloon ride in China unfortunately went south real fast in the Shandong province city of Yantai last week.  According to TVBS, the incident took place last Tuesday and has since gone viral over several Chinese social media platforms.Footage shows a highly questionable makeshift hot air balloon made of nothing but some puny little poles, a bit of rope and two seats instead of an actual basket.Just looking at the contraption should have sent the Oh-Hell-No warning signals to potential riders. Clips show a woman and her daughter actually choose to take a ride on the jerry-rigged balloon. According to Outdoor Troop, hot air balloons are normally only supposed to fly between 1,000 and 3,000 feet. But for some reason, the balloon carrying the two soared to a dizzying height of 10,000 feet before it suddenly burst. The two passengers sadly did not make it, and were found later on the ground. According to Chinese authorities, the balloon ride was illegal and had not been registered. The ride has now been shut down and the operators are now looking at criminal charges.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/07/3902522/3902522_F0C956E7EB3243E7BF16194FB55D88AA_191007_3902522_Makeshift_hot_air_balloon_explodes_10_000_feet_u_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B1D/20B/B1D20BE3E8B9BEE8CF04ED8FC885C8BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China hot air balloon, hot air balloon accident, makeshift hot air balloon,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902519</guid>
      <title>China is breeding giant pigs the size of polar bears</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANNING, CHINA  As African swine fever continues to ravage pigs across the country, China is facing a growing pork shortage problem.Things have gotten so bad in China that they've even had to break into their emergency national pork reserves.  Bloomberg reports that some Chinese pig farmers are now looking to breed super sized pigs that are about as heavy as a polar bear in order to try and meet demand. According to Bloomberg, in southern China pig farmers like Pang Cong are raising pigs that weigh a whopping 1,100 pounds that can sell for more than $1,400, over three times higher than the average monthly income in Nanning. Pang Cong's pigs may be on the more massive size, but pig farmers across China have been trying to raise porkier pigs.   Some of China's biggest hog producers are also trying to increase the weight of their porkers. Bloomberg reports that African swine fever has decimated China's pig population by as much as half according to some estimates. Pork prices have skyrocketed and Beijing has given exceptions for U.S. pork to be allowed in even as the U.S.-China trade war continues. So what effect will the polar bear sized pigs have on the market? Most likely, China will just start to see an increased rate of crazy large pigs getting African swine flu. Problem solved!?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 09:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/07/3902519/3902519_8CB97D6E8E5B46A497514253179E88D8_191007_3902519_China_is_breeding_giant_pigs_the_size_of_polar_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/20D/FCB/20DFCB287A58796724BB296AB0282EFA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China breeding giant pigs, China giant pigs polar bear size, China giant pigs, China African swine fever, agriculture, pigs, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902477</guid>
      <title>NBA, Houston Rockets kowtow to China over Daryl Morey tweet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  The Houston Rockets have gone into kowtow mode after general manager Daryl Morey sent out a pro-Hong Kong tweet which angered annoying Beijing. ESPN reports that on Friday, Morey tweeted an image that read: "Fight for Freedom. Stand with Hong Kong." in reference to the ongoing pro-democracy protest in the semi-autonomous city.Well, China didn't like that. And despite Rockets spineless owner Tilman Fertitta denouncing Morey's views with a tweet of his own later that day, crap still hit the fan. The Chinese Basketball Association, headed by former Rockets t-rex Yao Ming, said Morey had made "improper remarks" and expressed its "strong opposition." The CBA later said it would cut all ties with the team.Wonder who ordered the CBA to make those statements??More backlash was ordered from Tencent, a major media partner of the NBA in China, and Chinese state television. Both declared they would not be showing Rockets games.Even the Chinese consulate office in Houston jumped into the fray with a statement that urged the Rockets to "correct the error and take immediate concrete efforts to eliminate the adverse impact." Whatever that means  corrective action as far as China is concerned could be anything from a simple tweet apology to full kowtown in front of Emperor Xi.Morey has also deleted the controversial tweet and "apologized." He tweeted a statement Sunday saying he didn't mean to cause offense to Rockets fans and friends in China, and has since heard and considered "other perspectives" to the Hong Kong issue.The NBA also released a statement to shamelessly try and get back in the Police State's good graces. Guess protecting the bottom line is more important than human rights.But let's be honest...the only people that need to be apologizing are the butthurt Chinese.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 08:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/07/3902477/3902477_A56DA38ED35D4980B69B7314A8B6EDAF_191007_3902477_NBA__Houston_Rockets_kowtow_to_China_over_Daryl__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AFA/FC6/AFAFC6BAF1A17129BA8C78729403D448.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Daryl Morey tweet, Daryl Morey HK, Houston Rockets tweet, Houston Rockets GM, Daryl Morey, butthurt China, anti China, Hong Kong protest, HK protest, Hong Kong democracy, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902472</guid>
      <title>Microplastics cause immune cells to die 3 times faster than normal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UTRECHT, NETHERLANDS  New research from the University Medical Center Utrecht has found that immune cells that target microplastics die three times faster than cells that aren't exposed to microplastics. The research was presented at the Plastic Health Summit on October 3 in Amsterdam.To test the microplastics and the immune cells, the scientists compared clean microplastics with contaminated microplastics. Researchers put microplastic particles of different sizes in a petri dish along with immune cells and blood plasma.The experiment found that clean microplastics were not recognized as intruders by the immune cells, and were therefore left untouched. However, the study found that larger contaminated microplastics were targeted by immune cells. According to a news release by the University Medical Center Utrecht, those immune cells died shortly after while the microplastics remained.The study also found that smaller microplastics encapsulated by the cells did not harm the immune cells.Lead author of the study Nienke Vrisekoop explained in the news release that it's unclear what will happen in the body as microplastics accumulate and are unable to be eliminated by the immune cells.She said their team plans to follow up on their research by testing microplastics that have been exposed to the wind and the weather.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 08:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/07/3902472/3902472_6C56515CDDAF4B04B6E7FCD771AA2570_191007_3902472_Microplastics_cause_immune_cells_to_die_3_times__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/27A/ADB/27AADBD2E6D419E16D877F5341F3DCFD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, microplastics, microplastic pollution, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, microplastics cell death, microplastics accelerates cell death, cells exposed to microplastics, immune cells microplastics, microplastics related to cell death, microplastics human health, microplastics effect on human health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902356</guid>
      <title>Ocean Cleanup's new system successfully collects plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROTTERDAM, NETHERLANDS  The Ocean Cleanup's plastic-catching system is now collecting and retaining plastic debris from the Great Pacific Garbage Patch for the first time, the Netherlands-based nonprofit said on Wednesday.The Ocean Cleanup redesigned its cleanup system earlier this year and added a parachute in order for the system to collect plastic at a more consistent speed.The company explained on their website that their previous system failed to retain plastic as the system would travel either faster or slower than the plastic.This meant that the plastic would float into the system only for it to float out of it.System 001/B uses a parachute to allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system. The system's plastic-collecting screen has been moved forward to prevent fracturing to its floating barrier.Ocean Cleanup explained on their website that the organization added bigger floats to the system's corkline in order to increase buoyancy. These are stacked on top of one another to prevent plastic waste from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier.In a news release on Wednesday, the organization explained that the system has successfully collect large pieces of plastic waste and ghost nets that are typically used for fishing. The system was also able to collect microplastics as tiny as one millimeter from the Pacific Ocean.The plastic will eventually be returned to land for recycling.Ocean Cleanup said they will start designing its next cleanup system, System 002, which will be able to collect and retain plastics for longer periods of time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/07/3902356/3902356_50DDE852F4DB4FD3A5130DF0BAA81506_191007_3902356_Ocean_Cleanup_s_new_system_successfully_collects_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B9A/3DE/B9A3DE6F2495C4FA23C6D14A654FCE43.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ocean cleanup 2019, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup technology,  ocean cleanup project 2019, ocean cleanup, garbage patch, Great Pacific Garbage Patch, floater, plastic, plastic in ocean, beta cleanup system, plastic parts, pollutants, plastic pollution, polluted oceans, technology, cleaning up the oceans, pacific ocean cleanup]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902332</guid>
      <title>Xi learns about space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Xi calls his spacemen to learn about food, space and unfortunately for him... man-love.Outro Music: 'Chinaman' by Jad Abstrockhttps://soundcloud.com/jad-abstrock]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/07/3902332/3902332_90B06CE04FA34A5DAF46466F14DEB91A_191007_3902332_Xi_learns_about_space_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8E6/56A/8E656AE58687311DA05ED65D2F166E1F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Xi Jinping, Chinese president, Chinese space, Xi learns, Xi calls to learn, Xi Jinping calls astronauts, President Xi Jinping calls space, learning with Xi, learn with Xi]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903292</guid>
      <title>Trump withdraws U.S. troops from Turkey-Syria border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYRIA  America's Kurdish allies have been left in the dust after Trump decided to suddenly up and withdraw U.S. Troops from Syria.According to The Guardian, the U.S. and Turkey established an arrangement in August to carry out joint patrols along a 'safe zone' on the Turkey-Syria border and keep Turkish and Kurdish troops apart.But on Monday, the U.S. began pulling its troops, leaving the Kurds to face a possible Turkish invasion alone.Prior to the withdrawal, Turkey had proposed to extend the safe zone deeper in Syria to resettle non-Kurdish Syrian refugees there.The plan was opposed by the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Front, or SDF, who Turkey considers terrorists.According to Reuters, U.S. withdrawal of troops and military vehicles from key positions on the border effectively gives Turkey a green light to move into the area.On Monday, the Turkish defence ministry declared in a Twitter post that preparations for a possible military operation into Syria are completed.SDF Spokesman Mustafa Bali accused the U.S. of leaving to turn the area into a warzone, but added that SDF will defend northeast Syria at all costs.Trump's decision has received much backlash from both Republicans and Democrats.House Speaker Nancy Pelosi called it a threat to regional security, while Senate leader Mitch McConnell worried it might increase the risk of ISIS and other terrorist organizations regrouping.Trump has also been accused of betraying the very same Kurdish fighters that helped defeat ISIS, and sending a dangerous message that U.S. partners aren't to be trusted. even as his administration.According to The Guardian, the Trump administration had insisted it wasn't supporting a Turkish offensive. A senior administration official later claimed that troops were pulled back from the border, but won't be leaving Syria.Instead, he says the soldiers will be redeployed to more secure positions inside the country.Eventually, dear old Orange took it upon himself to hammer home his non-support of Turkey's invasion plans, threatening via tweet to "decimate Turkey's economy" if it does anything off-limits.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 16:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/09/3903292/3903292_C332972F6CA14F52A87939D71C21C340_191009_3903292_Trump_withdraws_U_S__troops_from_Turkey_Syria_bo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5F4/6EF/5F46EFAD89AB283F69A611243A2598CB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Syria withdrawal, Trump Syria withdrawal, US troops in Syria, Trump Syria, US Syria, US pulls out of Syria, Trump, Turkey, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903183</guid>
      <title>Rockets GM Daryl Morey's tweet sends NBA into full court kowtow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON  Houston Rockets general manager Daryl Morey fired off a tweet last week heard 'round the world.Morey tweeted an image last Friday that read: "Fight for Freedom. Stand with Hong Kong." It was in reference to the pro-democracy / anti-China protests that have been raging in Hong Kong for the past four months. And then faster than an SJW can get outraged, Chinese people across the universe were deeply offended. Chinese feelings were so hurt the USGS released a statement saying it measured 8.7 on the Richter scale.The Chinese Basketball Associationwhat's that??whose president is former Rockets center Yao Ming, was so outraged it said it was suspending its relationship with the team. Suspending??Chinese state television and Tencent both said they wouldn't be showing Rockets games. Guess that means VPNs for Chinese that want to watch the Beard or Westbrook. Probably one of the most pathetic responses however came from Rockets owner Timan Fertitta who instantly took to Twitter to kowtow and say that Morey didn't speak for the Rockets.         Luckily the No Backbone Association had Morey's backin that that is exactly where they stuck the knife.     The No Balls Association immediately called a full court kowtow calling Morey's tweet "regrettable" in the free world, but then tailoring a China-pleasing version for their official Chinese-language page on Weibo.  Unfortunately, Morey has had to delete the original HK tweet and go into apology mode. Why? For speaking the truth? Fight for Freedom. Stand with Hong Kong.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/08/3903183/3903183_FA7CD11AB76744F0834A66BA9EF2EE69_191008_3903183_Rockets_GM_Daryl_Morey_s_tweet_sends_NBA_into_fu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/748/634/7486342BEAE85321F2189BCD568580E9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Daryl Morey tweet, Houston Rockets HK tweet, China Daryl Morey, NBA China Morey, Daryl Morey Hong Kong, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902966</guid>
      <title>Angelina Jolie lookalike arrested for blasphemy in Iran</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN  An Iranian woman known for sharing eerie images of herself looking like the zombie version of Angelina Jolie, has been arrested by Tehran's guidance court for blasphemy.Sahar Tabar shot to fame in 2017 when she shared images of herself on Instagram with exaggerated features such as extremely pouty lips, a gaunt face and a sharp nose that turns upwards.Tabar was originally believed to have undergone some 50 plastic surgeries to look like the American actress, according to the BBC.However, Tabar later told Russian news agency Sputnik News in an interview that she uses a whole bunch of makeup and Photoshop to create her artistic photos. Though the 22-year-old did admit that she got her nose and lips surgically enhanced.Tabar is accused of blasphemy for instigating violence, insulting the nation's dress code and encouraging the youth to be corrupt, BBC News reports, citing Iran's Tasnim news agency. Tabar's official instagram account has disappeared, though a duplicate account showcasing her "zombie" avatar is still open.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 07:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/08/3902966/3902966_68C1127A51C44D279DE84CC44556217C_191008_3902966_Angelina_Jolie_lookalike_arrested_for_blasphemy__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3EB/161/3EB16170D1AB071F57605AE7FB6067F6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sahar tabar angelina jolie, angelina jolie lookalike, celebrity lookalike, sahar tabar, sahar tabar arrested, extreme body modification, sahar tabar surgery, sahar tabar 2019, zombie angelina jolie, zombie angelina, sahar tabar arrested for blasphemy, makeup, prosthetics, corpse bride, Plastic surgery, extreme plastic surgery, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3902964</guid>
      <title>Woman accidentally shot in the thigh by labrador retriever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ENID, OKLAHOMA  A woman in Oklahoma was accidentally shot in her left thigh when a dog jumped onto a handgun hidden under the console of a pickup truck.Tina Springer and Brent Parks, the man she is taking care of, were sitting in a pickup truck waiting for the train to pass. Brent's golden Labrador was a little anxious and was jumping around in the backseat.The dog jumped from the backseat onto a folding center console in which a .22 caliber handgun was concealed, the Enid News & Eagle reports. The golden lab accidentally set off the gun, causing a bullet to hit Tina right in the left thigh.The vehicle's seat cover cloth may have gotten into the gun's trigger and caused the gun to go off easily, the Associated Press reports, citing the police.Brent told the police that the handgun usually isn't loaded.The two frantically called 911, explaining their situation and asking for assistance. The dispatcher told Brent to find a clean cloth to cover Tina's wound. Brent didn't have one so he used his belt to stop the blood flow.Tina was then taken to the hospital in an ambulance for treatment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 07:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/08/3902964/3902964_DCA4FB2BBADB4F87916A8D51EDBCEF8A_191008_3902964_Woman_accidentally_shot_in_the_thigh_by_labrador_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1FA/C47/1FAC475573699FA4463AC96375A43A35.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dog shoots woman in oklahoma, woman shot by dog, dog accidently shoots woman, labrador retriever accidentally shoots woman, freak accident dog gun, dog accidentally sets off gun, woman accidentally shot in the thigh by dog, woman accidentally shot by dog, woman gun wound dog, woman dog gun accident, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903957</guid>
      <title>Mysterious fireballs in Chile were not meteorites</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DALCAHUE, CHILE Fireballs falling from the sky, burning bushes... sign of the times?On September 25, residents of Chile's Chiloe Island saw a mysterious fireball streaking across the sky before fragmenting into smaller glowing orbs.According to TVN, a local woman said that following the incident, she found burning bushes near her house.Science Alert reports that Chile's National Geology and Mining Service issued a report three days later, saying it found no evidence of a fallen meteorite.CNet reports that since the object was not identified, it was officially an unidentified flying object, or UFO.According TVN, Chilean astronomer and astrophysicist Jose Maza had said the fireball was either a meteorite or space debris that fell back to Earth.Popular Mechanics reports that since the authorities ruled out a meteorite fall, the object may well have been parts of a spacecraft, satellite, or rocket booster.TVN reports that the National Geology and Mining Service is carrying out a detailed analysis of soil samples, and that it will release the results later this month.According to Science Alert, another explanation is that the falling object and the burning bush could be events that were entirely unrelated.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/10/3903957/3903957_14B7B15C8B364C23B085722516B7C888_191010_3903957_Mysterious_fireballs_in_Chile_were_not_meteorite_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B1D/0DE/B1D0DE35AAA8C4C511A626E7A52A35A0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mysterious fireballs, meteorites, unidentified flying object, ufo, space debris, chile fireballs, chilean fireballs, burning bush, aliens, chile, dalcahue, chiloe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903804</guid>
      <title>Brooklyn Nets owner Joe Tsai is nothing but a China puppet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BROOKLYN  The U.S. has a new panda in the mist in the new owner of the Brooklyn NetsJoe Tsai.As co-founder of China's Amazon knockoffAlibababillionaire Tsai obviously has a ROCK SOLID relationship with the CCP.That too close for comfort relationship was on full display after Tsai posted an open letter in response to Rockets GM Daryl Morey's pro-Hong Kong tweet that literally read like Chinese propaganda, but in Engrish.  KD and Kyrie will no doubt soon regret their decision to move to the Commiest team in the league. For starters...say goodbye to the Brooklyn Nets and say hi to the BrookRn Nets. You know how Chinese get with those pesky L's.The national anthem is probably going to get a bit less star spangled and way more Big Brothery.As for the team, don't be surprised if we see a few new faces on the roster as well as some new sponsorship deals. And as with most things not Beijing's, expect Brooklyn to be now included in new Chinese maps going forward, as well as the introduction of the awesome one country, two systems framework that has failed so miserably in Hong Kong.Go Brookryn, go Brookrn, go, go, go Brookryn.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 13:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/09/3903804/3903804_1E39572AB38542848F2788484CEA8E87_191009_3903804_Brooklyn_Nets_owner_Joe_Tsai_is_nothing_but_a_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C0E/126/C0E126B89CEBC5F78DF8D49BD2337A81.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Brooklyn Nets, Brooklyn Nets owner Joe Tsai, Brooklyn Nets Joe Tsai CCP, Brooklyn Nets Joe Tsai China, NBA China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903427</guid>
      <title>Chinese tourists flock to hot pot style hot spring in Chongqing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA  A hot spring in Chongqing, China has been done up to look like a hot pot where people can just soak themselves in red colored water to relax.The pool consists of plastic vegetables, chilies, Chinese medicinal herbs and even red wine for a brighter hue, according to a video by China's Yishu Media. Images from social media show entire families just chilling at the pool during China's week long holiday celebrating the PRC's national day.An older female tourist claimed that the pool has healing properties, while kids are seen just goofing off and having fun.Chongqing is known for its spicy hotpots which could be a reason why the pool was created, besides serving as a tourist attraction.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 02:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/09/3903427/3903427_95C873826E3344C4A8047DF7586C741C_191009_3903427_Chinese_tourists_flock_to_hot_pot_style_hot_spri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5F0/ABE/5F0ABEC447F9B7EA0C594004AED1FE67.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, hot pot, China hot pot, China human hot pot, hot pot hot springs, human hot pot china tourists, hot pot in China, chongqing human hot pot, hot pot-style hot spring, bathing in hot pot, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3903420</guid>
      <title>Microplastics cause immune cells to die 3 times faster than normal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UTRECHT, NETHERLANDS  New research from the University Medical Center Utrecht has found that immune cells that target microplastics die three times faster than cells that aren't exposed to microplastics. The research was presented at the Plastic Health Summit on October 3 in Amsterdam.To test the microplastics and the immune cells, researchers put microplastic particles of different sizes in a petri dish along with immune cells and blood plasma. The experiment found that smaller microplastics were not recognized as intruders by the immune cells, and were therefore left untouched.However, the study found that microplastic particles with a thicker coating were targeted by immune cells. According to a news release by the University Medical Center Utrecht, those immune cells died shortly after while the microplastics remained.The study also found that smaller microplastics encapsulated by the cells did not harm the immune cells.Lead author of the study Nienke Vrisekoop explained in the news release that it's unclear what will happen in the body as microplastics accumulate and are unable to be eliminated by the immune cells.She said their team plans to follow up on their research by testing microplastics that have been exposed to the wind and the weather.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 02:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/09/3903420/3903420_DF4D2C5B8A944697963CF2EEFBC5901C_191009_3903420_Microplastics_cause_immune_cells_to_die_3_times__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/847/7EE/8477EEE8656AE9DA7E5F9CF9412981B1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, microplastics, microplastic pollution, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, microplastics cell death, microplastics accelerates cell death, cells exposed to microplastics, immune cells microplastics, microplastics related to cell death, microplastics human health, microplastics effect on human health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904252</guid>
      <title>China Has Entered The Game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD  Is China's pressure to adhere to its policies changing our content?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 11:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/10/3904252/3904252_C47A28FCD82541D58C4DF7E2B04E23DA_191010_3904252_China_Has_Entered_The_Game_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B3/521/3B35212BA830BECF96A806DA255F837F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tencent games, Blizzard bans esports players, Hollywood censors content, Band in China, South Park band in China, Ubisoft Tencent, NBA China, Houston Rockets, Daryl Morey, Chinese censorship, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904233</guid>
      <title>Man grows jugs after taking Johnson and Johnson drugs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW BRUNSWICK, NEW JERSEY  A jury in Philadelphia has ordered Johnson & Johnson to pay up  $8 billion to be exact  to Nicholas Murray after he claimed that he grew breasts after taking an antipsychotic drug from the company's subsidiary Janssen Pharmaceutica.Citing the lawsuit, the Irish Times reports that Murray was prescribed the drug Risperdal by doctors after he was diagnosed with autism at age 9 in 2003.Risperdal is typically given to treat schizophrenia or bipolar disorder, but doctors are allowed to prescribe the drug if they think the patient is in need of it, the BBC reports.Murray started taking the drug as prescribed, but he realized something was wrong when his chest started to swell and grow in size. He sued Janssen Pharmaceutica in 2013, accusing them of not warning doctors about the risks of the drug and marketing it as a treatment for mental health disorders in kids.Previously, a jury in 2015 ordered the company to pay Murry US$1.75 million dollars, finding the company negligent as they didn't warn consumers about the risks the drugs carried.A state appeals court then reduced that amount to US$680,000, but upheld the verdict.Now another jury has come up with the same verdict, but this time awarding $8 billion dollars in punitive damages.Johnson & Johnson disagreed with the verdict and called it "grossly disproportionate," and said that they will appeal the ruling.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 10:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/10/3904233/3904233_A13C550F08354FA5AC36E8AA2EFF0781_191010_3904233_Man_grows_jugs_after_taking_Johnson_and_Johnson__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B0A/22B/B0A22B6B6AD5B20C9CFEC39C9A2E65CA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Johnson & Johnson, Johnson & Johnson court order, johnson & johnson lawsuit, antipsychotic drug Johnson & Johnson, Johnson & Johnson ordered to pay man $8bn, Risperdal, Johnson & Johnson Risperdal breast growth, man breast growth, breast growth in man over antipsychotic drug, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904231</guid>
      <title>Mexico mayor tied to truck and dragged through streets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAS MARGARITAS, MEXICO  A Mexican mayor is probably wishing he never made certain assurances while campaigning after he was tied up and dragged through town for failure to follow through on said assurances. According to the BBC, mayors and small time politicians in Mexico are usually targeted by gangs for refusing to break the law, but this time the mayor was taken to task for not fulfilling a campaign promise. BBC reported that Mayor Jorge Luis Escandn Hernndez of Las Margaritas had promised to fix up a local road while he was on the campaign trail. Like most politicians after getting in office, Hernndez then failed to fix the street. Well that didn't sit too well with 11 of his constituents, so they paid a little visit to Hernndez at his office, dragged him out and threw him in the back of a pickup. They then decided to tie the mayor's hands up with a rope and strung him up to the back of the truck. CCTV footage shows the angry locals then dragging him through the streets of town.According to the BBC, it took dozens of police to stop the vehicle and rescue the Hernndez. Several people were injured in the incident.  The 11 people have now been arrested. The mayor says he plans to press charges too. Okay, but who's going to fix that road now?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 10:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/10/3904231/3904231_E4811F3F60F143B7B8F987FC20465178_191010_3904231_Mexico_mayor_tied_to_truck_and_dragged_through_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AE/690/1AE69091C22196E923E3C3BD1C39C138.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mexico mayor, Mexico mayor truck, Mexico mayor truck streets, Mexico mayor dragged, Mexico, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904093</guid>
      <title>Aspirin could protect your lungs
from pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON New research has found that aspirin could protect our lungs from air pollution.According to the EPA, air pollution has been known to have an adverse effect on respiratory health. Exposure to particulate matter in the air can inflame and irritate lung cells and impair lung function.A study published in the American Journal of Respiratory and Critical Care Medicine explored whether non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs or NSAIDs, such as aspirin, could protect the lungs from pollution.Researchers analyzed data from 2,280 male veterans in the greater Boston area who were given tests to determine lung function.According to a Columbia University press release, the study examined the relationship between the lung test results, self reported NSAID use, and ambient particulate matter and black carbon in the month before the test. They found that the use of NSAIDs, mainly aspirin, reduced the effect of particulate matter on lung function by half.Aspirin appeared to have a protective effect regardless of age, health status, or tobacco use. Although the mechanism remains unknown, researchers suspect NSAIDs may be mitigating the inflammation triggered by air pollution.According to study author Xu Gao, the findings suggest NSAIDs could protect people from short-term spikes of air pollution.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 06:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/10/3904093/3904093_9C9DD3253F1B41BDB8563DFD3FBA4264_191010_3904093_Aspirin_could_protect_your_lungs_from_pollution_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/255/617/255617F59E90A045F52C37D03042A047.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[air pollution effects, air pollution harm, lungs, lung health, aspirin, NSAID, air pollution, particulate matter, pollution particles, black carbon, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904066</guid>
      <title>Hungry 'burger man' shoves protestors aside so he can feed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DENMARK  A Danish man was outraged when a group of what he calls, "hippies" attempted to block him from buying a burger.According to the Metro, the group were 'Extinction Rebellion' protestors and were organized outside a Danish burger chain in Denmark protesting for climate change. The man was determined to get purchase a burger and tells the activists that he'll "run through" unless they moved.He then demands the demonstrators to, "behave themselves" before squaring up to a beardy activist and branding them all, "hippies!"The clip was uploaded to VidMax and has since gone viral on Twitter with over 11,000 likes.Climate Change protests are taking place internationally this week as part of a fortnight of Extinction Rebellion civil disobedience.Activists in Aarhus, the second-largest city in Denmark, are taking part in the protests, alongside countries such as Germany, France, Spain, Australia, India, and New Zealand.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 05:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/10/3904066/3904066_D12BE2CA74CE42B8B3FD6F3109AF88AD_191010_3904066_Hungry__burger_man__shoves_protestors_aside_so_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1D4/210/1D421037D28AB788EB4AE267FC9BFE3A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Danish Burger man, protestors stop burger man, protestors outside burger chain, climate change,  Extinction Rebellion, man pushes protestors for burger, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904051</guid>
      <title>Hackers swipe credit card info from 1000s of online store</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS  New research has found that stores on an online shopping platform have been hacked.According to ZDNet, Volusion, a software company hosting online stores, was hacked in a bid to steal credit card information from their clients.Citing research from Check Point and Trend Micro, ZDNet reports that hackers implanted malicious Javascript code onto the company's servers after gaining access to its Google Cloud infrastructure.The malicious code was then able to hijack credit card details from information that customers entered through the online stores.Cyber security company RiskIQ explained on their website that these types of hacking attacks are called "Magecarts."According to a Medium blogpost by a researcher at Check Point, more than 6,500 online stores have been impacted. This includes a Sesame Street Live online store which has since been taken down.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 05:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/10/3904051/3904051_0FD421AB95A0447B8132055FD8A8A168_191010_3904051_Hackers_swipe_credit_card_info_from_1000s_of_onl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/417/0E3/4170E3AFE093DB2BEADE95706FDDB78D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Credit card data, hackers steal credit card data, volusion, volusion credit card data stolen, volusion hacking operation, credit card numbers hacked, credit card hacks 2019, credit card hacking operation, credit card hacking online, online store hacking, online shopping credit card hacking, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904724</guid>
      <title>Smartphones are changing the way people type</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EUROPE  It looks like pounding your thumbs into that smartphone to type is catching up to the speed of typing on old school keyboards.  The Washington Post reported that according to a new study, double thumb typists hammer out on average of 38 words-per-minute, compared to 51.56 words-per-minute on physical keyboards. Researchers from Finland's Aalto University, the University of Cambridge and ETH Zrich carried out the largest mobile typing study to date by testing 37,000 volunteers.The study also found that smartphone typists who use auto-correct are quicker than those who use word-prediction tools. Akayou can type faster if you ignore spelling.   Most mobile phone users type on their overpriced devices with one or two thumbs, while some apparently just use a single index finger. No shocker here, 10- to 19-year-olds type about 10 wpm faster than older people in their 40s, regardless of whether the keyboard was on a phone or a computer. Researchers also found that smartphone users left more uncorrected errors and use the backspace less. That's probably because it's an enormous pain in the behind to go back and change things when you're typing on your phone.  According to the Washington Post, smartphones may have some other ergonomic risks that we don't see with physical keyboards, such as neck, shoulder and grip issues.  And not to mention staring at the smartphone screen will probably make you go blind one day, but until that day comes, pound away.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 10:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/11/3904724/3904724_2352845703DE45DD915413045797FCC4_191011_3904724_Smartphones_are_changing_the_way_people_type_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/577/299/577299C71A250B6425CAD381CA9CCA84.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Smartphone, smartphone typing, mobile phone typing, smartphone typing study, physical keyboard, virtual keyboard, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3904499</guid>
      <title>New flying taxi powered by hydrogen produces zero emissions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOPKINTON, MASSACHUSETTS  Massachusetts-based Alaka'i Technologies has developed a hydrogen-powered air vehicle called Skai that uses six rotors and performs vertical takeoffs and landings.The aircraft also sports an airframe parachute in case if several of its props fail.According to the company's website, Skai has a range of 400 miles and will be able to remain airborne for approximately four hours. It has a capacity of five passengers, including the captain.Skai will be powered by hydrogen fuel cells, which emit only pure water, according to Skai's project page.Hydrogen fuel cells consists of compressed hydrogen which reacts with an oxidizing agent such as oxygen to create energy. These cells have a greater weight-energy density than batteries and fossil fuels.The aircraft will initially be piloted. However, the company said it is looking into remote or autonomous options.Reuters reports the company is currently waiting to receive certification from Federal Aviation Administration. Steve Hanvey, the CEO of Alaka'i Technologies, told Reuters that they expect to receive certification by the end of 2020. He added that they plan to start selling the aircraft in the beginning of 2021. The company has yet to announce the price of the aircraft.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 04:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/11/3904499/3904499_D13CC848CCC04AC5A8A5ABE00608CEA5_191011_3904499_New_flying_taxi_powered_by_hydrogen_produces_zer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F4B/582/F4B5825731221884D320A860A5168BE1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Skai, skai flying car, Alaka'i Technologies, urban air mobility vehicle, EVTOL, skai aircraft, skai hydrogen-powered aircraft, hydrogen-powered flying vehicle, skai flying vehicle zero-emissions aircraft, skai zero-emission aircraft, skai EVTOL aircraft, air taxi, hydrogen-powered air taxi, EVTOL air taxi, skai flying taxi, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3905995</guid>
      <title>Chinese zoo glues basket to tortoise shell for kicks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANNING, CHINA  A tortoise at a Chinese zoo was mostly likely an unwilling participant after photos emerged of a basket glued to its shell for visitors to chuck coins at. Pictures shared over Twitter knockoff Weibo from Nanning Zoo located in Guangxi province show the African spurred tortoise with a basket and a Chinese flag sticking out of it. The photos were taken on October 1the PRC's National Daywhen China was giving itself an enormous pat on the back. Guess that explains the cheap flag.Zoos and playgrounds have become popular destinations for families and their kids over the National Day holiday.And what better way to take advantage of that than by enlisting the help of the lightning-quick tortoise. One post by user Tea-tia accused the zoo of trying to trick visitors out of cash and urged the relevant authorities to investigate the incident. He also claimed the tortoise was being kept in a "very bad environment" with no zookeepers around. Zoo officials have said they were investigating the matter and have yet to release a statement. The zoo is most likely having trouble getting anything out of the tortoise. It's notoriously difficult to get them to crack during interrogation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 13:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/14/3905995/3905995_902825F2B6F64FFEB7724854C04FE1F1_191014_3905995_Chinese_zoo_glues_basket_to_tortoise_shell_for_k_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/85E/E54/85EE545B32EC8250E1391E28732185F9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese zoo tortoise, tortoise basket glued to shell, basket glued to shell, Nanning Zoo tortoise, tortoise chinese flag , TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3905987</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protester destroys policeman with flying kick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  A fearless Hong Kong protester was filmed unleashing a massive flying kick on a riot police officer in order to save his friends from getting arrested by the pro-China authorities.According to the Hong Kong Free Press, the incident occurred on Sunday afternoon outside the Mong Kok Grand Plaza. The clip starts out with a police officer in full riot gear kicking and grabbing one protester so that he can arrest him. A second protester can be seen trying to help his friend get away. That's when from out of nowhere, a third protester enters the picture and unloads a flying kick to end all flying kicks right into the cop's chest.  The Hong Kong movie style kick sends the officer reeling back about 10 feet before he embarrassingly eats it. A struggle then ensues between the first two protesters and the disgraced copper with a few blows being exchanged. The protesters then run off, while the cop gets back up. The police officer takes a few steps like he's about to give chase, but then has second thoughts and turns around and does the walk of shame in retreat. According to the BBC, several peaceful protests in Hong Kong on Sunday got a bit out of hand between protesters and riot police. The BBC reported that public transport stations and shops deemed to be pro-Beijing were damaged. Police said they used "minimum force" to disperse protesters, which means the force was anything but minimum. Anti-China protests have been raging in Hong Kong since June. More than 2,300 people have been arrested since the protests began.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 12:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/14/3905987/3905987_5754300ACDC64961849A7F097A3EB433_191014_3905987_Hong_Kong_protester_destroys_policeman_with_flyi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong China protests, Hong Kong protesters, Hong Kong riot police, China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3905882</guid>
      <title>Blizzard finally breaks
silence on 'Blitzchung's' ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Blizzard Entertainment has broken its silence over the controversial banning of e-sports player, 'Blitzchung'. #StandWithHongKong #BoycottBlizzard]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 09:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/14/3905882/3905882_354D2646CC074741B4CD7D7850228551_191014_3905882_Blizzard_finally_breaks_silence_on__Blitzchung_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6AC/163/6AC1639DC003B30608A2D372D2A3ACF0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Blizzard, Activision Blizzard, Tencent, Tencent investment, Blizzard breaks silence, Blitzchung, Hearthstone, e-sports, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, #StandWithHongKong #BoycottBlizzard, Chinese censorship, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3905648</guid>
      <title>Squirrels stash hundreds of walnuts under hood of car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PITTSBURGH  A Pittsburgh area couple thought it was pretty strange that almost all the walnuts that had fallen from a black walnut tree in their yard had disappeared without a trace. According to CBS News, that was because a bunch of overactive squirrels had been storing them allunder the hood of the couple's SUV. Chris Persic told KDKA that his wife Holly called from Northland Library and said it smelled like her car was burning, and that it was making a weird sound. Persic told her to pop open the hood and have a look. She then sent over a hilarious picture with more than 200 walnuts and grass piled up under the hood of their Kia. Persic had to rent a car and then go over to help his wife clean out all the nutty nuts, which took them almost an hour.  What's even more nuts is that after they took the vehicle into the shop, they found another half a trashcan worth of walnuts under the engine too.  Looks like these squirrels were planning for the next zombie apocalypse. Luckily, the stashed walnuts didn't do any serious damage to the couple's ride. The squirrels were asked for a comment on the incident, but did not respond before the story went to print.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 02:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/14/3905648/3905648_6BFE282DF6484F6AA825E9065015C5B9_191014_3905648_Squirrels_stash_hundreds_of_walnuts_under_hood_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DF8/451/DF84515EC19AFAE481ED5EB3137B7C40.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Squirrel, squirrels stash walnuts, squirrels walnuts car, walnuts car engine, walnuts under car hood, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3905646</guid>
      <title>435 Holly wins Fat Bear Week 2019 crowned fattest bear in U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KATMAI NATIONAL PARK & PRESERVE  Fat Bear Week 2019 came to an end on Tuesday night with 435 Holly taking home this year's crown. Katmai National Park and Preserve said in a Facebook post, "She is fat. She is fabulous. She is 435 Holly. And you voted her the 2019 Fat Bear Week Champion. All Hail Holly whose healthy heft will help her hibernate until the spring. Long live the Queen of Corpulence!"According to NPR, Fat Bear Week has been an annual event for the past five years at Alaskan national park. Katmai started the contest to help educate the public and celebrate the process of bears chowing down to build up fat reserves in preparation for winter hibernation. According to Popular Science, park rangers picked the 12 chunkiest bears and tossed them into a large March Madness style bracket.The public then threw its weight behind their favorite bear and in the process help promote the National Park Service's conservation efforts.  According to NPR, Holly and the other contestants are coastal brown bears that forage by the Brooks River, which happens to have one of the largest concentrations of sockeye salmon in the world. NPR reported that a record 187,000 votes were cast this year, three times more than last year. Have a good sleep Holly, you've earned it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 02:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/14/3905646/3905646_978BE403E0E242CD9C34274297781397_191014_3905646_435_Holly_wins_Fat_Bear_Week_2019_crowned_fattes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/209/698/20969834B381F6EB2E2B29DF28CE6063.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fat Bear Week, Fat Bear Week 2019, 435 Holly Fat Bear Week, 435 Holly fattest bear, Katmai National Park and Preserve, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906489</guid>
      <title>Electric air taxi port to be showcased in Singapore</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE  German aviation startup company Volocopter is collaborating with British drone infrastructure and deliveries company Skyports to build the VoloPort, an electric station for flying taxis.The VoloPort will be unveiled at the Marina Bay in Singapore later this month.The VoloPort prototype in Singapore will include passenger lounges and will allow visitors to experience pre-flight check-in and boarding procedures, according to Volocopter's project website. Visitors will also have the chance to sit inside the Volocopter while it is on the ground, reports Bloomberg.A test pilot will be inside the air taxi vehicle as it takes off from the VoloPort for a three minute demo flight on October 22.Skyports Managing Director Duncan Walker told Bloomberg that visitors can provide feedback for the VoloPort so that they can tweak the final design before the air taxi service launches in 2025.He explained that the VoloPort was built in China and then taken apart to be reassembled in Singapore.Skyports' project website explains that the VoloPort will include a range of modular designs which can be adapted to fit different environments such as rooftops, parking lots and other urban locations.The air taxi flight will likely cost around US$3.75 per mile, which is roughly double the amount of money a ground-based ride would cost, according to Bloomberg.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 14:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/15/3906489/3906489_0E8896BE40C64FDAA336BE447499B19C_191015_3906489_Electric_air_taxi_port_to_be_showcased_in_Singap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D56/25F/D5625F2C55A1BB45769CCBCC24930B6E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Volocopter, VoloPort, Air Taxi VoloPort, Vertiport, vertiport singapore, skyport, VoloPort Volocopter, VoloPort Singapore, volocopter 2019, volocopter air taxi, volocopter flying taxi, volocopter air taxi port, flying taxis, volocopter electric aircraft, volocopter system, urban air mobility vehicle, EVTOL, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906451</guid>
      <title>Vietnam yanks 'Abominable' over South China Sea map</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VIETNAM  Vietnam has made a bold move by yanking DreamWorks film Abominable from movie theaters because of a scene that includes China's ridiculous South China Sea map. According to BBC, Abominable is about a Chinese girl who discovers a yeti on her roof and is a joint China-DreamWorks production. Well here's the first problem. A Chinese girl wouldn't find a yeti on her roof because yetis are from Tibet. Just saying. BBC reports that one scene in the movie shows China's unilaterally declared "nine-dash line' map, which carves out an enormous area in the sea that is nowhere even close to China. The thing is, Vietnam, as well as Taiwan, the Philippines, Brunei, and Malaysia all make claims to parts of the sea. According to BBC, the movie was jointly produced by Shanghai-based Pearl Studio and DreamWorks and was first shown in Vietnam on October 4. Vietnamese moviegoers quickly spotted China's fake map and began sharing screenshot over social media. The government then did the right thing and quickly announced the film was getting yanked from theaters. The move comes at a time of heightened tensions between Vietnam and China. Well apparently that's what you get when filming a make-believe moviemake-believe maps.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 12:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/15/3906451/3906451_34ABA3167F904FC2A637EF4EAE3B4B22_191015_3906451_Vietnam_yanks__Abominable__over_South_China_Sea__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/667/0A9/6670A9C60693230A34E0E4914F9C732C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Vietnam pulls Abominable, Abominable DreamWorks, Abominable South China Sea map, Vietnam vs China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906349</guid>
      <title>Taiwan president rejects China's 'one country, two systems' deal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Taiwan is giving China a hard no to its offer of reunification under the 'one country, two systems' formula.CNA reports that during China's National Day on October 1, President Xi Jinping vowed to uphold the 'one country, two systems' model in Hong Kong and Macau, and proposed a similar arrangement for Taiwan.According to The Economist, the policy formulated by then-Chinese president Deng Xiaoping would allow Taiwan to retain a separate administration, a capitalist system, and its own armed forces so long as it recognized Beijing's Communist government as legitimate.Taiwan president Tsai Ing-wen rejected the offer, calling the arrangement a failure, as evidenced by the current state of unrest in Hong Kong and the violent suppression of its citizens' freedoms.Reuters reports that according to Tsai, Beijing's policies toward Taiwan pose a danger to regional stability.She says that regardless of party or political affiliation, the general consensus among Taiwan's 23 million people is to reject "one country, two systems."According to Reuters, Beijing has steadily increased pressure on Taiwan to seek reunification, sending out warnings by flying regular bomber patrols around it. China has also been trying to isolate Taiwan diplomatically. Since Tsai came to power, seven countries have switched allegiance to Beijing, leaving Taiwan with only 15 nations it has formal state-to-state relations with.Despite this, Tsai claims the country is undaunted, and is working to increase combat capabilities by purchasing advanced weapons from overseas and developing home-made aircraftBasically, Taiwan isn't a part of China and sure the hell doesn't want to be.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 09:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/15/3906349/3906349_C9C9B3D01E674398941E56758696D345_191015_3906349_Taiwan_president_rejects_China_s__one_country__t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/021/46B/02146BF21EB74C803D389216C2A531E9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[one country two systems, taiwan sovereignty, china unification, taiwan china relations, taiwan china, taiwan president, taiwan democracy, taiwan freedom, hong kong, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906268</guid>
      <title>Toyota supplies driverless bus for 2020 Olympics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Toyota says it will supply up to 20 specially-designed e-Palette electric self-driving vehicles for ferrying athletes and related staff during the 2020 Tokyo Olympic and Paralympics, the company announced earlier this week.The battery-powered vehicle is equipped with large sliding doors and powered ramps to ease group boarding by Paralympians and other athletes, Toyota said in a press release published Wednesday on its website.Toyota says the vehicle will include handrails that are easy to grab regardless of height, high-contrast interior colors to assist the color-blind, and a low floor.According to Toyota, the driverless vehicle will have enough room for four wheelchairs and seven standing passengers.The vehicle is designed with a focus on safety and automated low-speed driving, with cameras and sensors for light detection and ranging, and high accuracy 3D mapping.The special e-Palette will have a 360-degree field of vision and is capable of safe self-driving at speeds up to 20 km per hour with an onboard safety operator, or level-4 autonomy.According to Toyota, the circular displays at the front and rear are designed to resemble stylized eyes, enabling the vehicle to signal its status, including driving, stopping for pedestrians, and recharging.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/15/3906268/3906268_BC63E40327E5403383E11485FF57823A_191015_3906268_TOYOTA_SUPPLIES_DRIVERLESS_BUS_FOR_2020_OLYMPICS_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CA8/8BF/CA88BF3041563AE2D933B49401F309BE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,satire,toyota,toyota motors,tokyo,japan,self-driving,driverless,autonomous,electric,vehicle,bus,car,pod,e-Palette,olympics,olympics 2020,paralympics,paralympics 2020]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906245</guid>
      <title>Cop guns down black woman through the bedroom window</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FORT WORTH, TEXAS  A black woman was shot dead by a police officer in Texas through the window of her own bedroom around 02:30 a.m. on October 12.Atatiana Jefferson was inside her bedroom playing video games with her 8-year-old nephew when she heard a noise outside the window and went to see what was going on. Her lawyer S. Lee Meritt told the Fort Worth Star-Telegram that she was promptly shot dead through the window by a Texan police officer.The newspaper reports that Jefferson's neighbor, James Smith, made a call to the non-emergency police hotline to check on her as the door of her house was left open.Surveillance footage from the officer's camera shows two police officers surveying the perimeters of her house using flashlights. In the footage, one of the officer spots a figure through the bedroom window and is heard saying, "Put your hands up! Show me your hands!" and proceeds to immediately fire a gunshot through the window.In the video, the man does not explicitly identify himself as a police officer.According to a press release by the Fort Worth Police, the officer drew his gun because he had perceived a threat by the person inside the residence.After the shooting, the officers entered the woman's residence and began providing emergency medical care. She was pronounced dead on scene.A press release by the police mentioned that there was a firearm in Jefferson's residence, though it isn't clear if she was holding the weapon during the incident.The 28-year-old was a pre-med graduate from Xavier University working in pharmaceutical equipment sales. He said that she was taking care of the house and her nephew as her mom was sick, according to a Go Fund Me page created by Jefferson's lawyer. The post mentioned that a candlelight vigil will be held for the woman at 7:00 p.m. local time tonight.The Fort Worth Police said that the officer in question has been placed on administrative leave until the police incident has been thoroughly investigated.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 06:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/15/3906245/3906245_BFFD75B6D91A40F89AE66A948862F9DF_191015_3906245_Cop_guns_down_black_woman_through_the_bedroom_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7E0/A0D/7E0A0D3F699368D1DFCA25DFFAC8A3F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Black woman shot dead by Texas police, US police shooting, texas shooting police, fort worth texas police shooting, black woman texas shooting, woman shot dead in her own home, US shooting, Texas police, texas shooting,  woman shot and killed in texas shooting, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906155</guid>
      <title>China grows cotton plant on the moon in biological first</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOON  China successfully grew a plant on the moon in a biological first, IEEE Spectrum reports.On January 3, China's Chang'e-4 lunar probe made a milestone soft-landing on the far side of the moon.CNN reports that the spacecraft carried a self-contained biosphere called the Lunar Micro Ecosystem, or LME, that was activated upon landing.A cotton seed inside the biosphere sprouted two leaves, making it the first living thing humans have grown on the moon.Xie Gengxin of Chongqing University told IEEE Spectrum that Chinese scientists initially believed the seed grew only one leaf. But a 3D reconstruction made using image processing and data analysis later revealed there were two.According to China's state-run Science and Technology Daily, the 2.6-kilogram LME cylinder measured 20 centimeters in length and 17 centimeters in diameter.Apart from cotton, it also carried potato and arabidopsis seeds, fruit fly eggs, and yeast. These were all kept in Earth-like conditions except for microgravity and lunar radiation.Xie told CNN that Chinese scientists had hoped the LME would raise seeds and hatch flies to create a stable biosphere to inform food production on the moon.Xie said the LME experienced erratic temperature fluctuations, forcing scientists to terminate the experiment and shut down the power.The shutdown left the seeds and eggs unprotected in the lunar night, when temperatures dropped to a low of minus 190 degrees Celsius, according to the China Daily.IEEE Spectrum reports the cotton leaves were dead within one lunar daytime, or 14.5 Earth days.Xie told IEEE Spectrum that the team had wanted to put a small tortoise in the LME to research the effects of the moon's low gravity on animals. But oxygen inside the craft would have been usable to tortoises for only 20 days.The tortoise for sure dodged a bullet on this one.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 02:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/15/3906155/3906155_EE5BD20F243D4FBB8C0207D0B4C5A73E_191015_3906155_China_grows_cotton_plant_on_the_moon_in_biologic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D24/06B/D2406B9B6DD47D864137538AE8F1835D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china cotton plant, china cotton on moon, china moon mission, china lunar mission, china lunar probe, far side of the moon, dark side of the moon, chang'e 4, chang'e 4 spacecraft, china lands on moon, lunar micro ecosystem, LME, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906145</guid>
      <title>Hard Rock Hotel collapse in New Orleans leaves 2 dead, 1 missing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS  At least two people have been killed after a partially constructed hotel collapsed in New Orleans on Saturday.According to the Times-Picayune, 112 workers were at the construction site of the 18-story Hard Rock Hotel in New Orleans on Saturday morning.Around 9:10 a.m., the upper six to eight floors of the half-built structure collapsed, raining down debris and knocking over a construction crane in the process.According to CNN, two people were killed in the incident, and at least 30 were hospitalized. Search teams are also looking for a missing worker that may still be trapped inside the building.Officials say the site is still highly unstable, so a second collapse is still possible.According to the Times-Picayune, the threat of further collapse prompted officials to evacuate nearby buildings on Sunday night. Authorities have not said what caused the structure to fail, but promised a "relentless" investigation into the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 02:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/15/3906145/3906145_90AEC3FB7CE64A8F9465EE70101B82B5_191015_3906145_Hard_Rock_Hotel_collapse_in_New_Orleans_leaves_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8E0/5E3/8E05E3F08787D95E1EF7CCAD251087E7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hard rock hotel collapse, new orleans construction collapse, hard rock collapse, new orleans collapse, deadly collapse, hard rock hotel, hard rock hotel new orleans, new orleans, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907029</guid>
      <title>Chinese speed reading contest will leave you at a loss for words</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  On the hunt for a real page turner? These students in Beijing taking part in a quantum speed reading contest will probably leave you at a loss for words.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 13:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/16/3907029/3907029_A652F7C3A89B4DB2AC747FFA6A857710_191016_3907029_Chinese_speed_reading_contest_will_leave_you_at__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FCC/5E5/FCC5E5750C2D91BD1DACB68AE1654E05.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China speed reading contest, China quantum speed reading contest, QSR, quantum speed reading, China speed reading contest hoax, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907020</guid>
      <title>Lebron gets destroyed for his first 'misinformed' comments on China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  LeBron James spoke Monday night for the first time about China's temper tantrum over Rocket GM Daryl Morey's Hong Kong tweet, unfortunately he decided to blast Morey and side with the authoritarian dictatorship in Beijing instead.With one pre-game press conference at Staples Center, James' carefully crafted public image went down the toilet in the blink of an eye.   According to For the Win, Lebron said he wasn't educated enough about the Hong Kong protests to talk about it when the Lakers were in China.And then King Jamessorry, Emperor Jamesopened his trap and delivered this hot mess:"We all talk about freedom of speech  yets, we do have freedom of speech. But at times, there are ramifications for the negative that can happen when you're not thinking about others and you're only thinking about yourself. I don't believe  I don't want to get into a  feud with Daryl Morey but I believe he wasn't educated on the situation at hand. And he spoke. And so many people could have been harmed, not only financially but emotionally, physically and spiritually."What LeBron was trying to say was that all he cares about is money, while throwing everything we hold dear in the country under the bus. James went on, "so just be careful with what we tweet and what we say and what we do, even though, yes, we do have freedom of speech, but there can be a lot of negative that comes with that, too."    Oh the irony. LeBron's bootlicking comments received instant blowback, which caused him to then have to jump on Twitter and try to explain his panda hugging comments.    Apparently a great receding hairline, also comes great receding responsibility.Maybe it's time for LeBron to pack it up and move over to Beijing where they really get to enjoy the freedoms of speech and are really into "education."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 13:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/16/3907020/3907020_C5147BB12BE14E9B865BA0BFD1991D46_191016_3907020_Lebron_gets_destroyed_for_his_first__misinformed_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C1D/BD4/C1DBD43B8921F7C2617723F3A7F084B7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Lebron James, Lebron James China comment, Lebron James pro china comment, NBA China, Daryl Morey Hong Kong, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906932</guid>
      <title>CBA highlights will make you fall in love with basketball again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Who needs the NBA in China when you have the high flying ballers of the Chinese Basketball Association?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/16/3906932/3906932_3DDA6142BD094F54AA06A1FDE513992D_191016_3906932_CBA_highlights_will_make_you_fall_in_love_with_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AC1/955/AC19557B5C64D7CA7DA4A6546D6B7011.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[CBA highlights, Chinese Basketball Association, China NBA, NBA vs CBA, China basketball, basketball highlights, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906637</guid>
      <title>Pet lion unleashed on Pakistani man for demanding wages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAHORE, PAKISTAN  An electrician in Pakistan found himself on the receiving end of some very sharp claws after demanding fair pay.The Khaleej Times reports that electrician Mohammad Rafique had been hired to do work on a congregation hall in Lahore. When Rafique finished and asked to be paid, caretaker Ali Raza told him to come back later.He did, but the caretaker kept delaying the payment. When the electrician persisted in his demand for wages, Raza got annoyed and decided to sic his pet lion on the poor man, who ended up with wounds on his face and arm.Some folks passing by happened to hear Rafique's screams for help, and somehow managed to rescue him from the beast.The electrician didn't file a complaint immediately after because Raza promised to provide treatment for the injuries he got from the lion mauling.But when the caretaker made like the first time and refused to fork over the money, he lodged the complaint.Raza the caretaker is now facing a case of attempted murder, which isn't a problem he can fix by unleashing a lion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/16/3906637/3906637_D7DD7570C6EA43B7A2A61A9E467C73FF_191016_3906637_Pet_lion_unleashed_on_Pakistani_man_for_demandin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6A6/E35/6A6E3500305CC5287FD40DFF0128423D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Lion unleashed on man, pet lion, lion, lion unleashed on electrician, man sics lion on electrician, pakistan lion, pakistan man, pakistan lion wages, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3906626</guid>
      <title>Chinese propaganda app on Xi harvests data from users' phones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  A new report from German cyber security firm Cure53 in collaboration with the U.S.-based Open Technology Fund has found that Chinese app Study the Great Nation contains code that allows authorities to access users' phone data including messages, photos, internet history and phone contacts.The app was launched in January and consists of news articles, videos and quizzes about President Xi Jinping's ideology, called "Xi Jinping Thought."Users earn points for reading and commenting on different articles on the app. They are also able to compete with each other as there is a scoreboard.Cure53 said the propaganda app has become the most downloaded free program in China, with more than a 100 million downloads.The terms and conditions for the app, which was developed by Alibaba and the Chinese Communist Party, allow for it to have access to take photos and videos, collect location data, activate audio recording and even dial phone numbers. The app can also collect information from 960 different apps present on the users' phone, including apps related to shopping and traveling.Cure53 observed the Android version of the app and found that it was actively collecting data on numerous running services and then storing the data onto the phone's external storage.However, the report said it found "no evidence" that this information was being used.The security firm's report also found that the code also permits "superuser" privileges. This could allow authorities to download any software, modify files or even log users' keystrokes.Adam Lynn, research director at the Open Technology Fund, told the Washington Post it is very uncommon for an app to require that much access to a device. He added that there is no reason for an app to have these privileges, "unless you're doing something you're not supposed to do."When contacted by the Washington Post, China's State Council Information Office said, "We learned from those who run the Study the Great Nation app that there is no such thing as you have mentioned."Alibaba declined to comment and referred the Washington Post's questions to China's Propaganda Department.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 02:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/16/3906626/3906626_D20A7C7AFFF3488786410F52785052DE_191016_3906626_Chinese_propaganda_app_on_Xi_harvests_data_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China Study the Great Nation app, Study the Great Nation, chinese app enables spying, chinese propaganda app enables spying, chinese government cyber espionage, chinese tech enables spying,  chinese propaganda app, chinese app on Xi Jinping, chinese app spying, chinese spyware app, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907661</guid>
      <title>Kim Jong-un forces horse to take his big butt up sacred mountain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNT  PAEKTU, NORTH KOREA  North Korea's chubby little dictator Kim Jong-un has climbed the Hermit Kingdom's tallest mountainon horseback.According to BBC, North Korea's official Central News Agency released a bunch of IG-friendly snaps of tons and tons of fun plopped on top of a white horse galloping up the slopes of snow-covered Mount Paektu[a].   The Beebs says Fats likes to haul his big behind up the 2,750-meter high mountain ahead of major announcements. According to USA Today, the mountain and the white horse are both symbols associated with the Kim family's line of fun-loving dictators.According to KCNA, "his march on horseback in Mt. Paektu is a great event of weighty importance in the history of the Korean revolution." Hahaweighty."Sitting on the horseback atop Mt. Paektu, collected with deep emotion the road of arduous struggle he covered for the great cause of building the most power country, with faith and will as firm as Mt. Paektu."     USA Today reported that Rocket Man previously visited the mountain before offing his uncle in 2013 and before entering talks with South Korea and the U.S. in 2018. But honestly though, the white horse is a good look for Kim. He should think about keeping it long term.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 14:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/17/3907661/3907661_62350AF34A264D049F5FE3B08094A287_191017_3907661_Kim_Jong_un_forces_horse_to_take_his_big_butt_up_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/791/E57/791E576B45D1F7821AF7DE0B3EF9B53E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Kim Jong-Un, North Korea Kim Jong-un, Kim Jong-un rides horse, Kim Jong-un rides horse up mountain, Kim Jong-un Mt. Paektu, Mount Paektu, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907652</guid>
      <title>HK protest leader Jimmy Sham attacked by men with hammers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONGKOK, HONG KONG  A prominent leader in the Hong Kong protests is in stable condition following an attack by unknown assailants.  According to the Hong Kong Free Press, Civil Human Rights Front leader Jimmy Sham was en route to a meeting in Mong Kok on Tuesday night when he was attacked by four to five men wielding hammers.The South China Morning Post reports that fellow CHRF member Figo Chan said bystanders attempted to save Sham during the ambush, but one of the attackers pointed a knife at them.According to police, officers found Sham in the street bleeding from his head and arms. His assailants fled in a car, and as yet remain unidentified.He luckily suffered no damage to his brain or bones, reports the Hong Kong Free Press, and was taken to a nearby hospital. The attack on Sham is the second to occur since the anti-government protests in Hong Kong began. In August, he and a friend were attacked at a restaurant in Kowloon by two masked men with a baseball bat and steel rod. Sham was unharmed, but his friend sustained serious bruises from being hit with the bat.The CHRF strongly condemned the incident, and accused the attackers of spreading political terror to threaten people from going out onto the streets and fighting for their rights.The South China Morning Post reports that Democratic Party lawmaker Lam Cheuk-ting described the assault as clearly politically motivated, and accused police of failing to protect opposition politicians and activists.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 14:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/17/3907652/3907652_DFC7C878A0034FCE9484A7D1D7E2FD45_191017_3907652_HK_protest_leader_Jimmy_Sham_attacked_by_men_wit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/391/93D/39193D9D0AD54CA60E27B0AB2A5340A7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Jimmy sham attack, jimmy sham assault, hong kong protest, hong kong protest leader, jimmy sham, civil human rights front, CHRF, hong kong attack, hong kong assault, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907432</guid>
      <title>NASA unveils new spacesuit designs for next lunar mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA has unveiled next generation spacesuits for the space agency's 2024 Artemis III lunar mission.One of the spacesuits, called the Exploration Extravehicular Mobility Unit, or xEMU, will allow for an increased range of movement for the arms, wrists, hips and knees while astronauts are on the lunar surface as the suit uses bearings instead of zippers.The xEMU spacesuit features a backpack called the Portable Life Support System, similar to the one used during the Apollo moon landing missions in the 1960s and 1970s.According to NASA's website, the spacesuit's communication system inside the helmet has been redesigned to include multiple microphones on the inner part of the upper torso that will automatically be activated as the astronaut speaks.NASA says the new spacesuits will allow astronauts to perform longer spacewalks, withstand moon dust and the moon's extreme temperatures ranging from negative 250 degrees to 250 degrees Fahrenheit. The space agency said the increased mobility of the astronauts is to perform different scientific tasks such as analyzing moon rocks or planting scientific instruments.Though one thing remains the same. Astronauts will still be required to wear a diaper-like garment during long spacewalks just in case they need to relieve themselves.NASA also debuted its second spacesuit, called the Orion Crew Survival System, which will be used by astronauts during launch and reentry in the Orion spacecraft.The suit features a lighter helmet which connects to the communications system more easily, improved thermal protection and a new interface that removes carbon dioxide and supplies air to the crew members wearing the suit. NASA says each astronaut will have a customized spacesuit to ensure a better fit and a better range of motion.These lunar missions are part of NASA's plan to eventually make its way from the moon to Mars in order for humans to explore the red planet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 09:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/17/3907432/3907432_A0EC90F512C44E8187553F39ACCFBA7B_191017_3907432_NASA_unveils_new_spacesuit_designs_for_next_luna_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/895/853/8958536860C18C17C7332E365733A557.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA spacesuits, moon spacesuit, nasa new moon spacesuit, future moon spacesuits, nasa new spacesuits, new nasa spacesuits for the moon, nasa spacesuit design, nasa spacesuit 2019, NASA Extravehicular Mobility Unit, xEMU, Orion Crew Survival System, new spacesuits for moon, Next Generation Spacesuit, new Artemis spacesuits, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907356</guid>
      <title>Xi secures another win for China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Xi travels to Russia to tell a man about his new idea, a flag competition.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 07:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/17/3907356/3907356_B994E117225442D7AF07B2E6BD39D053_191017_3907356_Xi_secures_another_win_for_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7EE/A18/7EEA18C598CC189D0BC2C038313EA62F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Xi comedy, Xi spoof, Xi parody, Learning with Xi, Xi with subs, Xi with subtitles, Xi Jinping comedy, Xi Jinping joke, Chinese president with funny subs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3908281</guid>
      <title>Woman lost in Aussie wilderness found after CCTV spots giant 'SOS'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEDAN, AUSTRALIA  A camper that went missing in the Australian outback is now back in civilization after her giant SOS message was spotted by a man's remote security cam.According to ABC News, Deborah Pilgrim was last seen Sunday morning at a campsite with friends on a rural property near Sedan, South Australia.Authorities searched for the 55-year-old for three days, with no luck.Poor Deborah had gone for a walk but quickly found herself lost in the bush. While wandering around, she came across a remote cottage, which, though empty, was fitted with a security cam.Cottage owner Neil Marriott had just had the cams installed after several break-ins. On Tuesday afternoon, he checked the footage and saw a large SOS on the ground that hadn't been there before. He put two and two together and alerted the cops. It was already dark when officers arrived at the site. They found a jacket, but no Deborah.They continued looking and eventually found her on a neighboring property. The poor woman had was about seven kilometers from where she was reported missing.  She was taken to a nearby hospital to be checked, but appeared to be in good health, according to police.Good thing the creatures of the outback didn't get to her first, either, or it would've been a very different ending.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 14:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/18/3908281/3908281_DE57F83E53FD49BAAE861D75681DE71F_191018_3908281_Woman_lost_in_Aussie_wilderness_found_after_CCTV_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EAF/B49/EAFB49E3A2F2522FCC14E61C4C94A4A8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[SOS, giant SOS, SOS message, SOS message in sand, missing Aussie woman, missing camper, Missing in outback, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3908253</guid>
      <title>Trump picks own struggling golf resort to host next year's G-7</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  President Donald Trump has decided to hold next year's G-7 summit at one of his own resorts down in Florida becauseyeah, why not!?According to Politico, Trump's gut instincts to inject millions of dollars into his financially struggling Trump National Doral Miami resort puts him at risk of violating the Constitution.  Politico reported that according to acting White House Chief of Staff Mick Mulvaney, it was Trump himself who told his staff to consider Doral when they began considering possible summit sites. Apparently, after looking at 12 locations in California, Colorado, Hawaii, Florida, North Carolina, Michigan, Tennessee and Utah, Trump's guys decided to keep it in-house. Mulvaney actually told reporters that Doral was "far and away, the best physical facility for this meeting."Mulvaney continued with the blatant buttkissing, blurting out, "in fact I was talking to one of the advance teams when they came back and I said, 'What was it like?' And they said, 'You're not going to believe this but it's almost like they built this facility to host this type of event.'"The chief of staff said the summit would be made available "at cost" and that using Trump's OWN resort would save millions of dollars. If Trump is so rich and successful, why doesn't he just host the summit for free then?The New York Daily News reported that according to business filings, Doral has been bleeding cash, with its net operating income plummeting 69 percent in the past two years.  The filings also show that room rates, golf and overall revenue are all down. But not to worry folks, there's clearly no conflict of interest going on here. Golf anyone?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 13:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/18/3908253/3908253_601A8792994742D4B04DC52AC2552E4B_191018_3908253_Trump_picks_own_struggling_golf_resort_to_host_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FEE/F0B/FEEF0B4C5D02BE57E00171EC03756DCC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Trump resort G-7 summit, Trump picks own resort for G-7, Trump National Doral G-7, President Trump, Donald Trump, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3908250</guid>
      <title>China bans exports of black clothing to Hong Kong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  The brains up in Beijing have come up with an ingenious plan to quell the protests in Hong Kongthey're banning exports of black clothing.  For the last four months, anti-government protesters have taken to the streets in their black t-shirts, black jeans, black kicks, and black face masks. According to the SCMP, courier companies in Guangdong province, which borders Hong Kong, have said they've been told to stop deliveries of black clothing and other attire worn by protesters. According to a Guangdong courier company PHYBUY statement, Chinese customs sent out a long list of things that are now no-no's for Hong Kong."They include yellow helmets, yellow umbrellas, flags, flagpoles, poster banners, gloves, masks, black T-shirts, metal rods, fluorescent tubes and bludgeon clubs."  And even longer list of banned items by Guangdong-based EXPRESS includes: foodstuffs, liquids, powder, gases, counterfeit brand products, big machines, helmets, umbrellas, wrist bands, towels, safety vests, speakers, amplifiers, trestles, walkie-talkies, drones, black shirts and other clothing, goggles, metal beads, metal balls, horticulture scissors, metal chains, torches, binoculars, and remote-controlled toys.People mailing things also have to use their real names. Here's a question though, what happens if the protesters start wearing a different color? Or the colors of the Chinese flag? But anyways, banning black. Yeah, that should totally work.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/18/3908250/3908250_11AAAD0DDC92455DABA9A4098C4996A4_191018_3908250_China_bans_exports_of_black_clothing_to_Hong_Kon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/60C/6E1/60C6E1484D7B3F1133140EB3498ACD71.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China bans black clothing exports, black clothing exports, China bans black clothing shipments, China protests, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3907802</guid>
      <title>Texas prisoners caught escaping jail for whiskey and cell phones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEAUMONT, TEXAS  Four prisoners who repeatedly escaped jail only to return with booze and cell phones were caught in the act and promptly taken into custody.According to a Facebook post by officials at Jefferson County, four men at the Federal Prison Complex in Beaumont, Texas decided to escape prison grounds but were caught by investigators and U.S. Marshals hiding behind the complex on October 11 around 10:30 p.m.The men tried to make a run for it, but were caught and taken back to the prison.Officials also seized contraband the guys were carrying, including whiskey bottles and cell phones.It's not clear how or why they obtained these items.Julian Lemus, Robert Young, Leo Martinez and Silvstre Rico were booked into the LaSalle Correctional Facility on charges of escape.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 02:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/18/3907802/3907802_194DDED240974A79A2DA4074705B3237_191018_3907802_Texas_prisoners_caught_escaping_jail_for_whiskey_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/223/6E0/2236E0BCCE27AE94B46EF45ED5843335.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Prison escape, prisoners caught escaping for whiskey and cell phones, breaking out of jail texas, inmates escaping jail for whiskey and cell phones, inmates break out of prison, inmates try to escape prison, prison escape texas, prison escape in beaumont texas, texas prison escape 2019, inmates escape and return to jail with alcohol and cell phone, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3909478</guid>
      <title>Great white shark bitten in the head by giant great white shark</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH ATLANTIC OCEAN  Researchers found a great white shark with head injuries that were apparently inflicted by an even bigger shark in the North Atlantic Ocean.OCEARCH said in a Facebook post that its scientists named the shark Vimy before they tagged and released him.OCEARCH founding chairman Chris Fischer told the McClatchy news group Vimy bears scars on the lower jaw and fresh wounds on the top of his head."Fischer said the new injuries appeared to be the toothiwork of something significantly bigger than Vimy's 12 feet.Vimy, weighing about 1,200 pounds and measuring less than 13 feet, is actually smaller than the average great white shark.Fischer told McClatchy that Vimy could have been trying to mate with a female shark before a larger male rival bit him.Fischer was quoted as saying, "Maybe Vimy was just the small guy on the block."Another possibility was that Vimy tried to make the moves on a much bigger female shark that chomped on his head instead."Vimy could also have been attacked when trying to snack on a seal that the proverbial bigger fish had its beady eyes on.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 13:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/10/21/3909478/3909478_9967C77681ED4CE493E44D49887AE251_191021_3909478_Great_white_shark_bitten_in_the_head_by_giant_gr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/439/8A1/4398A1D8E0D0230BFC8904955C3BF995.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[great white shark, great white shark attacked, gr