<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 15:00:01 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3219721</guid>
      <title>Third structure discovered inside Temple of KuKulkan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A hidden third temple was discovered this month inside the Kukulkan Pyramid, one of the world’s most famous ancient structures. Researchers used a 3D scanning technique called electrical resistivity tomography to find the 10-meter-tall structure inside the Temple of Kukulkan in Yutucan, Mexico.  Experts believe this third structure was constructed between the years 550 and 800, reported the BBC, citing researchers.Also known as El Castillo, the Kukulkan was already known to have been made of up other two temples. According to an AFP report, these consist of a 30-meter-tall external structure with another 20-meter-tall pyramid inside of it. It is thought that the new structures were added to cover decaying ones or to welcome new leaders.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/30/3219721/3219721_97056CE72AC548FB8D016AE79D12B697_161130_3219721_Third_structure_discovered_inside_Temple_of_KuKu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D3D/840/D3D8409BB65B4F48973336E321E0D724_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3220552</guid>
      <title>This is what airports of the future might look like</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A U.K. company has released a concept of what airports might be like by the year 2040, and they may be a lot more efficient and passenger-friendly than the ones now.According to the company, passengers will be expected to check-in via self-service desks, which include biometric scanners that can scan passengers’ facial features, iris patterns and fingerprints in order to verify their identities. After check in, a biometric token will be issued and stored in the passenger's smartphone that serves as a boarding pass and ID. Luggage can be dropped at drop-off points.Laser molecular body scanners can detect even tiny-quantities of dangerous materials in passengers’ clothing or their luggage without the need for a body search.Passengers may buy duty-free goods from virtual shopping stations and have the goods delivered to their homes. However, passengers can still get help from virtual assistants when the airport enters self-service phase.Airport control is likely to be operated remotely outside the airport, with staff monitoring live video footage of the airport, similar to the system introduced Sweden. Other technologies, such as biometric scanners, are currently being trialled at Heathrow and Schiphol airports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 13:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/01/3220552/3220552_69F8D2C79F144595A174943AE59A9CFB_161201_3220552_This_is_what_airports_of_the_future_might_look_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EB3/641/EB36418FEA7C4D0A9CA29464F4EF3689_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3224360</guid>
      <title>Private German moon mission to inspect Apollo 17 rover</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team of scientists in Germany has developed a lunar rover that will soon fly to the moon and visit the legendary Apollo 17 Lunar Rover Vehicle.The rover is developed by the team called PTScientists, in collaboration with automaker Audi. Dubbed Audi Lunar Quattro, the rover is made of aluminium and titanium, and created almost entirely from 3D printing technology. It is equipped with 4-wheel drive technology, solar panels, rechargeable lithium ion batteries, as well as science-grade high-definition cameras.Two rovers will be carried by the ALINA spacecraft, which stands for the Autonomous Landing and Navigation Module. ALINA will also carry several other payloads, including a lunar plant growth experiment. It has not been confirmed, but a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket is reportedly will likely be used to transport the rovers into space.ALINA will touch down about 5 km from the Apollo 17 in the Taurus-Littrow valley. After landing on the moon, the two rovers will be deployed and will travel toward the Apollo 17 lunar rover. However, they are not allowed any closer than 200 meters of the Apollo rover, per NASA’s request. The rovers will send live HD pictures of the Apollo rover to Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 12:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/06/3224360/3224360_E7CF33B51B9C406A81FEA57CD7DD1EA4_161206_3224360_Private_German_moon_mission_to_inspect_Apollo_17_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/597/B4E/597B4E014AEA46708B6F16C7E803401A_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Ptscientists,audi lunar quattro,german moon mission,google lunar x-prize,space,moon,apollo 17,apollo 17 lunar roving vehicle,science,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3226296</guid>
      <title>Cameroon turns human waste into clean power in biogas project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Two towns in Cameroon have installed biogas systems to turn human waste into sustainable energy that can provide fuel and electricity for local communities.The project was initiated by Bioenergy-Cameroon, a non-governmental youth organization. Local students, especially female students, are trained on how to install and maintain innovative technology systems such as solar power and biogas mechanisms.According to Reuters, the system includes a septic tank, which is connected to a bio-digester at individual households. Human waste placed in the septic tank is converted into biogas inside the bio-digesters, which release energy into people’s homes for cooking and lighting.Reuters reports that more than 3,000 households and local schools in the towns of Buea and Bamenda have installed the biogas system. The Center for Environment and Development, an NGO in Cameroon, estimates that the biogas project may reduce greenhouse gas emissions in the vicinity by up to 60 percent.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 15:26:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/08/3226296/3226296_28FF41227B4E47E79360FF9DE1E8727C_161208_3226296_Cameroon_turns_human_waste_into_clean_power_in_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/38E/659/38E659DCB27F48C8BB58E8741AC60226_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Cameroon biogas project,buea biogas project,bamenda biogas project,biogas,clean energy,technology,bioenergy-cameroon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3230948</guid>
      <title>Scalp cooler reduces hair loss in chemotherapy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy may not have to suffer hair loss anymore, thanks to a ‘cooling cap’ technology.Chemotherapy drugs are designed to attack rapidly dividing cells, and as both cancer cells and hair cells divide rapidly, chemotherapy can cause damage to hair cells, which leads to hair loss.A cooling cap system was developed by scientists at Baylor College of Medicine. The system can lower the scalp temperature to about 66 degrees Fahrenheit. The low temperature constricts the blood vessels and reduces blood flow to the area by up to 40 percent. Less blood flow to the scalp means fewer chemotherapy drugs can attack the hair cells.“Hair loss takes a tremendous toll on the patient’s body image, and they no longer have the anonymity of hiding the disease; everyone can see that they’re sick,” Dr. Julie Nangia, assistant professor in the Lester and Sue Smith Breast Center at Baylor College of Medicine said in a press release. Researchers say the cooling caps should work on patients with solid tumors, but will not work for patients with leukemia or blood cancers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 13:56:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/13/3230948/3230948_3092E0D889A547A78E2813FA3F22A09B_161214_3230948_Scalp_cooler_reduces_hair_loss_in_chemotherapy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6AC/C51/6ACC511B7FC14683BED85A8703B5E1E2_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Scalp cooling cap,hair loss,alopecia,chemotherapy,cancer,Baylor College of Medicine,cancer side effects,cancer symptoms,chemotherapy side effects,chemo side effects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3236123</guid>
      <title>New car technology can recognize road signs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A new technology has enabled some cars to recognize road signs and alert the drivers when driving on congested roads.Volkswagen recently released its Dynamic Road Sign Display system, which is described as the driver’s “companion on board”. The system can automatically detect the traffic signs and display the signs on both multifunction display and on the navigation system unit display.The car is equipped with a forward facing mirror and a rain sensor. It can recognize important traffic signals such as speed limits, highway exits, no overtaking signs and end of motorway indicators.The on-board computer system cross-references the traffic signs detected by the camera, information from the navigation device and current vehicle data to make sure the information given to the driver is correct.The technology is also available on selected car models produced by companies such as Audi and Mercedes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 13:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/21/3236123/3236123_671777A11EEF497083AD0356929034B1_161221_3236123_New_car_technology_can_recognize_road_signs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1A6/521/1A652168097E469583B24B41EB9A312E_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Volkswagen sign assist,Dynamic Road Sign Display system,car technology,automobile technology,car recognizes road signs,smart car technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3236120</guid>
      <title>Floating Paris gym uses human energy to cruise down the Seine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[An Italian design firm has unveiled a floating gym that can cruise down the Seine river using the power generated by gym-goers.The project, known as Paris Navigation Gym, is developed by Carlo Ratti Associati in collaboration with Technogym, Terreform ONE and URBEM.The gym is a 20-meters-long boat and can host up to 45 people. It is equipped with Technogym’s ARTIS bikes that can harness human energy. The movement generated by the gym-goers are transferred into energy used to propel the gym boat.According to Carlo Ratti Associati, the gym also contains augmented-reality screens inside that shows the gym-goers of the amount of energy sourced from their workouts.The gym will inhabit the river all year long and the transparent glass can be opened in the summer to let in the breeze on River Seine.Although the gym is purely a concept for now, studies show it could be implemented in less than 18 months, reported BreakingNEWS.ie.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 13:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/21/3236120/3236120_B98BF01B6C47429CBFD26CDDFD7DD9FC_161221_3236120_Floating_Paris_gym_uses_human_energy_to_cruise_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/83F/FAF/83FFAF1955F24DF0897F8F094EE3F457_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Paris navigation gym,paris floating gym,floating gym uses human energy,carlo ratti associati,paris,technology,paris seine river]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3236118</guid>
      <title>U.S. surgeon general claims e-cigarettes harmful for young people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCKVILLE, MARYLAND  The U.S. surgeon general is calling for action on the use of e-cigarettes among young people, and has released a report emphasizing its harmful effects.E-cigarettes have been touted as a healthier alternative to regular smoking, which produce tar and carbon monoxide through burning.However, according to a report released by U.S. Surgeon General Vivek Murthy, it is now the most commonly used form of smoking among youth. A 900% increase has been reported among middle and high school students between 2011 and 2015.But e-cigarettes still contain the drug nicotine, which when exposed to developing teen brains, makes them more susceptible to addiction, mood disorders, and lower impulse control.Some claim e-cigarettes are a gateway to other tobacco products, with some evidence suggesting it may be linked to alcohol and drug use as well.Secondhand aerosol released into the air during vaping also has been found to contain potentially harmful, cancer-causing chemicals.The FDA already restricted the sale of vaping devices to minors under 18 in August, but Murthy believes further action is necessary. Murthy is calling for the inclusion of e-cigarettes in smoking bans, increases in taxes and price, and regulation of marketing practices that mostly target the youth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 13:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/21/3236118/3236118_1FBB01765763436CBBE50E8CA1A0B3D5_161221_3236118_U_S__surgeon_general_claims_e_cigarettes_harmful_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2FE/26C/2FE26C20755842A4AFEF1C23FDCEE8C8_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Vaping,e-cigarette,ecigarette,electronic cigarette,vaping culture,youth vaping,nicotine,smoking,tobacco,addiction]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3236914</guid>
      <title>$50 million fund set up to tackle deadbeat dams</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A $50 million fund will be devoted to help communities in the U.S. to remove old and unneeded dams in an attempt to restore rivers.The funding was provided by the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation to establish a 10 year program in order to remove obsolete dams and restore rivers across the West.“The Open Rivers Fund honors this legacy by boosting local efforts to remove aged dams that have broad support in the community. The safety, economic, and environmental benefits of removing these dams will be immediate and long-term,” Hewlett Foundation president Larry Kramer said in a press release.Three projects will be benefited by the funding, including the removal of the Matilija Dam in Ventura, California; a series of dams in Oregon’s Rogue River basin; and the Nelson Dam in Yakima River watershed in Washington.According to the New York Times, of the more than 80,000 dams in the U.S., more than 26,000 pose high safety hazards, the majority does not serve any real purpose while only about 1,750 produce hydropower.These deadbeat dams block the natural migration and spawning of some fish, threatening the ecosystem. They also block the movements of nutrients and sediment in the river, which deprives downstream estuaries of nutrient-rich water. The reduced water flow raises the temperature and results in algae bloom.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 14:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/22/3236914/3236914_8E202AC85C4443369E40BF2C2B601030_161222_3236914__50_million_fund_set_up_to_tackle_deadbeat_dams_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7F3/428/7F342840E1A44FF1AB95C37F28CFC135_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Deadbeat dams,deadbeat dams in us,deadbeat dams problems,dams problems,open river fund,matilija dam,oregon dams,hydropower]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3237658</guid>
      <title>Rolling guardrail could prevent fatal road accidents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A South Korean company has designed a rolling guardrail system that is almost unbreakable in accidents and thus could save lives more lives than traditional guardrails during serious auto accidents.South Korean company Evolution in Traffic Innovation (ETI) has named the guardrail as the “Rolling Barrier System”. It consists of rotating barrels made of ethylene-vinyl acetate and metal frames. Ethylene-vinyl acetate has excellent shock absorption power and is more durable than rubber or urethane.The guardrail has a luminescent quality which makes it highly visible to drivers during the night time.When a car hits the guardrail, the barrels rotate to convert shock energy from the vehicle into rotational energy. As a result, the car is propelled forward back onto the road rather than breaking through the barrier. The upper and lower frames of the guardrail can prevent both large and small vehicles’ steering systems from suffering functional loss.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 11:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/23/3237658/3237658_94E414BF69C34E4B8D7441C5873B3B7A_161223_3237658_Rolling_guardrail_could_prevent_fatal_road_accid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C52/806/C528067D4BC34564B80A454E6A56753A_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Evolution in traffic innovation,eti south korea,south korea rolling barrier system,rolling guardrail south korea,road safety,auto accident prevention]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3238681</guid>
      <title>NASA&#x2019;s space bound robot will fix satellites</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In the summer of 2020, NASA will launch the Restore-L, a robotic spacecraft tasked with carrying out maintenance and repair on satellites orbiting earth.According to information posted on the Restore-L section of NASA Robotic Servicing Mission website, it will navigate Earth’s orbit using a combination of advanced hardware and algorithms at speeds of over 16,000 miles per hour. This technology will allow it to calculate how to connect with a satellite orbiting the earth at the same speed.Restore-L will use dexterous mechanical arms to service satellites in low earth orbit. This service will reportedly involve a maintenance check and repairs as well as redeployment of the satellite. The robotic spacecraft could also upgrade satellites and, all-in-all, prolong the lifespan of those already in space.NASA awarded a $127 million contract to California-based Space Systems/Loral build Restore-L, reported Vice’s technology news website Motherboard.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 15:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/24/3238681/3238681_0A754D53C13A4E51B954DA99339C757B_161224_3238681_NASA___s_space_bound_robot_will_fix_satellites_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5EA/EC7/5EAEC75314084A80B13FA672E5BC40A6_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Space robot,repair robot,robots in space,nasa,restore-l,space systems,space repair,NASA,NASA robot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3241082</guid>
      <title>Personal submersible can transport divers 95 meters deep</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Dutch engineering company Ortega Submersibles has developed an underwater vehicle that can ferry divers to depths of 95 meters  more than twice a deep as most recreational divers can swim.The vessel is named the named the Mk. 1C. According to information posted on the Ortega Submersibles website and a press kit from the company, the submersible can  carry three people and 350 liters of cargo, meaning divers can carry more air or equipment as required.The 570 kg vessel is powered by two 10 kilowatt hour electric thrusters. These propel it at speeds of up to 16.7 kilometers per hour on the ocean surface, and 20 kilometers per hour underwater. The submersible has lightweight batteries that allow it to operate for 11 hours.The Mk. 1C also features on-board navigational equipment for below and above water as well as on-board air supply for each passenger. Ortega says its designs are based on the World War II Royal Air Force motorized submersible canoe project Sleeping Beauty. These were used by British forces for clandestine reconnaissance missions.Recreational scuba divers can usually swim to depths of between 30 and 40 meters depending on their training agency.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 12:27:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/28/3241082/3241082_3305F92ED53745A98D5702CC04F0EEF0_161228_3241082_Personal_submersible_can_transport_divers_95_met_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7EC/516/7EC516DA7D464E70AAA54DFEE3C0D85C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Awesome technology inventions,ortega submersibles,ortega mk. 1c,ortega mk1 c,submersible,personal submarine,MSC sleeping beauty]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3241081</guid>
      <title>Futuristic UFO-shaped houseboat to set sail by 2018</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Italian mini yacht manufacturer Jet Capsule has come out with an updated design for their sleek, floating villa that’s set to be the home of the future.Designed by 34-year-old Pierpaolo Lazzarini, the aptly named UFO 2.0 or Unidentified Floating Object is a houseboat that’s shaped like an alien flying saucer.According to the company’s website, the UFO yacht is equipped with twin 80-horsepower engines, with a maximum speed of up to 10 miles per hour. Built-in solar panels, wind and water turbines are meant to generate enough electricity to fully sustain the vessel, with excess energy being stored in a 16 battery array. The 314-square-meter houseboat will be made from carbon fiber and fiberglass and have three levels. The upper deck will house the controls as well as a hot tub and desk. The first level will consist of a kitchen and bathroom, while a submerged level will hold the bedroom and another bathroom.Its enormous size means the only way to transport the UFO yacht is via military helicopters.Caters News reports that the floating home can be used amid different conditions around the world, and is unsinkable even in rough seas. The external deck is customizable, and the vessel itself can be used for different purposes: a floating restaurant, gym, even a resort.The UFO yacht is expected to be available by 2018. For now, a Kickstarter campaign is underway to raise one million euros to fund the project.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 12:26:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/28/3241081/3241081_D10EE937F5D74ABBA92A31DA9546124A_161228_3241081_Futuristic_UFO_shaped_houseboat_to_set_sail_by_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AE9/CFB/AE9CFB95FFA14093B029FBD2A32BE772_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Ufo yacht,ufo houseboat,ufo floating home,unidentified floating object,jet capsule,pierpaolo lazzarini,houseboat,homes of the future,futuristic home,houseboat,off the grid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3241080</guid>
      <title>New Delhi attempts to clear air pollution with jet engines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A group of scientists led by an MIT professor hopes that an innovative idea can help clear the thick smog that plagues India’s capital city.Researcher Moshe Alamaro and his team will use old jet engines in an attempt to blast air pollution out of New Delhi’s atmosphere, the Times of India reported.The jet engines will be taken to a coal-fired power station and turned on, facing skyward. The engines generate a nozzle speed that’s more or less equal to the speed of sound, which the researchers believe will push smog out of the atmosphere, BBC News reported.During the winter, Delhi experiences a temperature inversion, which traps pollution near the ground. But the scientists said the jet engines have enough power to blast emissions through this lid of warm air. Around 60 percent of India’s energy is provided by coal-fired power plants, which contributes to terrible air pollution in the country’s cities. This pollution is linked to millions of asthma cases, respiratory diseases and thousands of deaths each year, according to the Times of India.The level of harmful fine particulate matter in Delhi’s air last winter reached 15 times the Indian government’s safe level, and more than 90 times the level considered safe by the World Health Organization.The researchers said one jet engine can handle emissions from a 1,000 megawatt capacity power plant. The scientists also said the fuel emissions from the jet engines will be negligible compared to the amount of pollution they can clear, and are working to reduce noise pollution during the experiment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 12:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/28/3241080/3241080_403C43D8B80C464E9E8FCA92B18F6722_161228_3241080_New_Delhi_attempts_to_clear_air_pollution_with_j_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7C8/C40/7C8C40E51C8C4A57A9D6E1BE53E30E50_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Delhi fog,delhi air pollution,delhi air quality,jet engine blast,jet engines blast smog,jet engines blast pollution,india pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3242178</guid>
      <title>New York&#x2019;s Second Avenue subway will open on Jan. 1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[After almost a century of delays, the first phase of the Second Avenue subway is set to open for service on Jan. 1, officials at the Metropolitan Transportation Authority said. The new line is an extension of the Q line, which currently stops at 57th Street and Seventh Avenue and will run along Manhattan’s East Side, the New York Times reported. Beginning in January, Q trains will travel to a station at Lexington Avenue and 63rd Street and then to three new stations at 72nd, 86th and 96th Streets.They have been under construction since 2007, although planning for the project as a whole dates all the way back to 1929, according to the Wall Street Journal. The first phase of the project cost around $4.4 billion, reported the New York Times. The MTA is expecting the new route to carry 200,000 riders each day, which should ease overcrowding on the No. 4, 5 and 6 lines along the Lexington Avenue route, which carry 1.3 million commuters daily, AM New York reported. The second phase of the project is in the initial planning stages, and would extend the line to 125th Street in Harlem, according to the New York Times. However, the second phase will cost billions of dollars and take several years to complete, while plans to extend the line to Lower Manhattan are less certain.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 18:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/29/3242178/3242178_51F7A72188894EF0A55E2BB460F940C5_161229_3242178_New_York___s_Second_Avenue_subway_will_open_on_J_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B95/162/B95162FB93764C889F5279790570F1A1_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,New york subway,mta,architecture,infrastructure,city planning,metro transit authority,second avenue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3242676</guid>
      <title>Inside Apple&#x2019;s $5 billion new headquarters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple’s new Campus 2 headquarters is expected to open in early 2017, according to Mashable.The main building is a ring-shaped, four-storied structure that looks like a huge spaceship. The site covers 176 acres, or about the size of 100 soccer fields.At over 1,500 feet, the main building is greater in diameter than the Empire State Building is tall, and wider than the Pentagon. More than 3,000 sheets of curved glass cover the main building, which is a perfect circle.The site will be be powered completely by renewable energy, including solar power and biofuels. Around 80 percent of the site is green space, complete with jogging and cycling trails.Some 13,000 Apple employees will work at the new headquarters, which has seven different cafes. A thousand bicycles will be available for staff to get around the campus, which will be planted with 7,000 trees.The campus will have a 1,000-seat auditorium, a 100,000-square-foot fitness center, and 300,000 square feet of research and development facilities.Parking garages above and below ground have space for about 14,000 vehicles, while a visitor center offers views over the entire campus. The total cost to build the Apple Campus 2 is estimated to be $5 billion. That figure is equal to around 2 percent of the company’s $215 billion in total cash reserves as of January 2016, according to Macworld.The Apple Campus 2 will be the world’s fifth most expensive building and quite possibly the world’s coolest office.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 13:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/12/30/3242676/3242676_266855266D094512AADB354B4974A75D_161230_3242676_Inside_Apple___s__5_billion_new_headquarters_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/715/C30/715C30CEA9A14DBA87014265B3A61781_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Apple,apple campus 2,apple new headquarters,apple new hq,apple campus tour,apple campus january 2017,apple campus 2017]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
