<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 19:31:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3454021</guid>
      <title>Bali's Mt Agung volcano looks like it's gonna blow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALI, INDONESIA  The Mount Agung volcano in Bali, Indonesia is expected to erupt.Indonesian officials have marked several danger zones for a potential Mount Agung eruption and have evacuated over 75,000 people in the past days.According to the Guardian, hundreds of tremors have been noted near the volcano each day. If this continues, experts expect an eruption is imminent.The most deadly threat resulting from it would be pyroclastic flows, a superheated killer gas that lays waste to everything in its path. The gas is laden with volcanic matter such ash and rocks and can travel up to 450 miles per hour.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 09:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/02/3454021/3454021_7FCA73B9AB9B40769801BF82DE872C5A_171002_3454021_Bali_s_Mt_Agung_volcano_looks_like_it_s_gonna_bl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/89A/E11/89AE116A8F26FF3A6002054A24BD98D2"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bali volcano eruption 2017, bali mt agung volcano, mt agung eruption, bali erupton, bali volcano, volcano in bali, eruption explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3453939</guid>
      <title>Airbus A380 engine disintegrates mid-air flying over Atlantic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  An Air France flight en route from Paris to Los Angeles was forced to make a slight detour when one of its engines fell apart over the Atlantic.One of the four engines on the Airbus A380 flight AF66 failed as the aircraft was west of Greenland on Saturday, the BBC reported. The plane was carrying 496 passengers and 24 crew at the time of the incident, an Air France spokesperson told AFP, according to BBC.One of the passengers, David Rehmar, a former plane mechanic, said he thought it was probably a fan failure. Rehmar said there was a sudden movement followed by a loud noise, which caused a lot of people on the plane to freak out.Pilots quickly shut the failed engine down and were able to stabilize the aircraft within 30 seconds.  The Air France flight flew for about an hour on three engines before arriving at Goose Bay Airport in eastern Canada. Two 777s were eventually sent from Montreal to pick up the passengers and take them the rest of the way to L.A.The cause of the engine failure is still unknown and currently being investigated.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 07:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/02/3453939/3453939_6D116451EFB84480BA9CC3E429A981A9_171002_3453939_Airbus_A380_engine_disintegrates_mid_air_flying__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4D3/79A/4D379AAF909F56AE7AA22E895B862B99"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Airbus plane loses engine, Air France flight loses engine, airplane engine fail, plane loses engine, plane loses engine cover, Airbus A380 engine falls apart]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3453899</guid>
      <title>Czech brewery uses crayfish with smart sensors to check water purity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PROTIVIN, CZECH REPUBLIC  A Czech beer brewery has enlisted some curious creatures to help maintain the purity of their water supply.Reuters reports that Protivin Brewery in the Czech Republic's South Bohemian region equipped crayfish with high-tech biosensors that monitor their heartbeat and movement.The crayfish were placed in tanks, which were pumped with water from the same natural spring source the brewery uses to make its beers.Crayfish are able to detect pollutants or impurities in the water, and react to it with changes in their body or behavior.A computer analyzes the data and flags down changes in water quality when three or more crayfish change their pulse activity  with results coming in within 3 minutes.Scientists at South Bohemia University have patented the water system, and plan to upgrade the technology to include a special crayfish-heart monitoring camera.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 06:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/02/3453899/3453899_78295FB9C35742198D0A3A0BBF38042F_171002_3453899_Czech_brewery_uses_crayfish_with_smart_sensors_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0DF/08A/0DF08A830DF7036C9F8CCCAA0BB9B045"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, crayfish, biosensor, czech brewery, crayfish sensor, czech beer, beer, pure water, water purity, impurities, spring water, protivin brewery, protivin, czech republic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3453884</guid>
      <title>Russia and the U.S. team up to build lunar space station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON / MOSCOW  NASA and Russia's space agency Roscosmos will team up to work on a new space station near the moon.Space agencies from Japan, Europe and Canada are also interested in working on the project that is currently at the conceptual stage of design.According to Popular Science, the two agencies last month signed an agreement to work on the Deep Space Gateway at the International Aeronautics Congress in Adelaide, Australia. The proximity of the station to the moon would create opportunities for lunar missions and future deep space exploration such as missions to Mars, and beyond.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 05:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/02/3453884/3453884_C54A6CB46CAD4103BCCEC6E27336C164_171002_3453884_Russia_and_the_U_S__team_up_to_build_lunar_space_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0D9/628/0D9628381F00BACBC94F0F553BD3F7AA"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, moon space station, russia and usa friendship, nasa, roscosmos, lunar space station, deep space gateway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3453840</guid>
      <title>Model's eyeball tattoo goes dreadfully wrong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OTTAWA, CANADA Model Catt Gallinger, 24, was recently convinced by a tattoo artist to get her eyeball tattooed, but the procedure went very, very wrong.NEWSWEEKhttp://bit.ly/2xC6zS4]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 04:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/02/3453840/3453840_4BDFE2786D884779B5B23006F265D231_171002_3453840_Model_s_eyeball_tattoo_goes_dreadfully_wrong_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/111/5F2/1115F21775027E51C7B7FC05F0EE3798"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, eye tattoo goes wrong, vision loss, eyeball tattoo gone wrong, tattoo fail, catt gal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3453789</guid>
      <title>Creepy clown sightings spook Israeli townsfolk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AFULA, ISRAEL  Seems a couple of clowns in Israel have taken a cue from their U.S. counterparts, and are wandering the dark streets scaring the bejesus out of the Jews.The Times of Israel reports that residents of the northern Israeli town of Afula have been spotting scary-looking clowns hanging about and are not amused.The terrified townsfolk have taken to expressing their fears online, while also probably locking themselves inside their homes, away from any murderous circus freaks.So even though it's not criminal to don face paint and a red nose, police still investigated, and revealed the culprits to be … a couple of 12-year-olds.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 02:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/02/3453789/3453789_083BF3E7492540DC8F6DF9CF23BAC8CF_171002_3453789_Creepy_clown_sightings_spook_Israeli_townsfolk_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/216/6BB/2166BB368D012C4115DA2068040EC065"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, creepy clowns, clowns, IT, pennywise, afula, israel, scary clowns, clown sightings]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454823</guid>
      <title>How the Las Vegas shooting unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS  At least 59 people were killed and 527 injured when a sniper opened fire at a Las Vegas concert on Sunday night. Gunman Stephen Paddock, a 64-year old white male, from Mesquite, Nev., opened fire from the 32nd floor of the Mandalay Bay Hotel towards a country music festival, the Washington Post reported. Authorities found dozens of guns in his hotel room and "in excess of" 19 firearms and bombs at his Nevada residence. At 10:08 p.m., Paddock open fire straight down into the concert venue across the street, a quarter-mile away, according to the Washington Post. Paddock was staying in a suite with two rooms, Las Vegas Sheriff Joseph Lombardo said. Authorities think he fired from both rooms to get better angles. The shooting went on from between five to fifteen minutes, however estimates vary. Authorities were able to locate the shooter because the smoke from his guns set the fire alarm off. A SWAT team entered Paddock's room. Around that time, Paddock killed himself, Lombardo said.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 10:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/03/3454823/3454823_12A8162219D44AD1B5A716A8DE9CF060_171003_3454823_How_the_Las_Vegas_shooting_unfolded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FBF/1A4/FBF1A4162444F414C979F35043786716"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Las Vegas shooting, Mandalay Bay, Stephen Paddock, Vegas shooting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454619</guid>
      <title>Orbital reflector will be first sculpture</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RENO, NEVADA  An artist is working with the Nevada Museum of Art to send a satellite sculpture up into space that can be seen from Earth. The "orbital reflector" is a satellite that will serve no military, commercial or scientific purpose, the museum said. The sculpture will be packed inside a small CubeSat that will be launched aboard a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket scheduled for early 2018. Once in orbit at a height of approximately 350 miles (575 km), a 100-foot long diamond-shaped balloon will deploy from the satellite. The balloon will reflect sunlight back to Earth, causing the CubeSat to be visible to the naked eye, according to the museum. It will stay in space for about two months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 06:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/03/3454619/3454619_B84177C3044647618587805AA0D2DE98_171003_3454619_Orbital_reflector_will_be_first_sculpture_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/254/C1F/254C1FBA918C2095F9B7527258A396CC"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Orbital Reflector, space sculpture, Orbital Reflector satellite, satellite sculpture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454593</guid>
      <title>Here's why farting and belching cows are warming up the planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Methane emissions from cattle are much higher than previously thought, according to a new U.S. government funded study. Research published in the journal Carbon Balance and Management says that previous data on methane emissions from livestock were off by 11%Methane gas absorbs much more sunlight than carbon dioxide, and as a result, is a significant contributor to rising global temperatures.Previous research failed to account for developments in land and animal use, reported Forbes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 06:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-video/124/210/124210EF8B894B6F8FE15AF0D22342D4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/10F/29D/10F29D2BADCE89549A72126D0228385D"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cow farting and global warming, global warming cattle, cow farting and co2, methane from cattle, cow study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454459</guid>
      <title>Vanuatu volcano eruption forces all 11,000 residents to be evacuated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMBAE, VANUATU  Residents are being evacuated after a volcano on one of Vanuatu's northern islands began to erupt.The Manaro volcano in Ambae is a shield volcano whose summit features three crater lakes. Reuters reports that the volcano began releasing ash and toxic gas in September, and is now spewing rocks and lava amid repeated explosions.Many of the island's water sources were polluted by the eruption, leaving thousands without access to safe drinking water.Islanders are currently being ferried off the island by an assortment of ships and boats. Others have flown out to safety, as the Vanuatu government wants all 11,000 residents evacuated by October 6.The Manaro eruption poses a serious threat, especially with the possibility of deadly volcanic mud called lahar overflowing down the mountain.The volcano last erupted in 2005. Half of the island's population was evacuated and couldn't return until at least three months later.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/03/3454459/3454459_85D5B9A2E0274813AC8F72048BE301C1_171003_3454459_Vanuatu_volcano_eruption_forces_all_11_000_resid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4E4/270/4E427098DDA53CB300766E5DB143BE90"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, volcanic eruption, volcano, eruption, vanuatu eruption, vanuatu volcano, manari volcano, lava, lava flow, volcanic ash, smoke cloud, lahar, volcanic mud, mudflow, mudslide, ambae]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3454449</guid>
      <title>How could a radioactive cloud spread across the Pacific?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  A new graphic shows the effects an atmospheric burst would have if North Korea were to carry out a nuclear test over the Pacific Ocean. The simulation of the radioactive cloud spreading for two weeks across the globe was posted by Lassina Zerbo, head of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty Organization, on Twitter. The graphic did not include any supporting data such as nuclear payload or height of detonation, the Telegraph reported. Experts say the explosion, fire and radiation created from a hydrogen bomb test over the Pacific Ocean could have catastrophic effects. Aquatic life in the immediate blast zone would be killed instantly, while radioactive isotopes  with the help of wind  could impact other organisms and humans thousands of miles away.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 01:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/03/3454449/3454449_FF695E74B17B4B02BA55B08C9BFD389C_171003_3454449_How_could_a_radioactive_cloud_spread_across_the__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/64E/8E2/64E8E25C3065816F930CBF767D7FEFC7"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, North Korea, atmospheric burst simulation, radio-isotope cloud, pacific ocean, nuclear test]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455561</guid>
      <title>Las Vegas shooter's rifles had 'bump stock' modifications</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS  The man behind Sunday night's atrocity had nearly 2 dozen weapons in his hotel, including rifles modified with a bump stock.POPULAR MECHANICShttp://bit.ly/2fPOkSB BUMP FIRE SYSTEMShttp://bit.ly/2xfVX7jBEARING ARMShttp://bit.ly/2g9KaSr]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 09:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/04/3455561/3455561_5BF38F5394EC4BB283323319353F9B9F_171004_3455561_Las_Vegas_shooter_s_rifles_had__bump_stock__modi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/451/904/45190403BC18877EE7FFD821C32EE58A"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Las Vegas, fully auto v bump stock, bump stock fully auto, what is a bump stock, how do bump stock work, bump stock, fully auto, semi auto]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455511</guid>
      <title>Catalonia history and referendum, explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BARCELONA  On October 1, 2017, Catalonia voted for independence, despite massive opposition from the central Spanish government.BBC reports that the northeast region of Catalonia is one of Spain's 17 autonomous communities. It's home to 7.5 million people, and has its own distinct language, history, and culture.Catalonia was once under the kingdom of Aragon, which unified with Castile in the 15th century. It remained a state until it was defeated in the 1714 Siege of Barcelona, and its sovereignty was abolished. Under the newly centralized Spanish realm, Catalans were forced to adopt the Castilian language and customs.The region regained autonomy when Spain became a republic in 1931, but lost it again during the Franco dictatorship. Franco's death restored democracy, allowing Catalonia to have its own Parliament, police force, and education system.Though they have a high degree of autonomy, Catalans are not satisfied with the central government.As Spain's wealthiest region, it generates 20% of the national GDP. But high budget cuts during the 2008 financial crisis, and complaints of paying more taxes than they get back have increased separatist sentiment.The Brookings Institute reports that in 2010, the Spanish Constitutional Court reversed a 2006 ruling that granted the region 'nation' status and its own tax system, angering many and fueling the movement for independence.This movement culminated in the October 1 referendum, which Madrid has called illegal.A Catalonian secession would impact the Spanish economy, but also see the region out of the EU. With no free trade, the region's economy could shrink, and the unemployment rate could double.But do all Catalans want independence? Polls taken before the referendum showed that while 70% wanted the right to vote, only 41% sought independence.Still, Madrid's response was aggressive. It arrested Catalan leaders, and took down websites and apps in an effort to thwart the vote.On the day of the referendum, violence erupted as police seized ballots, and forcibly stopped people from voting. Despite the danger, voter turnout was at 42.3%, with nearly 90% of those who voted backing secession.Catalan's president has said he will declare independence within 48 hours if the 'yes' side won. If this happens, Spain will enter a constitutional crisis and may be forced to suspend Catalonia's autonomy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/04/3455511/3455511_FA193A3343FD454C8CFCE8EA08D3D9D6_171004_3455511_Catalonia_history_and_referendum__explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2DD/EEC/2DDEEC4C07D1E471F9BFB797F2A004D9"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, catalonia, catalonia referendum, catalexit, catalonia secession, catalan, separatist, catalan independence, catalonia independence, spain, referendum, independence, violence, explainer, catalonia history]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455487</guid>
      <title>What are the different types of volcanoes?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EARTH  A volcano is an opening in the earth's surface where molten rock can escape. The earth's crust is made up of tectonic plates that shift and move. Volcanoes are often located at the fault lines between these plates. Volcanoes can be active, dormant or extinct, according to Universe Today. There are four major types of volcanoes: cinder cone, composite, shield and lava domes.Cinder cone volcanoes occur when lava is ejected from a volcanic vent. Lava is shot into the air, and pieces accumulate around the vent. Over time, this creates a circular or oval-shaped cone, with a crater at the top. Composite volcanoes contain a conduit system that channels magma to the surface. These volcanoes can have clusters of vents along the sides of the mountain where lava flows out. Shield volcanoes are large, broad volcanoes where lava pours out in thin layers, allowing it to travel farther down the shallow slopes of the volcano. Shield volcanoes build up slowly with hundreds of eruptions creating several layers. Lava domes are created when small masses of thick lava that can't flow far from the source, so domes pile up around the vent. The dome grows by expansion of lava from within, and the mountain forms from material spilling off the sides of the dome.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 08:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/04/3455487/3455487_4E0B3A7DB8C44B738C23D8E1CB8BF9AB_171004_3455487_What_are_the_different_types_of_volcanoes__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/96C/4DF/96C4DF5ED4C945A8CE7DDD5017DF32BE"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, volcano, volcano types, cinder cone volcano, composite volcano, shield volcano, lava domes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455476</guid>
      <title>New osteoarthritis pill could stop bone loss and damage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LEEDS, UNITED KINGDOM  Scientists have found a new drug that can potentially stop bone loss and damage in people with diseased joints.The Daily Express reports that osteoarthritis is a degenerative joint disease caused by the breakdown of protective bone cartilage, often in the knees, hands, hips, and spine.The condition has no known cure, but a new drug called M1V-711 has been shown to help reduce bone damage in affected joints.The treatment is based on a molecule involved in bone and cartilage turnovers, and works by interfering with the process that leads to joint breakdown.When tested in patients aged 40 to 80, the drug reduced bone loss in the knees by 65% and improved cartilage thickness in just six months. By contrast, those given a placebo reported a slight increase in bone loss.According to lead investigator Philip Conaghan of the University of Leeds, the drug has very few side effects, and is reportedly the first to target the diseased bone structure, instead of simply managing pain like most existing treatments.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 08:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/04/3455476/3455476_6343A0CFA901461AAFF87C3FBE2180B5_171004_3455476_New_osteoarthritis_pill_could_stop_bone_loss_and_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/319/980/3199805D56115BF15E82FC988D6AD054"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, arthritis, osteoarthritis, arthritis treatment, joint pain, joint treatment, medical trial, joint pain, cartilage, M1V-711]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3455242</guid>
      <title>What will happen if the Bali volcano blows?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DENPASAR, INDONESIA  An eruption from Bali's Mount Agung volcano is imminent. Authorities have evacuated some 75,000 people in danger zones surrounding areas.The volcano has been quiet for almost five decades, but last week 700 tremors were detected in a single day.  Experts, as well as the Indonesian government believe this to be a sign that Mount Agung is ready to erupt.The last time Mount Agung erupted was in 1963, and the resulting catastrophe killed more than 1,000 people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 01:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/04/3455242/3455242_7CDD1A1071C14064B65AE8CD3CA35F01_171004_3455242_What_will_happen_if_the_Bali_volcano_blows__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A21/1F3/A211F34AD263A61553716137DF47034B"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bali volcano eruption 2017, bali volcano eruption, eruption mt agung, 1963 mt agung eruption, volcano eruption, volcanic eruptions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456263</guid>
      <title>Your wildlife selfies are killing the wildlife</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOCIAL MEDIA   Wildlife selfies have become all the rave over social media, only problem is they encourage animal cruelty. As more people look for pointless reasons to share pictures of themselves, local wildlife around the world are paying the price, according to Wild Animal Protection. The charity found a 292% increase in the amount of wildlife selfies posted on Instagram since 2014. The demand for wildlife selfies has led to an increase in local animals being snatched from the wild and forced into becoming props. Investigators found animals being abused in the Amazon cities of Manaus, Brazil and Puerto Alegria, Peru. The team discovered green anacondas wounded and dehydrated, kept in small wooden crates, when not being strangled by the throat for selfies.Sloths snatched from the wild, so they can be held by tourists. The handling from all the tourists naturally causes the sloths to freak out. And when they're not needed for photos, they're roped to trees. Caiman crocodiles are jammed in broken refrigerators with their mouths closed shut with rubber bands. Rule of thumb, next time you think about taking a selfie, don't. No one cares. That is, unless you slip and fall while taking it and happen to pass away in the process. In that case, send it over to us and we'll Tomo it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 10:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/05/3456263/3456263_866788AB51A647A8994AEC77F2D21FE2_171005_3456263_Your_wildlife_selfies_are_killing_the_wildlife_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/580/82D/58082D4EF3431D9778246E47E24D7A2B"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, wildlife selfies, animal selfies, instagram wildlife selfies, social media wildlife selfies, selfies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456143</guid>
      <title>Scotland about to enact country-wide fracking ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EDINBURGH, SCOTLAND  The Scottish government looks set to make fracking illegal in the country following opposition against it from the public.BBChttp://bbc.in/2xe0GvgTHE NATIONALhttp://bit.ly/2xTSYDx]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 07:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/05/3456143/3456143_AA159CD4F8FF4E188DA6D64335A5E418_171005_3456143_Scotland_about_to_enact_country_wide_fracking_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/866/CD3/866CD3A1DC14C84802AE09606F3BC4D4"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, what is fracking, fracking ban in scotland, scotland fracking, fracking in the uk, fracking climate change, fracking water fire, fracking fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3457235</guid>
      <title>Most of the world's honey contains yummy pesticides</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SWITZERLAND  Neonicotinoid pesticides are showing up in honey on every continent with honeybees, according to a new study. "On the global scale, the contamination is really striking," said study coauthor Edward Mitchell, a soil biologist at the University of Neuchâtel in Switzerland.Around 200 samples of honey were tested and 75 percent found to contain measurable levels of at least one of the five common neonicotinoids, Science News reported. Neonicotinoids are used on various crops grown in different climates, but still showed up in honey from remote islands with almost no agriculture. The insecticide works by targeting crop-destroying insect's central nervous system. A number of studies have found the insecticide also reduces and weakens honeybee hives. Pesticide levels varied from region-to-region. In North America, 86 percent of samples contained pesticides; Asia, 80 percent; Europe, 79 percent; Africa, 73 percent; the Australian region, 71 percent and South America, 57 percent. Bees and other pollinators are necessary to three-quarters of the world's food crops, but have been declining in number in recent decades, the Guardian reported. Destruction of wild habitats, disease and massive pesticide use are all contributing factors.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 13:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/06/3457235/3457235_E7D6A2EA4ACC4493A710CDFFEAF70044_171006_3457235_Most_of_the_world_s_honey_contains_yummy_pestici_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/048/1D9/0481D9A32531B6193D5B93499FF379DC"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bees, honey pesticide contamination, neonicotinoid, honey neonicotinoid contamination, insecticides, honeybees]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456844</guid>
      <title>Scientists may have discovered water at Mars' equator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE, MARYLAND  After reexamining old satellite data, scientists may have discovered ice around Mars' equator. A team from the Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory analyzed data from 2002 to 2009 by Mars Odyssey's Neutron Spectrometer (MONS), Science News reported. The neutron spectrometer can't directly detect water, but by measuring neutrons, it can detect hydrogen signature, which could mark the presence of water or other hydrogen-bearing substances, according to Space.com.  Researchers discovered an unexpected amount of hydrogen around the equator by reducing the blurring or "noise" in data using image-reconstruction techniques used for other spacecraft and for medicine, Space.com reported. This improved the spatial resolution of the images to 180 miles (290 km), from the previous resolution of 320 miles (520 km). More research needs to be done to determine if the signature is actual that from water ice. Having water on Mars could mean that future human missions wouldn't need to bring water with them for drinking, cooling equipment or watering plants, thus reducing the number of resources needed for transport.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 07:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/06/3456844/3456844_5A99D104EC7F425AB28ED19306F4305E_171006_3456844_Scientists_may_have_discovered_water_at_Mars__eq_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D86/E43/D86E435756EEAA4E16DF6B617C5E4587"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Mars, water Mars' equator, water on Mars, Odyssey satellite data]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456781</guid>
      <title>Santa Claus may be buried under Turkish church</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DEMRE, TURKEY  Sorry kids, Santa Claus is dead, and is apparently buried in Turkey.Hurriyet Daily News reports that archaeologists have found an intact shrine underneath the Demre church in Turkey's Antalya province, and suspect it to be the final resting place of St. Nicholas.The area where the church is located is reportedly the same region where St. Nick was born during the 4th century. It was there that the jolly saint formed the reputation for gift-giving that eventually gave rise to the legend of Santa Claus.After his death in 343 AD, the saint was interred in the church, and lay undisturbed until the 11th century.It's widely believed that Italian sailors then took his remains in 1087 and transported them to Bari, where they lie to this day in the Basilica di San Nicola.According to documents obtained by the Turkish archaeologists, however, the remains that were taken supposedly belonged to a local priest.Though many are skeptical, the Turkish team is determined to prove their theory right, and will soon begin the arduous task of removing an intricate mosaic tile by tile in order to get to the untouched tomb.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 05:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/06/3456781/3456781_9EBF33336D68455DB3F4E45A517E252C_171006_3456781_Santa_Claus_may_be_buried_under_Turkish_church_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1F0/294/1F0294E5DAE3B293018FBC00E63EE548"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, santa claus, st. nicholas, st. nick, christmas, archaeology, archaeologists, demre, demre church, tomb, shrine, temple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456738</guid>
      <title>Bulging iPhone 8 Plus batteries reported around the globe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA  Nearly half a dozen iPhone 8 Plus owners from around the world have seen their devices cracking and swelling.The swelling in these cases reportedly occurs while the iPhone 8 Plus's lithium-ion battery is charging.  Apple says it is investigating the problem and is in possession of one of the damaged phones.Five iPhone 8 Plus owners in Canada, Greece, Japan, Taiwan and Hong Kong have reported similar issues, reported mobile news website BGR.According to Apple news site MacRumors, it's common for a small number of devices out of the millions made to have some battery issues.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 04:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/06/3456738/3456738_E765BD05914D424BB849E5B9AD0EC928_171006_3456738_Bulging_iPhone_8_Plus_batteries_reported_around__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/308/D1F/308D1FD67A1EA4011B9E125DF243390F"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, swelling iphone, iphone 8 teardown, iphone issues, iphone problems, iphone battery issues, iphone battery problems, iphone 8 charging, Apple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456722</guid>
      <title>Can drinking black tea help you lose that fat? Science says maybe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  University of California scientists have connected the effects of drinking black tea to weight loss in mice.The study was published in the European Journal of Nutrition.Over a period of 4 weeks, three groups of mice were fed high-fat, high-sugar diets and compared to a group was given a low-fat, high-sugar diet. Two of the high-fat, high-sugar groups' diets were supplemented with black and green tea."After the 4 weeks scientists found that weight among the mice who consumed tea had lowered to the same level as those on a low-fat, high-sugar diet.Analysis of intestinal samples revealed both black and green tea lessened bacteria associated with obesity and increased bacteria associated with lean muscle mass.Green tea was also shown to be easily absorbed by the liver, while black tea was found to stay in the intestine and help build bacteria that help with metabolism.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 04:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/06/3456722/3456722_FECB0C3345BA47D79666A1782F62985B_171006_3456722_Can_drinking_black_tea_help_you_lose_that_fat__S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/552/2FB/5522FB474620ECCE11633B03BBAA7FBD"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, tea and weight loss, black tea fat, green tea fat, how does tea help you lose weight, gut bacteria, weight loss in mice, ucla, new weight loss study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3456744</guid>
      <title>American gun ownership and violence, in numbers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA  In the wake of the deadly mass shooting in Las Vegas, gun violence and ownership have once again taken center stage in public discussions.According to the UN office on drugs and crime, the U.S. had the highest rate of gun ownership in 2012, with 88 guns for every 100 people. Yemen is second on the list but trails far behind with 54.8 guns.Results from the 2015 National Firearm Survey revealed that handgun ownership in particular has increased by 70%, from 65 million in 1994 to 111 million in 2015. America is one of the countries where the right to bear arms is protected by the constitution. It’s also incredibly easy to arm yourself.In 2007, the Small Arms Survey found that half the world’s civilian-owned guns were in the U.S. Fifty percent of these were owned by a mere 3% of American adults, according to an unpublished survey from Harvard and Northeastern University.Mass shootings take place in the country more than 11 times as often as other developed nations. One study estimates over 100,000 gunshot victims, and 30,000 gun deaths annually, which totals to $2.8 billion in hospital expenses.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/763/17/10/06/3456652/3456652_BFA35E9E4FB541FAADD63B73F667CB3C_171006_3456652_Guns_in_America__Gun_ownership_and_violence_in_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/000/FE5/000FE58AA5A57F6B6210813DEDE85AAC"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,gun control,gun ownership,guns,guns in America,guns in the US,US guns,firearms,US firearms,statistics,user/TomoNewsUS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458739</guid>
      <title>Police still don't know the Vegas shooter's motive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS  Authorities are still trying to determine a motive for the deadly Las Vegas shooting that killed 58 people and wounded nearly 500 last weekend. Investigators found a handwritten note with distance and trajectory calculations in shooter Stephen Paddock's hotel room, CBS News reported.  The note was found in Paddock's Mandalay Bay Resort and Casino suite along with 23 firearms and ammunition. Even with over 1,000 leads and tips, authorities still have no credible information about Paddock's potential motive.Police said they believe a Mandalay Bay security guard responding to a door alarm near Paddock's room on the 32nd floor caused the shooter to shift his focus from the Route 91 concert crowd across the street, Undersheriff Kevin C. McMahill told CNN. Officials are confident Paddock was the only shooter, although they are still trying to determine if anyone knew of his plans, CNN reported. Paddock brought the 23 guns and ammunition found in his suite over the course of several days, McMahill said. Investigators still do not know what Paddock planned to do with the 50 pounds of explosives found in his vehicle in the hotel parking garage.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 08:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/09/3458739/3458739_0609CEF7F2764B09885665BD849D39BD_171009_3458739_Police_still_don_t_know_the_Vegas_shooter_s_moti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/457/F48/457F481C74C78197F138FEB03AF1BBF2"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Las Vegas, Mandalay Bay hotel and Casino, Stephen Paddock, Stephen Paddock note, Stephen Paddock motive]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458721</guid>
      <title>Deadly poison may've killed Kim Jong Un's big bro</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR, MALAYSIA  Traces of the nerve agent VX were found on the clothing of Kim Jong Nam's suspected assassins.REUTERShttp://reut.rs/2xsNoGnSTRAITS TIMEShttp://bit.ly/2kzRP12]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 08:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/09/3458721/3458721_E2AF4BD862DF4C35880E57D50C5C92F8_171009_3458721_Deadly_poison_may_ve_killed_Kim_Jong_Un_s_big_br_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/782/1B1/7821B192DB3DCCF3D9F4C4DFA6879650"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, kim jong nam assassination, kim jong un, dprk, kim jong nam trial, kim jong nam, kim jong il, vx, venomous agent x]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458683</guid>
      <title>This 'smart bandage' will help you heal like the Wolverine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LINCOLN, NEBRASKA/ CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  Researchers have designed a 'smart bandage' they say heals skin tissue 3 times faster than a regular medical dressing.It accomplishes this via medication loaded inside the bandage threads and drug delivery can then be controlled via smartphone. The researchers say in the future this could accelerate healing of battlefield wounds.Details of the technology were published in the journal Advanced Functional Material. It was co-developed by MIT, Harvard and the University of Nebraska-Lincoln.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 07:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/09/3458683/3458683_69499E29B0364B938C9F678BBA82262F_171009_3458683_This__smart_bandage__will_help_you_heal_like_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/524/566/524566E5C738C61F7AAC40568B9C8225"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, accelerated healing, smart bandage, medical healing, healing quick, wolverine, x-men]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458677</guid>
      <title>NASA says dimming of Tabby's Star likely caused by dust, not aliens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FINAL FRONTIER  New research from NASA may have solved one of the most prevalent astronomy puzzles in recent years.Dyson spheres are theoretical cosmic megastructures. They envelop a planet with energy-absorbing technology which directs power to a central location.Some astronomers previously theorized the dimming of Tabby's Star was caused by this. This star is located 1,280 light years from Earth.New research using data from NASA's Spitzer and Swift space telescopes suggests the dimming is actually due to an dust cloud orbiting the star.Known as circumstellar dust, NASA says these particles are not small enough to fly into space, but also not big enough to block light all the time on all wavelengths.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 07:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/09/3458677/3458677_7DBD0D8610944907AC88E5243047B9D5_171009_3458677_NASA_says_dimming_of_Tabby_s_Star_likely_caused__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/55C/F8A/55CF8A6FDC529762EB846FB4FA714E07"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, tabby star, tabby star update, tabby star 2017, dyson sphere, alien megastructure, nasa, aliens and nasa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458604</guid>
      <title>New molecule uses 'kick and kill' approach to eliminate dormant HIV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Researchers may have finally found a way to eliminate the HIV reservoirs that often remain hidden in the body.Science Daily reports that HIV spreads by taking over a cell's DNA and using it to make copies of itself. Most AIDS treatments are engineered to block this replication cycle, effectively stopping the spread of the virus.But though these drugs allow patients to live longer, they do not rid the body of the virus, which hides in reservoirs and re-emerges once treatment stops.A new 'kick and kill' approach aims to get rid of these reservoirs by using a synthetic molecule called SUW133 to wake up the dormant virus, which will then be eliminated by antiretroviral therapy.The technique was developed by researchers from UCLA, Stanford, and the National Institutes of Health, and is detailed in a study published in PLOS Pathogens.When tested on HIV-infected mice that had been given antiretroviral drugs, 25 percent of the once-dormant virus cells died within 24 hours of being reactivated.With further development, researchers believe the technique could lower the viral reservoir enough for infected patients to stop antiretroviral treatment.The molecule will also need to be tested on larger animals before it can go to human trials.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 05:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/09/3458604/3458604_A0784D4A84DF40F7B19AC64553F25A59_171009_3458604_New_molecule_uses__kick_and_kill__approach_to_el_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C1C/6A8/C1C6A80E60A6956AE7E60776A3979C45"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,HIV,AIDS,HIV virus,AIDS treatment,HIV treatment,AIDS cure,HIV cure,kick and kill,antiretroviral therapy,antiretroviral,antiretroviral drugs,SUW133,dormant HIV]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458594</guid>
      <title>Brain-eating parasite may be killing off sharks, marine life in SF bay</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Scientists are concerned by a massive shark die-off in San Francisco bay, but are unable to get state funding to research the exact cause.NBC Bay Area reports that two thousand leopard sharks and hundreds of bat rays, smoothhound sharks, striped bass, and halibut have turned up dead on San Francisco Bay between February and July this year.The culprit is suspected to be a parasite known as Miamiensis avidus, which enters the shark's nose and eats away at its brain.When the animal eventually succumbs to the parasite, it either swims aimlessly in circles or beaches itself.But scientists say only a small fraction end up on shore. Sharks aren't naturally buoyant, so the infected ones sink to the bottom of the ocean once they stop swimming.Leopard sharks are the most commonly spotted victims of the parasite, but it's a lesser concern for the California Department of Fish and Wildlife, since the species is not endangered.Scientists fear, however, that other species are also becoming infected and dying, but just aren't washing up on shore. They also worry that the parasite could spread farther along the California coast.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 05:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/09/3458594/3458594_082D3B7965E44506B4FFC2C5E1485164_171009_3458594_Brain_eating_parasite_may_be_killing_off_sharks__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D72/B03/D72B03AF8B217D0216D984ED89DF120D"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, parasite, shark deaths, sharks, marine pathogen, pathogen, single cell parasite, miamiensis avidus, leopard sharks, san francisco bay, brain eating parasite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3458506</guid>
      <title>Apple gave Uber 'unprecedented' access to secret backdoor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Apple gave Uber's iPhone app access to a secret backdoor that potentially allows the company to record a user's screen and access other personal information without his or her knowledge. According to Business Insider, Uber does not mention the backdoor is any consumer-facing information included with their app. Apple's backdoor is so powerful, it rarely allows third-party companies to access the feature. Security researcher Will Strafach discovered the situation and told Business Insider, "granting such a sensitive entitlement to a third-party is unprecedented as far as I can tell, no other app developers have been able to convince Apple to grant them entitlements they've needed to let their apps utilize certain privileged system functionality." There's no evidence that Uber used the special iPhone feature. Uber told Business Insider the code was not being used and was a leftover from an earlier version of its Apple Watch app. A majority of iPhone apps use software to enable features like the camera or ApplePay known as "entitlements." Many of these can be easily turned on by outside app creators. But certain entitlements are only used by Apple to allow optimal integration with the iPhone.   Uber's app was found to be the only app other than Apple's own apps granted access to the entitlement, Strafach said in an email to Business Insider.Uber says the entitlement isn't being used, and it is working with Apple to remove the API completely from the app.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/09/3458506/3458506_23BB5259C8DC4EA0887EE4C948888D7D_171009_3458506_Apple_gave_Uber__unprecedented__access_to_secret_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3D2/FB2/3D2FB2A352B6E09F839029E589AA0B95"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Apple, Uber, Apple Uber secret backdoor, entitlements, Uber iPhone secret backdoor access, Apple entitlements]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3459497</guid>
      <title>Las Vegas shooter wounded hotel guard before massacre</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS  Authorities say Las Vegas shooter Stephen Paddock wounded a security guard prior to carrying out last Sunday's events. REUTERShttp://reut.rs/2y8bWGJLAS VEGAS REVIEW-JOURNALhttp://bit.ly/2xvxX0k]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/10/3459497/3459497_40034F0FB281469A8BD41128AC82EF24_171010_3459497_Las_Vegas_shooter_wounded_hotel_guard_before_mas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1ED/03A/1ED03AA0212317A4CE0F58886126282A"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,las vegas 2017,stephen paddock,campos,campos paddock,nevada,las vegas incident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3459391</guid>
      <title>Puppies sold in Petland tied to outbreak of campylobacter infections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA  An outbreak of campylobacter infections has been connected to puppies sold by U.S. national pet chain Petland.CDChttp://bit.ly/2y4g9gMWTSPhttp://on.wtsp.com/2xsFZqt]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 06:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/10/3459391/3459391_7BFBC94DAF9C4E8585BABEBAF13F1AF0_171010_3459391_Puppies_sold_in_Petland_tied_to_outbreak_of_camp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/760/9A6/7609A678ADEF409F9FB556A4C3804D11.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, petland puppies making people sick, cdc, campylobacter petland, campylobacter outbreak, puppy human sick, puppy and human]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3459354</guid>
      <title>Madagascar is in the middle of plague outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADAGASCAR  Madagascar is currently experiencing an outbreak of the plague with 231 confirmed cases, and at least 33 deaths as of October 6, according to the World Health Organization.  The country usually sees about 400 cases per year, but this outbreak has officials concerned because it has spread to the capital and coastal cities for the first time, Vox reported. This year a large number of the cases are pneumonic plague, which targets the lungs and is passed on by coughing, according to the BBC. It is the most deadly form of the disease and can cause death within 24 hours.  The WHO has delivered more than a million doses of antibiotics to help combat the spread of the disease, according to BBC. Two regions on the island nation have been hit particularly hard, eastern Madagascar and the center of the island in Antananarivo.  Public gatherings have been banned in response to the outbreak. Officials have also put in place screening protocols at the country's main airport.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 05:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/10/3459354/3459354_628E8ED5EDE44796BCB0776129A31EB0_171010_3459354_Madagascar_is_in_the_middle_of_plague_outbreak_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6AE/4EF/6AE4EF5AD0682DE84A30576D632CC74C"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Madagascar, Madagascar plague, pneumonic plague, plague outbreak, WHO plague antibiotics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460215</guid>
      <title>Dude finds 30,000 bees living in the walls of his house</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HILLSIDE, NEW JERSEY  A man found 30,000 bees and 40lbs inside his house wall last month.CBS NEW YORKhttp://cbsloc.al/2kFs3bLWASHINGTON POSThttp://wapo.st/2gtLbVE]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 08:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/11/3460215/3460215_02147A8208D14778A9332FCC7B637249_171011_3460215_Dude_finds_30_000_bees_living_in_the_walls_of_hi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C41/26A/C4126A10007053B7ED9DE3437AFB373B"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ...]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460191</guid>
      <title>Plastic surgery leaves Chinese women stuck in airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH KOREA  Three Chinese woman were reportedly stopped from boarding their flight and got stuck in an airport in South Korea because after getting massive plastic surgery done, they looked nothing like their passport photos. The picture of the three women was widely shared over Chinese social media platforms.It's become a thing over the past decade for Chinese women to travel to South Korea to go under the knife, so they can get transformed into women who clearly look like they've gotten way too much work done. Chinese women in search of a new face visit South Korea using 'Medical Tourists' visas. Almost 100,000 Chinese visited South Korea in 2016 to get things pumped up, sliced off and reshaped.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 08:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/11/3460191/3460191_4FF2C54DD95C4C00932910CD1C61A329_171011_3460191_Plastic_surgery_leaves_Chinese_women_stuck_in_ai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3F1/F47/3F1F47821D71C3335CE0AC3BA514C650"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, plastic surgery, plastic surgery gone wrong, Chinese plastic surgery Korea, plastic surgery passport problems]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460179</guid>
      <title>Carbon from soil may warm planet even quicker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE GREEN  Carbon emissions from soil microbes could lead to a further rise in global temperatures, scientists have warned.According to new research published in the journal Science, soil releases more carbon when heated passed a certain point.In 1991, scientists placed heaters 10 cm under soil in the Harvard forest in Massachusetts. They artificially heated that area over 26 years and found that the warmed soil released 17 percent more of its carbon content compared to unheated soil."If the microbes in all landscapes respond to warming in the same way as we've observed in mid-latitude forest soils, this self-reinforcing feedback phenomenon will go on for a while and we are not going to be able to turn those microbes off," explained lead author Jessy Melillo in a University of Chicago news release.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 07:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/11/3460179/3460179_F92A84C38E0E46F2ACDE6F6302CDBE1F_171011_3460179_Carbon_from_soil_may_warm_planet_even_quicker_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AAF/2C3/AAF2C38185FCF3B2F199E2A8C6E8A4F8"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, soil releases carbon, carbon dioxide, climate change, global warming, science, 26 year study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460083</guid>
      <title>A massive wind farm in the Atlantic could meet world's power needs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA  The entire world could be powered by one deep-sea wind farm stretching across the Atlantic, a new study finds. Building an installation the size of India would could meet the whole world's power needs, according to a study published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.   Doctors Anna Possner and Ken Caldeira from the Carnegie Institution for Science at Stanford University pointed out wind speeds over the ocean are on average 70 percent higher than over land, the Independent reported.Land-based wind farms have an upper threshold in the amount of energy that can be converted into electricity due to the combined drag of the spinning blades. Other studies have found land-based farms to have a limit of about 1.5 watts per square meter. Possner and Caldeira say it would be possible to produce 6 watts per square meter in the North Atlantic. Power output would be seasonal, with levels dropping to a fifth of the yearly average during the summer time. Several engineering challenges would have to be overcome. A deep-sea wind farm would have to operate in remote and harsh conditions where waves frequently exceed three meters (9.8 ft), according to the researchers. Laying transmission cables that stretch across the ocean floor and then connect to floating turbines in open ocean would be another obstacle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 06:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/11/3460083/3460083_672E69D7882D40EEB0299ADFF3662F5A_171011_3460083_A_massive_wind_farm_in_the_Atlantic_could_meet_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A8B/5C1/A8B5C1E34CAB10798B60F9C0DA874668"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, floating wind farm, floating wind turbine, wind turbine, renewable energy, wind power]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461019</guid>
      <title>Switzerland flushes $1.8 million in gold through its sewers every year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SWITZERLAND  Scientists say around 43 kg of gold worth around $1.8 million is flushed through Switzerland's sewer system each year. The report was released by researchers at the Swiss Federal Institute of Aquatic Science and Technology, Bloomberg reported. According to the report, the gold is lost through sludge and effluent from the country's waste treatment facilities. Scientists believe the gold flecks originate from the watchmaking industry and gold refineries. Switzerland is a major gold-refining hub with about 70 percent of the world's gold making its way through the country's refineries every year, according to Bloomberg. The study looked at 64 water treatment plants and also found around 3,000 kg of silver worth around $1.7 million.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 09:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/12/3461019/3461019_A1F5E3F9029E4B67B6B741ACFCDC9556_171012_3461019_Switzerland_flushes__1_8_million_in_gold_through_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/199/4CF/1994CF656DF96E1968D45C6E6729B727"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, gold sewage treatment plants, gold flecks wastewater treatment plants, Swiss gold refineries, Swiss gold sewage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460921</guid>
      <title>Dirty old birds help track air pollution over last 135 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Researchers analyzed the amount of soot on birds in museums from Rust Belt cities to track air pollution over the last 135 years. A new paper in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences shows the discoloration of birds in museum collections can be used to estimate the amount of black carbon air over time, Science Daily reported.Researchers from The Field Museum and the University of Chicago sampled over a thousand birds collected over the last 135 years to find out and quantify the effects of soot in the air in Rust Belt cities like Chicago, Detroit and Pittsburgh. To track changes in sootiness, the scientists photographed the birds and measured the light reflected off of them.   They found that older birds were dirtier and new birds were cleaner. The team discovered that soot on birds closely tracks the use of coal over time. Researchers also pointed out that even though newer birds are cleaner, it doesn't necessarily mean U.S. air is less polluted. Many of the pollutants released into the atmosphere today aren't as easily tracked as soot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 07:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/12/3460921/3460921_AD0AB17CB50D4F9FB10DDF56B6E29662_171012_3460921_Dirty_old_birds_help_track_air_pollution_over_la_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/860/0AE/8600AEF131D8FB0C821CF1F0F2379FAE"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, air pollution, bird feather soot, black carbon pollution, environmental pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3460872</guid>
      <title>Malware hacks millions of PCs via world's most popular skin-flick site</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTREAL  Millions of visitors to a specific website, providing a specific form entertainment may have been malwared.PROOFPOINThttp://bit.ly/2ze8cn2GUARDIANhttp://bit.ly/2xvGAg9]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 06:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/12/3460872/3460872_A30B3EC0F18E49598B48E5F2EFEA1894_171012_3460872_Malware_hacks_millions_of_PCs_via_world_s_most_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E1F/DE3/E1FDE3EF25830154A195BC58A8AFEBAD"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, malware hack, kovter, kovter malware, kovter virus, Kovter group, malvertising, spamming, pop up malware, infected computer, cybersecurity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3462042</guid>
      <title>Russia-tied election trolls used Pok&#xE9;mon Go, claims CNN</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW / WASHINGTON  A report by CNN claims that Russian-linked election trolls attempted to sway American politics last summer through the mobile game Pokémon Go.CNNhttp://cnnmon.ie/2xD4h64\]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 13:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/13/3462042/3462042_FD0E7057ED8E465B95C81CC736C3076F_171013_3462042_Russia_tied_election_trolls_used_Pokemon_Go__cla_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FCF/1B3/FCF1B3E87E09DFE2634FF2A2F5CC506A"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, russia pokemon go, russia pokemon go election hacking, russia pokemon go, niantic, election hacking, do not shoot us, putin pokemon go, CNN pokemon russia fake news, pokemon go, nintendo, pikachu]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461730</guid>
      <title>Football-shaped Haumea found to have giant ring system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE OUTER SOLAR SYSTEM  Scientists in Granada, Spain have discovered a ring system around the dwarf planet HaumeaNamed after that Hawaiian goddess of childbirth, Haumea is orbited by two moons and, according to a new Nature study, a giant ring system.The only other celestial bodies observed to present a ring system Saturn, Jupiter, Neptune and Uranus. Details of the finding were published in the journal Nature.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 08:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/13/3461730/3461730_935E7A4B4BF24D558AC407C90F360873_171013_3461730_Football_shaped_Haumea_found_to_have_giant_ring__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5C8/4AB/5C84AB052F3AAD45DA7E54B89F2A38DB"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, haumea, football planet, ring system, space discovery, haumea dwarf planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461710</guid>
      <title>China designs useless glass skywalk that pretends to crack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HEBEI, CHINA  A glass skywalk on a mountain in China was designed to look like it may be cracking when you step on it.Naturally, it scares the chicken chow mein out of the people who walk across it. The skywalk hangs 1,180 meters up on the eastern face of the Taihang Mountain. It uses video screens and even adds sound of breaking glass to make people think they're done for.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 08:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/13/3461710/3461710_766ED0801B4940C18EC95318AD502F32_171013_3461710_China_designs_useless_glass_skywalk_that_pretend_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/601/FB9/601FB98CCC61FB0ED4FFA78CA9CE3AF8"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China skywalk, China glass skywalk, China cracking skywalk, China fake cracking skywalk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461644</guid>
      <title>Sewage plants are leaking millions of plastic beads into UK seas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  Sewage plants could be leaking millions of tiny plastic beads used for wastewater treatment into seas around the U.K., according to a new report. Dozens of treatment facilities across the country use Bio-Bead plastic pellets to filter chemical and organic contaminants out from sewage, the study from the Cornish Plastic Pollution Coalition (CPPC) said, the Guardian reported. The study found several millions of the 3.5 mm wide pellets had been spilled into the surrounding seas.The Bio-Bead system is used by at least 55 sewage plants around the U.K., according to the CPPC. Bio-Beads are used in the last step of the sewage treatment process before treated effluent water is discharged back into rivers or the sea. The CPPC found no systems are currently in place at sewage plants to handle Bio-Bead spills. Plastic microbeads and industrial pellets, like Bio-Beads, are often mistaken for food by fish, birds and other marine wildlife. The plastic kills animals by blocking the digestive tract, but also as a result of exposure to chemical pollutants like DDT and PCBs that attach to the plastic beads in seawater.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 06:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/13/3461644/3461644_68AEE964FF4D47669F4F401F61EBB162_171013_3461644_Sewage_plants_are_leaking_millions_of_plastic_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B34/A50/B34A509C30C2F1E67C5C9B9E8C948A3A"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Bio-Beads, Bio-Beads spilling into sea, plastic microbeads, microbeads, ocean plastic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461592</guid>
      <title>Chinese find innovative ways of carrying fresh poultry home</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGDONG, CHINA  Video of a chicken and a duck hanging out  literally  inside a plastic bag while speeding down an expressway in China has gone viral on Chinese social media.Apparently the two were traveling along a Guangdong expressway during the Chinese Spring Festival holiday, no doubt being brought back to someone's home where they would be enjoyed as freshly as possible.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 05:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/13/3461592/3461592_C118B845AC6743909F6DF2A8C12C829C_171013_3461592_Chinese_find_innovative_ways_of_carrying_fresh_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5BA/4AB/5BA4AB0C6C9B8353476E1DCAC4CAF63B"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, chicken, duck, Spring Festival, animals, farm to table]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3461526</guid>
      <title>Massive lake cracks open in Antarctica</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA  A nation-sized body of water known as a polynya has opened up inside the world's southern frozen continent.Scientists say this is the second year in a row the massive hole has appeared. According to National Geographic it is 30,000 square miles in size. This would make it half the size of Florida, around the same size as the UAE and three times as big as Hawaii.Warming waters from changes in the environment are said to play a part in the formation of such holes, as well as weather factors.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 04:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/13/3461526/3461526_35C6774E96844867BFB235EF2B9F1DB6_171013_3461526_Massive_lake_cracks_open_in_Antarctica_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D8B/4B0/D8B4B0D8BF4E0C935C16A8669EC1515C"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Antarctica hole in the Earth, Polynya, hole in Antarctic ice, antarctica, climate science, changes to antarctica, what is a polynya]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3463745</guid>
      <title>China's awesome Tiangong-1 space station is going to crash into Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China's Tiangong-1 space station will crash into Earth within the next few months, according to experts. The Tiangong-1 was launched in 2011 as part of China's push to become a space superpower and has been used for manned and unmanned missions, the Guardian reported. In 2016, Chinese officials confirmed that they lost control of the space station and that it would crash to Earth in 2017 or 2018. The station's orbit has been steadily decaying ever since then. Over the past few weeks, the 8.5-tonne station has dipped below 300 km in altitude. When the Tiangong-1 was operational, the lab orbited at an altitude of 370 km.  The lower the altitude, the denser the atmosphere and the faster the Tiangong-1 will burn up. Most of the space station is expected to disintegrate in the atmosphere, but experts say some parts weighing up to 100 kg could reach the Earth's surface, the Guardian reported. China's space agency has told the UN it expects the Tiangong-1 to come down between October 2017 and April 2018.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 12:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/16/3463745/3463745_C93C35D0CBA948C5913E4964E79D5CE8_171016_3463745_China_s_awesome_Tiangong_1_space_station_is_goin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4DC/F5C/4DCF5C5555C7CE723DB83D5357BA195A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China space station, Tiangong-1, Tiangong-1 falling to Earth, Tiangong-1 crash, Chinese Tiangong-1]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3463580</guid>
      <title>Otaku penguin passes with waifu at his side</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  An elderly penguin, famous for being transfixed on popular manga character Hululu, is on his way to that big iceberg in the sky.The Japan Timeshttp://bit.ly/2zqkKb4]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 09:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/16/3463580/3463580_70A7322C24B44A79BE9324021939F630_171016_3463580_Otaku_penguin_passes_with_waifu_at_his_side_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/60C/6BA/60C6BA539EFB1C2D75C4013D51F003EE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, penguin loves anime, grape kun, tobu zoo, saitama, penguin love, humboldt penguin, tokyo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3463541</guid>
      <title>Yellowstone supervolcano could blow faster than expected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YELLOWSTONE NATIONAL PARK  A new study suggests Yellowstone's supervolcano could become active in just a few decades if the right conditions developed. Arizona State University researchers analyzed minerals in ancient fossilized ash from the most recent mega-eruption and believe the supervolcano became active after two injections of magma into the reservoir underneath the caldera, National Geographic reported. They found the minerals showed that the critical changes in temperature and composition built up over a few decades. Geologists previously thought it took centuries for supervolcanoes to go active.  Supervolcanoes have an eruption magnitude of 8 on the Volcano Explosivity Index (VEI) and spit out more than 1,000 cubic kilometers (240 cubic miles) of hot rock and ash, according to Science Alert. For now Yellowstone's supervolcano hasn't shown any indications of an eruption, although experts agree there's no way of knowing when the next blast will occur.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 08:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/16/3463541/3463541_30C8B6D70CB742FEB8886202A7B81F5B_171016_3463541_Yellowstone_supervolcano_could_blow_faster_than__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5E4/40E/5E440E04E93EAEDEE84E7C46188BFC4A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Yellowstone supervolcano, Yellowstone supervolcano eruption, supervolcano, Yellowstone caldera]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464367</guid>
      <title>WiFi networks worldwide at risk from 'Krack' attacks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUILFORD, U.K.  WiFi networks worldwide could contain a security flaw that lets hackers disrupt internet traffic, according to researchers. A hacker in range of a WiFi network would be able load viruses onto the network, read and gather communications like passwords, credit card numbers and photos sent, the Telegraph reported. Experts call it a "Krack" attack and say it's a "fundamental flaw" in wireless security techniques, with Apple, Android and Windows software all vulnerable to some extent. The Krack attack takes advantage of the "handshake" between device and router to insert a "key" that can decrypt communications to allow things like passwords and credit card data to be stolen, according to the Telegraph. Researchers suggest only connecting to secured WiFi networks and avoiding unsecured networks like those hotels, coffee shops and public spaces.Most banking and online shopping websites use https, an encryption technique that protects against Krack attacks.Security analysts also suggest updating your router, although updates for Krack attacks may not be available yet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 10:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/17/3464367/3464367_768FD61ABA70422696EE8BB98D8A3937_171017_3464367_WiFi_networks_worldwide_at_risk_from__Krack__att_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/958/F45/958F45190324DB25000C72FE1685C5C6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, WiFi, WiFi security, Krack attack, Krack hacking attack. WiFi unsecured networks, password theft, credit card data theft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464273</guid>
      <title>Pok&#xE9;mon Go reportedly getting massive Onix-pected Gen 3 update</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAVENDER TOWN  Hit mobile game Pokémon Go is reportedly getting a big update this Halloween, but does that mean more poke-mishaps?  You may remember the game from last summer when it spawned hordes of smartphone Pokémon trainers.  With this new update, it looks set to do the same again, only this time at Halloween. And that means more Pokémon  Go mishaps, but, with a Halloween twist.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 08:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/17/3464273/3464273_755601876DC44C19AF98316FF1298C66_171017_3464273_Pokemon_Go_reportedly_getting_massive_Onix_pecte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A6A/CFE/A6ACFE4D5F470703C224BBEFDE0CB40C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, gen 3 pokemon go, pokemon go update news, niantic, pokemon go halloween, pokemon, nintendo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464213</guid>
      <title>TomoNews guide to PC Halloweening costumes</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  With Halloween quickly approaching, we here at TomoNews decided to publish a quick guide on what PC costumes won't outrage other ultrasensitive Americans. As with every Halloween, bros and sorority chicks across the country have put on their collective thinking caps to come up with their best costume ideas.For girls, the decisions are pretty easy. Just put the word 'sexy' in front of any costume and they're ready for action. As a rule of thumb just don't dress up as another race. As for the other important rules, there are none. Remember to Halloween responsibly this year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 07:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/17/3464213/3464213_9E8291DD37284E9690DAC55F700F67CF_171017_3464213_TomoNews_guide_to_PC_Halloweening_costumes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A61/427/A614279589F4E66F1B9FAF09483C93EA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Halloween, Halloween costumes, Halloween costume ideas, trick or treat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464121</guid>
      <title>Atmosphere stacked with ozone-killing chemicals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE ATMOSPHERE  New research suggests the ozone layer maybe be at threat once again.Scientists looking at data from Taiwan and Malaysia found that the atmosphere is stacked with the chemical dichloromethane.This chemical is said to deplete the ozone layer over Earth. The ozone helps to protect Earth from the sun's cancerous ultraviolet rays.Scientist also discovered large traces of the chemical dichloroethane, another ozone depleting chemical.The findings were published in the open-access journal Atmospheric Chemistry and Physics.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 05:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/17/3464121/3464121_29C598354649469B81CE60F4D7E254C2_171017_3464121_Atmosphere_stacked_with_ozone_killing_chemicals_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/577/237/57723719F9CDCB50FA803FBF1FF5DD0B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ozone, ozone study, ozone research, ozone hole, montreal protocol]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465094</guid>
      <title>That's no moon!  Earth's new asteroid pal proven to not be junk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Astronomers have confirmed an asteroid discovered last summer isn't space debris.Dubbed Earth's "new constant companion" by NASA last summer, 2016 HO3 is a small asteroid orbiting the Sun on a trajectory that overlaps with the planet.The space agency speculates that it is between 120 and 300 feet in size. Some thought it was actually "space junk"  debris from old rockets and satellites  but new research has confirmed that it is indeed an asteroid.The asteroid is a quasi-satellite to Earth. It orbits closer to the sun than Earth does in 6-month period, while the rest of time it falls further behind. This is different to natural satellites, such as the Moon, where orbits are tied solely to a planet or a star.The findings were presented by University of Arizona Professor Vishnu Reddy at the annual Division for Planetary Sciences Conference of the American Astronomical Society in Provo, Utah.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 10:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/18/3465094/3465094_81388041A402467387C37CF5ADA378DF_171018_3465094_That_s_no_moon___Earth_s_new_asteroid_pal_proven_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/09D/42A/09D42AE703674C069789BE19C37A216B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, asteroid 2016 ho3, new asteroid, mini moon, nasa asteroid, earth asteroid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465089</guid>
      <title>Iceland flips switch on first 'negative emissions' power plant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ICELAND  Iceland has opened the world's first power plant that eliminates more carbon dioxide than it produces. The geothermal plant in cooperation with Climeworks will remove an estimated 50 metric tons of CO2 from the air each year where it will be turned into limestone and stored in the ground, Quartz reported.The process works by pulling CO2 from the ambient air using a special filter. The heat from the power plant warms up the filter which extracts pure carbon dioxide. The gas is then combined with water and pumped 700 meters underground. When the carbon dioxide reaches with basaltic rock, it forms minerals. The project is still in the pilot phase, but researchers at Climeworks believe negative emissions plants could be set up around the world. One major obstacle in place is the price. Climeworks estimates it runs around $600 to extract one ton of carbon dioxide from the air. However if economies of scale can be utilized and more plants open up, that price would drop significantly.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 10:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/18/3465089/3465089_8F9839FAE58C4E76B8ECED519052682E_171018_3465089_Iceland_flips_switch_on_first__negative_emission_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/147/B9E/147B9EB94506E8C6306CACFEC0CD4F5C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, negative emissions power plant, renewable energy, carbon direct air capture, Iceland negative emissions power plant, carbon dioxide]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465013</guid>
      <title>Dutch startup training crows to pick up your cigarette butts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NETHERLANDS  A Dutch startup is working to train crows to pick up cigarette butts, according to Popular Mechanics. Crows are highly intelligent and are able to make and use tools. Cigarette butts are the most littered item on the planet with an estimated 4.5 trillion butts thrown away each year, according to Inhabitat. The startup Crowded Cities plans to use the crows to help rid the streets of cigarette butts by teaching them to swap butts for food. The CrowBar is a device with a large funnel for cigarette butts and a peanut dispenser. It works by training crows using a four-step process. The first step presents food next to a cigarette butt, training the birds to expect food from the machine. Second, the machine only gives out food when the crow arrives at the device, teaching the crow how the machine functions.Third, the device only presents a cigarette butt with no food. The crow then starts to look for the food and in the process, knocks the butt into the funnel, dispensing the food. The fourth step involves removing the cigarette butt, but leaving them scattered around the CrowBar. The crow will then start to pick up butts they find and bring them back to the machine. Crowded Cities is currently in the process of putting together a working prototype, Popular Mechanics reported. The next step for researchers will be to study how collecting toxic cigarette butts affects the crows.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 09:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/18/3465013/3465013_5895300602164D579D486D2A4B113B76_171018_3465013_Dutch_startup_training_crows_to_pick_up_your_cig_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F68/3F2/F683F25FD5E567F442EAF2383B126D61.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, CrowBar, Crowded Cities startup, crows cigarette butts, cigarette butt litter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464937</guid>
      <title>Pennywise is taking Halloween art to a whole new level</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  This Halloween will definitely go down in history as the year of the clown. Okay, maybe last year too, and kind of the year before that.But what's new this year is Pennywise paraphernalia popping up profusely. The It movie has helped take pumpkin art and jack-o'-lantern carving to a whole new level.  Talented pumpkin professionals have taken to Twitter en masse to show off their hauntingly terrifying works of art. Some people went the painting route and came up with some crazy colorful creations. While others elected to go the traditional pumpkin carving path plus a pinch of petrifying Pennywise. But in the end, there can only be one true orange clown to rule them all.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/18/3464937/3464937_354E78770A5E4A0EBBF0EB06198A6CE2_171018_3464937_Pennywise_is_taking_Halloween_art_to_a_whole_new_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D8D/34B/D8D34B4C2FEC1A0901CC23852FAACFB8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Pennywise,Pennywise pumpkin carvings,It movie pumpkin carvings,Pennywise clown sightings,Pennywise jack o lanterns]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464906</guid>
      <title>AirAsia flight plummets 20,000 feet, terrifying passengers and crew</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PERTH / AUSTRALIA  Reported by BBC, AirAsia flight forced to turn back after take-off on Sunday morning after the pilots were alerted to a possible loss of cabin pressure. Flight QZ535 from Perth to Bali have problem about 25 minutes after take off on Sunday The flight plunges 20,000 feet. The plane drop from 32.000 feet to 10.000 without warning.  Oxygen masks dropped and make all 145 people on board panicked. The panic was escalated because of the behavior of the flight attendants who were screaming, looked tearful and shocked. The flight turned around and made it safely back to Perth.AirAsia has apologised after a that terrifying incident and confirmed on the technical issue on QZ535]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/18/3464906/3464906_506D75DE9F5B4C38BE536EB3E2D7631C_171018_3464906_AirAsia_flight_plummets_20_000_feet__terrifying__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9A7/E76/9A7E76467721FA8C5A525796BA1B878E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, airplane, airasia, Australia, plane emergency, emergency landing, plane plummets, plane falling]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3464853</guid>
      <title>Two colliding neutron stars may have made a black hole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE HYDRA CONSTELLATION  In an astronomical first, scientists detected light and gravity from what they believe was the collision of two ultra-compact dense neutron stars in galaxy NG 4993.First detected in 2013, a kilonova is a class of supernova explosion resulting from two colliding neutron stars.The Space Telescope Science Institute says each neutron in this case was no wider than Washington, D.C. Typically, they're between 6 and 12 miles in diameter.The Institute added that the stars in question weighed between 10 percent and 60 percent more than our sun."What followed the kilonova is unknown, but NASA astrophysicist Eleonora Troja told Space.com the cosmic explosion may have a formed a black hole.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 05:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/18/3464853/3464853_7B2573CD6F9D434A8128932946025E25_171018_3464853_Two_colliding_neutron_stars_may_have_made_a_blac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/065/426/065426D9D63C746BC6B7EFFC8770BFFF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, neutron star collision, neutron star, black hole formation, neutron star, what is a neutron star, black hole explainer, nasa, eso]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465715</guid>
      <title>Dog stays behind to protect baby goats from wildfire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WINE COUNTRY, CALIFORNIA  A hero farm dog called Odin stayed behind to protect his herd of baby goats during a raging blaze in Cali this week. His owners tried to get him to leave, but Odin wouldn't budge, so they left him behind. They returned days later fearing the worst, but to their surprise Odin was alive, albeit a burned, as was the herd of baby goats. YOU CARINGhttp://bit.ly/2ytmZwQ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/19/3465715/3465715_D2E63BB05B7F424DB4ED63CCF92F9354_171019_3465715_Dog_stays_behind_to_protect_baby_goats_from_wild_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/93A/99F/93A99FACFBB20A513A1C6267737DB9DC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, dog rescue stories, odin saves goats, dog rescues goats, california, dog saves baby goats, odin the dog]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465656</guid>
      <title>Critics calling for a virtual Trump border wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEBB COUNTY, TEXAS  A Texas sheriff believes a virtual wall at the U.S.-Mexico border would be more effective than a physical wall. Building an actual wall would have to overcome environmental issues, and deal with the abundance of privately owned land along the border, Webb County Sheriff Martin Cuellar said, the Dallas News reported. Cuellar says the wall would also have an adverse effect on Mexican shoppers traveling between both countries and could potentially hurt Texas' economy. The sheriff has been looking for $92 million in funding over five years for a virtual wall that uses technology and agents on the ground as an alternative to a physical wall, according to the Dallas News. His proposed virtual wall would extend around 300 miles from Starr County to Del Rio. Cost estimates for Trump's border wall range from $21 billion to $40 billion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/19/3465656/3465656_A8A4FCD410C54DBC9AAF11708E3C3B80_171019_3465656_Critics_calling_for_a_virtual_Trump_border_wall_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/240/AE2/240AE27EDA880FE530BB3A7CEF7B5DB7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Trump border wall, Trump virtual border wall, virtual border wall, border wall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465623</guid>
      <title>Aerospace companies partner to launch inflatable lunar habitat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Aerospace companies United Launch Alliance and Bigelow Aerospace are collaborating to put a space station in orbit around the moon.According to a press release from ULA, the lunar depot plan is aiming to place a Bigelow B330 inflatable habitat in low lunar orbit by the end of 2022.ULA's Vulcan rocket will launch the B330 into lower Earth orbit, where it will stay for about a year. While there, the habitat will receive supplies and get crew members rotated every few months.Two more Vulcan rockets will then be launched, and their upper stages  called Advanced Cryogenic Evolved Stage, or ACES  left in orbit. After propellant from one ACES is transferred to the other, the fully fueled stage will attach to the B330 and deliver it to its final position orbiting the moon.The companies claim the habitat can serve both as a platform for lunar business development, and a location for NASA to conduct exploration and astronaut training missions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 08:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/19/3465623/3465623_F5D8403C5DCA4F3B906E057D21ED017E_171019_3465623_Aerospace_companies_partner_to_launch_inflatable_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E4E/6A2/E4E6A29911CB62FF60D4BEA0D7412133.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, moon habitat, lunar habitat, space station, moon space station, bigelow, ULA, united launch alliance, vulcan rocket, b330, b330 habitat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465476</guid>
      <title>China conceptualizes colony of Martian forest cities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW SHANGHAI, MARS  China has conceptualized a colony of forest cities on Mars dubbed "New Shanghai".The concept from the Chinese Space Agency, Tonji University and Stefano Boeri Architects would see a spaceship ferry a colony of massive pods containing forest cities from Earth, toward Mars.Once the pods have touched down on the red planet, Inhabitat reports that they would use "eco-systemic seeds" to take root.This colony of forest city giant pods, dubbed New Shanghai, would also reportedly contain an infrastructure and an Earth-like atmosphere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/19/3465476/3465476_B9DB02C035904EC4830AE03F217357CF_171019_3465476_China_conceptualizes_colony_of_Martian_forest_ci_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0F2/D17/0F2D1787C677B999941D97BBDCF7803F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, mars colony, colonizing mars, china mars, new shanghai, city on mars, forest city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3465469</guid>
      <title>Boy beats back creepy clown prankster with selfie stick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DELTONA, FLORIDA  Florida police are warning creepy clown cosplayers to think twice before sneaking up on unsuspecting victims, who may just serve a can of whoop-ass in self defense.The Volusia County Sheriff's Office put out the statement on their Facebook page after a getting wind of a suspicious incident involving a boy and a clown.On Friday the 13th, the 11-year-old boy had been biking to school when a clown suddenly jumped out at him from some bushes.When it looked like the perp was going to grab him, the boy whipped out a metal selfie stick and whacked the clown multiple times to defend himself.Undeterred, the creeper began to chase the boy, but soon tripped and fell flat on his face, ultimately slinking back into the bushes from whence he came.The boy didn't see any weapons on the clown, but went ahead and told a crossing guard and several teachers about his ordeal. Deputies went back to the scene but didn't find the clown, who was described by the boy as 5 foot 9, about 230 pounds, with blue hair, a rainbow painted face, and red foam nose. With October 31 just around the corner, you'd think people would be less bothered by creepy clown activity. But, guess even Halloween can't save the clowns now.Y'all really need to blame IT on this one.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 04:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/19/3465469/3465469_54CC1BA6D54049CE83D876D892E16205_171019_3465469_Boy_beats_back_creepy_clown_prankster_with_selfi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/656/DDF/656DDFBAB7C23BE0FD6793AC5A22F169.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, creepy clowns, creepy clown, evil clown, creepy clown warning, self defense, creepy clown activity, selfie stick, boy beats clown, halloween, scary clown]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466977</guid>
      <title>Pup dropped from CIA after losing interest in bomb-sniffing job</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LANGLEY, VIRGINIA  An adorable labrador puppy recently got dropped from the CIA after realizing the job wasn't her true calling.According to the CIA blog, Lulu the black labrador retriever had been scouted by the agency a few weeks back, and was being trained to sniff out explosives.As one of six female labs on this year's CIA puppy class, Lulu seemed to be enjoying her valiant new role saving lives...at least at first.Before long, the pup began looking tired and sad, and not at all excited to contribute to society. It soon became clear the bomb-sniffing life wasn't for her.Off days are apparently a thing, even for dogs, though they get back into the groove after some extra playtime or rest.But Lulu could not care less about saving the hoomans from things that go kaboom. Can't say we blame her. Who wants that when you can run and frolic and get belly rubs?In the end, Lulu got cut from the team, but was adopted by her handler and now spends her days living the dog life. The only things she sniffs out now are bunnies and squirrels.Congratulations, dog. Here's hoping the rest of us can muster up the courage to leave the misery of the daily grind and just run wild.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 23:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/21/3466977/3466977_28E125301B694A809A870F95B3864081_171021_3466977_Pup_dropped_from_CIA_after_losing_interest_in_bo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/836/F3C/836F3C057200D73D514F33C30B9DA40F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, CIA, CIA dog, k9 training, k9, bomb sniffing dog, bomb sniffer, dog training, Lulu, Lulu the labrador, CIA puppy class, CIA dogs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466367</guid>
      <title>Study shows massive drop in flying bug populations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GERMANY  Three quarters of insects in protected German nature reserves have disappeared, according to new research. Researchers looked at the biomass of flying bugs of flying insects inside 63 German nature reserves. They found that 76% of the total insect population between 1989 and 2016 had been lost.The cause of the decline is unclear, but the fact the insects vanished at a high rate has scientists concerned. They say their findings could be representative of other areas around the world.The study was published this week in the journal PLOS One.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 07:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/20/3466367/3466367_469F05D4621843FEA43A26CDBCFF36EA_171020_3466367_Study_shows_massive_drop_in_flying_bug_populatio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/103/C49/103C492A24919F9034B5379BCAC1212C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bug population, plos one, germany insect study, bug population, flying insects, nature stories]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466342</guid>
      <title>Study shows mind remains conscious even after clinical death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  Research from the NYU Langone School of Medicine suggests that people's consciousness continue to work even after they have been pronounced dead.According to the study published in the journal Resuscitation, doctors define death as the moment the heart stops beating, cutting off circulation and halting brain and other organ function.Scientists looked at patients who flatlined but were later revived and found that 39% reported some form of awareness while technically dead. Several recalled full conversations, and saw things happening around them- details which were verified by staff present at the time.Theoretically, this could mean the recently deceased are fully aware of their condition, and may even hear the pronouncement of their own death.The study suggests the awareness may be a result of a burst of energy that is released in the brain immediately post-mortem.This finding has been echoed in a 2013 research from the University of Michigan, which observed brain patterns pointing to a 'hyper-alerted state' in nine clinically dead rats.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 07:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/20/3466342/3466342_F1C1A8E4BA5740FF81867942048563B6_171020_3466342_Study_shows_mind_remains_conscious_even_after_cl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3D1/13C/3D113C6A22B4391D62937C245B8FC642.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, brain dead, life after death, near death experience, after death, technically dead, clinically dead, dead, flatline, flatliners, cardiac arrest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466185</guid>
      <title>11-year-old forced to change after school deems dress 'distracting'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BILLINGS, MONTANA  Most schools have no problem with girls in sleeveless outfits. But at Lockwood school in Billings, Montana, shoulders are apparently considered scandalous.Yahoo Lifestyle reports that 11-year-old Vegas learned this the hard way when she showed up for picture day in a cute new sleeveless dress over black leggings. The kid had simply dressed up for the perfect photo, but promptly got policed for violating the dress code. It seems the ultra-conservative school board came up with a ridiculous new policy banning bare shoulders. The school even reportedly said the child's shoulders were "distracting."The girl's family was so outraged by the asinine rule that both mom and grandma took to social media to rant. Miffed netizens soon began to chime in, criticizing the school and its dress code for sexualizing young girls.Ultimately, the school did allow the poor student to take her photo in the dress, but forced her to change into something more "appropriate" for the rest of the day.The girl has since been understandably upset, but the administration refuses to discuss the issue further, noting that since the child changed her clothes, the case is closed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 02:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/20/3466185/3466185_110F2D6A734A49DC87A90965A4815C29_171020_3466185_11_year_old_forced_to_change_after_school_deems__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BDE/1E0/BDE1E072A4F754B52DF3F889CAA9DC6E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, dress code violation, school dress code, dress code, bare shoulders, school policy, student dress code, Lockwood school, Billings, Montana]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3466179</guid>
      <title>Los Angeles police to test drones amid privacy concerns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  The Los Angeles Police Commission has voted in favor of allowing the LAPD to use drones in a year-long pilot program, the Los Angeles Times reported. This will make the LAPD the largest US police force to use the robotic aerial drones. Only SWAT team members in high-risk situations will be able to fly the drones. They will be deployed for aerial searches and gathering intelligence in tense situations. The drones will also be used in search and rescue missions. Every flight needs to be approved, documented and reviewed, according to Engadget. The Police Commission will receive quarterly reports that will be made public, the Los Angeles Times reported. Weapons and facial-recognition technology are prohibited. LAPD officials have attempted to address privacy concerns by saying the restrictions in place along with strong oversight would be sufficient, although many critics still remain wary. The commission will evaluate the performance of the pilot program after a year in order to decide whether to continue or not.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 02:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/20/3466179/3466179_608E6067AF4A401C961CA50DAC17A107_171020_3466179_Los_Angeles_police_to_test_drones_amid_privacy_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3DC/9B1/3DC9B1C23F3A13237430D99F039F81CE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, LAPD drones, LAPD drones pilot program, police drones, aerial drones, drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3467072</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered cave system on the moon could host lunar base</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOON  A cavernous lava tube was this week confirmed to exist beneath the surface of the moon. The discovery was after by a team of Japanese and American scientists using data from the SELENE and GRAIL spacecraft to acoustically map the enormous lava tube.These tubes are volcanic underground passages formed by flowing lava to funnel the substance. Once the flow stops, the tube remains with features similar to a cave.The chasm is around 100 meters wide and 50 kilometers long, reported the Guardian. It is located in the Marius Hills region of the celestial body.The cave could provide shelter to astronauts during moon missions, protecting them from dangerous cosmic radiation. This could potentially allow for the development of a lunar exploration base.Details of the finding was published in the journal, Geophysical Research Letters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 06:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/21/3467072/3467072_2BBF8A68F63F425C859EC25489D79A15_171021_3467072_Newly_discovered_cave_system_on_the_moon_could_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B69/608/B696087E7180C9D0FA6891347674EA1A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, moon cave, moon base, human moon colony, nasa, jaxa, colonizing the moon, moon exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468347</guid>
      <title>What is broken heart syndrome?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMP WOOD, TEXAS  A Texan woman was hospitalized due to literal heartbreak after her pet dog Meha passed away. Also known as Takotsubo cardiomyopathy, the condition affects vastly more women than men. Symptoms involve a shortness of breath and chest painExperts believe the sheer amount of adrenaline and hormones triggered by the stressful event may temporarily stupefy the heart. NEW YORK DAILY NEWShttp://nydn.us/2yZrpvSHARVARD HEALTHhttp://bit.ly/2gC6AiO]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 11:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/23/3468347/3468347_B51D746D0A1040C1992B4A95B92EB94B_171023_3468347_What_is_broken_heart_syndrome__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/989/30A/98930AE6737031D79175BAD341A06B47.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, what is a broken heart, broken heart explained, broken heart syndrome, how does the heart break, heart break hospitalization, Takotsubo cardiomyopathy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468316</guid>
      <title>South Korea plans 'frankenmissile' to take out North Korean weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  South Korea has revealed plans to build a new missile to take on the North, should war break out on the Korean peninsula.Korea Herald reports that the South Korean military is planning to counter Pyongyang's growing weapons capabilities by developing the Hyunmoo-IV, a surface-to-surface missile with an 800-km range and a payload of up to 2 tons.It will be powerful enough to destroy the North's underground military facilities and command centers, and is set to be the final weapon to be mobilized in Seoul's three-tier attack plan.According to Yonhap News, the plan's first step involves launching a KTSSM missile to strike North Korean artillery that have been camouflaged and embedded along the DMZ and on the coast of border islands.Hyunmoo-2 ballistic missiles will then be deployed to neutralize the enemy's nuclear weapons, weapons of mass destruction, and their delivery systems.The development of the 'frankenmissile' is part of army efforts to establish a five-pillar operational concept that can minimize civilian casualties and put an early end to armed conflict.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 10:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/23/3468316/3468316_B60900D4863045CD9184C07825062793_171023_3468316_South_Korea_plans__frankenmissile__to_take_out_N_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/453/2A7/4532A71864845946889477E18FCFC566.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, frankenmissile, monster missile, south korea missile, hyunmoo missile, hyunmoo 4, hyunmoo IV, north korea weapons, korean war, north korea nuclear]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468286</guid>
      <title>Maryland gives Elon Musk green light for hyperloop tunnel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE  Maryland officials have given Elon Musk the green light to dig tunnels for a hyperloop project between New York and Washington, the Baltimore Sun reported. Last Thursday, the state issued a conditional utility permit to allow Musk's Boring Co. to dig a 10.3-mile tunnel between the state-owned section of the Baltimore-Washington Parkway, between the Baltimore city line and Maryland 175 in Hanover, according to the Baltimore Sun. The Boring Co. wants to construct two 35-mile tunnels between Baltimore and Washington, D.C., according to Maryland Transportation Secretary Pete Rahn, reported the Baltimore Sun.The U.S. government owns roughly two-thirds of the land Musk's company plans to dig underneath, Ars Technica reported. The 10-mile section approved by Maryland will be the first section of the underground system.   Once completed, the hyperloop trip between Washington and New York would only take 29 minutes. The Boring Co. looks to reduce traffic congestion by creating a low-cost system of tunnels. The company has developed tunneling machines that can efficiently drill through soft soil at only a fraction of the cost of traditional tunneling.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 10:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/23/3468286/3468286_471434AE6B6E4339A88765BFE2C1E374_171023_3468286_Maryland_gives_Elon_Musk_green_light_for_hyperlo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/62F/DB4/62FDB49298722A487D96E4F8F02C7380.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Hyperloop, The Boring Company, Elon Musk, Maryland hyperloop project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468155</guid>
      <title>Badger breaks into house, feasts on cat food and foodcomas on cat bed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LINLITHGOW, SCOTLAND  A soporific badger broke into a Scottish home last week and took a nap on a cat bed.The animal reportedly feasted on a loot of cat food before dozing off. The Scottish Protection for Cruelty to Animals were alerted to the break in and dispatched an officer to deal with the errant beast. The badger reportedly took one look at the female officer, and then escaped via an open back door.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 07:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/23/3468155/3468155_64085100E7784F0A86C7F5ED7EC73C9E_171023_3468155_Badger_breaks_into_house__feasts_on_cat_food_and_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/27F/B09/27FB09222E252B06D142FB59056EE1DD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, animal break in, animal invasion, badger, cat food, cat bed, home intruder, Linlithgow, Scotland, home predator, house break in, home invasion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468068</guid>
      <title>Woman's catfishing nightmare ends with dreamy romance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  While other women who got catfished online ended up in tears, one lucky gal's catfishing nightmare led her to find her dreamy happily-ever-after.The Atlantic reports that Emma Perrier joined matchmaking app Zoosk in 2015 and met a hot Italian named Ronnie. The two hit it off spectacularly, but unbeknownst to Perrier, 'Ronnie' was really a balding, 53-year-old divorcee named Alan Stanley.Stanley was a serial catfisher, and 'Ronnie' was one of several personas he'd used over the years to bait women into online relationships.The two chatted for six months, forming a romance and exchanging 'I love yous' without ever meeting in person.Perrier set out to investigate after growing suspicious of Ronnie's excuses, eventually finding out the identity of the man in the photos, and the man she was actually talking to.Stanley tried to cover up his lie at first, but ended up confessing to his duplicity.The real Ronnie turned out to be Turkish model Adem Guzal, who Perrier decided to hit up to warn of the catfishing scheme.The pair began messaging back and forth, and pretty soon sparks were flying between the long-distance lovebirds.Guzel flew to London in January 2017 to visit Perrier, and the deal was sealed.The two have now been in a relationship for six months and are living together in London. Ironically, Guzel is auditioning for 'Aladdin', which one paper called the original catfishing story.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 04:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/23/3468068/3468068_0D2F7DE883724E479885D44A76700822_171023_3468068_Woman_s_catfishing_nightmare_ends_with_dreamy_ro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C41/E63/C41E6315F73E294B55980C4AB074AA20.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, catfishing, online relationship, online dating, Zoosk, Emma Perrier, Adem Guzel, Alan Stanley]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469146</guid>
      <title>New study says it's possible to sweat blood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANADA  A rare condition called hematohidrosis causes people to sweat blood, says a new study. A 21-year-old Italian woman was found to have been bleeding intermittently from her face and palms for three years, according to a study published in the Canadian Medical Association Journal. Episodes seemed to be triggered without warning, although stress would often intensify the bleeding.  She was eventually diagnosed with blood sweating, or hematohidrosis. This condition causes blood to seep out of unbroken skin like normal perspiration.It's most common on the face, ears, nose and eyes and is often associated with fear and emotional stress, according to the National Institutes of Health Genetic and Rare Diseases Information Center, Time reported. The woman was treated with a beta blocker  propranolol  normally used to regulate blood pressure and heart rate. The medicine did not stop the bleeding, but she did experience a "marked reduction" in symptoms.  Medical experts still don't know what causes the condition.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 13:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/24/3469146/3469146_3C0130A6BC264FB18BA6D1B09C9776DC_171024_3469146_New_study_says_it_s_possible_to_sweat_blood_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/53F/2B2/53F2B23A113A5E857DED9A63DC0D6446.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Hematohidrosis, blood sweating, blood crying, stress induced conditions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469041</guid>
      <title>Ovarian cancer may actually start in the fallopian tube</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE  A preliminary study of ovarian cancer suggests that its roots may lie in the fallopian tubes  a finding that could provide new insight in treating the deadly disease.Science Daily reports that ovarian cancer is the fifth largest cause of cancer deaths in women, as it is often detected late, or is already widespread at the time of diagnosis.Scientists from the Johns Hopkins Kimmel Cancer Center and the Dana Farber Cancer Institute in Boston examined cell samples from women with ovarian tumors and those with cancer risk factors. The analysis revealed that all the women had mutations affecting the cancer-guarding p53 gene, and had lost chromosomes containing one or both BRCA1 and BRCA2 tumor-suppressing genes.They tracked the source of the mutations to the fallopian tubes, where the cancer developed and eventually migrated to the ovaries over a 6.5-year period. Once in the ovaries, the cancer progressed more rapidly, metastasizing within two years.The team's findings will need to be further validated by additional studies, but the results provide a glimmer of hope.With such a large window from fallopian tube to ovarian cancer, scientists believe new methods should be developed to detect and treat the cancer while it's still localized in the tubes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 11:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/24/3469041/3469041_1D6BFB99FD914883861C4922889DACB8_171024_3469041_Ovarian_cancer_may_actually_start_in_the_fallopi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EEE/C30/EEEC30B63041B369481EEA8E02C5E8A6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ovarian cancer, cancer, fallopian tube cancer, cancer cells, tumors, cysts, metastasis, deadly disease, johns hopkins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468804</guid>
      <title>A spacecraft cemetery exists in the middle of the Pacific Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[POINT NEMO  Nations around the world bring down old spacecraft when possible in the most remote place on Earth called Point Nemo, Business Insider reported.  Smaller satellites burn up in the atmosphere upon reentry, but larger pieces can reach Earth's surface. The spacecraft graveyard is around 1,450 nautical miles away from any land. It lies in the South Pacific in a no-man's land between Australia, New Zealand and South America, according to the BBC.  This oceanic pole of inaccessibility covers an area around 580 square miles (1,500 sq km) and is home to more than 260 dead spacecraft, mostly Russian, the BBC reported.China lost control of its Tiangong-1 space station in March 2016, which is now expected to crash into the Earth by early 2018. Since the Chinese are not in control of the spacecraft, they are currently unsure where pieces of the station will make contact. Experts won't be able to make predictions until days before Tiangong-1 is expected to break up in the atmosphere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 06:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/24/3468804/3468804_4F8E517B79AD41D6A7973472B00391FB_171024_3468804_A_spacecraft_cemetery_exists_in_the_middle_of_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/283/A5F/283A5F9A5C272FC0FA8E10720F11CE92.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, spacecraft graveyard, spacecraft cemetery, satellite graveyard, Point Nemo, Pacific Ocean satellite debris]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468785</guid>
      <title>Mars has a twisted magnetotail, says NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE RED PLANET  New research using data gathered from NASA's MAVEN mission to Mars suggests the planet's atmosphere maybe getting destroyed by thinned via solar wind.Mars, like most planets, has a magnetotail. This is the side of a planet not facing the sun.NASA now suspects that Mar's is different, in that it's magnetotail is twisted by solar winds from the sun.The space agency suspects this may have contributed to the thinning of the red planet's atmosphere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 06:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/24/3468785/3468785_B4D44F1AFFE44AC8AD349EBEEC12B30B_171024_3468785_Mars_has_a_twisted_magnetotail__says_NASA_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3BD/142/3BD142C042174F7DFF57CC5D3B47789C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, magnetotail reconnection, martian atmosphere, solar wind, maven mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3468721</guid>
      <title>Giant floating balloons deliver mobile service to Puerto Rico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN JUAN, PUERTO RICO  Giant balloons are now delivering mobile access to hurricane-ravaged Puerto Rico, thanks to a team-up between Google's parent company Alphabet, and AT&T.According to the Federal Communications Commission, more than 68% of cell sites in Puerto Rico are still out of service as of OCtober 20  one month after the island was devastated by Hurricane Maria.Reuters reports that to help restore communications, Project Loon has deployed giant balloons, which use the AT&T network, to provide emergency internet service on the island.The service is limited to those with LTE-enabled phones, and supports text messaging, email, and basic web browsing.The balloons float 20 kilometers up in the stratosphere, providing service to a roughly 5,000 square-kilometer area. Solar panels power daytime operations, while also charging a battery for nighttime use.Though still an experimental technology, Project Loon proved effective in early 2017, when it provided basic connectivity to flood-affected areas in Peru.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 04:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/24/3468721/3468721_00F7EBE161BA4CC19C1E914D760C1C55_171024_3468721_Giant_floating_balloons_deliver_mobile_service_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E64/C4E/E64C4E4DE4774F6529745852FB62C60C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, connectivity, internet access, mobile service, mobile signal, project loon, balloon signal, balloon, puerto rico, hurricane maria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469627</guid>
      <title>Google investigating reports of screenburn in new $800 phone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Technology giant Google is investigating reports of screenburn issues with its latest smartphone. Android Central editor Alex Dobie reported how a test Google Pixel 2 XL he was sent suffered from screen burn after 7 days of use.Screen-burn usually happens after several years of use. Others have reportedly told of similar issues with the device.A mobile analyst told Reuters, that if the company finds a problem with the device, it may need to halt production of it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 08:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/25/3469627/3469627_0522EAD2F6634433A3B243B3A704B2E4_171025_3469627_Google_investigating_reports_of_screenburn_in_ne_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C66/777/C667770F12477DAA4AD1D38A664C07F9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, pixel 2 xl, google pixel 2, pixel 2 xl screen burn, screen burn-in, google recall, google pixel 2 2017]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469601</guid>
      <title>Photo of cute rescue dog's smile goes viral</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WALLER, TEXAS  Meet Cheech, this little guy's a rescue dog at the City of Waller Animal Shelter in Texas whose smile has gone viral. CITY OF WALLER ANIMAL SHELTER AND RESCUEhttp://bit.ly/2zOIMgkFOX 13 (ARTICLE)http://bit.ly/2i3DsNJ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 07:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/25/3469601/3469601_1606519C507A49D18B33957F5C29C12E_171025_3469601_Photo_of_cute_rescue_dog_s_smile_goes_viral_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AE8/320/AE8320FA5AAB3420CEF0FC3C7F665D65.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, rescue dog story, rescue dog, cheech, smiling dog, happy dog stories, positive dog stories, people making a difference, texas rescue dogs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469584</guid>
      <title>Mars study reveals planet maybe ideal for CO and O2 production</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MATT DAMON'S HOME AWAY FROM HOME  New research suggests that the carbon-dioxide dense Martian atmosphere might be key to producing oxygen on the red planet.Researchers believe that this abundant resource, combined with the cold Martian temperature and non-thermal plasma can produce oxygen and carbon monoxide.Local production of these gases on Mars could, in theory, help sustain an outpost or even colony on the red planet, and help with the deeper exploration of the solar system.The study was published in the journal Plasma Sources Science and Technology.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 07:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/25/3469584/3469584_0479024948124F3B982B00575A517619_171025_3469584_Mars_study_reveals_planet_maybe_ideal_for_CO_and_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/33C/9A7/33C9A7D99A255C53C5246C0020A8ACD9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, carbon dioxide to oxygen mars, martian colony, oxygen on mars, co2 on mars, making co2 from oxygen, decomposition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469565</guid>
      <title>China plans to launch Social Credit System in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Beijing plans to launch its Social Credit System nationwide by 2020 to rate the trustworthiness of 1.3 billion people by assigning each individual a score.  The goal of the program is to "forge a public opinion environment where keeping trust is glorious. It will strengthen sincerity in government affairs, commercial sincerity, social sincerity and the construction of judicial credibility," according to the Chinese government, Wired reported. Participation currently remains voluntary, but by 2020, it will be mandatory. The Chinese Communist Party has given out eight licenses to private companies to develop systems and algorithms for a social credit score system. The two biggest projects are run by China Rapid Finance and Sesame Credit. Sesame Credit, for example, gives individuals a score between 350 and 950 points based on a private algorithm calculated from five factors: credit history, contract obligation fulfillment, personal characteristics, behavior and preferences and interpersonal relationships.Once the system becomes mandatory, people with low scores could be punished with slower internet speeds, be denied access to certain restaurants, night clubs or golf courses and restricted from traveling. Scores will also affect an individual's rental applications, ability to secure insurance or a loan, as well as social security benefits. Citizens with low scores will be forbidden from certain jobs and from applying to better schools.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 06:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/25/3469565/3469565_823D9E3E876E4692809A52AD92FA2061_171025_3469565_China_plans_to_launch_Social_Credit_System_in_20_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FF0/936/FF09364A1920425F89AF33C6172955A2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China Social Credit System, China state surveillance, China social credit score, big brother, big data]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469555</guid>
      <title>Police save cat during California wildfires</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SONOMA COUNTY, CALIFORNIA  Earlier this month deputies in Sonoma County banded together to save this little feline from underneath a car.SFGATEhttp://bit.ly/2gH3Dx4]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 06:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/25/3469555/3469555_C4055049696F4B559E8ECA7EBEBD4FEC_171025_3469555_Police_save_cat_during_California_wildfires_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C60/2EA/C602EAD64A4F4CF7030472656EFC7B8D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cat rescue stories, cop saves cat, police save cat, happy cat stories, cat reuinited with owner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469525</guid>
      <title>'Idiots of the century' swim into baited crocodile trap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA  Photos of four men messing around with a baited croc trap have surfaced outline, and everyone's heads are reeling from the stupid.The Sydney Morning Herald reports that a 79-year-old woman got snatched by a 4.3-meter-long croc in the same area less than two weeks ago, which makes the foursome's stunt even more dangerous and idiotic.Most people see a trap and take it as an indication that the water is unsafe and teeming with crocodiles. But not these fellas.We're not sure if they were dumb enough not to know what traps were for, or if they just didn't care.Either way, the four men played around the baited trap like it was some sort of adult jungle gym  climbing on top, and even going inside. Nevermind that there was a big glaring warning sign. Australian authorities have yet to identify the men, but they stand to face fines of up to $15,000 if found and convicted of tampering with the traps.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 06:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/25/3469525/3469525_7CE869ED558E4E1DB08F9BDBB670587A_171025_3469525__Idiots_of_the_century__swim_into_baited_crocodi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AC9/0D9/AC90D948D445F2A5F5EEAFF2EB96402F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, crocodile, croc trap, idiots, crocodile bait, croc bait, queensland, port douglas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3469434</guid>
      <title>Super Mario to visit NYC-inspired kingdom in new video game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DONK CITY  Nintendo will this week release Super Mario Odyssey for their Switch console.The game reportedly features a New York parody city dubbed New Donk City, "the city that never leaps."Super Mario Odyssey is available October 27.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 03:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/25/3469434/3469434_C3643E2234A44BAA8986FB1A195DB939_171025_3469434_Super_Mario_to_visit_NYC_inspired_kingdom_in_new_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F6C/5D2/F6C5D28C993B35E0376AD03120F284CE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, super mario, super mario odyssey, mario, luigi, bowser, princess peach, new donk city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470415</guid>
      <title>Study finds way to rewrite genetic blueprint without DNA alterations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  Scientists have found a way to rework genetic information without altering DNA, according to new research.The study, published in the journal Science, details how DNA instructions directed at proteins can be chemically altered via edits to information in the RNA. The DNA remains unchanged, but proteins build cells based on the edited instructions.The method is not ready for human trials but it could be used to help sufferers of degenerative diseases such as amyotrophic lateral sclerosis in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/26/3470415/3470415_3B91034C540D465BA320F42B02EBFB07_171026_3470415_Study_finds_way_to_rewrite_genetic_blueprint_wit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DCD/004/DCD0040FDFBB5B469B80949D01EA85C6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, dna, broad institute, dna changes, changing dna, cell manipulation, rna repair, rna editing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470371</guid>
      <title>US Navy sends third aircraft carrier to the Pacific</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PACIFIC OCEAN  The aircraft carrier USS Nimitz arrived in the Pacific on Tuesday, bringing the number of carriers to three now operating in the region. The carrier and its accompanying strike group of destroyers, cruisers and submarines has joined the U.S. Navy's 7th Fleet area of operations, the Navy said news releases, CNN reported. The Nimitz now joins the USS Ronald Reagan, which is stationed in Japan year-round, and the USS Theodore Roosevelt, which is currently far east of Japan, according to Business Insider. The Navy reported that the Nimitz just finished three months of in the Middle East battling ISIS, launching 1,322 sorties with 903 pieces of ordnance dropped, according to Military.com.Navy spokeswoman Lt. Mary Walsh described the carrier's activities as standard, and said that the Nimitz would only be in the region temporarily, Military.com reported.  The USS Roosevelt is expected to eventually take the Nimitz's place in the Middle East, according to CNN. Pyongyang hasn't launched a missile in over a month, however tensions still remain high in the region.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 08:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/26/3470371/3470371_48C810F8676C4874A715B9AD60AFE72D_171026_3470371_US_Navy_sends_third_aircraft_carrier_to_the_Paci_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7C7/71E/7C771E6BA641C598C779C1CF09631880.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US aircraft carriers, USS Nimitz, USS Nimitz Pacific Ocean, USS Ronald Reagan, USS Theodore Roosevelt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470260</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia planning to build $500 billion mega-city</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIYADH, SAUDI ARABIA  The Saudi Arabian government says it plans to build a $500 billion mega-city that stretches into Jordan and Egypt, and is completely powered by renewable energy. Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman announced the project on Tuesday at the Future Investment Initiative conference in Riyadh, Business Insider reported.  The project is called NEOM and will measure 10,230 square miles, which is 33 times larger than New York City, according to Business Insider. The $500 billion dollars will come from the Saudi government, its sovereign wealth fund and investors, according to the statement released at the conference, Bloomberg reported. One of the main goals of NEOM will be to diversify Saudi Arabia's economy in an attempt to move it beyond oil. The mega-city will focus on industries such as energy and water, biotechnology, food, advanced manufacturing and entertainment, Business Insider reported. No master plans have been released yet as to what the city will look like.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 05:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/26/3470260/3470260_C081FCB0AC87408ABEE5D2E77629D217_171026_3470260_Saudi_Arabia_planning_to_build__500_billion_mega_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/972/1A9/9721A925429419E173098596019E3D5D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Saudi Arabia mega-city, NEOM mega-city, NEOM project, NEOM city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470220</guid>
      <title>Russia to test new 'Satan-2' ICBM that it claims can hit the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Russia is preparing to test-launch its latest nuclear-armed intercontinental ballistic missile, which it claims can get through America's defense shield. The RS-28 Sarmat, or Satan-2, weighs over 100 metric tonnes, with Russian state-linked media claiming it has a 10,000-km range, according to the Independent.Moscow says the Satan-2 is capable of destroying an area the size of Texas.The RS-28 Sarmat is equipped with multiple hypersonic warheads  MIRVs  to help it evade missile defense systems. The Russian government says the new missile can carry a payload of up to 15 warheads. The first test-launches are slated to be held at the Plesetsk testing ground in western Russia by the end of the year.   Russia is planning for the RS-28 to enter service by the start of the next decade as a part of its ongoing push to modernize its nuclear arsenal.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 04:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/26/3470220/3470220_7876AFBEFC5E4CD5B919F0B3B52295EB_171026_3470220_Russia_to_test_new__Satan_2__ICBM_that_it_claims_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F74/8B0/F748B07AACE8A0AB30DC975E5DB8B627.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Russia, ballistic missile, Russia Satan-2 missile, ICBMs, MIRVs, RS-28 Sarmat missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3471337</guid>
      <title>Trump declassifies some JFK assassination documents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  President Trump has ordered the release of 2,800 JFK assassination files, but blocked others because of national security concerns.Congress passed a law in 1992 requiring all assassination records  about five million pages  to be open to the public within 25 years. That deadline was Thursday.More than 90% of the files were already public, according to BBC. Will these new files shed some more light on the assassination? Was Lee Harvey the actual shooter, or just a patsy? News sites have actually taken to live streaming the document release  aka  posting the documents online for you to read as well as promising plenty of "live updates". Who would have thought a dead topic could have so much life? At least now with the records out, all conspiracy theories on JFK will finally be put to rest. Maybe even all conspiracy theories?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 11:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/27/3471337/3471337_670964487E15471498F6DF26EF1B8255_171027_3471337_Trump_declassifies_some_JFK_assassination_docume_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/57B/5F4/57B5F419D64EA273F6F439AAC4D85346.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, JFK assassination documents, JFK assassination files, JFK files, JFK file release]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3471193</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia just gave a fembot citizenship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIYADH  The Kingdom of Saudi Arabia has granted a Hong-Kong designed cyborg citizenship. It's a world-first, but automatically puts a machine's rights miles ahead of many men and women's in the country.Under Saudi law, kids born there to a foreign pops and Saudi moms aren't considered citizens until they reach a very vaguely defined "age of maturity".]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 09:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/27/3471193/3471193_78E5C63F45C144DDA77E2232F39223AA_171027_3471193_Saudi_Arabia_just_gave_a_fembot_citizenship_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D64/2CB/D642CB893CB09048D0ED53FEB13D227E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, saudi arabia, ksa, citizenship, robot, first robot citizen, saudization]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3471085</guid>
      <title>DNA tagging spray helps UK cops identify, link suspects to crime</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Police in the UK are deploying a chemical liquid that clings to clothes and skin in order to crack down on moped-riding bandits.According to SelectaDNA, officers can spray fleeing offenders with a tagging spray, which marks them and their vehicles with an invisible dye.The spray contains DNA code, with each can bearing a unique chemical signature.The odorless liquid can only be seen under UV light. It cannot be scrubbed off, and can remain on a person's clothes and skin for months.The spray not only helps identify suspects, but also serves to effectively link them to their specific crime.According to the Pontefract and Castleford Express, one 18-year-old has already been charged and sentenced with the help of the tagging spray. At least two other teens have been arrested for moped-related crimes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 07:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/27/3471085/3471085_C91C9F19D0BD46B381A3DE1EA1D3FA71_171027_3471085_DNA_tagging_spray_helps_UK_cops_identify__link_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7BC/791/7BC791343113A55909FDD70B638FF1AF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, dna tagging spray, dna spray, selectaDNA, dna, dna marker, criminals, crime, anti theft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3471038</guid>
      <title>India is sending a rover to the Moon in 2018</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BENGALURU, INDIA  The Indian Space Research Organization has announced plans to send a rover to the moon early next year, nearly a decade after its first lunar journey met with mixed success.First Post reports that the spacecraft for India's Chandrayaan-2 moon mission is comprised of an orbiter, a lander, and a rover, which will first slingshot around Earth before being going into lunar orbit.The lander will attempt a controlled or soft landing near the moon's south pole, while the orbiter travels around the moon.Once on the surface, the lander will take thermal measurements and deploy the six-wheeled rover to explore the lunar terrain.Among the things the mission will pay close attention to are abrasive particles known as lunar dust, which pose a significant challenge to human colonization of the moon.The Chandrayaan-2 will be carried into space by the GSLV Mark II rocket, and is scheduled to launch from an island in the Bay of Bengal in March 2018.India will carry out the final testing phase for the spacecraft in the coming weeks. The program's budget for the mission is relatively small, at only 93 million dollars.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 06:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/27/3471038/3471038_55941DEAD52345AFB9C57BD521A5DFF0_171027_3471038_India_is_sending_a_rover_to_the_Moon_in_2018_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F65/41F/F6541FC1B6033C14FA2647484E2312F1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, moon mission, india moon rover, india moon mission, chandrayaan, chandrayaan 2, moon rover, lunar mission, india space program, ISRO]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3471005</guid>
      <title>Japanese police finally catch 74-year-old grandpa ninja</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OSAKA, JAPAN  Japanese police say they have finally caught a notorious thief who dressed up as a ninja during his robberies. The guy was 74. Police believe the suspect, also known as the "Ninja of Heisei", is responsible for more than 250 break-ins, BBC reported. The old dude was able to lift over 30m yen ($260,000) worth in stolen goods. Authorities had been trying to catch the crafty ninja for over eight years, but they always thought the suspect was someone much younger. But luck was on their side when a security camera was able to get a look at his uncovered face earlier this year. The police started tailing him, which eventually led to his arrest in July. The police said he would change into his ninja outfit after dark before going on jobs. Looks like the old guy enjoyed showing off his skills by running on tops of walls instead of taking the streets. After his arrest, the ninja said this, "If I were younger, I wouldn't have been caught. I'll quit now as I'm 74 and old enough."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 06:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/27/3471005/3471005_9907B66E091C4139BD43D8087FF6A591_171027_3471005_Japanese_police_finally_catch_74_year_old_grandp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DAD/8D3/DAD8D388A5C2B57677AAA666481512BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ninja, ninja thief, ninja robber, 74-year-old ninja, 74-year-old ninja thief, 74-year-old ninja robber, Osaka ninja robber]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3470992</guid>
      <title>Norway has designed Europe's first underwater restaurant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALY, NORWAY  Design firm Snøhetta this week unveiled concept art for Europe's first subsea restaurant on the south Norwegian coast.Aptly dubbed Under, Inhabitat reports that the establishment will provide viewers with a panoramic view of the seabed.Diners will also be able eat locally procured seafood while taking in the view of underwater life.Under is said to be heated via thermal energy gathered from the seabed, and it will also double as a marine research center.The restaurant is set to open in early 2019, reported CNN.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 05:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/27/3470992/3470992_29BC5C27ADD449C7961128DA72D6696A_171027_3470992_Norway_has_designed_Europe_s_first_underwater_re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2F7/A43/2F7A4381F4601E779C6A1F74A53BFDE1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, underwater restaurant, underwater dining, subsea diner, underwater diner, unique dining experiences]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3473025</guid>
      <title>Experimental vaccine targets HIV's protective shield</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLLEGE PARK, MARYLAND  University of Maryland and Duke University researchers have designed a new vaccine that was able to stimulate an immune response against HIV's protective shield.According to the study published in the journal Cell Chemical Biology, HIV virus cells are covered with a protective protein called GP120, which itself is covered by a sugar shield to help bolster its defenses.Some infected individuals who can keep the virus at bay without medication often have have antibodies that attack the protein.There has been little success in creating a similar vaccine, because the sugars found in the shield resemble sugars in the human body. It's also difficult to engineer antibodies that can be effective against the multiple strains of HIV, which frequently mutate.Using a synthetic chemistry method, scientists have now designed a vaccine combining a gp120 fragment and a sugar molecule, and tested it on HIV-infected rabbits.The vaccine prompted the rabbits' immune systems to produce antibodies that physically bound to gp120 found in four dominant HIV strains.It takes roughly two years to build immunity against HIV, so despite sticking to the virus, the antibodies weren't able to prevent further infection.But the vaccine's ability to induce a strong immune response in a short amount of time is encouraging, and researchers believe further studies can produce a vaccine that can ultimately neutralize the deadly virus.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 10:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/30/3473025/3473025_C5A2F595C6DD4F0B946C673B7F84BEB5_171030_3473025_Experimental_vaccine_targets_HIV_s_protective_sh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C1F/E3F/C1FE3F1A43556184725397AC71264753.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, hiv vaccine, hiv cure, aids cure, aids vaccine, hiv, aids, gp120, hiv shield, hiv sugar shield, university of maryland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472949</guid>
      <title>Woman gives birth to her biological son during surrogate pregnancy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA  Earlier this year Cali woman Jessica Allen gave birth to what she thought was twins while acting as a surrogate mother. Little did she know, one was actually her own biological son. She conceived him while already carrying the surrogate child in a rare case of superfetation. Speaking to the New York Post, Jessica says the Chinese couple who hired her womb wanted nearly $20,000 in compensation after finding the child wasn't theirs.  The adoption agency who arranged it all wanted money for looking after their baby boy,  Jessica told the Post. To make matters worse, she says both the agency and couple were separately considering putting the child up for adoption. But Jessica says the couple nada and she eventually got her son back, though the legal costs left her and husband Jasper $3,000 out of pocket. NEW YORK POSThttp://nyp.st/2xzS3XN]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/30/3472949/3472949_FA7BC60B95D64F5D960CB403D2522865_171030_3472949_Woman_gives_birth_to_her_biological_son_during_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/707/0C4/7070C461AA35441A86415E394FD79114.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, superfetation, what is is superfetation, pregnant while pregnant, getting pregnant while pregnant, woman gets pregnant, amazing baby stories, pregnant again, can you get pregnant while pregnant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472910</guid>
      <title>Paralyzed man can stand again after experimental treatment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOUISVILLE, KENTUCKY  A man paralyzed following a serious motorcycle injury has regained the ability to stand and move his legs after receiving an experimental epidural treatment. Andrew Meas was paralyzed from the chest down after his spine was broken at the sixth and seventh cervical vertebrae in a accident nearly 10 years ago, Newsweek reported. Meas has spent four years in physical rehabilitation, but has also been receiving an experimental treatment called spinal cord epidural stimulation (scES) from a research team at the University of Louisville, Quartz reported.    The device sends electrical signals to motor neurons telling them to move. Meas was one of four patients to receive the implant. At the end of the study, Meas was able to move his legs, stand on both feet or one foot entirely on his own. The other three patients did regain some leg movement, but not to the degree Meas experienced. The results from the study, published in the Oct. 26 Scientific Reports, show that the nervous system may be more resilient than previously thought.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 08:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/30/3472910/3472910_55DDDFC77BA1419484DB3779DE781A70_171030_3472910_Paralyzed_man_can_stand_again_after_experimental_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BF3/9CD/BF39CD7E9C5FF9580B3905526DBA60B7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, paralyzed, experimental epidural treatment, spinal cord epidural stimulation, experimental treatment, Andrew Meas spinal injury]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472860</guid>
      <title>The Yellowstone Caldera was made by two mega eruptions, not one</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YELLOWSTONE NATIONAL PARK  Two super eruptions made the iconic Yellowstone Caldera what it is today not one, according to new research. Scientists analysed samples of shell sediment and volcanic ash from the Santa Barbara Basin. From these they were able to determine that the Yellowstone Caldera was formed by two volcanic eruptions 170 years apart.Each eruption was so powerful that it lowered the temperature of the planet and altered the climate, New Atlas reported. These two volcanic winters reportedly took place just as Earth was recovering from an ice age hundreds of thousands of years ago.  The findings were presented last week the annual meeting of the Geological Society of America.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 07:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/30/3472860/3472860_B7492C6D8445409FBF26F5159DD15BE8_171030_3472860_The_Yellowstone_Caldera_was_made_by_two_mega_eru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5CD/155/5CD1559F892B2593484D294D15B980A7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, yellowstone caldera, super eruption, mega eruption, volcano, volcano compilation, volcano stories]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472855</guid>
      <title>Stanford's internet cables double as earthquake sensors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Researchers are using miles of optical cable beneath the Stanford university campus to observe earthquakes.According to a news release from the university, scientists used laser interrogators from company Optasense to record seismic activity on the cables.Stanford Geophysics professor Biondo Biondi says every meter of cable in the 3-mile long network acts as a sensor. "We can continuously listen to  and hear well  the Earth using pre-existing optical fibers that have been deployed for telecom purposes," Biondi said.The technology could one day be used by civil engineers to design buildings more capable of withstanding earthquakes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/30/3472855/3472855_1D2EC667B5014856AE1A29712471207F_171030_3472855_Stanford_s_internet_cables_double_as_earthquake__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CBA/2D7/CBA2D7F5EA2A414EE8E5D2D9B3A4802D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, earthquake detection, earthquake early warning, stanford, the big glass, stamen, stanford earthquake, fibre optic cables]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472752</guid>
      <title>Dead dude found still breathing at own funeral</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TINGO MARIA, PERU  A family in Peru was both shocked and distressed to discover their dead family member still breathing at his own funeral.Los Andes reports that 24-year-old Watson Franklin Mandujano Doroteo had undergone a root canal on October 21, where he was reportedly given diazepam, aka valium. He began developing fever and chills soon after, and was taken to the hospital, where he was pronounced dead.But at the wake, grieving relatives were shocked to notice the man exhibiting signs of life, and immediately called a doctor.After the doctor confirmed he still had vital signs, the man was taken from the coffin and transferred to a hospital...only to be confirmed dead. Again. The man is now legitimately dead, but his family believes he was very much alive at his funeral, and merely sedated due to the dental drugs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/30/3472752/3472752_0920F792A3ED4E54915749A87F1F5910_171030_3472752_Dead_dude_found_still_breathing_at_own_funeral_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/364/B41/364B41C8DB93ECA92824BB43EBFB9979.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, dead man walking, dead man waking, dead man lives, dead man wakes up, waking dead, open casket funeral, root canal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3472739</guid>
      <title>Americans lost at sea for 5 months spotted by Taiwanese fishing boat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PACIFIC OCEAN  Two Americans lost at sea for five months in the Pacific were rescued by the US Navy after being spotted by Taiwanese fishing boat. Jennifer Appel and Tasha Fuiaba left Hawaii for Tahiti this spring with their two dogs, but had their engine fail on May 30 during a storm. The pair continued on hoping to reach land by sail. They began issuing daily distress calls for two months, but were too far out to be heard by anyone. On Tuesday, a Taiwanese fishing boat spotted the pair 900 miles southeast of Japan and contacted the U.S. Coast Guard in Guam. The USS Ashland arrived the next morning to pick the women and their pooches up.Appel and Fuiaba were able to survive because they had water purifiers and more than a year's worth of food on board.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 02:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/17/10/30/3472739/3472739_67781D51465E44BFBD420C2C01F938D4_171030_3472739_Americans_lost_at_sea_for_5_months_spotted_by_Ta_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/47F/251/47F2511242ED438ABC57A75F7929A3FA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, lost at sea, rescued, americans lost at sea, sailboat lost at sea, water rescue, Taiwanese fishing boat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
