<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 15:00:02 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3246982</guid>
      <title>&#x2018;Jet stream&#x2019; of molten iron liquid discovered at Earth&#x2019;s core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[European Space Agency satellites have detected a large jet stream of liquid iron flowing beneath earth’s surface at a quickening pace.The findings were published in the research journal, Nature GeoScience.The stream is around 10,000 feet deep and moving beneath Canada and Russia at pace of 30 miles per year, reported the New Scientist. It is 260 miles wide and is nearly 20,000 miles long.“We can explain it as an accelerating band of molten iron circling the North Pole, like the jet stream in the atmosphere”, lead researcher Dr. Phil Livermore said in a an article on the University of Leeds website. This molten jet stream could be caused by buoyant forces in the earth’s core, or variations in the magnetic field within the core, explained University of Leeds Professor Rainer Hollerbach explained in a ESA article detailing the findings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 14:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/17/01/05/3246982/3246982_9AAA75533340454881E465C6B25FB225_170105_3246982____Jet_stream____of_molten_iron_liquid_discovere_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/802/4A3/8024A303E7264EABB07BE129E14727E1_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Earth core,core of earth,inner core earth,outer core earth,iron jet stream earth,european space agency,swarm mission,swarm satellites,university of leeds,university of denmark]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3246976</guid>
      <title>UK blind patients to be fitted with bionic eye</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The NHS England will fund the procedures for 10 blind patients to be fitted with bionic eyes, which can restore partial eyesight.The bionic eye is also known as Argus II, which was developed by American company Second Sight Medical Products. The procedure requires the patients to have implants placed in their retinas.They must also wear camera-mounted glasses equipped with transmitters, along with a small computer attached to their waist.The camera records the scene before them while video is sent to the small computer. The image is then transmitted wirelessly to the implant in the eye. The image is converted into electrical pulses and sent to the electrodes attached to the retina. The electrodes then stimulate the remaining cells in the retina to transmit the image to the brain.According to NHS England, the procedures will take place in 2017 and the patients will then be monitored for one year in order to assess how the implants have affected their lives.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 14:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/17/01/05/3246976/3246976_10012405DD5F45188FFE39BB44645626_170105_3246976_UK_blind_patients_to_be_fitted_with_bionic_eye_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/058/0F7/0580F7522E714E19A311A5261631DF65_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Nhs england bionic eye,bionic eye,argus II,second sight argus II,uk bionic eye,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3246978</guid>
      <title>China plans to send probes to the moon and Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[China this week published a white paper detailing the country’s activities in space for the next half-decade and beyond. According to state-run newspaper the Global Times, the Chinese government plans to launch and land probes on Mars and the moon by 2020. The lunar mission is set for 2018 and, if successful, would see the first ever probe being landed on the far side of the moon. China also plans on robotically exploring the Moon’s north and south poles, reported the Planetary Society, citing Wu Yanhua, deputy administrator of the China National Space Administration.China’s Mars mission is slated for 2020. China plans to send a lander, rover and orbiter to Mars all in one go. There, China aims to collect samples from the planet and transport them to Earth by 2030.Other plans include the exploration of an asteroid and the Jupiter system, with the latter expected to take place in the next 10 to 15 years, reported the Financial Times, citing Wu.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 14:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/17/01/05/3246978/3246978_BF9972FCC6B342FD9E7CE62F8169A8AB_170105_3246978_China_plans_to_send_probes_to_the_moon_and_Mars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/881/DE6/881DE6C15C7D46B0AE04B884D3F7103C_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,China space program 2016,china space program,chinese space exploration,china space,china mars,china moon mission,jupiter,deep space exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3246975</guid>
      <title>Huge coal fire sunk the Titanic, new documentary claims</title>
      <description><![CDATA[An enormous and uncontrollable fire could be the main reason the Titanic sank on on its disastrous maiden voyage more than a century ago.According to Irish journalist Senan Molony, 30-foot-long black marks seen on the hull of the Titanic before it left Belfast shipyard in 1912 are proof that a huge fire sunk the ship, the Independent reported.The marks can be seen in old photos discovered by Molony, and point to a blaze in a coal room that would have reached temperatures of 1,000 degrees Celsius and warped the ship’s steel bulkhead.Molony says the marks appear on the exact area where the Titanic hit an iceberg on its way from Britain to New York, before sinking to the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean.Some 1,500 people died, making the sinking of the Titanic one of the worst disasters in maritime history.Molony’s theory was presented in a TV documentary shown in the UK earlier this week titled “Titanic: The New Evidence.”He said the ship’s owners were aware of the fire and even took the unusual step of reversing into the dock to hide the damage from passengers.Molony said even though the fire was known, the significance was downplayed and the Titanic “should never have been put to sea.”]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 14:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/17/01/05/3246975/3246975_3F5D0383183D406BBFE2D65B301CD605_170105_3246975_Huge_coal_fire_sunk_the_Titanic__new_documentary_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/83F/F74/83FF747F8364437881FEB3E9983A3D44_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Titanic,titanic fire,titanic blaze,what sank the titanic,titanic sinking,titanic sinking animation,titanic fire animation,fire on the titanic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3246973</guid>
      <title>Campi Flegrei supervolcano stirring under Bay of Naples</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A supervolcano that last erupted nearly 500 years ago is showing signs of reawakening.The Campi Flegrei supervolcano lies beneath the Bay of Naples in southern Italy and contains 24 craters along with numerous geysers and vents.There has been a recent decrease in gas pressure at the supervolcano, which combined with an increase in temperature of the hydrothermal reservoir means the magma may be approaching critical degassing pressure, scientists wrote in the journal Nature on Dec. 20.That could lead to volatility and even culminate in an eruption.Campi Flegrei is Italian for “Burning Fields.” The supervolcano is 8 miles wide and sits directly under more than half a million people.Campi Flegrei spewed ash across Europe for eight consecutive days when it last erupted in 1538.The Italian government has raised the threat level of the supervolcano from green to yellow, meaning that it now requires scientific monitoring, according to National Geographic.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 14:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/17/01/05/3246973/3246973_6E772EFD0C534967898F3B4BA716D098_170105_3246973_Campi_Flegrei_supervolcano_stirring_under_Bay_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AD6/F7E/AD6F7E43F95F43E98432EFA8FD15F7D0_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Supervolcano,campi flegrei supervolcano,supervolcano campi flegrei,italy supervolcano,volcano animation,supervolcano eruption]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3246971</guid>
      <title>Amazon patents self-driving airships to launch delivery drones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Amazon has filed a patent for a self-driving airship that can store inventory and be used as a base to launch delivery drones.Amazon’s airborne fulfillment centers would hover at an altitude of 45,000 feet and be the focal point of a network of unmanned aerial vehicles.The patent for the airship was filed in 2014 but only came to light last week, when it was uncovered by Zoe Leavitt, an analyst at technology research company CB Insights, Reuters reported.The self-driving airships would carry a cargo of Amazon products and unmanned drones to deliver goods to customers.The drones could navigate horizontally to their destination and would use little to no power, according to the patent.The airships would be replenished by smaller, unmanned service vehicles, which could carry workers, drones, fuel, and inventory.One potential use of the airships could be at big events, such as concerts or football games, where they could be used to deliver souvenirs, or food.Amazon has successfully tested deliveries by drone in the UK and is waiting for federal approval to roll out the service in the United States, USA Today reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 14:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/17/01/05/3246971/3246971_C1688DD943114F7CA54ADAE6623F53E0_170105_3246971_Amazon_patents_self_driving_airships_to_launch_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EF9/31B/EF931B2589454EC6B207771D35714E13_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Amazon airship,amazon blimp,amazon drone,amazon drone delivery,amazon drone shipping,amazon,drones,future tech]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3247855</guid>
      <title>Smart bed designed to help users get better sleep</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Minneapolis mattress company unveiled a smart bed at Las Vegas’ Consumer Electronics Show that can help prevent users from snoring, thus eliminating the chances of them disturbing their partners in their sleep.Sleep Number has developed the 360 Smart Bed, which can continuously track users’ heart rates, movement and breathing, then automatically adjusting depending on body positions.When the bed detects the sound of snoring, it is programmed to raise the user’s head slightly to help clear his or her airway. It also traces bedtime routines, and helps wake up the user when they’ve reached the lightest stage of sleep.This year’s CES featured a SleepTech Marketplace, which showcased technologies such as sleep trackers and alarms that can improve the quality of sleep.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 14:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/17/01/06/3247855/3247855_A2FB36FA42694D47A1A4F54EA2B6C429_170106_3247855_Smart_bed_designed_to_help_users_get_better_slee_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/44A/1EF/44A1EF569BAF4CE1A3CE727E4B5399A5_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Sleeptech,sleep number,sleep number 360 smart bed,smart bed,consumer electronics show las vegas 2017,ces 2017,las vegas ces,sleep technologies,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
