<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 19:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3644562</guid>
      <title>Alabama woman's stomach issues turn out to be 50-pound cyst</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTGOMERY, ALABAMA  A woman in Alabama suffered through a slew of mysterious health issues before doctors discovered something was massively wrong with her.WSFA reports that for months, Kayla Rahn had unexplained stomach pain that made it difficult to even carry out daily activities. The solution, doctors told her, was to lose weight.The 30-year-old had been trying to do just that for about a year, but she kept gaining weight and was sick of being mistaken for a pregnant lady.When the pain got too much in May, Rahn's mother rushed her to the ER, where a series of tests finally revealed what was wrong: a benign but massive growth on one ovary.Doctors immediately operated on her, and extracted a giant 50-pound cyst. The mucinous cystadenoma was something they'd seen before, just never this humongous.Since the operation, Rahn says she feels like 'a huge burden has been lifted.' Well yeah, literally.She hopes her ordeal will get people to listen to their bodies, and continue taking it up with a doctor if something doesn't feel right.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 12:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/02/3644562/3644562_DEE6306CAC034419A9CE6E7CB121E9DD_180702_3644562_Alabama_woman_s_stomach_issues_turn_out_to_be_50_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7C7/FD2/7C7FD225A51B62C7CDB56875B59F81A9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tumor, massive tumor, large cyst, ovarian cyst, growth, benign, weight loss, 50 pound cyst, weight gain, how to lose weight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644558</guid>
      <title>Paris gangster makes spectacular helicopter prison break</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REAU, FRANCE  A manhunt is underway in France after a convicted gangster broke out of jail- his second attempt since blasting his way out of a different prison in 2013.AFP reports that on Sunday, three armed men took a flying instructor hostage, ordering him to fly a helicopter to a prison outside Paris where Redoine Faid was serving a 25-year robbery sentence.The helicopter landed in the prison courtyard- the only area not protected by anti-aircraft netting, according to the BBC. Two of the men got out, while the third stayed to guard the pilot.Angle grinders and smoke bombs were used to break Faid out of the visitors' room where he was waiting with his brother, and into the chopper.The helicopter was found abandoned 60 kilometers from the prison. Faid and his accomplices had freed the pilot and boarded a getaway car, which was also later abandoned at a carpark.Authorities have since arrested Faid's brother, and deployed over 3,000 police officers to locate the dangerous fugitive.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 12:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/02/3644558/3644558_549D1AC36BBF42BB8DEBB1EF4768A233_180702_3644558_Paris_gangster_makes_spectacular_helicopter_pris_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DF4/5CE/DF45CE5A3D14D3A8BCF253F415ACD8CB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, prison break jail break, helicopter prison break, helicopter, fugitive, gangster, wanted criminal, France most wanted, Redoine Faid, hostage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644509</guid>
      <title>Shark pulls woman into waters filled with crocodiles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA    Melissa Brunning was excited to be on her friend's superyacht in a remote part of Australia...little did she know she was in for a treat.Apparently sharks and crocodiles were surrounding the yacht when Brunning and her friends decided to feed the sharks.Her friends went first, throwing tiny fish for the sharks to snack on.When it came to be Brunning's turn, the Tawny nurse shark sucked her right index finger into its mouth 'like a Hoover' vacuum.Luckily her friend was quick to yank her back out of the water, leaving her with only an injured index finger.Brunning blamed the incident on her hair color.Perth Now reports Brunning said she has learned her lesson to leave the wildlife alone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 10:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/02/3644509/3644509_9A47E7A8600E4004833AB7FE600F4B43_180702_3644509_Shark_pulls_woman_into_waters_filled_with_crocod_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6F7/36E/6F736E8C2B7416F5BD290C9DE0AFCDCE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Australia, Shark, yacht,shark drags woman, feeding sharks, sea, woman dragged by shark, crocodile-infested waters, remote Australia, vacation, once in a lifetime experience]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644494</guid>
      <title>How Supreme Court justices are nominated and confirmed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Justice Anthony Kennedy is stepping down at the end of July, paving way for the president to nominate a new Supreme Court judge, reports CNBC.When a supreme court justice retires, the president has to nominate a candidate, someone considered qualified enough to serve.The nominated candidate will then be questioned by the Senate judiciary committee about key issues, a process that takes an average of 60 days."The Senate judiciary committee sends the candidate to the Senate, where they debate back and forth about his or her qualifications. To end the discussion, 60 votes are required in what is known as a cloture motion.According to CBS News, those voting in the Senate tend to reject or accept candidates based on their political leanings.After ending the debate, the Senate will conduct a simple majority vote, requiring at least 51 votes, with the vice president breaking the tie if necessary.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/02/3644494/3644494_E36038E2BEED48C689B0981A9F2559B8_180702_3644494_How_Supreme_Court_justices_are_nominated_and_con_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/674/89A/67489AB49F1F835EB0CA1DABB98F8B65.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, Supreme Court justice, Senate, nominating and confirming a Supreme court justice, Senate Committee hearing, US Supreme Court, Politics, US Politics, Politics explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644449</guid>
      <title>Woman drives 19 miles with ex on hood of her car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FLORIDA   A video showing a Florida woman cruising at 70 mph down the interstate with her ex clinging for dear life onto the hood of the car has gone viral.Twenty-four-year-old Patresha Isidore and twenty-two-year-old Junior Francis reportedly had a fight before they went all Fast and Furious.Apparently both Isidore and Francis needed to use the car but Isidore got a hold of it first.Francis jumped on top of the hood of the car to try to stop Isidore but....it didn't quite work out.The two were then seen barreling down the freeway for a short 19 miles.Francis told WPLG he "held on to the car with one hand while calling 911 with the other." Isidore was then arrested on a negligence charge, even though Francis reportedly told the police he didn't want to press charges against his baby mama. The two love birds have a 5-year-old daughter together.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 09:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/02/3644449/3644449_6078E9B0A2624C158451E830616C7D11_180702_3644449_Woman_drives_19_miles_with_ex_on_hood_of_her_car_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/49A/CB9/49ACB996A2C5F1343013F44B7FB30E8F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, Woman, Man, car, highway, woman drove down highway with ex on hood of the car, car hood, interstate, viral video, driving, negligent driving, ex-couple]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644314</guid>
      <title>Passenger whose body odor caused emergency landing dies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPAIN  A man's body odor that was so bad it forced a plane to make an emergency landing appears to have been suffering from necrosis and has passed away.According to Dutch media De Telegraaf, on May 29, the 58-year-old Russian guitarist was on a Transavia Airlines flight from Spain to the Netherlands.He smelled so bad other passengers became nauseous and some began to faint. The flight was forced to make an emergency landing in Portugal and the man was booted.Turns out the smell was caused from an untreated case of necrosis. Necrosis causes body tissue to die after being starved of oxygen. It can be caused by injury, infection, frostbite, and deep vein thrombosis. It can only be treated with surgery.  Suchilin was eventually treated in Spain and was given antibiotics with doctors telling him he had an "ordinary beach infection."Unfortunately it wasn't an ordinary infection. The necrosis eventually spread to his kidneys, heart, and lungs. He passed away on June 25. Transavia Airlines issued a statement assuring there was no risk of infection.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 07:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/02/3644314/3644314_260FEAA302B3493EB59EADF901748FF8_180702_3644314_Passenger_whose_body_odor_caused_emergency_landi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5C3/7EB/5C37EBC090ECBD7DAC42163BC93B2E70.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, body odor men, body odor plane, body odor plane landing, necrosis, necrosis smell, emergency landing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3644143</guid>
      <title>Diamond dust in space may be emitting microwave light</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GREEN BANK, WEST VIRGINIA  Astronomers may have finally figured out the decades-old mystery of certain glowing regions in our galaxy: nanodiamonds.According to the Green Bank Observatory, faint microwave lights known as anomalous microwave emissions, or AME, were first spotted in the Milky Way 20 years ago.Infrared-light emitting polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons were initially thought to be responsible, but not all systems with PAH clouds had an AME glow.A new study published in the journal Nature studied 14 newly formed star systems using West Virginia's Green Bank Telescope and the Australia Telescope Compact Array. Researchers noticed AME coming from three newborn star systems, all of which were the only ones surrounded by diamond dust.The light is believed to result from the rapidly spinning nanodiamond particles producing a dipole moment and emitting electromagnetic radiation in the microwave range.Apart from being both unexpected and cool, scientists suggest the findings can shed light on the chemical signatures of early solar systems, with implications on how ours looked right after the Big Bang.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 01:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/02/3644143/3644143_B48CFFE119C34A848B51075B456FD652_180702_3644143_Diamond_dust_in_space_may_be_emitting_microwave__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8C4/7ED/8C47ED5FF097CAA07E2E44E80C68CB70.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, microwaves, nanodiamonds, ame, light emissions, microwave emissions, anomalous microwave emissions, milky way, star systems, newborn stars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645987</guid>
      <title>Samsung bug causes phones to text photos to random contacts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON   Have a Samsung? Has it been sending texts and photos by itself?As first reported by Gizmodo, Samsung users are complaining online of a new bug, which causes phones like the Galaxy S9 and S9+ to send users' stored photos to people on their contacts list without permission.Those who have been affected say evidence of the photo sharing did not appear on the Samsung messages app, but were recorded on phone carrier logs.Many of the complaints have been from T-Mobile subscribers, leading to speculation that the bug was triggered by the carrier's RCS or Rich Communication Services update, which adds features like GIF support, video, location and file sharing to improve texting.While Samsung is still looking into the problem, there are two temporary fixes. Users can revoke Samsung Messages' permissions to access storage, or switch to a different texting app.The fixes may be a pain for some, but until Samsung rolls out a real solution, it's either this or sending out your entire camera roll for friends and family to see.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645987/3645987_811BBE1B9FFE48FC83A994BAB5B7904F_180704_3645987_Samsung_bug_causes_phones_to_text_photos_to_rand_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/50E/285/50E2854D7B22F3A3735964A5CC4AF8F8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, samsung, phone glitch, phone problems, samsung bug, samsung glitch, samsung sucks, galaxy s9, s9, s9+, t mobile, samsung messages, message app, texting, RCS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645977</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered bacteria chows down on plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON  A U.S. undergraduate student has discovered a new kind of plastic consuming bacteria.Morgan Vague, a senior at Reed College in Oregon has developed a new bacteria that eats polyethylene terephthalate, or P.E.T.This synthetic fiber is a polyester polymer mostly common found in plastic bottles and clothing. P.E.T. takes hundreds of years to break down in the environment and is a major contributor to worldwide waste and pollution.According to the Oregonian, Vague took soil, sand and water samples polluted with petroleum from Galveston Bay in Texas. From these, she narrowed down the microbes that produced the highest amount of plastic dissolving chemicals.Next, she left three with nothing but plastic to feed on. She later found the three types of microbes had consumed all of the plastic. Two of the bacteria are known, but the third is a new bacteria discovered by Vague. She is calling it Pseudomonas morganensis, reports the Oregonian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645977/3645977_0AC177A3FA204AEBA179A860901B005C_180704_3645977_Newly_discovered_bacteria_chows_down_on_plastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/24C/E89/24CE89FBB22FDDA903584E594B135312.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic, plastic bacteria, plastic eating bacteria, plastic in the ocean, pollution, plastic and marine life, chemistry, science, plastic bottles, new discovery, awesome science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645960</guid>
      <title>Woman found alive in morgue after being declared dead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARLETONVILLE, SOUTH AFRICA  A South African woman who medics thought had kicked the can in a bad car accident was later found alive in the morgue. The woman had gotten into a real bad fender bender around Johannesburg around two months ago. When paramedics arrived they said it was too late. After the crash, her body was kept in a morgue fridge for several hours.When a worker came back to check on the body, he discovered that the woman was still breathing. The woman was then rushed to the hospital.  The ambulance service said they made all the right checks. Well, it's pretty obvious they missed something.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645960/3645960_01A4F2B504F34DF591F03B7272C99912_180704_3645960_Woman_found_alive_in_morgue_after_being_declared_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2B5/737/2B573728D60226755E8C4F887B5630A4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, morgue fridge, waking up in morgue, people waking up in the morgue, breathing in morgue, alive in morgue, woman alive in morgue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645806</guid>
      <title>White woman hits and forces black teen to leave swimming pool</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH CAROLINA    A woman was filmed hitting and threatening a black teenager at a swimming pool.The teen was just chilling by the pool with his friends when a white lady appearing out of nowhere and started yelling at them, The Hill reports.The teen had his phone out rolling as the woman punched him in the chest and face. Lady looks like she needs to hit the gym.Stephanie something something  aka Pool Patrol Paula told the 15-year-old and his friends they "did not belong" there and demanded they leave.The 38-year-old beast allegedly used racial slurs and called them 'punks' but the guys were respectful enough to leave. The teens then reported the incident to the police.Steamhead Stephanie resisted arrest, allegedly shoving one cop into a wall and biting another one on the arm, reports NBC News.Pool Patrol Paula is now facing a third-degree assault charges along with two counts of assaulting and beating an officer. Guess she's not going to be at the pool for a while.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 06:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645806/3645806_15828ECDE1C5466DAB3BC7A54742CC7D_180704_3645806_White_woman_hits_and_forces_black_teen_to_leave__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15C/CE8/15CCE84003BEE8EDB3964E5A8893DE96.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, White woman, white people, teenager, black teen, woman hits teen, swimming pool]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645987</guid>
      <title>Samsung bug causes phones to text photos to random contacts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON   Have a Samsung? Has it been sending texts and photos by itself?As first reported by Gizmodo, Samsung users are complaining online of a new bug, which causes phones like the Galaxy S9 and S9+ to send users' stored photos to people on their contacts list without permission.Those who have been affected say evidence of the photo sharing did not appear on the Samsung messages app, but were recorded on phone carrier logs.Many of the complaints have been from T-Mobile subscribers, leading to speculation that the bug was triggered by the carrier's RCS or Rich Communication Services update, which adds features like GIF support, video, location and file sharing to improve texting.While Samsung is still looking into the problem, there are two temporary fixes. Users can revoke Samsung Messages' permissions to access storage, or switch to a different texting app.The fixes may be a pain for some, but until Samsung rolls out a real solution, it's either this or sending out your entire camera roll for friends and family to see.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645987/3645987_811BBE1B9FFE48FC83A994BAB5B7904F_180704_3645987_Samsung_bug_causes_phones_to_text_photos_to_rand_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/50E/285/50E2854D7B22F3A3735964A5CC4AF8F8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, samsung, phone glitch, phone problems, samsung bug, samsung glitch, samsung sucks, galaxy s9, s9, s9+, t mobile, samsung messages, message app, texting, RCS]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645977</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered bacteria chows down on plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON  A U.S. undergraduate student has discovered a new kind of plastic consuming bacteria.Morgan Vague, a senior at Reed College in Oregon has developed a new bacteria that eats polyethylene terephthalate, or P.E.T.This synthetic fiber is a polyester polymer mostly common found in plastic bottles and clothing. P.E.T. takes hundreds of years to break down in the environment and is a major contributor to worldwide waste and pollution.According to the Oregonian, Vague took soil, sand and water samples polluted with petroleum from Galveston Bay in Texas. From these, she narrowed down the microbes that produced the highest amount of plastic dissolving chemicals.Next, she left three with nothing but plastic to feed on. She later found the three types of microbes had consumed all of the plastic. Two of the bacteria are known, but the third is a new bacteria discovered by Vague. She is calling it Pseudomonas morganensis, reports the Oregonian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645977/3645977_0AC177A3FA204AEBA179A860901B005C_180704_3645977_Newly_discovered_bacteria_chows_down_on_plastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/24C/E89/24CE89FBB22FDDA903584E594B135312.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic, plastic bacteria, plastic eating bacteria, plastic in the ocean, pollution, plastic and marine life, chemistry, science, plastic bottles, new discovery, awesome science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645960</guid>
      <title>Woman found alive in morgue after being declared dead</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARLETONVILLE, SOUTH AFRICA  A South African woman who medics thought had kicked the can in a bad car accident was later found alive in the morgue. The woman had gotten into a real bad fender bender around Johannesburg around two months ago. When paramedics arrived they said it was too late. After the crash, her body was kept in a morgue fridge for several hours.When a worker came back to check on the body, he discovered that the woman was still breathing. The woman was then rushed to the hospital.  The ambulance service said they made all the right checks. Well, it's pretty obvious they missed something.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 09:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645960/3645960_01A4F2B504F34DF591F03B7272C99912_180704_3645960_Woman_found_alive_in_morgue_after_being_declared_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2B5/737/2B573728D60226755E8C4F887B5630A4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, morgue fridge, waking up in morgue, people waking up in the morgue, breathing in morgue, alive in morgue, woman alive in morgue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3645806</guid>
      <title>White woman hits and forces black teen to leave swimming pool</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH CAROLINA    A woman was filmed hitting and threatening a black teenager at a swimming pool.The teen was just chilling by the pool with his friends when a white lady appearing out of nowhere and started yelling at them, The Hill reports.The teen had his phone out rolling as the woman punched him in the chest and face. Lady looks like she needs to hit the gym.Stephanie something something  aka Pool Patrol Paula told the 15-year-old and his friends they "did not belong" there and demanded they leave.The 38-year-old beast allegedly used racial slurs and called them 'punks' but the guys were respectful enough to leave. The teens then reported the incident to the police.Steamhead Stephanie resisted arrest, allegedly shoving one cop into a wall and biting another one on the arm, reports NBC News.Pool Patrol Paula is now facing a third-degree assault charges along with two counts of assaulting and beating an officer. Guess she's not going to be at the pool for a while.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 06:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/04/3645806/3645806_15828ECDE1C5466DAB3BC7A54742CC7D_180704_3645806_White_woman_hits_and_forces_black_teen_to_leave__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15C/CE8/15CCE84003BEE8EDB3964E5A8893DE96.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, White woman, white people, teenager, black teen, woman hits teen, swimming pool]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642447</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Episode 4 - MAN ON THE RUN</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured from cops around the globe.THIS WEEK: 1. An Arizona DPS trooper chases a man in car, then on foot and over a fence. 2. London cops take down man plotting Parliament attack.3. Ocala, Florida cops talk down someone on the edge.4. Fulshear police find then rescue an allegedly impaired woman sleeping on the road.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/29/3642447/3642447_C2D8EE3DDDFA400D86432116E2AACE1A_180629_3642447_LAWMAN_CAM__Episode_4___MAN_ON_THE_RUN_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE9/5B5/CE95B58EAE5F23721F66B17728B6006F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,good cop,hero cops,cops doing amazing things,latest police videos,new police videos,latest cop video,new cop footage,police footage,police body cam,police dash cam,police compilation 2018,cop videos,police chase 2018,latest police chase videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646746</guid>
      <title>Torrential rainfall causes major flooding in Chengdu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENGDU CITY, SICHUAN Chengdu city in China has been pounded by rain over the past week, which resulted in a major flooding.As subway stations soon disappeared under water, and most roads were flooded, some people were seen going around on boats or even PWCs. According to the Xinhua News agency, at least 25 000 people had to be relocated across the region.The Chengdu Economic Daily reports schools were evacuated and roads were cut across the region.After days of storm, the sky finally cleared out on Tuesday morning.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/05/3646746/3646746_0172F50BC1F14AC2AEAD7DD067DCBEC3_180705_3646746_Torrential_rainfall_causes_major_flooding_in_Che_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/573/037/573037540CC183DDA63D613B020FFD0C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, rainfall, rainstorm, storm, Chengdu, Sichuan, water,  road collapse, China, road, flood, natural disaster, flooding, downpour, chengdu city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646739</guid>
      <title>Third-party developers may have access to Gmail messages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA   Google has confirmed that third-party app developers can sometimes read private emails sent by Gmail users. Third-party developers gain access to read private emails when Google asks users for permission via a pop-up box the app asks to "read, send, delete and manage your email," according to CNet.Google indicates that this practice isn't against its policies...instead it claims that third-party developers help Gmail build various services, reports The BBC.According to a report by the Washington Post, there are two specific apps that was used by Google: Return Path and Edison Software.Return Path allegedly read 8000 user emails from two years ago to develop Google's software.Edison Software helped manage user emails to help train Gmail's "Smart Reply" Feature.Both Return Path and Edison Software defended their actions..with the latter claiming they have "since stopped this practice."Google said users can revoke access from any third-party apps that users have previously given access to by going to its Security Checkup page, reports EnGadget.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/05/3646739/3646739_8ED15258772446FB94A98F12C8FDD653_180705_3646739_Third_party_developers_may_have_access_to_Gmail__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/46D/6C3/46D6C373E080FC8D99616302A8055741.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  Google, Gmail, messages, private emails, user inbox, app developers, third-party apps, data, data mining, software, Gmail app developers read private emails]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646723</guid>
      <title>Solar-powered school has  enough surplus energy to power 50 homes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SWITZERLAND  A Zurich-based architecture firm has designed a Swiss school with a rooftop covered in solar panels.The self-sufficient solar-powered school, located in Switzerland, produces enough solar energy to also power 50 homes.The school has around 1,100 solar panels with the buildings connected with a zigzag roof Inhabitat reports.The building was made by using sustainably sourced tinder and wood. The self-sufficient school covers an area of more than 180,000 square feet. The interior of the building is filled with light because of the number of windows and also because of light generated from solar power.According to DesignBoom, the ground floor would be spacious enough to conduct different learning activities for children.Each classroom would look like a little house because of the folded rooftops, creating a cozy atmosphere, reports Inhabitat.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/05/3646723/3646723_5FC171CFA58744CE9083E171165D0E01_180705_3646723_Solar_powered_school_has__enough_surplus_energy__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B1/3AD/3B13AD62FFD42DB21CE33E47C4C6C851.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Switzerland, solar power, solar energy,  going green, producing energy, surplus energy, using solar energy to power schools and houses]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646712</guid>
      <title>'Unluckiest man in history' didn't die Looney Tunes style after all</title>
      <description><![CDATA[POMPEII, ITALY  New evidence has been unearthed in the case of the history's unluckiest man.Archaeologists searching the site of the man believed to have been crushed by a stone block during the Mt Vesuvius eruption in 79 A.D. have found the rest of his remains.They found the other remains buried deeper below the man's lower body in a tunnel created several hundred years ago. They recovered his thorax, upper limbs and skull.Analysis of the remains revealed they belonged to a 30 year-old man with a limp, reports CNN. Archaeologists now believe the man's death was brought about by pyroclastic asphyxiation resulting from the eruption.Researchers say more analysis needs to be performed on the bones in order to get a better picture of the man's final moments.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/05/3646712/3646712_DBBBAC65E9C7426BB3A7D340E4EBF643_180705_3646712__Unluckiest_man_in_history__didn_t_die_Looney_Tu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C90/93A/C9093A52588FE6023539186283022437.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pompeii, skeleton, mount vesuvius, excavation, volcanic eruption, stone block, man crushed by rock, ancient rome, pyroclastic flow, volcanic blast]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646693</guid>
      <title>Super absorbent wound dressing could save soldiers' lives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. Army is developing a super absorbent wound dressing that could potentially save the lives of soldiers on the battlefield. According to the Army, around 80 to 90 percent of potentially survivable deaths by American troops in battle occur as the result of uncontrolled bleeding.   Researchers published their results in the journal ACS Publications. According to Digital Trends, the new polystyrene and rubber wound dressing can absorb up to 800 percent of the material's weight in liquid. The new material is 5.7 times more absorbent than the current state-of-the-art wound dressing. The plasticity of the dressing makes it stronger and more flexible, while acrylic acid gives it the super absorbent properties which allow it to pull water out of the blood, so that it can clot faster. As the material swells, the bandage forms a tough hydrogel shell three times stronger than gauze. The project currently is still in the research phase with animal tests set to be the next step in the testing process.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/05/3646693/3646693_E2E4EC61C4F14D54B6509FDEB5F7B05C_180705_3646693_Super_absorbent_wound_dressing_could_save_soldie_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1DD/416/1DD4169052B16C81292BC82134A86A29.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, wound dressing, super absorbent wound dressing, uncontrolled bleeding, gauze]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646591</guid>
      <title>Millions of pigeons perish in Taiwan's grueling pigeon race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN  More than a million pigeons pass through the pearly gates every year while being forced to compete in Taiwan's controversial pigeon sea races. The competition is a series of grueling events where young birds are shipped out on cargo ships and released in order to see which ones make it back to Taiwan the fastest.Some of the birds fall into the water right away, others collide into each other or the ships. Most succumb to fatigue as they battle fierce typhoon-strength winds. Around 500,000 pigeon racers get together annually to compete for millions in prize money.  "Prizes" such as refrigerators are listed on gambling sheets as a cover for huge amounts of betting. Less than one percent of the pigeons actually make it back to land.  According to PETA, competitors cheat by importing breeds, drugging birds and kidnapping other racers' pigeons.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 06:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/05/3646591/3646591_8CFFD7CE4B8142829442F0CE82B19FB4_180705_3646591_Millions_of_pigeons_perish_in_Taiwan_s_grueling__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A06/BCC/A06BCC6B39FEFA3FEB972444D3B7A5BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pigeon race, pigeon race taiwan, race pigeon, pigeon racing abuse, pigeon sea race, taiwan pigeon sea race]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3646562</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman crashes Ferrari immediately after renting it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WENLING, ZHEJIANG PROVINCE, CHINA : A Chinese woman crashed a Ferrari moments after renting it next to Shanghai. Last month, a Chinese woman paid $1000 to rent a Ferrari for a ride around the streets of Wenling city. Right after, she filmed herself boasting about how amazing it was to drive the Italian sports car.  Unfortunately for her, she was caught crashing by a CCTV camera a few minutes later. On a straight and empty road, she suddenly lost control and drifted into the dividing barrier. While she blamed the wet pavement, some netizens suggest she might have been distracted by her phone. Videos shot right after the accident showed the $600,000 Ferrari completely destroyed, alongside debris coming from two other vehicles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 06:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/05/3646562/3646562_79FF6AC3134D42A98DA863AFD7C95CF9_180705_3646562_Chinese_woman_crashes_Ferrari_immediately_after__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D5D/DC7/D5DDC73A5387F65AEC6A2B1C2631D784.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Shanghai, China, road, driver, car, car crash, crash, Ferrari, sports car, FastAndFurious, race, car race, china, zhejiang, selfie]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647927</guid>
      <title>Woman's toenails fall off after fish pedicure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  Fish spas that are supposed to rid your feet of old, dead skin can apparently take out your nails, too.It's a disturbing medical case that happened to one U.S. woman in her 20s, according to a case report published by her doctor in JAMA Dermatology.The unlucky female had apparently gone to get a fish pedicure, letting tiny Garra rufa fish gnaw on her toe gunk. Six months later, she noticed her toenails had stopped growing and were beginning to fall off  a condition known as onychomadesis.The woman had no pain or previous trauma, no family history of nail disorders, and no other medical issues, leading her dermatologist to suspect the fish spa as the likely culprit.It's not exactly clear how the fish effed up the lady's nails, but they aren't exactly sanitized in between feet feedings, and have been known to carry harmful bacteria. The water in the spa tubs are just as filled with microbes, not just because of the fish but from the water and the countless nasty feet that have been in them.Doctors say the woman's nails will grow back, but not for a long long time, since toenails only grow a millimeter a month on average.So yeah, might be best to just stay away from any toenail-snatching Dr. Fish pedicures.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 15:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647927/3647927_08A51AB48CDD4F219E15B4142EB9105F_180706_3647927_Woman_s_toenails_fall_off_after_fish_pedicure_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D5F/A06/D5FA063DF6C2B9FB6C2BAD6B6A700B40.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fish spa, fish pedicure, dr fish, toenails fall off, nails fall off, bacteria, onychomadesis, toenails, nails, JAMA dermatology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647919</guid>
      <title>Two more people poisoned by deadly nerve agent Novichok</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SALISBURY, UK  Two more people have become victims of the Russian nerve agent that affected a former Russian spy and his daughter, reports the BBC.Charlie Rowley and Dawn Sturgess were found unconscious in Salisbury in southwest England where they were poisoned by the same nerve agent, Novichok, as the Russian ex-spy Sergei Skripal and his daughter Yulia Skripal.Rowley and Sturgess were in Salisbury were taken to the hospital when Sturgess collapsed and was found "foaming at the mouth" and Rowley fell ill and was found with eyes "wide open" and he was "sweating … and making weird noises," reports the BBC. According to the BBC, Novichok nerve agent is five to eight times more toxic than the VX nerve agent.Novichok nerve agents may exist as liquids, in solid form or as an ultra-fine powder.Novichok works by inhibiting an enzyme called acetylcholinesterase, which is involved in muscle movement, according to the National Institutes of Health.Motor neurons release a neurotransmitter called acetylcholine, which signals muscles to contract.Acetylcholinesterase removes the neurotransmitter, relaxing the muscle. Novichok prevents acetylcholinesterase from relaxing the muscle, resulting in muscles contracting involuntarily and no longer functioning normally.The effects are wide-ranging, but the most critical are the effects on lung and heart function. These include respiratory paralysis and cardiac arrest, according to a Reuters report.If one is exposed to the nerve agent, they should immediately remove their clothes, rinse their eyes, and wash the exposed skin with water and soap, reports the BBC.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647919/3647919_62081928EA32488B83C3BFE31505704F_180706_3647919_Two_more_people_poisoned_by_deadly_nerve_agent_N_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AE7/3E1/AE73E1374B85C384DA64E9F3CF69FF2D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, UK, nerve agent, Novichok, Novichok nerve agent, how nerve agent Novichok works, Russian nerve agent, two more victims affect by russian nerve agent]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647909</guid>
      <title>Rhino poachers mauled to death by lions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENTON-ON-SEA, SOUTH AFRICA  A group of Rhino poachers recently entered a South African game reserve thinking they'd hunt a little rhino, but in a turn of events, the poachers became food for the lions instead. According to the reserve owner, at least three rhino poachers entered the game reserve late night on July 1. The rhino poachers were armed with a high powered rifle with a silencer, an axe, wire cutters, and had food supplies enough for a number of days.The BBC reports that demand for rhino horns has increased throughout the years, Asian countries like China and Vietnam have a huge demand for rhino horns as they believe they have aphrodisiac qualities.The group apparently strayed into a large group of lionesse, and since lionesses do the hunting for the family, the poachers became a prime target as their next meal.What was left of the poachers were first spotted Tuesday afternoon, and an anti-poaching team had to tranquilise several lions before recovering the remains.According to the BBC, more than 7,000 rhinos have been killed in South Africa in the past decade.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647909/3647909_0A8B6B82E5E5492EA1E42200742A5474_180706_3647909_Rhino_poachers_mauled_to_death_by_lions_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EC6/696/EC669638CB4A8164B2A4521A4EB3067D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, rhino poachers, rhino poachers eaten by lions, rhino poachers eaten, rhino poachers caught, rhino poachers in south africa, illegal poaching, illegal poaching in africa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647903</guid>
      <title>Options to free trapped Thai soccer team from flooded cave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHIANG RAI, THAILAND  Twelve boys and their soccer coach were finally found nine days after going missing inside a northern Thailand cave, but the problem now is how to get them out.With most of the passageways inside Chiang Rai's complex Tham Luang cave system still underwater, there are four options to safely extract the trapped boys, reports the BBC.Rescuers are pumping water out of the cave to create walkable conditions, and have drained the first 1.5 kilometers. But the operation could be set back by heavy rains predicted in the coming days.Rising waters may force the team to dive to safety, donning full scuba masks and suits and being guided by experienced divers through the 5-hour journey with the help of guide ropes, according to the Guardian.But though this method is the fastest, it's also the most dangerous. The dive through narrow passageways under zero-visibility conditions is risky even for seasoned divers.One rescue diver has already died after delivering supplies to the trapped team.A third option being considered is drilling into the cave from above and pulling the boys out, but this is the least feasible since it requires a thorough survey of the cave system to know where to drill.If all else fails, officials say the boys and their coach have enough food and water to last them through the four-month wait for flood waters to recede, so they can walk out.For now, rescuers are keeping an eye on the team and monitoring their condition. A fiber optic cable is also being fitted so the boys can talk to their worried parents.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647903/3647903_BE02796A1DBB4442BB2114333815E62A_180706_3647903_Options_to_free_trapped_Thai_soccer_team_from_fl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/280/FDF/280FDF4B7EE22A06F7C5EA5B1BDBA572.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, thai cave rescue, cave rescue, thailand cave, thai soccer team, boys trapped in cave, drilling, diving, cave diving, flooded cave, rescue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647632</guid>
      <title>9-year-old girl with cerebral palsy saves baby brother from drowning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HALIFAX, NOVA SCOTIA, CANADA  A 9-year-old girl from Halifax, Nova Scotia, saved her baby brother from drowning, and received honors for her heroic conduct.Lexie Comeau-Drisdelle is a 9-year-old Canadian girl from Nova Scotia. She lives with cerebral palsy, a condition caused by abnormal brain development that affects her motor skills and movement. On the day of her ninth birthday, while the rest of the family was busy getting ready for her party, her 18-months-old sibling Leeland sneaked outside and wandered dangerously close to the swimming pool.According to CTV, Lexie, who uses a wheelchair and is unable to speak, understood how critical the situation was, pointed at the door and screamed out as loud as she possibly could.Her mom and her grandmother quickly realized Leeland was not around, and rushed outside. They found him floating by the edge of the pool, and quickly pulled him out. He was in stable condition after coughing up some water, but the family took him to the hospital for good measure.CNN reports that the young girl received an award from the Halifax Region Council for her heroic conduct, and was also honored by the city's police department.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 10:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-video/A9E/CB5/A9ECB5F0C2F04D9E9F121352CD101242" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CDB/FE5/CDBFE57829AAC01D6614154EDB97EC94.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, toddler, baby, hero, girl, handicap, cerebral palsy, Canada, Halifax, swimming pool, pool, drowning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647505</guid>
      <title>A massive landslide in Sichuan causes road to collapse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGAN CITY, CHINA  A huge landslide occurred on July 1st in Guangan city in China's Sichuan province.A surveillance camera caught the moment trees and lights started tumbling down.The road soon collapsed, causing retaining walls to plunge to the ground.According to the Epoch Times, torrential rains have been continuously pouring on Southern China, causing landslides and floods in several places.The authorities have yet to determine what caused the collapse, but an investigation is underway. The landslide miraculously spared the overlooking buildings, and no one was injured or hurt.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 08:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647505/3647505_D1A598D6167F48A89BEF9471E14344E6_180706_3647505_A_massive_landslide_in_Sichuan_causes_road_to_co_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/88F/911/88F9113B1D3A90A469F431A8CEE6444C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cctv collapse, road collapse, China, road collapse in china, landslide flood, natural disaster, Sichuan, sichuan, guangan city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647450</guid>
      <title>Bored Chinese woman stung by bees after trying to catch them</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Even though the rest of the world knows it's a bad idea to try and steal honey from under a bee's nose, one Chinese woman apparently didn't get the memo.In a video circulating on Chinese social media, the woman can be seen talking to the camera with a puffed up face full of stings, explaining how she got into her current predicament.While bored one day, she said she decided to go up to the mountains to try and catch some bees.But while she made it up the mountain and found her honeypot, that's where her luck ended. The bees were not happy with auntie trying to get at their honeycomb, so they expressed their displeasure with stings  lots of 'em.Following her failed attempt, the now swollen-faced auntie trudged down the mountain and filmed her explanation of the incident.On the bright side … guess who probably isn't bored anymore?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 07:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647450/3647450_8E8F03AE646348E5AF6A546F1E57E859_180706_3647450_Bored_Chinese_woman_stung_by_bees_after_trying_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/610/460/610460EF54EC0736BD0EF412AAD5122C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bee sting, viral video, swollen face, chinese auntie, stung by bees, woman stung by bees, catch bees, bee catcher, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647425</guid>
      <title>Football dives: How to tell if a soccer player is faking injury</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUSSIA  Soccer players dive to gain an unfair advantage by falling to the ground and possibly faking an injury  all to give the impression that a foul has been committed.A 2009 study identified four distinct actions that may indicate a player is taking a dive. These are: Taking fully controlled strides before falling; clutching a part of the body where the player was not hit, such as when a player is kicked in the right leg but clutches the left leg; taking extra rolls after falling and hitting the ground; and performing an exaggerated and unnatural gesture of raising the arms above the shoulders and extending the chest while falling, which researchers dubbed "the archer's bow."The 2009 study was published in the Springer Journal of Nonverbal Behavior by Paul Morris, an expert on the embodiment of emotions and intentions in the Department of Psychology at the University of Portsmouth.A separate study, led by Robbie Wilson of the University of Queensland, found that dives most often occur when a player is near the offensive goal or when a match is tied. Wilson's study found players dove more often when referees rewarded such behavior.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 07:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647425/3647425_77AA747D01D647C7BA2CE1498AAE5BB0_180706_3647425_Football_dives__How_to_tell_if_a_soccer_player_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B5E/8E1/B5E8E100299E40CEED963BA6F0638C7B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, diving in soccer, diving in football, diving in football debate, diving in football is cheating, soccer player faking, soccer player faking injury]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647250</guid>
      <title>Chinese guy goes viral for falling while riding horse on street</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAIYUAN COUNTY, CHINA  A Chinese man went on an insane horseback ride through a busy street, all in the name of going viral.A viral video posted on Chinese video sharing site Miaopai shows the young daredevil as he death races on the streets of Laiyuan, China. At first, he demonstrated pretty convincing skills, cutting the flow of cars and zigzagging through traffic.However, his glorious ride did not last too long, and he soon got thrown off his steed. In the video, he can be seen lying on the floor, looking severely hurt. He was taken to the hospital, where doctors found the only injury he sustained was a mere broken arm!The crazy stuntman later explained that he had been inspired by internet videos, and that he did this only to generate buzz.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 03:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647250/3647250_AA927D28D0EF4D6685037BE5B31CBB22_180706_3647250_Chinese_guy_goes_viral_for_falling_while_riding__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F0A/E38/F0AE38DCAA7DA1968BD5BD7B31BACDB6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, viral, viral video, horseback, road, horseback riding, horse riding, ride, horse ride, crash, fall, epic fall, buzz, viral, Fast and Furious, Fast furious, street racing, race, china, zhejiang]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3647187</guid>
      <title>Mexico skull discovery reveals large-scale Aztec human sacrifice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY  Modern historians have doubted the existence of a massive skull display that 16th century Spanish conquistadors claimed to have seen in the ancient city of Tenochtitlan  until now.According to Science Magazine, archaeologists at the National Institute of Anthropology and History have uncovered a vast collection of human skulls beneath modern Mexico City, in an area that was once the epicenter of the Aztec empire.In 2015, the team discovered and began excavating the remains of the tzompantli, an enormous rack of skulls placed in front of the Templo Mayor, and flanked by two towers of mortared skulls.Both are believed to be part of human sacrifice rituals, which starts with removing a tribute’s still-beating heart. Priests then decapitated the body, cut out the flesh from the head until it’s reduced to a skull, and carved holes into the side to mount the skulls on wooden poles.The Mexicas performed the ritual as an offering to the gods, and believed doing so would ensure the continued existence of their civilization.75 percent of the skulls found at the site belonged to warriors  men aged 20 to 35. But 20 percent were found to be from women, and 5 percent were of children.Researchers have taken DNA samples from the excavated skulls, which they hope can provide more insight into the grisly ritual and its victims.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 02:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/06/3647187/3647187_85C45832676144D4814F8E3AC3701789_180706_3647187_Mexico_skull_discovery_reveals_large_scale_Aztec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/50B/F2E/50BF2EB0B9034EDFAB6B3534F3860829.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,aztec,tzompantli,skulls,skull,skull rack,rack of skulls,skull tower,human sacrifice,ritual sacrifice,mexico,mexica,educational]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649654</guid>
      <title>Four boys rescued from cave, but rainfall threatens mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHIANG RAI, THAILAND  Operations to extract the remaining eight boys and their coach from the flooded Thai cave system have resumed, after the first four were safely taken out.CNN reports that 18 cave-diving experts retrieved the trapped boys on Sunday, guiding them through the cave system, which had been installed with guide ropes and air tanks every 25 meters.Wearing full scuba masks, wetsuits, and helmets, each boy is escorted by two divers. He is tethered to the diver in front, who is also in charge of his air supply.According to the Chiang Rai governor, the first boy emerged from the cave at 5:40 p.m., with the second one following 10 minutes later. Two more boys came out at 7:40 p.m. and 7:50 p.m.All four were transported by helicopter to a nearby hospital, where they are currently being monitored.Oxygen tanks had to be refilled before rescuers resumed the next phase, which is currently being threatened by heavy rainfall that's expected to continue in the coming days.Divers are currently on a race against water and time to get the boys out. Monsoon season is only just beginning, which means flooding will likely worsen and hamper efforts to pump water out of the cave.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/09/3649654/3649654_815C21EE8A6A4916B30DAC3530E8F602_180709_3649654_Four_boys_rescued_from_cave__but_rainfall_threat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7D3/128/7D31285A821082565C3C5CF2920199B5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, thai cave rescue, thai cave, trapped boys, cave diving, thai soccer team, wild boars, chiang rai cave rescue, tham luang cave, rescue mission, rain, monsoon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649645</guid>
      <title>Florida waters threatened by algae</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FLORIDA  Florida's coastline is being threatened by toxic algal bloom, and it seems to be getting worse every year, the Tampa Bay Times reports.An algal bloom is a "rapid increase of the population of algae" in a relatively short period of time and can take place on freshwater or marine water systems, reports CNBA.Algal bloom is caused by the overabundance of nutrients nitrogen and phosphorus. This nutrients typically come from rainfall and waste water outflows.The nutrients combined with the temperature of the sea, sunlight and water movement can work to trigger an algal bloom.According to the EPA, the toxic blooms hurt marine life by blocking out sunlight as well as creating toxins that hurt small fish and shellfish after they consume it.Not only do the algae hurt the environment, they also end up creating dead zones in the water where "aquatic life can no longer survive" because of the lack of oxygen, forcing marine life to either leave the area or die. Environmentalists are urging the state government to do more to "address its polluted water," reports Tampa Bay Times.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/09/3649645/3649645_57C19926296F445BA4537C5CE1676C77_180709_3649645_Florida_waters_threatened_by_algae_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0B3/B68/0B3B6830C00E8AFB6DAD5632FAA3D04A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, Marine life, ecosystem, algae, toxic algae, algal blooms, algae bloom, harmful algal blooms, Florida, Florida coasts, florida coasts threatened by toxic algae, slimy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649639</guid>
      <title>Ballooning spiders use electric fields to fly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRISTOL, UNITED KINGDOM  Spiders may not have any wings, but turns out all the eight-legged critters need to fly is a little charge.Spiders have been known to release long strands of silk to carry them up to 2.5 miles up in the air and over a thousand miles out to sea  a process known as ballooning, according to a new study published in the journal Current Biology.The common belief is that the strands catch on to the wind and help generate lift. But since it doesn't explain how spiders balloon even on days with light wind, another theory emerged: electrostatic repulsion.When spiders release their silk, it picks up a negative charge, which repels the Earth's similarly negatively charged surface and creates enough force to propel them into the air.The University of Bristol study tested the theory by putting the arachnids on vertical cardboard strips in a plastic box, and then generated an artificial electric field.Sensory hairs on the spiders' feet detected the charge and prompted them to start ballooning. They were able to take-off despite no wind, but dropped when the electric field was turned off.While the study proved that spiders can fly using electricity alone, scientists believe air currents may still play a role in it. Previous studies have recorded the crawlers raising their front legs into the wind, possibly to determine how strong it is.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/09/3649639/3649639_8F7C37A759664BE385C8B1E238D7C08E_180709_3649639_Ballooning_spiders_use_electric_fields_to_fly_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BBD/8B7/BBD8B784502860340A73EFAE592AF972.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, spider, spiders, flying spider, ballooning spider, ballooning, electrostatic force, wind, electricity, animal science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649413</guid>
      <title>Self-driving buses to become a reality in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA   The future of buses is here.China's Baidu has announced they have begun production of driverless buses in partnership with Chinese manufacturer King Long, reports Xinhua.Baidu released video footage of the bus, called Apolong, which shows it to be much smaller than a regular sized bus.The buses will first be put to use in cities such as Beijing, Shenzhen and even Tokyo, reports the South China Morning Post.According to Xinhua, the bus will initially be used in tourist spots, airports and other enclosed areas.Local reports say Apolong is capable of Level 4 operations, which means it is able to drive without any drivers in specific areas and has 14 seats inside it with no steering wheel.The autonomous vehicle will be powered by Baidu's own autonomous driving platform.Baidu says they will be working with Mobileye, a subsidiary of Intel, to incorporate the Responsible, Sensitive Safety(RSS) driving model to its buses which would "mimic human judgment" while it's driving.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 08:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/09/3649413/3649413_BACC428B502945BDB95DA268E18F4C9F_180709_3649413_Self_driving_buses_to_become_a_reality_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1EA/293/1EA293EC9744EB61C058B5361D6FC3E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, Self-driving buses, buses, Baidu, driverless buses, Apolong, RSS driving model, driverless bus in china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3649365</guid>
      <title>Dogs swipe mail carrier's lunch, become celebrities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SMITHFIELD, VIRGINIA  The hilarious story of two labradors swiping their mail carrier's lunch went absolutely viral. Last month, two 6-year-old labrador brothers went for a mischievous prank. Their owner Carol Jordan found a handwritten note left by the mail carrier in her mailbox. It stated the dogs crawled in the mail carrier's car and ate the lunch the was left there. Far from being angry, Jordan was mainly concerned for the labradors wellbeing.No signs were left from the hungry pair's loot, except two small carrots in the grass.To make up for her boys' thievery, Jordan left an apology note at the post office, along with a Subway gift card.Jordan posted everything on Facebook, and the story went absolutely viral, with thousands and thousands of shares and likes from around the world. She even created a dedicated Facebook page for the two internet celebrities!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 07:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/09/3649365/3649365_AFC3F67028C6420F805392EFC03D103C_180709_3649365_Dogs_swipe_mail_carrier_s_lunch__become_celebrit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/822/981/822981810F5C26929C53C825D4CBDA1A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, funny, cute, animals, doggies, puppies, dogs, prank, postman, mail carrier, stealing, viral, internet celebrity, hungry]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650472</guid>
      <title>Genetically modified polio virus used to treat brain cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA  A new experimental treatment is using a modified version of a once-dreaded virus to fight against a deadly form of brain cancer.Glioblastoma is a type of cancer that occurs in the brain or spinal cord that is typically treated using surgery, radiation therapy, or chemotherapy. It is an aggressive disease, with only a 12 to 18 month prognosis for those with grade 4 tumors.According to a study published in the New England Journal of Medicine, Duke University researchers removed genetic code from the polio virus and replaced it with DNA from the rhinovirus, which causes the common cold.The modified virus is then injected directly into the tumors of glioblastoma patients through a catheter.Instead of replicating itself, it attaches to receptors on the surface of the cancer cells, infecting them and prompting the body's immune system to attack.Of the 61 glioblastoma patients treated using the re-engineered virus, 21 percent are                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         still alive three years later, compared to only four percent for those who underwent conventional treatment.The experimental treatment, like many immunotherapies, had varied, sometimes dramatic effects on the subjects.Scientists are still figuring out how to get the virus to produce the exact same results in different people, but are confident that it can be done.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 14:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/10/3650472/3650472_45EDD4FD51CC4535B5FE42D4901169DE_180710_3650472_Genetically_modified_polio_virus_used_to_treat_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E40/3DD/E403DDE7433CC22685BC8EB2ED7AA2D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, brain tumor, cancer, cancer cure, cure for cancer, glioblastoma, brain cancer, glioma, polio virus, polio, cancer treatment, experimental treatment, duke university]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650395</guid>
      <title>China found using banned chemicals which hurt the ozone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA   A home insulation chemical used extensively throughout China may be damaging the earth's ozone layer, reports the BBC.The chemical, CFC-11, was completely banned eight years ago because it resulted in a "massive rise in emissions of a gas" to the earth's protective layer.According to the BBC, around 70% of sales in China used the illegal gas to insulate their houses because it is "better quality and much cheaper" than other alternatives.CFC-11 is made from chemicals such as carbon, chlorine and fluorine.CFC-11, or trichlorofluoromethane, was mainly used as a refrigerant and is a colorless liquid which is quick to escape containers even if it is packed tightly.When CFCs are exposed to UV rays in the atmosphere, the molecule breaks down into individual atoms which includes chlorine.The oxygen atoms in the ozone then react with the chlorine atom and 'rips apart' the ozone molecule, which damages the ozone layer.Because of the sheer amount of CFC-11 being used, this could have the potential to "reverse the healing that is starting to take place in the ozone layer."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 12:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/10/3650395/3650395_35BB74375CAD41199172BEA91FB12897_180710_3650395_China_found_using_banned_chemicals_which_hurt_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/665/A8B/665A8B8534054954AD77A26009793241.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, CFC, CFC-11, banned chemicals, illegal chemical, ozone, ozone layer, ozone depleting gas,  CFC emissions,  gas emissions,  Earth's ozone layer, CFC damaging to Earth's ozone layer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650349</guid>
      <title>Woman discovers some 50 brown recluse spiders in her bedroom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRENTWOOD, TENNESSEE  A woman got the shock of her life when she discovered dozens of spiders inside her bedroom.Angela Wright made the discovery after she was bitten by several and rushed to the emergency room, reports CBS News. Apparently the brown recluse spider infestation was unknown to Wright until she was bitten several times on her chest and arm while she was sleeping."Wright said she "woke up with arm pain" and noticed bumps on her chest and arm but she didn't suspect it to be anything serious.She even went to the doctor to get medication for the bumps, but felt like it "didn't help" because her chest starting hurting.A few days later, Wright said she felt like she was "hallucinating" and could barely walk. That was when she was rushed into the emergency room.Wright later claimed she found nearly 50 spiders in her bedroom, hanging out everywhere from the ceiling to her bed, reports WSMV.Wright said she and her fiance are now trying to move out of the apartment as soon as possible. Yeah, that makes sense.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 11:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/10/3650349/3650349_A8B6C57604C143D5909530B186AFC077_180710_3650349_Woman_discovers_some_50_brown_recluse_spiders_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/602/32D/60232D7F570F336CFF6129F9E3DAED57.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, spiders, brown recluse spiders, spiders in bedroom, dangerous spiders, spider bite, spider bite sends woman to the hospital, ER, hospital, spider bites woman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650337</guid>
      <title>Fake beggar in Beijing subway gets into heated argument</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  This fake beggar got into a heated argument with security officials on Beijing subway, and was exposed for his fraudulent ways.This video of a presumed beggar getting into a heated argument with security on Beijing subway went viral in China.The footage shows the high-tech and supposedly homeless man holding a box with a QR code printed on it, soliciting cyber payments from passersby.Chinese netizens were flabbergasted by the man's attitude, as he seems to speak very aggressively to a security official, daring him to call the police.People were quick to realize that the beggar was actually a Line 5 regular, and often faked being blind or afflicted with mental and/or physical disabilities.Two years ago, a local TV show had already exposed his fraudulent ways and revealed he actually owned two small flats and earned as much as US$1,500 a month. However, the major scammer sued the television station, and received US$750 in financial compensation for moral injury.He is now closely escorted by security officials as soon as he enters the subway.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 11:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/10/3650337/3650337_7051C400A1B14D29BAC0879738504A94_180710_3650337_Fake_beggar_in_Beijing_subway_gets_into_heated_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AB3/429/AB3429F3597CF6A49220DF86D847B826.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, faker, scammer, fake beggar, homelessness, homeless man, begging, Beijing, subway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650246</guid>
      <title>42 killed in deadly tourist boat accident off Phuket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHUKET, THAILAND  Dozens are dead and several others missing after a tourist boat capsized off southern Thailand in one of the country's worst sea disasters.Reuters reports that the double decker cruise ship Phoenix had been off the coast of Phuket on Thursday, carrying 89 tourists mostly from mainland China, and 12 Thai crew and tour guides.The ship encountered bad weather at sea, and reportedly capsized after being hit by a 16-foot wave.More than 40 passengers and crew managed to jump from the sinking boat and have since been rescued.Divers sent to check the sunken vessel found that many had been trapped in the lower deck. As of Monday, 42 are confirmed dead, and five are still missing, according to the provincial governor of Phuket.The Phoenix and several other boats were out at sea despite severe weather warnings, prompting authorities to investigate.Its captain has since been charged for negligence, along with the captain of another boat, Serenita, which also overturned around the same time but did not result in any casualties.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 09:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/10/3650246/3650246_2DA826905EF64FBFA3C0B2DF3271A06C_180710_3650246_42_killed_in_deadly_tourist_boat_accident_off_Ph_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/31F/D3D/31FD3D1B9472D00E43A2AE7B3D6A25D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, thailand boat disaster, thailand boat accident, thai boat rescue, tour boat disaster, tour boat sinking, tour boat accident, phoenix, phuket, chinese tourists, thai tourism, storm warning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3650091</guid>
      <title>Joyous England fans and their wild celebrations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ENGLAND  After England made it to their first semi finals in 28 years by beating Sweden 2:0[b] at the World Cup, their supporters were over the moon as they celebrated the historic occasion.The win was watched by nearly 20 million people, the BBC reported.In celebration, rowdy and passionate England fans reportedly jumped on an ambulance and danced on the vehicle in London. Meanwhile, a taxi suffered a similar fate in Nottingham.Luckily, a supporters' club managed to raise enough fund to help repair the London ambulance. Even Ikea, the Swedish furniture retailer, couldn't escape being a target of Three Lions' fans. One man was seen climbing up a lamp post near London Bridge station while being egged by fans. Smoke bombs were also reportedly set off inside pubs.According to Devon and Cornwall Police, there were double the number of police reports than what they received on New Year's Eve. Lancashire and West Midlands Police received their highest-ever number of police calls over a 24-hour time period.England will next be playing against Croatia, one of their international rivals, on Thursday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 06:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/10/3650091/3650091_730F0F5D5B55487E962983A1F02D7D8F_180710_3650091_Joyous_England_fans_and_their_wild_celebrations_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6C0/9AC/6C09AC68CA7B7502656A064C6A37A532.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, england fans, england fans celebrate sweden, england fans reaction sweden, england fans reaction, england fans celebration, england fans wild]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651210</guid>
      <title>Poisonous books found in Danish university library</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ODENSE, DENMARK  Researchers in Denmark accidentally discovered three books that were covered in poison.Two researchers from the University of Southern Denmark were examining three medieval books to see whether any old Latin texts had been used in the binding.The scholars, Josh Povl[g] Holck and Kaare[h][i][j] Lund Rasmussen wrote in the Conversation that the university library had previously found medieval manuscript fragments, such as copies of Roman law and canonical law, but they said this is normal as book binders in the 16th and 17 centuries used to recycle older parchments.The X-ray result showed something surprising  the green paint covering the works contained poisonous arsenic.According to Atlas Obscura, the use of arsenic-tinted green paint was common to be used for things like mail stamps, dresses, and ball gowns in the 19th century. And it wasn't until the early 20th century that scientists understood arsenic is actually dangerous when inhaled or when a person makes contact with it.The researchers believed that the paint was used to protect books from insects and vermin. For now, each book of the three poisonous books they've found will be stored in a ventilated cabinet while specialists will digitize them so people won't have to physically handle them.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 12:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/11/3651210/3651210_B16F1A7299964309AD950941EA841151_180711_3651210_Poisonous_books_found_in_Danish_university_libra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9CE/C30/9CEC308DE612224797F033B3FEA42484.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, arsenic poisonous, arsenic paint, arsenic painting, arsenic paint color, arsenic green paint, poisonous books]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651120</guid>
      <title>Kylie Jenner just had her lip fillers removed &#x2014; here's how that's done</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  When Kylie Jenner showed up on her Sunday 'gram without her signature pouty lips, fans were quick to notice.People reported that after a follower commented on her looking like the "old Kylie", the Keeping Up with the Kardashians star responded that she got rid of her lip fillers. The revelation has prompt the curious to look up whether that is even possible. Answer: yes, totally!According to cosmetic surgeons interviewed by the Irish Examiner, People, and several other publications, lip fillers are made of hyaluronic acid, a substance found naturally in the body, typically in the skin, hair follicles, eyes, gums, and joints.The fillers are temporary, and need maintenance every six to eight months. Otherwise, the hyaluronic acid will dissolve and wear off, which is the simplest way to undo them.Another way to get rid of them is by injecting hyaluronidase, an enzyme that speeds up the filler's breakdown and helps it dissolve in about 48 hours.The procedure is completely safe if done by a professional. There may be side effects from the needle, but not so much from the enzyme and filler, which are both harmless substances.In most cases, the lip goes back to how it was pre-filler, but eagle-eyed netizens and plastic surgeons have noticed that that's not quite the case with Kylie.So either something else is still in there plumping her lips, or those Kylie Cosmetics are just that good.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 10:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/11/3651120/3651120_B346FD7F8A1C442ABCA67A8E7FE588BD_180711_3651120_Kylie_Jenner_just_had_her_lip_fillers_removed____2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EDC/158/EDC1584989463DDC1969D3CF363D56D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, lip fillers, kylie jenner, kardashians, fillers, lip procedure, full lips, duck lips, temporary filler, plastic surgery, cosmetic procedure, hyaluronic acid, hyaluronidase, kylie cosmetics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651077</guid>
      <title>UK animal charity rescues dozens drunk seagulls</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DORSET, ENGLAND  Britain's animal service recently rescued a number of seagulls on English beaches.The birds appeared to have gotten into a little alcohol, causing them to go a little coo coo.Britain's Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals said they got a call about over a dozen seagulls that were seen walking around on the beach like they are bunch of drunkards.The RSPCA staff said the birds at first looked like they had botulism, and most seemed to recover after vomiting. The RSPCA suspect that a brewery or other alcohol distributor in the nearby area did not handle their alcohol waste properly and the birds somehow gained access to the alcohol being dumped out.A veterinarian with the animal welfare charity told Sky News a few of the seagulls have died after showing symptoms of intoxication, but many are recovering.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 09:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/11/3651077/3651077_68534D810E144A8F802066E00F32FF79_180711_3651077_UK_animal_charity_rescues_dozens_drunk_seagulls_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BF1/063/BF1063DB717D01E5F5D6C56D5CDEB47B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, drunk seagulls, animal service, animal drunk, animal drunk alcohol, drunk seagull alcohol]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651074</guid>
      <title>Fearless thieves snatched $27K of Apple gadgets in brazen heist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FRESNO, CALIFORNIA / US  Last Saturday, at 11:30 a.m., four fearless robbers swiped $27,000 worth of Apple gadgets in a brazen heist.As customers were leisurely shopping at the Fashion Fair Mall, a group of hoodlums suddenly swooped into the Apple store. The four robbers wearing hoodies did not lose any time; it took them mere seconds to wipe out the first three showcasing tables. Everything went so fast employees and customers alike remained dumbstruck, while a little girl even dived under a table.The daring raiders then ran out, pushing through a crowd of frightened teenage girls. A brave Samaritan unsuccessfully tried to stop them, but was fended off by the fleeing thugs.According to local authorities, the bandits snatched 26 items, including various iPhone models and laptops. The estimated value of their loot was $27,000.Authorities are still investigating whether the heist might be connected to other similar robberies. An audacious takeover raid following the same mode of operation took place last month in San Luis Obispo, California.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 09:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/11/3651074/3651074_3D4E4CF4567A414D9E4D4F4D54F198B6_180711_3651074_Fearless_thieves_snatched__27K_of_Apple_gadgets__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4C2/438/4C2438B0E9D36F124C65C0A34358AA93.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, robbery, thievery, opportunity knocks, Apple, gadgets, tech, heist, holdup, California, Fresno, mall, burglary, larceny, break-in, bold, audacious, intrepid, CCTV, surveillance camera]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651067</guid>
      <title>Facebook pushes facial recognition tech</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Social media giant Facebook is pushing facial recognition as a way to safeguard online identities, but is instead raising concerns over privacy in several sectors.According to the New York Times, Facebook's facial recognition technology works by analyzing users' photos and generating a string of numbers called a 'template' that's unique to each user. When photos and videos are posted to the social network, the unnamed faces are scanned and matched to names and templates stored in a database.A Facebook spokeswoman claims that if the system cannot find a match, it doesn't identify the unknown face, adding that the facial data is deleted immediately.While it's possible to turn facial recognition off, critics still find the software problematic, since it scans every image- even of people who have opted out of the feature.Facebook has also applied for several patents that use the technology. One aims to tailor ads by analyzing users' facial expressions via their phone camera. Another checks shoppers' online profile and uses it to determine a 'trust level'.This Big Brother-style approach to facial data is worrisome, especially since Facebook doesn't exactly have the best track record for honesty, or for keeping user data safe.Fortunately, a lot of groups recognize this and are moving to protect biometric data. The company is facing a class-action suit filed by Illinois consumers for violating a state biometric privacy law, and could stand to lose money and what's left of their reputation if it moves forward.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 09:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/11/3651067/3651067_5842FD9D09CA4CB9BCE53BDA0569CF9A_180711_3651067_Facebook_pushes_facial_recognition_tech_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DE8/3F0/DE83F0849D04CAF50A1B309989E5C022.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, facebook, facial recognition, facial recognition tech, facial scan, big brother, photo tagging, facebook settings, privacy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651054</guid>
      <title>Thai boys rescued from cave may face "cave disease"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THAILAND   All the boys and their coach have been rescued from the cave in Thailand, but they may have to face another challenge: cave disease.Cave disease, also called histoplasmosis, is a fungus infection that is "aided by nutrients it gets from bat and bird droppings," reports ABC News.The disease is reportedly transmitted via air, with the fungus becoming airborne through its spores that are so tiny they are "undetectable to the human eye."However, the disease itself is not contagious from person to person.According to the CDC, any movement that disturbs the ground like digging or even walking can spread the disease.Histoplasmosis may affect those with a weaker immune system, causing the disease to "spread from the lungs to … the brain."Those who don't get sick may appear to have a flu, or have body aches and chest pain.One way to prevent "cave disease" is to avoid walking into any caves where bird and bat droppings are suspected to be there.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 09:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/11/3651054/3651054_DC3D0EE4A9854D4C927BF9759DABA7E9_180711_3651054_Thai_boys_rescued_from_cave_may_face__cave_disea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/851/1D6/8511D65B4B5FB2FEE9A55AF4B7AEBF0B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Thailand, thai cave, cave, boys, boys trapped in thai cave, thailand cave rescue, unusual disease, cave disease, histoplasmosis, health risks, fungus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641654</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Ep. 5 - GET CHAPO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY Three years ago El Chapo Guzman made a brazen escape from the big house. Six months later, the Federales came-a-knockin’. THIS WEEK: In this special edition of Lawman Cam, TomoNews takes you back to summer of 2015 when one of the world’s most wanted men made his government look like fools.Then, nearly half a year later, we’re on his trail with a party of Mexican Marines.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-video/795/AED/795AED8717A44AB9B0181BC269940ABC" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/49A/BAD/49ABADAA70227D79BC6E0DCFAEC5ABE3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,el chapo documentary,el chapo gets caught,el chapo,get chapo,sinaloa,mexico,latest police videos,new police videos,latest cop video,new cop footage,police footage,police body cam,police dash cam,police compilation 2018,impaired driver,us police videos,cop camera,lawman cam,tomonews lawman cam,police responding,police news,latest police video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651992</guid>
      <title>Sex disease continues to spread rapidly, may turn into superbug</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  Mycoplasma Genitalium, or MG, is a rare sexually transmitted infection that may become a "superbug" if it is not taken seriously, reports the BBC.MG is a bacterium which can live in the urinary and genital tracts of the body, causing a burning sensation during urination or pain during sex, reports Newsweek.MG causes inflammation of the urethra in men, and inflammation of the reproductive organs, such as the womb and the fallopian tubes, for women, the BBC reports.In the worse case scenario, the infection may cause infertility for women.The infection is often misdiagnosed as chlamydia and treated as such, which is why the infection is currently "developing resistance" to some of the antibiotics used to treat it.The British Association of Sexual Health and HIV issued guidelines saying the disease may be treated with the antibiotic doxycycline for seven days, followed by azithromycin.Dr. Peter Greenhouse, a member of the association, is urging the public to take precautions and use condoms to prevent the spread of Mycoplasma Genitalium, reports the BBC.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 12:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/12/3651992/3651992_50D7895985E54726BAC94321C40C6F3C_180712_3651992_Sex_disease_continues_to_spread_rapidly__may_tur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6CF/E77/6CFE77AFB0E3839A46FC23AB99436090.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, UK, sex disease, MG, rare sex disease, sex infection, STD, mycoplasma genitalium, superbug, condoms, reproductive organs, inflammation, sexually transmitted infection, diagnosed with MG]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651920</guid>
      <title>Plastic straw ban isn't good for people with disabilities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  The recent crackdown down on plastic straws may be good for the environment, but it's not doing the disabled any favors.CNN reports that single-use plastics like straws have been facing a growing backlash because of the harm it causes the environment. As a result, many cities and establishments have banned or are planning to ban their use entirely  a decision applauded by many.But the ban will also negatively affect people living with physical disabilities, for whom plastic straws are a necessity.According to NPR, current alternatives are not as efficient as plastic. Paper straws, for example, dissolve in hot drinks. Metal ones can get too hot or cold, and like bamboo and glass, are hard and inflexible  which poses a safety risk.Going without straws is equally problematic, especially for those struggling with mobility, and may cause choking or leak liquid into the lungs.Seattle's new plastic straw ban does exempt people with medical conditions who need the disposable straws, but most places aren't aware of this.It's also been suggested that instead of an outright ban, companies should come up greener alternatives that will work for everyone, including the disabled.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 10:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/12/3651920/3651920_AAA49BB1B2AA4EA5B5F80FF9F48433B0_180712_3651920_Plastic_straw_ban_isn_t_good_for_people_with_dis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CF0/FDD/CF0FDDEE56312B3DCDF7F271510391D9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic straw ban, disabled, disability, plastic straw, straw ban, plastic ban, people with disabilities, plastic pollution, single use plastics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651763</guid>
      <title>Mutant human-like creature found alive on a beach in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  In recently released footage that has quickly gained popularity online, some people in China are seen finding an odd creature at the beach. People who were strolling by the sea stumbled upon the unidentified object floating along the shore.At first they were scared and did not want to approach the spongy body, but a man eventually picked it up to take a picture. The humanoid creature, which seems to possess a head and limbs, started moving the likeness of its feet.Footage of the find soon gained popularity online. Internet users started speculating about the monstrous thing's true nature. Some viewers suggested it could be come kind of mutated sea sponge or a new species of starfish.Most people remained skeptical and expressed doubts about the veracity of the footage. According to the YouTube channel that first published the footage, acclaimed cryptozoologist Karl Shuker asserted it was likely a mass of sponge.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/12/3651763/3651763_5F1DA12222C049BA916B34891D82E37F_180712_3651763_Mutant_human_like_creature_found_alive_on_a_beac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AA4/DF2/AA4DF26312F65F62D29BE6AB9178B4FA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, weird animal, weird creature, sea, beach, shore, seaside, weirdest animals, hoax, sea sponge, starfish, mysterious, freaky, creepy, gross]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651728</guid>
      <title>Timeline of how rescue of Thai soccer team unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THAILAND  A dozen boys and their soccer coach went missing on June 23 after entering the Tham Luang Nang Nom cave system in northern Thailand, prompting a rescue mission that lasted almost an entire month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/12/3651728/3651728_C62F63926AB647EB903885AF3B87AA8B_180712_3651728_Timeline_of_how_rescue_of_Thai_soccer_team_unfol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B6/EAD/3B6EADF27D2835E21D201680DC90F47A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Thailand cave rescue, Thailand soccer team, Thai Navy Royal SEAL, soccer team lost, soccer team found, Chiang Rai, Tham Luang cave]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3651677</guid>
      <title>Newlyweds suffer tragedy while zip-lining on their honeymoon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONDURAS   Two Israeli tourists were on their honeymoon in Honduras when tragedy struck, reports Providencial Journal.The couple was ziplining in Roatan, one of the Bay Islands of Honduras, during their post-wedding vacation. The woman went first, but got stuck in the middle of the zipline. Her husband was right behind her, careening down the zipline while she was still stuck mid-air, crashing directly into her.Local media reported two ambulances were rushed in to take the pair to the hospital. Unfortunately, the husband didn't survive the horrific accident, and his wife was left with multiple injuries, including a broken rib.Honduran media reports stated brain hemorrhage may have been the cause of the husband's death.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 06:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/12/3651677/3651677_ED0869BFD62B4254AA34C87FF587ADB8_180712_3651677_Newlyweds_suffer_tragedy_while_zip_lining_on_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC7/847/DC78472B85D8649D6728B6C2C87AADBB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Honduras, Tourists, Newlyweds, honeymoon, couple, getaway, zipline, zip-lining,  zipline accidents, couple crashes into one another while ziplining, tragic ending]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652785</guid>
      <title>Scientists reveal the world's oldest color has been discovered</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EARTH  It turns out bright pink is the oldest color in the world.According to a recent study from Australian National University, pink pigment was found in the marine black shales deep beneath the Sahara desert in Africa.The researchers reportedly crushed the rocks into powder then extracted and analysed the molecules of ancient organisms inside those rocks.The bright pink pigment discovered was actually the "molecular fossils" of chlorophyll produced by ancient photosynthetic organisms living in an ancient ocean, which no longer exists.The fossils itself range from "blood red to deep purple" in concentrated form, and turn bright pink when it's diluted.A researcher involved in the study commented saying after analyzing the ancient pigment, confirm tiny cyanobacteria used to live in the ocean a billion years ago.Ancient oceans filled with cyanobacteria started to disappear around 650 million years ago, which is when algae started to spread rapidly which helped the ecosystems to evolve.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 11:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/13/3652785/3652785_83A220B5280E42C48DD9B294845750E1_180713_3652785_Scientists_reveal_the_world_s_oldest_color_has_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2A5/6E0/2A56E015E5CBAA8BCA49E4777394DE76.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Scientists, color, biological color, world, earth, bright pink, oldest color, Sahara desert, rocks, ancient rocks, fossils, cyanobacteria, pigment, pink pigment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652548</guid>
      <title>Idaho man impaled by a spear at work miraculously survives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JEROME, IDAHO  A few days ago, an Idaho man was impaled by a spear in an accident. Quite miraculously, the spike did not hit any of his vital organs, allowing him to survive the traumatizing accident.Justin Firth is at the same time the unluckiest and the luckiest person on earth. A few days ago, he was at work, building a fence, when he suddenly felt something hit him in the back and went to the ground.In an attempt to understand what was going on, he looked around, and had the most horrific vision. A 40 lbs hay bale spear was literally coming out of his stomach and sticking into the ground. The spear was attached to a nearby loader, when for an unidentified reason, it suddenly fell and pierced through Firth's back.He did not feel any pain, and could not see any blood coming out of the injury. Surprisingly lucid and clear-headed, he requested his wife and his son not to see him like that. His coworkers cut the spear off the loader, and called 911. He was soon carried into a helicopter and transported to Portneuf medical center. It took the team of surgeons nearly four hours to take the spear out and repair internal injuries.Fortune was on his side, as the object missed his spinal cord, his aorta and the tube connecting his kidney to his bladder by only a few centimeters.The Firths plan to keep the spear as a reminder that Justin's life is far from being other yet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 07:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/13/3652548/3652548_A81FAD59E64E47AAAA362C69051212A7_180713_3652548_Idaho_man_impaled_by_a_spear_at_work_miraculousl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DBB/03C/DBB03C9EF3348F432C76EFEADE8216DF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, spike, spear, impaled, crazy injury, crazy accident, injury, accident, surgery, hospital, miracle, real life miracle, loader]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652496</guid>
      <title>China to increase surveillance by using robotic doves</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA   China has started using birdlike drones to monitor everyday civilians, reports The South China Morning Post.The Chinese government has reportedly sent the "dove" drones to at least five different provinces across China, especially to Xinjiang, which is home to a large Muslim population.These robotic doves look so authentic when they fly high in the sky, that even real doves start flying with them. The robotic drone mimics the flapping motion of a dove and would be able to 'evade human detection, The South Morning Post reports.The robot doves may even be camouflaged with feathers to further "distort radar signals."The interior of the robotic dove contains mechanisms such as a GPS antenna, a Data link antenna, a battery, an HD camera, flapping mechanism, and a flight control system.The project, code-named "Dove", is being led by a team of researchers who conducted various experiments such as flying the dove drones over a flock of sheep, who paid no attention to the drones above.One of the researchers of the project told the South China Morning Post technology has the potential to be used not only for military purposes but also for "disaster relief and emergency response."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 06:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/13/3652496/3652496_4C055D80803045CDB7A5113CCAA07CA6_180713_3652496_China_to_increase_surveillance_by_using_robotic__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/469/BB0/469BB0D41889863B52CDE142297D00CD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, Chinese military, chinese government, Xinjiang, Surveillance, Robots, Drones,birdlike drones, Robotic birds, robotic doves, spy birds, drone surveillance, china surveillance, china surveillance system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652418</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Episode 4</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured from cops around the globe.THIS WEEK: 1. Delray Beach, Florida cops save two kids after their mom takes them out onto a narrow ledge.2. Boozed up horse rider is arrested and charged for DUI.3. Police finds missing girl after 15 hours in the woods.4. Cop goes viral after putting gloves on for a friendly boxing match.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 04:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/13/3652418/3652418_819BC1BE12434F78A0F4694261486E23_180713_3652418_LAWMAN_CAM__Episode_4_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D18/F6B/D18F6BD9C55DC2146339CAAB92F48A3F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, good cop, hero cops, cops doing amazing things, latest police videos, new police videos,  latest cop video, new cop footage, police footage, police body cam, police dash cam, police compilation 2018, cop videos, police chase 2018, latest police chase videos, crazy car chases, police pursuit,, us police videos, cop camera, lawman cam, tomonews lawman cam, police responding, police news, latest police video, latest police videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3652359</guid>
      <title>Here's how your car is making you sleepier</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA  New research has found that feeling drowsy behind the wheel may not always be due to tiredness or lack of sleep  turns out it's your car.The Transport Accident Commission of Victoria estimates that about 20% of fatal car crashes in Australia are caused by driver fatigue.A growing body of evidence suggests that gentle vibrations made by car seats during a drive can lull the brain and body and contribute to feelings of sleepiness.To test the theory, a study from Melbourne's RMIT University hooked volunteers to a virtual driving simulator and tested them once with low frequency 4 to 7 hertz vibrations, and once without.Volunteers showed signs of drowsiness within 15 minutes of the vibrations, as indicated by their heart variability. It became significant at 30 minutes, with participants becoming sleepier until the end of the 60-minute test.Researchers believe one explanation could be that the brain becomes synchronized with the vibrations and enters the early stages of sleep.It's also been suggested that some frequencies may keep people awake instead of lulling them to sleep. But to harness these "good vibrations", more work is needed to examine a wider range of frequencies.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 03:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/13/3652359/3652359_40C336AEE9094F118C1F7D801105EB54_180713_3652359_Here_s_how_your_car_is_making_you_sleepier_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/628/EFA/628EFA5A21A5E8E1B0DEB4FF2BB6DE66.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, snooze mobile, sleepy driver, car drowsiness, car sleepiness, car vibrations, drowsy driving, why driving makes you sleepy, vibrations, car accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3655622</guid>
      <title>Chinese bypassers save kid who slipped into canal from drowning</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINLE COUNTY, CHINA  Footage posted to Chinese social media shows some passersby saving a kid from drowning in a canal.Earlier this month, in Gansu province, a kid was strolling by a canal when he suddenly slipped and fell into the water. The rims were too high for him to climb, and the current was so strong that he was quickly washed away.Clear-headed passersby witnessed his potentially fatal fall. They kept their cool, stopped a truck that was driving by, hopped inside and raced the current to get to the child before he drowned.It took them less than two minutes to catch up with him. As soon as they spotted him drifting down the canal, they jumped out of the truck and dropped rope in the water, hoping he would be lucid enough to catch it.Fortunately, they were able to drag him out of the water, thus preventing the situation from turning tragic.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 13:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/17/3655622/3655622_35D19E5E10A64FA9997037C62E5F4A9C_180717_3655622_Chinese_bypassers_save_kid_who_slipped_into_cana_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/14F/E99/14FE99FFFA299CC62F8B94FC9B1F386B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, viral, viral video, fall, buzz, viral, Gansu province, Gansu, canal, slippery, water, stream, current, kid, child, heroes, danger, dangerous, saving the day, drowning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3655618</guid>
      <title>Indonesian mob slaughters 292 crocodiles in revenge killing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SORONG / INDONESIA  Criminal charges may be filed after a mob slaughtered 292 crocodiles as an act of revenge at a sanctuary.The bloodshed took place after a villager was accidentally killed by one of the crocodiles.Last week, in the eastern Indonesian province of West Papua, a local resident Sugito was reportedly picking grass to feed his cattle in a local crocodile farm's breeding sanctuary.A local employee said he heard screams, then soon found a crocodile attacking Sugito. By the time help arrived, not much could be done for the unfortunate villager.Hundreds of enraged people attended the burial, and then marched to the sanctuary. The Washington Post reports that after storming the office, the mob went after the animals themselves. Armed with knives, machetes, hammers, and clubs, they dragged the beasts out of the water and tied their mouths before butchering them.Forty police officers were sent to stop the bloodshed, but they were helpless next to the 600 villagers. The endangered species bred in the sanctuary are protected, and officials from Indonesia's Natural Resources Conservation Agency said they may pursue criminal charges against those involved.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 13:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/17/3655618/3655618_828C0F0D7496437F9F6A0ED4FA9832F4_180717_3655618_Indonesian_mob_slaughters_292_crocodiles_in_reve_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7E1/94A/7E194AA2A9C2E5203C624B2C8E9BA28F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, slaughter, bloodshed, killing, revenge killing, Indonesia, crocodiles, crocs, gators, alligators, massacre, brutal, barbaric, villagers, West Papua, endangered species, protected species, purge, mob, carnage, massacre]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3655611</guid>
      <title>Study shows moisturizers with SPF not as effective as sunscreen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM   A study conducted by the British Association of Dermatologists shows that using a moisturizer with sun protection factor isn't as effective as applying sunscreen. The participants were asked to apply moisturizer with SPF where they missed around 16 percent of their face, of which 21% of their eyelids were missed, according to the study.Participants were then asked to apply sunscreen on their face, with a UV-sensitive camera taking pictures of their faces before and after application.They reportedly missed 10% of their whole face, while an average of 14% of their eyelid area was missed.As UVA rays and UVB rays penetrate the skin, it is important to use SPF protection of at least 15.If the skin is not protected from the sun, skin damage such as freckles and dark spots may occur.According to the National Health Service, additional protection such as a hat, a t-shirt, and sunglasses is also recommended.Researchers also reminded the public to apply sunscreen thoroughly to avoid diseases such as skin cancer in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 13:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/17/3655611/3655611_992BB6E9F0104DEDA8590C23AD4CF7ED_180717_3655611_Study_shows_moisturizers_with_SPF_not_as_effecti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A94/E0B/A94E0BDCAFD0A53F30976473D748AF1D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, UK, study, SPF, sunscreen, moisturizer, moisturizer with spf, spf 15, sun, importance of sunscreen, study shows SPF in moisturizer almost ineffective, protect the skin, UVA rays, UVB rays, SPF protection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3655337</guid>
      <title>Florida man staged suicide to look like murder by copying CSI plot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PALM BEACH GARDENS, FLORIDA  Police have ruled that a murder case they have been investigating for six months was actually a suicide.When police found Alan Jay Abrahamson with a gunshot wound to the heart and no weapon in sight, they assumed it was a homicide.But after a six-month investigation, detectives now believe the he staged the whole thing and took his own life, reports the Palm Beach Post.They believe the 71-year-old tied a gun to a weather balloon, and used it to shoot himself in the chest. Once he was down, the balloon lifted the gun and carried it several miles offshore, before popping and dropping down into the Atlantic.Investigators had been baffled by a line of blood that ran from the man's wound to his shoulder, suggesting something thin had been dragged across the shirt.Abrahamson's emails and search history revealed he'd been researching the scheme for over a decade. Receipts confirmed he'd bought two weather balloons and tanks of helium.Though far-fetched, the balloon-gun theory had appeared in one episode of CSI, and in one other real-life case, which attempted to copy the plot.Abrahamson also depleted his retirement fund and made large payments to his life insurance account before his death, which only backed the cops' suspicions.The case was officially ruled a suicide and is now closed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 08:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/17/3655337/3655337_53FC01D236D74A24AA49B1E8BA377336_180717_3655337_Florida_man_staged_suicide_to_look_like_murder_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6CD/029/6CD029C04840A1AB6BB7365875AA0ECB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, staged suicide, suicide, murder, CSI plot, balloon gun, weather balloon, life insurance, csi balloon, CSI, tv show]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3655311</guid>
      <title>Woman survives for a week after car plunges off cliff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN MATEO COUNTY, CALIFORNIA  An Oregon woman who disappeared a week ago was rescued from the bottom of a 200-foot cliff, where she survived by drinking water from the radiator of her wrecked SUV. Prior to her disappearance, 23-year-old Angela Hernandez had been driving from Portland to Southern California to visit her sister.According to the Monterey County Sheriff's Office, Hernandez said she was on Highway 1 when she swerved to avoid hitting an animal on July 6, and plunged over the cliff in the Big Sur area. After she stopped hearing back from her, Hernandez's sister filed a missing person report with the police.About seven days later, two hikers noticed Hernandez's partially submerged car wreck at the bottom of a cliff and immediately called 911.What's incredible is that Hernandez had apparently stayed alive by using the radiator of her white jeep to siphon water from a nearby stream.Hernandez luckily only sustained a shoulder injury, she was taken to a hospital for treatments and recovery.  Hernandez's sister, Isabel, recorded the event on her Facebook wrote that her sister is a fighter, and she fought for seven days and she will continue to do so.A GoFundMe page was set up to help with Hernandez's medical costs and to help her get a new car, which reached $3,470 of its $6,000 goal by Sunday morning.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 07:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/17/3655311/3655311_39DFE73243144284B69A540A2CB17C64_180717_3655311_Woman_survives_for_a_week_after_car_plunges_off__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B02/F1C/B02F1C5D496AE049C232CB34FEDFAB4D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, car plunging, woman survives on radiator, car falls off cliff, car falls off cliff into water, car falls off cliff california, woman survives]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3655248</guid>
      <title>Jaguar escapes habitat in New Orleans zoo and kills 6 animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUDUBON ZOO, NEW ORLEANS   A jaguar from the Audubon Zoo in New Orleans escaped and ended up killing six animals, reports CBS News.Zoo officials said the 3-year-old male jaguar escaped its habitat, because its roof may have been "compromised' and opened up an escape route.The incident took place around 7:20 a.m. before the zoo was open.After escaping, the jaguar  named Valerio reportedly attacked four aplacas, a fox and an emu, unfortunately they didn't survive. Valerio also attacked two other foxes and an alpaca, but they are expected to recover.Team members from the zoo sedated the jaguar within a few minutes with tranquilizers, reports Fox News.According to a press release from the Audubon Zoo, they plan to conduct a thorough investigation of how this happened.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 06:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/17/3655248/3655248_F8C63AF7F4084B2080465B2BB0FDCD21_180717_3655248_Jaguar_escapes_habitat_in_New_Orleans_zoo_and_ki_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/50C/CBE/50CCBEB33E96234FDCE563D870D9C85E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, zoo, New Orleans, jaguar, animal escapes, jaguar escapes, jaguar attack, zoo animals, zoo animals attacks, alpaca, fox, habitat, jaguar habitat, animal sedated, jaguar incident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656524</guid>
      <title>British tourist impaled by umbrella on Jersey beach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEASIDE HEIGHTS, NEW JERSEY  A British woman's Jersey Shore holiday took a terrible turn after she figured in a freak accident with a beach umbrella.WPVI reports that Margaret Reynolds had been relaxing at Seaside Heights Monday afternoon when a particularly strong gust of wind suddenly blew through the area.The wind uprooted a big beach umbrella and sent it flying toward the 67-year-old Londoner, which then impaled her right ankle with one of its thick aluminum spokes.A pediatrician and an EMT who happened to be on the beach tended to Reynolds and applied a tourniquet until emergency responders arrived and used a bolt cutter to cut the spoke off the umbrella frame.She was rushed to a hospital with a piece of metal still in her ankle, but it's since been dislodged.Reynolds was in good condition as of Tuesday, and already dismissed the incident as "just an accident" in true British fashion.Police say one way to prevent these impalements is to plant the umbrella at least two feet into the ground, with a back-and-forth motion instead of circular.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 14:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/18/3656524/3656524_4D9DE79BC4264702BCBA0177EBF36B9E_180718_3656524_British_tourist_impaled_by_umbrella_on_Jersey_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1D1/B2D/1D1B2D55675044B70100601A5403723F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, beach accident, impaled, impaled by umbrella, accident, freak accident, ankle injury, umbrella spoke, british tourist, jersey shore, new jersey beach]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656233</guid>
      <title>Judge orders L.A. Times to delete info from article on dirty cop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GLENDALE, CALIFORNIA  The Los Angeles Times is prepping for a legal showdown after a judge ordered them to change a story about a dirty cop.According to the L.A. Times, the article talked about John Saro Balian, a Glendale detective who got busted for working with the Mexican mafia and Armenian organized crime.Balian got into a plea deal with prosecutors that was supposed to be filed under seal, but instead was put on a public online database, where it was found by a Times reporter.Naturally, she included the information in her article, since it was relevant and publicly available.Balian's lawyer apparently didn't think so, and asked a judge to get the article thrown out. Lucky for him, he got Judge John F. Walter, who threw out First Amendment rights in favor of a dirty detective.The Times complied with the order to take out certain information, but is planning to fight back.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 09:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/18/3656233/3656233_F17D2FAD13404CA6A72DDF93D08A64A8_180718_3656233_Judge_orders_L_A__Times_to_delete_info_from_arti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA9/0E5/BA90E5F5C56D10736E3FB286C996E547.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, first amendment, press freedom, freedom of press, press rights, dirty cop, LA Times, Los Angeles Times, Glendale dirty cop, Mexican mafia, Armenian organized crime]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656131</guid>
      <title>Cops flip coin to decide whether to arrest or release speeding driver</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROSWELL, GEORGIA  A woman was pulled over by two officers for speeding, and her fate was decided by a coin toss. Three months ago, Sarah Webb was late for work, and rushing a bit too fast for police officers Courtney Brown and Kristee Wilson. She was pulled over for speeding, as she was allegedly driving as fast as 80 miles per hour on wet pavement. After checking her driver's license as well as her insurance details, Brown discussed with her colleague what they should do. Her first instinct was to arrest her on charges of reckless driving, but the police vehicle did not have a speed detector onboard, and the deputies could not decide whether to let Webb get away with a mere ticket or if she should be arrested.To make up their minds, they decided to go a coin flip. Although it appears the coin toss went in Webb's favor, Wilson used a police code to suggest that she should still be kept under custody.After footage of this incident was released, there was a massive public outcry. Members of the public have been speculating that the two officers may have used this coin toss tactic to determine the fates of other people as well.Roswell Police Chief Rusty Grant said investigation has been launched, and the officers involved have been placed on administrative leave. He also condemned their behavior in a statement. Webb did not know that it was a coin flip that ultimately decided her fate until the television station that broadcast the incident contacted her directly. All charges against Webb were eventually dismissed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 07:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/18/3656131/3656131_0CABC5331A884222BC8E289108D532B2_180718_3656131_Cops_flip_coin_to_decide_whether_to_arrest_or_re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7CC/99B/7CC99B5CADF58AE761B6AB19541CC90B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Georgia, Roswell, Cops, Roswell Police Deparment, Roswell PD, lousy cops, coin toss, coin flip, fate, bodycam, incident, speeding, driver, driving too fast, reckless driving]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656093</guid>
      <title>Tingling sensation in woman's feet turns out to be parasite in spine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FRANCE  A woman in France felt a tingling sensation in her legs, which turned out to be a parasitic tapeworm in her spine.The case was documented in a report from the New English Journal of Medicine.Doctors who conducted an MRI scan on the woman found parasitic tapeworm larvae in her spine.Parasitic tapeworms are typically found in farm animals such as sheep, cattle, goats, etc.The woman admitted she had a pet cat and "had been in contact with cattle."Tapeworm may lead to echinococcosis, which causes cysts to grow in the lungs and liver among other organs. If the cysts bursts, it can be deadly.Doctors ran a series of other tests as well and found the woman's white blood cell count had increased to around 19,000. Normal white blood cell counts range between 4,500 to 11,000, according to Medlineplus.gov.The woman was placed on anti-parasitic medication, and was clear of her infection with no symptoms of any recurrence after nine months, the New York Post reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 07:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/18/3656093/3656093_F0CAE31F6B664B94ABD56BA1A02E8A05_180718_3656093_Tingling_sensation_in_woman_s_feet_turns_out_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6DD/CAB/6DDCAB4EB18B8F9666F4555A8896EEA9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, France, woman, spine, parasite, parasite in spine,  feet, tingling sensation, electric shocks, tapeworm larvae, vertebrae, animals, farm animals, dogs, MRI scan, cysts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656055</guid>
      <title>A quadrillion tons of diamond may be hidden below Earth's surface</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EARTH    It turns out diamonds may not be that special.A new study from MIT suggests the interior of Earth is "filled with a quadrillion tons of diamonds."Scientists estimate the diamonds are more than 100 miles below the surface, beneath the continental tectonic plates.The study estimates 1-2 percent of the cratonic roots may be filled with diamonds.A statement from MIT News says scientists came to this conclusion while they were trying to "construct an image of what the earth's interior might look like."Researchers created virtual rock models to test what material would allow sound waves to travel that quickly through the cratonic roots. The result was diamonds. Scientists came up with an estimate of around a quadrillion tons of diamonds by taking into account the total volume of cratonic roots scattered inside Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/18/3656055/3656055_562189C179AD4331B3B7982C15C87B4A_180718_3656055_A_quadrillion_tons_of_diamond_may_be_hidden_belo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/92B/FF0/92BFF0A5BE3B4D14CE8A3E94992FD00C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Earth, diamond, diamonds in earth, scientists, study, cratonic roots, Earth's interior, rocks, virtual rock model, continental tectonic plates, Earth's surface, sound waves]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656040</guid>
      <title>Woman finds 'hundreds' of maggots on hotel floor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE BAY AREA, CALIFORNIA  A hotel is getting a ton of negative reviews after a video of "hundreds of maggots" in one of their bathrooms went public.Hayley Johnsen, a makeup artist, said she and her partner just checked into the hotel when she noticed something that "looked like a Tic Tac" on the floor, Fox News reported.She took a closer look and realised it wasn't a Tic Tac, but a maggot, and the bathroom floor was littered with them.She and her partner rush downstairs to the front desk inform them the room "is completely infested."The front desk offered to move them to another room but refused to give them a refund.Johnson and her partner insisted they get a refund, which is when the manager "demanded the couple check out immediately."Johnson said she and her partner then informed the police … they agreed it was a health hazard but were "unable to step in to resolve the issue."Johnson took to social media to share the story and told her followers to "call and complain"... after which the hotel received a ton of negative reviews.According to Mercury News, Johnson got what she wanted with the hotel apologizing to them and finally giving them a refund.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 06:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/18/3656040/3656040_C5EC47539CC249AE915FCA02D115D7D5_180718_3656040_Woman_finds__hundreds__of_maggots_on_hotel_floor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/98D/496/98D496BDF8BEE80F7D7B73E46559FFAC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, California, maggots, disgusting maggots, maggots in hotel room, maggots on the floor, hotel room, bathroom floor, hundreds of maggots, maggots everywhere]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656993</guid>
      <title>Rural city in Japan is facing a severe ninja shortage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IGA, JAPAN  Iga is trying to develop ninja tourism, but faces a shortage of performers.While Japan faces a major demographic crisis, it is also facing a lesser-known type of crisis triggered by the first one. Japan is going through a severe ninja crisis.The rural city of Iga, two hours away from Osaka, claims to be the birthplace of ninja culture. Like most middle size Japanese cities, Iga is suffering from depopulation. A constant flow of young people leaving for greater opportunities in bigger cities such as Tokyo or Osaka.According to NPR's "Planet money" podcast, the city is trying to take advantage of the recent surge in tourism that the whole country has been experiencing lately.There is a ninja museum, as well as a yearly ninja festival that brings about 30,000 tourists. But to make this ninja tourism scheme work, the city needs to attract a labor force.Specialized ninja performers have to go through intense training, and with an unemployment rate of just 2.5%, it is almost impossible to find candidates. Even though the payroll is really competitive, with modern ninjas earning up to $85.000 a year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 08:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/19/3656993/3656993_166378226543408890474A874CA81BDF_180719_3656993_Rural_city_in_Japan_is_facing_a_severe_ninja_sho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E91/C5C/E91C5CFCEAD55264A2A86681A25739F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Japan, Iga, ninja, ninja crisis, ninja shortage, high wage, high salary, Tokyo, tourism, money, economics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656950</guid>
      <title>Woman bites off neighbor's nose during assault</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON, TEXAS  A Texas woman is trying to raise emergency funds for her nose after her neighbor reportedly bit off part of it and swallowed it.In an interview with ABC 13, the victim, identified as "Tatiana", said she went to a bar Wednesday night with her next-door neighbor Jessica Collins, who was temporarily staying with her at the time. After a night out, the pair went home and Collins demanded more alcohol and cigarettes.According to Tatiana, she told Collins no and asked her to leave her property, Collins then jumped on her and pulled her to the ground by her hair.While Tatiana struggled to fight back, Collins apparently bit off a large part of Tatiana's nose off.After passing out several times before realizing a chunk of her nose is gone. Tatiana became hysterical and called her husband while screaming "I don't have a nose. I'm 28 years old and I don't have a nose anymore."Collins has been charged with misdemeanor assault inflicting bodily injury. She was released on bond on July 16, WRAL reported.Tatiana is in need of urgent plastic surgery, but she doesn't have health insurance. Doctors said she needs to have the surgery done in the next few weeks or it will become more complicated as the wound heals.Thankfully, Tatiana's friends have started a GoFundMe page to raise the money for her surgery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 07:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/19/3656950/3656950_0C1CEE98906B452BA069029C8268F512_180719_3656950_Woman_bites_off_neighbor_s_nose_during_assault_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7F8/C49/7F8C4984201AB438192356F7D1256CC4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, crazy neighbors, crazy neighbors 2018, bitten, plastic surgery, plastic surgery nose job, nose job recovery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656926</guid>
      <title>Details of how the Thai soccer team was extracted from the cave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THAILAND  Details of how the 12 boys of a Thai soccer team were extracted from a flooded cave have been released.The boys were first given anti-anxiety medication that prevented panic attacks while ensuring they remained conscious and breathing, the New York Times reports. The boys were then equipped with full face masks and secured to flexible plastic stretchers.In fully flooded areas, rescue teams held onto guide ropes while they moved the stretchers forward, surfacing roughly every 40 minutes to check the boys' vitals.To navigate downhill slopes, the stretchers were slid over thick hoses that were being used to pump water out of the cave.Teams carried the stretchers while navigating steeper, downhill areas.While crossing wet and uneven areas of the cave system, stretchers were supported by overhead ropes to keep the boys stable.In some flooded areas, the stretchers were placed on rafts that were pushed forward by rescue team members, who found their way with the aid of guide ropes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 07:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/19/3656926/3656926_C424529D48784DF6AEE6A8CC525EDE6D_180719_3656926_Details_of_how_the_Thai_soccer_team_was_extracte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1E7/90E/1E790EB3875D417EF396CEAB2CA29378.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Thai soccer team, Thai cave rescue, Pattaya Beach, Navy SEAL, trapped soccer team, trapped Thai boys]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656899</guid>
      <title>Woman missing in Shanghai after splashing ink on Xi Jinping poster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  A woman is missing in Shanghai, having disappeared after broadcasting a live video of herself splashing ink on a poster of Xi Jinping. Meanwhile, the Communist party has decided to take down posters of Xi Jinping, Radio Free Asia reports, as others have also taken to splashing ink on the president's face around the country.The movement spread as a way to support Dong Yaoqiong, 29, a Chinese blogger who posted a live video online on July 4th of herself throwing ink at a poster of Xi Jinping poster. In the video she says she opposes Xi's authoritarian tyranny.A few hours later, she posted a picture of men in uniform outside her door. That was her last tweet before her account was closed and she vanished.A Beijing artist who shared her video and expressed concerns about her safety, as well as Dong's father, were also both detained and questioned, Radio Free Asia reports. The two may have been placed under house arrest.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 06:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/19/3656899/3656899_CC5FF2268E1D4E0C90235F16E0CA21AA_180719_3656899_Woman_missing_in_Shanghai_after_splashing_ink_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/24C/43D/24C43D8659A82A4FF75F18E78ED7DC13.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, China, Shanghai, Communist Party, communism, one party state, police state, surveillance state, dissident, Xi Jinping, president for life, repression, ink girl, detention, jail, prison, dictatorship, tank man]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656757</guid>
      <title>Scientists reveal Otzi the Iceman's last meal 5,300 years ago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOLZANO, ITALY  Scientists have found out what an ancient iceman filled his belly with before he died.Otzi the Iceman was a hunter who died in the Alps 5,300 years ago, and his mummified body was discovered near the Italy-Austria border in 1991, National Geographic reports.Researchers were unable to locate the hunter's stomach until a CT scan revealed the misplaced organ tucked under a rib cage.An analysis published in the journal Current Biology revealed that half the stomach contents consisted of the fat and meat of an alpine goat. They also found red deer meat, whole wheat seeds, and traces of toxic bracken fern.The toxic fern may have been ingested accidentally, or possibly as medicine for whipworm parasites, which had previously found in his intestines, according to the Guardian.All in all, Otzi's final meal seemed to be pretty well-balanced. Goat fat made sense given the harsh terrain, but as for the taste: it's apparently really horrible.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 03:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/19/3656757/3656757_542B77EF38FF4D68B02BADEACDF50142_180719_3656757_Scientists_reveal_Otzi_the_Iceman_s_last_meal_5__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F75/726/F75726A0F284BEBDE19F419A61E2A7D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, otzi the iceman, iceman, ancient iceman, last meal, stomach contents, ancient diet, goat meat, alpine ibex, deer, toxic fern, toxic bracken, stomach parasites, whipworm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656747</guid>
      <title>2,500-year-old mummification workshop found in Egypt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAQQARA, EGYPT  During a dig in Saqqara, Egypt, a team of Egyptian and German archeologists discovered a mummification workshop dating back more than 2,500 years, according to a press statement released by Egypt's Ministry of State of Antiquities.The statement added that an embalming workshop contained labeled bowls and measuring cups, which held oils and substances that were used in the mummification process.Two basins were also found, which archaeologists believe may have been used to dry the mummies and prepare the bandages used to wrap them. A 30-meter burial shaft was also discovered near the mummification workshop in the Saqqara necropolis in Egypt.Five mummies with their sarcophagi were found. Archaeologists found a mummy with a gilded silver mask with eyes containing calcite, obsidian and a black gemstone inside one of the sarcophagi.Shabti figurines, which were placed with the dead to accompany them into the afterlife, and alabaster vessels were also found at the excavation site.More excavations in the area are expected to take place this year.The findings will soon be displayed in a museum, with Egypt hoping the discoveries will attract more tourists to the country.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 02:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/19/3656747/3656747_CF02F481454241D3A8F93B36A32CC421_180719_3656747_2_500_year_old_mummification_workshop_found_in_E_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B61/734/B61734A30DA7FE31B8392BBF996965CA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Egypt, mummies, burial site, sarcophagus, mummy burial, excavation, ancient egyptians, archaeologists, silver gilded mask, mummy workshop, pottery vessels, figurines, egyptian tourism]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3656742</guid>
      <title>Russia planning to build laser cannon to shoot space debris</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUSSIA   The Russian space agency is planning to get rid of space debris by shooting it with a laser cannon, reports RT.Scientists have noted the increasing amount of space debris floating outside of Earth's atmosphere, most of which is "the size of a marble" while around ⅓ of the debris is the "size of a softball."The cannon will be based on the 3-meter optical telescope, which is already being made. It will be designed to monitor space satellites and keep an eye out for potentially dangerous space debris.The optical telescope will eventually be transformed into a powerful laser cannon, if things go according to plan.The laser cannon will be supplied power from a type of solid-base generator, and will supposedly use a process called "laser ablation" to remove debris surrounding Earth's atmosphere.The energy of the laser would heat and pierce and object until it evaporates.Different countries such as China, Australia, and Japan have tried their hand at getting rid of the space debris..without any success so far, RT reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 02:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/19/3656742/3656742_DA64404B93BD443FBE82EA14E3883B6A_180719_3656742_Russia_planning_to_build_laser_cannon_to_shoot_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/21D/13D/21D13D1531AD2A5B0169C8E55ABFC9F3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Russia, Space, Laser, Space laser, Massive space laser cannon, Space junk, Space debris, blasting space junk with laser, Space debris around Earth, Space junk floating around Earth's orbit, Earth's orbit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657938</guid>
      <title>Trump plans to redesign Air Force One with red, white, and blue</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA U.S. President Donald Trump told CBS News that he will redesign the presidential plane Air Force One into a more patriotic color scheme.CBS reports that the White House announced in February, Trump had negotiated a $3.9 billion "fixed price contract" with Boeing for the Boeing 747-8 planes to used as the new presidential aircraft, commonly known as Air Force One.In an interview with CBS, Trump said he was able to save the country $1.5 billion and order a new one, this came as a response after his 2016 Tweet about the costs of the new planes being "out of control, more than $4 billion.Currently, the president's suite and office are housed at the very front of the aircraft.In the event of an emergency, Air Force One has a staff doctor and houses a medical suite that can function as an operating room at a moment's notice.Air Force One also has quarters for those who accompany the president, including travelling press who sit in the rear of the plane.As it is able to refuel mid-air, Air Force One effectively has unlimited range and can stay up in the air indefinitely.As part of its advanced security systems, the jet is equipped with chaff and flare dispensers that allow it to evade enemy missiles.Trump plans to redesign the aircraft exterior with the iconic American flag color setting, the red, white, and blue. The new presidential vehicle is expected to sport styling elements similar Cadillac's CT6 sedan. Known as 'Cadillac One' or by the Secret Service as 'The Beast,' it will use a Kodiak medium-duty truck frame with custom-made body panels.The seven-seat interior is sealed to protect against a biological or chemical attack, with windows that can withstand armor-piercing bullets.The current edition of the Beast has 20-centimeter-thick heavy armor-plated doors and a reinforced steel plate running underneath the vehicle to protect it from roadside bombs.The presidential limousine has tear gas cannons and a night vision camera, as well as a pump-action shotgun. Extra weapons, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type are also on board. The fuel tank is armor-plated and encased in foam to prevent it from exploding. The kevlar-reinforced tires are puncture and shard-resistant, with steel rims that allow the car to continue driving if the tires are destroyed.Trump said the current Air Force One is 30 years old and the new planes will likely be utilized more by the presidents who follow him. He also announced that he is making changes to the plane's interior including an increase the size of the beds, complaining they were smaller than those on his own private jet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 11:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/20/3657938/3657938_CC142BA377A74A40956AE85448D640B6_180720_3657938_Trump_plans_to_redesign_Air_Force_One_with_red___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C20/F65/C20F652E9663F4B1BD8811B9C4F484BE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, air force one trump, air force one trump plane,air force one new paint job, air force one redesign, us air force one, us air force one plane, air force one us president aircraft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657747</guid>
      <title>Esports to debut at 2018 Asian Games in Indonesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAKARTA  Competitive gamers, rejoice! Esports is finally getting included in the Asian Games for the first time since it started.Esports, or electronic competitive gaming, was recognized as a sport by the International Olympic Committee in November, Reuters reports.Esports has over 250 million players around the world, and a growing market worth a billion dollars a year.The 2018 Asian Games in Jakarta, held from August 18 to September 2, will only feature esports as a demonstration event, but it's set to debut as a medal event at the 2022 games in Hangzhou, China.Six game titles have been confirmed for the 2018 roster: League of Legends, Hearthstone, Pro Evolution Soccer, Starcraft II, Clash Royale, and Arena of Valor.Twenty-seven countries and regions had signed up for the Qualifier Competitions from June 6 to 20. Matches were held online and offline in in Hong Kong, Ho Chi Minh, and Changzhou.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 07:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/20/3657747/3657747_38BEF974855F4D3DA65972D9306F2831_180720_3657747_Esports_to_debut_at_2018_Asian_Games_in_Indonesi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/91E/FAE/91EFAE0860D37ECAC0BAF79453735325.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, esports, asian games, 2018 asian games, gaming, competitive gaming, sports, league of legends, hearthstone, arena of valor, pes 2018, starcraft, clash royale]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657727</guid>
      <title>Researcher finds six male sharks pregnant.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ODISHA, INDIA   That's unusual.A researcher has discovered six hermaphrodite sharks pregnant off the coast in eastern India, reports Science News.Marine biologist Alissa Barnes noticed there were more male bigeye houndsharks than females, yet the males had a "visible stomach bulge."Barnes dissected the fish and found the 'male sharks' had external claspers  like most male houndsharks   but they also had ovaries like their female counterparts.In her published report, Barnes called this phenomenon "intersexuality."Six of the seven dissected sharks turned out to be pregnant, with Barnes finding at least two baby sharks in one.Another shark biologist told Science News that hermaphroditism  an organism containing both male and female reproductive systems  is rare in sharks.Barnes claims this abnormality may have been caused by "pollutants in the water" or "hormonal changes," reports Science News.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 07:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/20/3657727/3657727_D452E157438F46CCA12920348E4BCE4D_180720_3657727_Researcher_finds_six_male_sharks_pregnant__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7B4/604/7B4604E20F569897BFE2B887F8D24A0D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, marine biologist, science, marine life, under the sea, sharks, male sharks, bigeye houndshark, hermaphroditism, pollutants, water, ocean, sea, pregnant male sharks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657553</guid>
      <title>Liver disease kills more Americans due to excess alcohol intake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED STATES    A study published in the British Medical Journal states that more young people are dying from liver disease than in the past.Data from the CDC shows the number of 24-34 year olds who died due to alcohol-related liver disease has nearly tripled between 1999-2016  from 259 in 1999 to 767 in 2016.Dr. Elliot Tapper, who co-wrote the study, believes that it may have something to do with the global financial crisis … as a "loss of opportunity" and "psychological burden" may have led some to "abusive drinking."According to the study, ethnic groups such as whites, Native Americans and Hispanic Americans saw an increase of liver-related deaths while Asian Americans saw a decrease. Binge drinking is defined by the CDC as drinking five or more "standard drinks" in a few hours for men and four for women.The CDC warns that drinking too much alcohol can cause liver cancer and may also cause liver cirrhosis.However, Dr. Tapper did have some encouraging news: liver disease is often reversible. The sooner the patients stop drinking, the better their chances of recovering.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/20/3657553/3657553_F57C8A71D107488F85496E17D89939EE_180720_3657553_Liver_disease_kills_more_Americans_due_to_excess_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/71B/142/71B1429EC1828F368B4035B5D4786E4E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Study, USA, Alcohol, young adults, liver cancer, liver disease, liver cirrhosis, alcoholism, alcohol addiction, alcohol abuse, drinking, heavy drinking, binge drinking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657546</guid>
      <title>How mosquitoes transfer viruses and diseases to humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S.  The diseases that mosquitoes transmit kill hundreds of thousands of people each year, Scientific American reports.Female mosquitoes only bite humans when they require blood to feed their eggs. To suck blood, female mosquitoes use six needle-like parts, which scientists refer to as stylets. Two of these are called maxillae[m]; they are equipped with saw-like teeth that are able ot cut through human skin without a person noticing.Another set of needles, the mandibles[n], hold tissue apart to allow the Labrum[o] to dig through human skin in search for blood. Once it locates a source, it sucks it out.The hypopharynx[p] injects saliva into blood vessels, delivering chemicals that keep the blood flowing. Mosquito saliva causes blood vessels dilate, blocks a person's immune response and lubricates the proboscis. This results in a person suffering from itchy welts. During this process, dangerous viruses, such as Zika and West Nile virus, can be transferred into the human body.Texas, Colorado, Utah, Ohio, Indiana are all experiencing outbreaks of the West Nile virus, with the number of mosquitoes carrying the virus seem to be growing as well.About 1 in 150 people who are infected with West Nile virus develop severe illness that affects the central nervous system. About 1 out of 10 people who develop this illness die.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/20/3657546/3657546_8D370C3CCA1A497D82A681D226B204FB_180720_3657546_How_mosquitoes_transfer_viruses_and_diseases_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/963/D9F/963D9FBB5402CA3C42E7E3536C47EDAF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mosquitoes viruses, viruses transmitted by mosquitoes, how do mosquitoes spread viruses, mosquitoes diseases, diseases spread by mosquitoes, how mosquitoes transmit diseases, west nile virus, zika]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3657534</guid>
      <title>New NASA jet design turns sonic booms into 'sonic thumps'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON/BETHESDA, MARYLAND  Lockheed Martin and NASA have partnered to develop a quiet supersonic plane named the X-59. According to information from the space agency's website, the proposed single-pilot craft has a wingspan of 29.5 feet, is 94 feet long and weighs 32,300 pounds at total fuel capacity. NASA says the X-59 will be powered by a General Electric F414 engine. This is the same engine used by F/A-18 E/F fighter jets. The craft's hull is designed to abate the noise from shockwaves traditionally associated with mach speed travel. During that, shockwaves come together and create loud sonic booms. The space agency says the X-59 is designed to separate these shockwaves, resulting in a much less noise reaching the ground.The aircraft's first test flight is scheduled for 2021, according to a Lockheed Martin news release.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/20/3657534/3657534_E2FB9D36587345CE8E2BCE87273D5CBA_180720_3657534_New_NASA_jet_design_turns_sonic_booms_into__soni_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D36/960/D369607FB7B28209F52C84BB59B64E3D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, x-59, supersonic jet, supersonic speed, mach speed, nasa airplane, nasa jet, lockheed martin, awesome science videos, cool science facts, NASA, cool nasa inventions, technology, NASA explainer, x-59 quesst, quiet supersonic sound technology, noise reduction technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659839</guid>
      <title>Israel's Merkava Mk. 4 Barak to be a smart tank with A.I.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISRAEL   Israel plans to equip its battle tank with artificial intelligence.The Merkava Mark 4 Barak will reportedly be the first tank to have a smart mission computer to manage tasks.Israel's Merkava Mark 4 Barak would have an advanced AI system which would help to locate targets and strike accurately, reports New Atlas.Virtual reality will also be added onto the tank, with combat soldier using a helmet called Iron View, developed by Elbit Systems, to "see the outside environment from inside the combat vehicle."Virtual reality simulations are aimed at allowing the soldiers to partake in military exercises in real time.A press release claims updated sensors equipped on the outside the tank would "allow the combat soldiers to operate the tank in a simple and advanced way."The press release also states these improvement will help the tank "carry out missions that are up to 30% longer than current ones."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 13:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659839/3659839_CA4D347911A741B9AEA0E2BDA1208D7B_180723_3659839_Israel_s_Merkava_Mk__4_Barak_to_be_a_smart_tank__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA9/A92/BA9A92673AECC2865BA9597EF1386793.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Israel, battle tank, smart battle tank, AI, smart mission computer, sensors, military exercises, virtual reality, VR, virtual reality simulation, soldiers, combat soldiers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659835</guid>
      <title>Bed bugs forced Air India to ground Newark-Mumbai flights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWARK, NEW JERSEY  Passengers of multiple flights from New Jersey to India were reportedly bitten by bed bugs last week.Air India had received complaints about the bugs in business class seats, but apparently ignored them last week. The Hindustan Times reports one man complained that the business class seats he and his family were sitting in during their 17-hour flight from New Jersey to Mumbai were "infested with bed bugs." Because of the bed bugs, the family were later moved to economy but had to deal with broken tables and TVs. Another passenger said he could see bed bugs crawling around on the seats.More complaints keep coming as another Air India passenger tweeted that his wife and three kids flew business from Newark to Mumbai and are now suffering bug bites all over their body.Last Thursday, a Mumbai-bound Air India flight was grounded because multiple passengers, including an 8-month-old baby, had allegedly suffered bug bites during the flight.Air India later said the aircrafts in question have been fumigated and seat covers and other hardware have been replaced. Meanwhile, NJ.com reported that the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey said the airline has not received reports of bed bugs in the terminal or other parts of the airport.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 13:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659835/3659835_76C7479780894978B2EC73B73C4F6C7C_180723_3659835_Bed_bugs_forced_Air_India_to_ground_Newark_Mumba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6CF/01A/6CF01AF753FC263BE9A404C3719CBCB7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bed bugs, bed bugs infestation, bed bugs bites, bed bugs air india, bed bugs complaints, air india bugs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659830</guid>
      <title>Burger King offers terminally ill dog cheeseburgers for life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOLEDO, OHIO  When Alec Karcher heard that his dog Cody was diagnosed with cancer, he decided to pamper his pooch to daily cheeseburgers.Every day, Karcher went to his local Burger King restaurant to order these plain cheese burgers.One day, out of curiosity, a Burger King employee asked Karcher why he was ordering plain cheese burgers on a daily basis.Karcher explained his 10-year-old dog had been diagnosed with cancer and had around 1-3 months to live. /Though heartbroken, they decided to make Cody's last days as enjoyable as possible.The employee was touched and went to talk to her manager. They decided that Cody would get free cheeseburgers at their Burger King store for life.Karcher appreciated the gesture and took to Twitter to thank Burger King for their "love and kindness.."Burger King also responded from their corporate account saying "the world needs more kindness and empathy.."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659830/3659830_C520CF449CB14C52AB8A1F90EC0D0056_180723_3659830_Burger_King_offers_terminally_ill_dog_cheeseburg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9C9/77C/9C977C32534571E09BBE00163E4E8F90.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,Burger King,dog,terminally ill dog,cancer-stricken dog,cheeseburgers,plain cheeseburgers,dog gets cheeseburgers for life at Burger King,dog videos,dog cancer video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659531</guid>
      <title>Update on 'ink-girl' who vanished after splashing ink on Xi's face</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  A woman is missing in Shanghai, having disappeared after broadcasting a live video of herself splashing ink on a poster of Xi Jinping. Meanwhile, the Communist party has decided to take down posters of Xi Jinping, Radio Free Asia reports, as others have also taken to splashing ink on the president's face around the country.The movement spread as a way to support a 29-years-old Chinese blogger who posted a live video online on July 4th of herself throwing ink at a poster of Xi Jinping. In the video she says she opposes Xi's authoritarian tyranny.A few hours later, she posted a picture of men in uniform outside her door. That was her last tweet before her account was closed and she vanished.A Beijing artist who shared her video and expressed concerns about her safety, as well as Dong's father, were also both detained and questioned, Radio Free Asia reports. The two may have been placed under house arrest.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 07:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659531/3659531_5E77FA560A794449A40991B4B1429E4E_180723_3659531_Update_on__ink_girl__who_vanished_after_splashin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/385/D0B/385D0B8EEB59E161950FD9983384CC4E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, China, Shanghai, Communist Party, communism, one party state, police state, surveillance state, dissident, Xi Jinping, president for life, repression, ink girl, detention, jail, prison, dictatorship, tank man, Youtube, youtube censorship, youtube AI]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659529</guid>
      <title>Teen usage of digital media may be linked to symptoms of ADHD</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA  The Journal of the American Medical Association has published a study which suggests the more teens use digital media, the more likely for symptoms of ADHD to develop.The study found nearly 81% of students reported using at least one type of digital media multiples times daily.At the beginning of the study, the students involved had to complete a survey in which they answered how often they consumed 14 different media activities such as social media, texting, watching videos online, and more, reports CNN.The students took a total of five surveys in the fall 2014, spring of 2015, fall of 2015, spring of 2016, and fall of 2016."Reports also say it is possible that phone notifications distract the students' attention, making it harder to develop concentration skills."According to the surveys, the teens who reported "infrequently using digital media" had a 4.6% chance of reporting ADHD symptoms in the surveys that followed.For teens who reported using seven digital media platforms, the percentage almost doubled to 9.5%.And for the students who said they use all 14 digital platforms on a daily basis, the percentage climbed to 10.5.Adam Leventhal, the lead author of the study, said to CNN there weren't any clinicians involved in the study to "provide a diagnosis" as the study was based on self-reports on digital media use compared to ADHD symptoms.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 07:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659529/3659529_5C4B4AAD34AD43B98B9D236270CFAC70_180723_3659529_Teen_usage_of_digital_media_may_be_linked_to_sym_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5E6/788/5E678801407EB207F7A777D81E7879C0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Study, teens, ADHD, ADHD symptoms, easily distracted, stimulation, digital media, digital media activities, technology, social media, smartphones, social networking, texting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659351</guid>
      <title>Boy "turning to stone" from rare medical condition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALAMOSA, COLORADO  A family is desperately searching for a cure for their son, whose debilitating condition is basically turning him into stone.Fox43 reports that Jaiden Rogers has congenital fascial dystrophy, or stiff skin syndrome  a connective tissue disorder characterized by thick, stone-like skin.The 12-year-old's struggle with the disease started six years ago, when his adoptive dad Tim Rogers noticed a small, hard lump on his right thigh that got bigger and spread at an alarming rate.It soon wrapped around his legs, hips, butt, and arms, and making it difficult and painful to move, and confining him to a wheelchair.Chemotherapy slowed the calcification for a while, but the symptoms have since gotten worse, with Jaiden now needing a respirator to help him breathe.Only 40 other cases of the rare condition have ever been documented in the world, so doctors know very little, and are still struggling to find a cure. They say the worst case scenario is total paralysis, with Jaiden becoming entombed within himself.Stem cell treatment in Europe could be the boy's last hope, but the family's finances have already been exhausted.A GoFundMe account has been set up to fund the medical costs. Only $43,000 of the  $1.5 million goal has been raised so far, but family and friends say donating air miles or hotel points would also help.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 03:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659351/3659351_64571D385170494C850DB96FD57AC981_180723_3659351_Boy__turning_to_stone__from_rare_medical_conditi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DCE/443/DCE44390666A61A6256594950223E1BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, stiff skin syndrome, stiff skin, stone skin, greyscale, congenital fascial dystrophy, rare condition, miracle cure, chemotherapy, stiff skin cure, jaiden rogers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659348</guid>
      <title>Swarm of 80,000 of bees sting  woman more than 200 times</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA   A lady was stung by a swarm of nearly 80,000 bees, reports CBS News.The 52-year-old cleaning lady was just going about her day, getting her cleaning supplies from the car when the bees decided to attack.Apparently the poor woman was attacked viciously with the bees in her hair, and "crawling all over her face."The firefighters reportedly didn't even have enough time to put on protective gear..they just grabbed a carbon dioxide fire extinguisher and made a run. As a result, the brave firefighters were injured with two of them needed medical treatment.An ambulance took the woman to the hospital. Meanwhile, bee experts arrived at the scene to get rid of the giant beehive.According to reports from CNN, the Fire Authorities commented saying the woman is recovering and "expected to survive."That was a close one.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659348/3659348_49E0FAE141834ECFAEC95D0CDB8FDDD3_180723_3659348_Swarm_of_80_000_of_bees_sting__woman_more_than_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ED3/A18/ED3A189D2F0D12D0D16124845A3F7E6A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, woman, bees, bees attack, bees attacking people, bees attack woman, swarm of bees, firefighters, fire extinguisher, bee experts, beehive, beehive removal, medical treatment, hospital, ambulance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3659337</guid>
      <title>Legalizing recreational weed could be lucrative for New York</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  A new report claims the benefits of legalizing recreational Houdini outweighs the risks.According to WNYC, the medical variety is allowed in New York, but can only be taken by patients with certain conditions. It's only permitted in pill, oil, or vape form   no smoking, and no space brownies.The state limits the number of licensed dispensaries, and requires each one to grow, harvest, and manufacture what they sell.Many are pushing for full legalization, but Governor Andrew Cuomo isn't sold, at one point even calling it a gateway into more sinister addictions.The New York Department of Health though, is. Their new report supports legalizing recreational pot, finding that it could earn the state millions.An infographic created by Syracuse University's Whitman School of Management shows that New York could earn over 400 million dollars in tax revenues, not to mention over a billion in gross sales, with recreational pot legalized.The health report also predicts that the move could decrease opioid use and remove criminal penalties related to dope, which disproportionately affect minorities.A majority of voters in the state are pro-pot, and many officials think legalizing it is more a "when" than an "if". But with state lawmakers not expected to convene until January, it's probably not gonna happen this year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 02:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/23/3659337/3659337_440B91B21A254FCCB4A415D3BB53FC42_180723_3659337_Legalizing_recreational_weed_could_be_lucrative__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/71D/947/71D947ABF0B10D7719B7929B82DA251D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, legal pot, legalized pot, pot, cannabis, grass, mary jane, dope, new york, nyc, tax revenue, colorado, california, infographic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660553</guid>
      <title>China recalls heart drug and rabies vaccines</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA    Two Chinese pharmaceutical companies have recalled their rabies vaccine and heart medication respectively after they were found to be tainted.Changchun Changsheng Biotechnology was found to be illegally producing "freeze-dried human rabies vaccines," reports Xinhua.The company reportedly fabricated production records and product inspection records.Zhejiang Huahai Pharmaceutical voluntarily suspended production of a heart drug after it was found to contain N-nitrosodimethylamine, or NDMA, reports Precision Vaccinations.The European Medicines Agency found the chemical  "tainted with an impurity linked to cancer," reports Reuters.NDMA was found in an ingredient called valsartan, which the company used to create drugs aimed at treating high blood pressure and heart failure.Chinese citizens have voiced their opinions about the situation on Chinese social media, with one netizen saying "if the state does not protect its citizens, how can we love our country?"According to Xinhua, authorities have launched an investigation and plan to conduct more unannounced inspections in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 12:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/24/3660553/3660553_77CD471CD3B1476481B21FCABA00A1C4_180724_3660553_China_recalls_heart_drug_and_rabies_vaccines_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE4/AB5/CE4AB5BE32C074C478869BD986D3ABDE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, pharmacy, pharmaceutical company, heart drug, rabies vaccine, illegal production, valsartan, NDMA, cancer-causing impurities, cancer, vaccine recall, drug recall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660466</guid>
      <title>This month will mark the longest lunar eclipse of this century</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOON  The longest lunar eclipse of this century is expected to take place on July 27 for about 1 hour and 43 minutes, reports Space.com.NASA reports Earth's shadow is made from three different parts, the outer part known as the penumbra, the central part known as the umbra and the antumbra, which is beyond the penumbra and umbra. The moon will reportedly turn a "ruddy brown color" when it enters the umbra.The entire event, from start to finish, will take about four hours.According to Express, this month's moon will be at its apogee, which is its farthest possible distance from Earth.However, when the moon is at its nearest to Earth, it is called a perigee.According to space.com, the blood moon will be visible in most places, except in north America.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/24/3660466/3660466_3B60F43DC4DE4683962DCDDDC2BCE820_180724_3660466_This_month_will_mark_the_longest_lunar_eclipse_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4F2/2B7/4F22B73BEF2EF0F4575FFDEFFE6D8A6E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, moon, lunar eclipse, earth, longest lunar eclipse of the century, blood moon, perigee, apogee, total lunar eclipse, penumbra, umbra, antumbra]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660070</guid>
      <title>Venezuelans turn to 'dog carts' as alternative transportation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARACAIBO, VENEZUELA  Venezuelans struggling with the country's nonexistent transportation system are resorting to dangerous and often illegal means of getting around.Reuters reports that two years ago, passenger buses in Venezuela numbered at least 280,000, but have disappeared gradually due to expensive or unavailable parts.Public transportation has become scarce, with 95% of buses, cars, and taxis no longer on the road. Instead, residents are relying on over 150,000 unlicensed vehicles, nicknamed "kennels" or "dog carts," to get to their destination.This alternative means of transport often takes takes the form of delivery trucks or vans that standing passengers can cram themselves into.The "kennels" are so named for their cramped and unsafe conditions, which this year alone has caused 39 deaths and 275 injuries, according to opposition lawmaker Nora Bracho.Residents are well aware of the risks of getting into the "kennels", but with a slow-moving government, it's not like they have a choice.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 02:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/24/3660070/3660070_AB834694783A4447B6F8049E2673C7D3_180724_3660070_Venezuelans_turn_to__dog_carts__as_alternative_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1A9/0D0/1A90D097FC08F8822BF1C2273F5220F1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  kennel, dog cart, venezuela, transportation, public transportation, public transport, illegal transport, cargo, delivery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660053</guid>
      <title>Wife rides on car's windshield to catch cheating husband's mistress</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANJING / CHINA  This video went viral in China. It shows a betrayed wife riding on her husband's car windshield, and desperately trying to go after the mistress who is sitting inside.The footage shows a woman perched on the hood of this Audi. Inside the car, happened to be her husband as well as his secret mistress. After the betrayed wife spent spending quite some time screaming and whacking at the windshield, the car eventually stopped at a crossroad. The unfaithful husband came out of the car in an attempt to calm her down, but only stirred up his wife's anger. She finally got hold of the mistress's hair, with her husband apparently helpless to separate them. The police had to intervene to put an end to the street soap opera. The last image of the footage shows the wife surrounded by police officers and completely breaking down. Chinese netizens didn't pass up on the opportunity to expose and shame the mistress, disclosing private informations about her on social networks.Some noticed that the secret girlfriend was wearing a designer bag and luxurious clothes worth $3,000, while the wife was wearing a much cheaper outfit.Rumor has it the husband convinced his wife to buy an apartment, but he instead used the money to treat his girlfriend. He also bought the car under her name.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 02:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/24/3660053/3660053_34D29D20169A4C0EB2986E9696848218_180724_3660053_Wife_rides_on_car_s_windshield_to_catch_cheating_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2AE/FED/2AEFED0E69FEFDBA6243CBF4FFFF8CA5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, China, Nanjing, secret lover, secret girlfriend, cheating husband, betrayed wife, couple, marriage, divorce, wife and husband, car, audi, public argument, angry wife, crazy wife, angry ex]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660050</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Episode 7</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured from cops around the globe.THIS WEEK: 1. Irving motorcycle officer has quick reaction time.2. A turtle doesn't show enough gratitude to policeman.3. A Baltimore deputy is at the right time and place to arrest villain.4. A suspicious bear investigates Russian police cars.5. A patrolling sergeant saves a kid running dangerously close to traffic.6. A cop pulls over an SUV that was being driven by a surprising driver.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 02:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/24/3660050/3660050_26192934972C443D8986441FF17C1277_180724_3660050_LAWMAN_CAM__Episode_7_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E7D/A09/E7DA0981B0EB3201CF9C3571F5E99817.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, good cop, hero cops, cops doing amazing things, latest police videos, new police videos,  latest cop video, new cop footage, police footage, police body cam, police dash cam, police compilation 2018, cop videos, police chase 2018, latest police chase videos, crazy car chases, police pursuit,, us police videos, cop camera, lawman cam, tomonews lawman cam, police responding, police news, latest police video, latest police videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661317</guid>
      <title>TSA and AA working together to develop new carry-on scanner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA   The TSA is working with American Airlines to bring about a new scanning machine that may change the experience of security lines for many travelers, reports CBS News.Travellers in the U.S. have become accustomed to long TSA lines where shoes and belts are removed, and smartphones are placed within X-ray machines, among other things.X-ray machines may soon be replaced with a CT, or computed tomography bag-scanning machine, which would create 3D images of the contents within a piece of luggage, reports Fortune.This way, passengers would not be required to take anything out of their carry-on baggage, as the machine would be able to "see through" it.TSA administrator David Pekoske described the technology as "revolutionary," reports CBS News.The machine would allow officers to directly zoom in and rotate the 3D image, which reportedly would be "much better at detection."Pekoske also said that in around five years, they expect passengers to not have to remove any items from their carry-on bags.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/25/3661317/3661317_390F3B6D662B4501A56C871972CD9C0C_180725_3661317_TSA_and_AA_working_together_to_develop_new_carry_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ACA/181/ACA181C7D07CE5A7C0CB91E9D7EE86C7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, USA, TSA, American airlines, airport security screening, X-ray machine, CT bag scanning machine, suitcase, luggage, travelling, 3D image, 3D carry-on luggage scanner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661069</guid>
      <title>Man develops serious condition because he exercised too much</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUNAN / CHINA  A Chinese newspaper reports that a man had to be hospitalized because he exercised too much.Mr. Luo, 36, usually does not exercise much, saying it's because his work keeps him busy.However, Luo and his wife had  just made plans to have their first baby. Like all future parents, they wanted to have a healthy infant, and they thought that if Mr. Luo worked out, it would have a positive impact on the health of their soon-to-be-conceived baby.He went out for a 3-kilometer run and came back exhausted, with his leg muscles completely sore. He soon realized something was very wrong and went to the hospital.After a medical examination, doctors concluded Luo was suffering from rhabdomyolysis, a condition during which damage skeletal muscles break down, releasing harmful proteins into the patient's blood.Although the condition is mainly seen in people injured during earthquakes or similar disasters, it can affect anyone whose muscles become damaged. Doctors advise that people should carry out exercise appropriate to their physicality, and gradually increase the intensity of their workout sessions in order to avoid these kinds of issues.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 08:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/25/3661069/3661069_91862B31B3BE4EC5B2D752527451EFE9_180725_3661069_Man_develops_serious_condition_because_he_exerci_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0DD/74D/0DD74D32D572B53A9AD82CF7D32973A5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, Hunan, jogger, runner, jogging, running, medical condition, weird condition, rhabdomyolysis, muscle pain, baby, pregnant, parents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661052</guid>
      <title>UK teen boys to be vaccinated against HPV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  A shot that protects against the HPV virus, which is said to cause causes cervical cancer in women, will be given to boys aged 12 to 13 in England, the BBC reports.Thousands of boys in England are expected to be vaccinated under the program each year, most likely starting sometime in 2019 or 2020.The HPV virus can be passed on through unprotected sex, and is also linked to head, neck, cervical, penile and vaginal cancers, states the UK's National Health Service.The HPV vaccine is already given to teenage girls, and is free up until they turn 18, the BBC reports.UK's National Health Service have been providing HPV vaccine shots to girls since 2008.Girls were prioritised because the virus causes cervical cancer that kills about 1,000 women every year, while around 500 women die from other HPV virus-related cancers.However, the BBC reports, that doctors say HPV infections cause cancer of the anus, penis, mouth and throat in boys.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 07:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/25/3661052/3661052_821E4E6FF5FA47728205A60A18BAEB30_180725_3661052_UK_teen_boys_to_be_vaccinated_against_HPV_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/92C/8C7/92C8C7E0D2503426687F5C9A65CD3FA8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, HPV vaccine, hpv vaccine for boys, hpv vaccine for girls, HPV virus, hpv virus in men, hpv virus in women, hpv virus cure, hpv virus cancer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3660803</guid>
      <title>Facial recognition system to boost school security in the US</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  Realnetworks has announced that it will offer facial recognition technology to schools for free, with the aim at making schools in U.S. safe, Geekwire reported.According to Realnetworks, SAFR is a highly accurate facial recognition software powered by artificial intelligence; it works with IP cameras to match faces in real-time.Schools will need a database with photos of people authorized to be on campus. When an unauthorized person or someone who poses potential threat appears on campus, SAFR notifies a member of the staff.Realnetworks says the facial data and images SAFR collects are encrypted as a privacy protection and the school gets to keep them.SAFR is also designed to function in rural schools with limited internet connectivity.However, facial recognition tech in general  and for kids in school in particular  is a growing area of concern for privacy supporters and parents alike, Geekwire reported.The tech is currently being tested at a school in Seattle where students can unlock a gate by smiling at a surveillance camera.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 02:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/25/3660803/3660803_D6992A907FAF4AD1AC2F9E95FB22BB8D_180725_3660803_Facial_recognition_system_to_boost_school_securi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BFB/92A/BFB92A16906863A6D374BF4EE1E82455.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, facial recognition technology, facial recognition technology school, facial recognition school, facial recognition software in schools, facial recognition privacy, facial recognition privacy issues, facial recognition privacy laws, facial recognition privacy policy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662131</guid>
      <title>Demi Lovato saved by Narcan after drug overdose</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Pop star Demi Lovato is in an L.A. hospital after reports say she had a little too much of an as-yet-undisclosed substance.A source told US Weekly that the 25-year-old had been on an all-night bender with friends, and suffered an overdose at her Hollywood Hills home around noon on Tuesday.There's been much speculation about what drug it was. TMZ initially reported heroin, while other sources said meth  right now, no one still knows for sure.But whatever the former Disney princess took flooded and blocked receptors in her brain, resulting in the overdose triad: pinpoint pupils, dangerously slow breathing, and unconsciousness.Luckily, one friend had Narcan on hand and used it to save the singer's life before paramedics whisked her off to the hospital.Narcan is an emergency medication used to reverse the effects of an OD, and is given either as a nasal spray or via arm, thigh, or butt muscle injection. According to the U.S. Surgeon General's Office, it works by knocking the drugs out of the brain receptors, which then temporarily restores the body to its pre-OD state.It's mostly effective, but sometimes doesn't work if administered too late or when a person has way too many drugs in his system.And even if a person is saved by Narcan, getting high on narcotics so soon afterward could also be fatal.In Demi's case, she's lucky she got treated when she did, and is now reportedly awake and in a stable condition.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 14:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/26/3662131/3662131_1725ECFBB185462DAC1C36F6A735CF22_180726_3662131_Demi_Lovato_saved_by_Narcan_after_drug_overdose_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DF0/AC5/DF0AC52E375E4CF470B778F7C771AC6A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, demi lovato, self care, emergency, relapse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662108</guid>
      <title>Explosion reported oustide of the US embassy in Beijing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  An explosion was reported in front of the American embassy in Beijing. The alleged assailant was injured in the explosion, but there no other victims.On July, 26th, several videos were published on Chinese social media that seem to show the aftermath of an explosion in front of the US embassy in Beijing. They were shot by passerby in the Chaoyang district, where most of the foreign embassies are located. Clouds of smoke and a small amount of debris are seen in front of the American embassy's entrance. Police urged passersby to stop filming and quickly move away, while cordoning off the area.Online mentions of the explosion have since been suppressed by Chinese censorship, and footage and pictures were quickly scrubbed from the internet. However, the very official Global Times confirmed shortly after that an explosion had occurred around 1pm. The Communist Party owned-media outlets also reported that police took away a woman who was pouring gasoline on herself in front of the embassy in the morning. It hasn't yet been established if the two events were linked.The official Weibo account of the Beijing Police published a message later in the afternoon, revealing that the alleged assailant is from Inner Mongolia and that his name is Jiang Moumou.The message also stated that there were no other victims than the assailant himself, whose hand was injured in the explosion. After subduing him, the police took him to the hospital.An investigation is still in progress.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 14:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/26/3662108/3662108_6B99E4FB564644C7935C7FC06B49F635_180726_3662108_Explosion_reported_oustide_of_the_US_embassy_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5AE/B77/5AEB77B8023D26A600E2BD47D7AA248F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, breaking news, Beijing, China, assailant, bomb, explosion, Chaoyang district, American embassy, US embassy, censorship, smoke, blast]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661903</guid>
      <title>Medical college student saves elderly man after he collapses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JINZHOU / CHINA  A second year college student became a star on social media after saving an elderly man's life, and turning down the reward offered by her family. A young Chinese medical student named Ding Hui recently became a social media star. As she was waiting for her train at Jinzhou south station, the second year university student heard people screaming for help. She quickly rushed toward the scene and discovered an elderly man on the floor.She kept her cool, started performing CPR, and asked people to call emergency services. Thanks to this good samaritan, the 81-year-old man regained consciousness. The local hero even missed her train, as she wanted to stay with the old man until first-aid arrived. When an ambulance finally arrived, the elderly man was taken to the hospital for safety.Ding Hui later politely turned down the 300 dollars offered to her by the elderly man's family. According to her, she only did what any medical student in the same situation would have done, and therefore didn't feel like she deserved any particular reward.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 09:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/26/3661903/3661903_5672F03FA8F9497EA49AEF0836458C38_180726_3661903_Medical_college_student_saves_elderly_man_after__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/750/80C/75080CD4ED0D8F07CBD0343A0AE56B44.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Ding Hui, China, Jinzhou, Liaoning, CPR, everyday hero, hero, elderly, heart arrest, heart attack, train station, humble hero]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661813</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show North Korea dismantling key nuclear site</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  Maybe the North Koreans will keep their end of the deal after all.North Korea has begun dismantling key facilities of the Sohae Satellite Launching Station, reports 38 North.According to satellite images of the launching site , the rail-mounted processing building  where different launch vehicles used to be prepared   was partially dismantled and now has been completely removed.Satellite images taken from July 20 to July 22 show the dismantling of the nuclear site.The nearby rocket engine test stand where there were liquid fuel engines for the ballistic missiles and launch vehicles have also been removed.However, in the images taken, the new fuel/oxidizer bunkers, the main processing building and gantry tower seem to be left untouched.Trump commented on North Korea's dismantling of key facilities of the satellite launch station and said "we appreciate that," reports CNN.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 08:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/26/3661813/3661813_F0257FD1BD214EAA8B256127A37E9004_180726_3661813_Satellite_images_show_North_Korea_dismantling_ke_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E77/8E9/E778E971C73AC559459044E190117E30.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Korea, missile testing site, missile, missile launch, dismantling key missing testing site, Sohae Satellite launching station, launch vehicle, nuclear missile, nuclear missile testing site]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661767</guid>
      <title>Millionaire who killed rare hybrid whale vows to kill more</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ICELAND  An Icelandic millionaire responsible for the offing of a giant blue whale hybrid says he is going to do it again.Animal rights campaigners say an endangered blue whale was harpooned and killed off the west coast of Iceland on July 8 by Hvalur hf owner Kristján Loftsson.In a response to the campaigners' accusation, Loftsson told the Telegraph he was pretty confident that genetic tests would confirm the whale was a hybrid species and not a blue whale.Loftsson says his company usually kills fin whales and if they see a blue whale in the ocean, they leave it alone. Iceland's Marine Research Institute carried out genetic analysis and confirmed the animal was the offspring of a female blue and a male fin whale.Photos taken by anti-whaling campaign showed the shocking scene of the whale being butchered. The International Fund for Animal Welfare says hybrids are rare and have previously been recorded by scientists, and are protected by international conventions. Loftsson said he isn't put off by the conservationists' accusation, he told indy100 that Hvalur hf has a quota of 161 whales for this seasons, starting in early June, however the final tally depends on the weather and could be less. The Icelandic representative of International Fund for Animal Welfare said they've worked alongside locals for many years to promote whale watching, instead of killing, as it is better for the marine ecosystems, Iceland's tourism industry and its international reputation.However, despite the horrifying event we have shown you here, other animal cruelty stories we've covered in the past often get demonetized by YouTube. Reasons for the demonetization remains unknown, but this makes it difficult to cover similar newsworthy stories in the future. So spread the word and share, we need your support to make sure these horrific events happen less frequently.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 07:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/26/3661767/3661767_19794EC6AC36486887825DD04050FFE0_180726_3661767_Millionaire_who_killed_rare_hybrid_whale_vows_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D53/B65/D53B656029E74DFCA3F39ED10ED881A9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, iceland whaling, iceland whaling 2018, icelandic whaler, fin whales, fin whales endangered, fin whales iceland, blue whales, blue whales endangered]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661585</guid>
      <title>Chinese firm builds highest artificial waterfall in the world</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUIYANG, CHINA  A Chinese firm has built a 350-foot artificial waterfall on the side of a skyscraper, which makes it the highest artificial waterfall in the world.The Time reports that some residents first thought they were witnessing a massive water leak coming out of the brand new Liebian Building. But after some confusion was cleared up, most locals described the cascade as new and original. They even expressed hopes for the high-rise to become one of Guiyang's landmarks.However, netizens were quick to point out that this is an immense waste of energy and water. The building's managers claim the mechanism uses recycled water. A spokesperson also declared to Kankan News that they would only turn it on for special events in the city, and no more than for 10 or 20 minutes at a time, as activating the waterfall's four pumps costs about $120 an hour.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/26/3661585/3661585_CBE40EBEBFB34A938E8BCACB5C6F6E63_180726_3661585_Chinese_firm_builds_highest_artificial_waterfall_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FED/F89/FEDF8911B69B938BE66BF0FD4E82F60A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Guiyang, China, skyscraper, waterfall, high rise, cascade, highest artificial waterfall, waste, energy, water, world record, water leak, Liebian building, building, high, heights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3661574</guid>
      <title>Vertical farming company to bring chemical-free produce to stores</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CLEBURNE, TEXAS   A next generation farming company is planning to be the first to offer vertically grown, local produce on a large scale.Eden Green aims to grow produce in vertical lines in a greenhouse to supply to different large-chain grocery stores, reports Forbes.Conventional soil-based farms have an average of two harvests a year, while Eden Green expects to have around 10 to 15 harvests a year.Their first produce line, Crisply, will include vegetables such as lettuce, stevia plants, and other greens.Each plant would be enclosed in a soil-free microclimate bubble free of chemicals, pesticides and herbicides.The company has come up with technology to enable the plants to feed on a steady flow of nutrient-filled water and natural sunlight, instead of LED lights. Eden Green Technology says the produce is picked and packaged on the same day, unlike traditional retailers where the process can take up to nine days.For now, the vertically grown produce can be found at Walmarts across Texas starting this month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 03:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/26/3661574/3661574_60DBBFB3DF1D42A298F17DBD80D0AE8B_180726_3661574_Vertical_farming_company_to_bring_chemical_free__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FC6/076/FC6076BC1C9E9FB07EE032199E95DA75.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, going green, vertical farming, vertically stacked layers, vertical farming company, vertical farming firm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662912</guid>
      <title>Japanese city's ninja shortage is actually fake news</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IGA, JAPAN  The Japanese city of Iga has been left fighting off wannabe ninjas after a news report suggesting the city had a shortage went viral.Iga was featured in an NPR program this month about Japan's depopulation and labor shortage problems, during the program, the show host said the labor shortage also included ninja performers themselves.NPR said those stealthy ninja performers in the land of rising sun earn from $23,000 to $85,000 annually.However, according to the Japan Times, many media outlets instead reported that the city was paying people a $85,000 salary to train as a ninja. Misleading everyone into thinking anyone could sign up, including us at Tomonews.With all the hype, Iga and its tourism association received 115 job applications from 14 countries, including the United States and Spain. Many aspiring ninjas expressed interest in providing their services or were looking for details about the role.The city's website stated that Iga's mayor Sakae Okamoto said the city never actually put any information out about suffering a lack of ninjas in the city, nor did they divulge information about a ninja's income.The city warned people to be wary of "fake news," but stressed there are many exciting activities available for tourists visiting Iga, including a ninja-themed attraction, but made clear visitors should leave their swords and throwing stars at home.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 10:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/27/3662912/3662912_3F680A50C1B6492CB1D9608D17D4ABD5_180727_3662912_Japanese_city_s_ninja_shortage_is_actually_fake__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/6EE/253/6EE2532F5B72494A84A03EFF48ED2986.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ninja japan, ninja japanese, ninja job, ninja jobs in japan, ninja crisis, ninja shortage, japanese ninja shortage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662804</guid>
      <title>Conspiracy theorists think Blood Moon 2018 will be the end of times</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  Conspiracy theorists and doomsday preachers are warning that the end is nigh just because the moon is turning red this week.NASA reports that this century's longest lunar eclipse is set to go down on July 27, and its getting some people's panties in a tizzy.Friday's total lunar eclipse will see the sun, Earth, and moon in perfect alignment with each other. When this happens, the moon moves directly within the Earth's umbra and turns a dark red  a rare astronomical phenomenon known as the blood moon.The ominous name has given rise to all manner of doomsday predictions. One YouTube preacher claims it's a sign of the second coming, while a new age earthquake researcher predicts a magnitude 7 quake could strike that day.Of course, neither of these claims are backed up by real science, even though both claim to be "factual". Clearly, that word doesn't mean what they think it means.The blood redness is really just from being hit by sunlight bent by the Earth's atmosphere. Nothing creepy or satanic about it.At one hour and 43 minutes, sure, it'll be the longest lunar eclipse of the 21st century so far, but that's hardly proof of imminent destruction.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/27/3662804/3662804_2995BD1AED954E7C8845639FFCA5E029_180727_3662804_Conspiracy_theorists_think_Blood_Moon_2018_will__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/678/F46/678F4663E4234066B75C7E82EDC27145.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, blood moon, blood moon 2018, lunar eclipse, total lunar eclipse, end of the world, end of days, earthquake, planetary alignment, conspiracy theories, doomsday, paul begley]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662723</guid>
      <title>HAV unveils Airlander 10's luxurious floor-to-ceiling interior</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RAF CARDINGTON, ENGLAND  Aerospace company Hybrid Air Vehicles (HAV) has unveiled what the interior of the world's largest aircraft will look like.The Airlander 10 is powered by four 325 HP turbocharged diesel engines and uses aerodynamic lift, like a fixed-wing aircraft to take off. Helium keeps the Airlander aloft.The airship can carry payloads of up to 10,000 kilograms and stay in the air for five days at a time with a crew. It also doesn't require a runway.The 302-foot-long airship is about 60 feet longer than the world's largest passenger plane, the Airbus A380.Travelling up to 91 miles per hour, the airship will be able to carry up to 19 passengers to take part in a three-day journey.Designed by aviation and automobile design firm Design Q, the airship features en-suite bedrooms, a bar, and a lounge area. And there's also floor-to-ceiling windows so passengers can enjoy the views from 16,000 feet.Stephen McGlennan, CEO of HAV, said in a press release that Airlander challenges people to rethink the skies. He also mentioned that air travel has become about getting from A to B as quickly as possible, what they are offering is a way of making the journey a joy.In the past, the airship had suffered some setbacks, from a nosedive in August 2016 to a safety feature was triggered that caused the airship deflated in 2017.Airlander 10 has completed six successful test flights so far. It needs to complete 200 incident-free hours to be able to carry passengers for commercial flights.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 07:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/27/3662723/3662723_FA7A4B5E6F284333952AA1FAED850063_180727_3662723_HAV_unveils_Airlander_10_s_luxurious_floor_to_ce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F6A/A0E/F6AA0E51A184D2049DF57C1F2DD44804.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, airlander interior, airlander 10 interior, airlander 10 airship interior, hybrid air vehicles, design Q, world's largest aircraft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662386</guid>
      <title>Study shows the effects of wearing a tight necktie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GERMANY   Scientists in Germany recently conducted a study which shows that wearing a tie could actually be bad for you health.According to Business Insider, the study was conducted by taking MRI scans of 15 men who wore ties and 15 men who didn't.The researchers found that tie-wearers received 7.5% less cerebral blood flow than those who didn't wear ties.According to a separate study conducted by the British Journal of Ophthalmology, wearing a tie could also increase the risk of eye problems such as glaucoma and cataracts, as it restricts the blood flow in the arteries and veins of the neck.Researchers at Yonsei University found that people who wear ties usually find their range of motion 'significantly decreased' when they wear a tight necktie.Even the risk of musculoskeletal trauma can be increased just by wearing a tie as tension would accumulate in muscles such as the upper trapezius.However, researchers involved did warn those who have high blood pressure and other health issues may suffer from headaches and nausea if a necktie is worn for too long.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 03:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/27/3662386/3662386_25E09BD58FE34BF1B377B08DF403205C_180727_3662386_Study_shows_the_effects_of_wearing_a_tight_neckt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/914/3F2/9143F29BB2AAFE8FAEF3F73AF6D47971.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nausea, arteries, veins, cerebral brain flow, eye problems, glaucoma, cataracts, Study, scientists, tie, bad for health, necktie, restricted blood flow, muscles, headache]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3662382</guid>
      <title>Boy's feet infected with parasitic hookworms after beach trip</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI, FLORIDA    Who knew a trip to the beach could result in a nasty infection underneath your skin?During a trip to Miami, Florida with his friends, Michael Duma, 17, contracted a nasty hookworm infection in his feet, reports Metro.Duma and his friends went to Pompano beach, where Duma was reportedly buried in the sand for fun.Soon after, he developed painful, itchy rashes on his feet.He visited a doctor and found out he had contracted a parasitic infection  hookworms had taken up residence under his skin.His mom took to Facebook to share the story saying that it has "become our nightmare" and are now warning others about the "dangers of the beach."She also she had to get him four different medications which cost around $1,300...that's a lot of money and that's including insurance.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 03:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/27/3662382/3662382_146AAC4DA04F4622AD976B1CF54CB39D_180727_3662382_Boy_s_feet_infected_with_parasitic_hookworms_aft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F11/263/F11263B4F17298E16EA7EF436E11E5C5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Florida, Miami, boy, beach, friends, fun, getting buried in the beach, feet, parasites, hookworms, feet infections, dangers of the beach, itchy rashes, trip to the beach]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3663503</guid>
      <title>Woman brutally bites random stranger in subway, then strips</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHONGQING CHINA  A woman had a serious dementia crisis in Chongqing's subway, brutally biting a complete stranger before stripping down in the train.On June 18th at around 1 p.m. in Chongqing, passengers on line 3 of the subway had to be evacuated when a woman surnamed Li, 36, suddenly went crazy.She started off brutally biting a total stranger sitting next to her. Various videos published on Chinese social media show the man struggling to get the woman off him while uttering cries of pain. He finally got rid of her by knocking her on the head.She left his face completely bloodied. According to Chongqing Rail Transit, the infortunate 56-year-old guy was later taken to the hospital.The woman was later seen screaming as if she were possessed by some kind of demonic spirit. She then rolled on the floor while helpless spectators desperately sought help. She finished by stripping off her clothes, standing alone in the empty train with her arms spread wide.Subway staff evacuated passengers, and the police had to intervene to subdue her and get her off the train.An investigation is still in process to explain the woman's behavior. According to local reports, she is currently going through marital issues, and she may have acted after a fight with her husband.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 09:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/28/3663503/3663503_1809198F656D471AB26D8B10EC5EEB42_180728_3663503_Woman_brutally_bites_random_stranger_in_subway___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AC/7D5/1AC7D59DB7BA23E5CF5BA69A543D50FD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Chongqing, subway, crazy girl, looney girl, mad girl, bite, dementia, hysteria, crazy girlfriend, couple issues, marital issues, unfortunate passenger, unlucky passenger, police, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3663498</guid>
      <title>Alphabet-owned Loon to send internet balloons to Kenya</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENYA    Google's sister company Loon, has announced it will soon deploy balloons to bring internet access to remote parts of Kenya.The "internet" balloons are the size of a tennis court and are made of polyethylene. It is also filled with helium and uses a solar panel for power, reports the BBC.The balloons will fly in the stratosphere, around 20 kilometers above sea level.Loon has designed the balloons to stay in the air for months.The company has programmed the balloons to move by wind channels. Its software will predict speed and direction, then maneuver itself to go where it needs to go, reports Wired.The "internet" balloons also have antennas that receive wireless internet signals from a local telecom partner Telkom Kenya, and relays the signal to other balloons in the region.According to a Reuters report, the balloons will provide 4G coverage to areas where internet connection is limited.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 09:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/28/3663498/3663498_25526BB8C1AB441484E9BFEAF67B372C_180728_3663498_Alphabet_owned_Loon_to_send_internet_balloons_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F1/CA3/8F1CA3EFB23BADE26089DE5ECFB1B994.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Google, Alphabet, Loon, balloons, balloons with internet, internet, Kenya, technology, wireless internet connection, internet connection, balloon powered internet, wind channels, stratosphere]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3664914</guid>
      <title>U.S. airlines cave to Chinese pressure, drop Taiwan name</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  Four major airlines in the U.S. have failed to satisfy China's aviation regulator despite bowing to the communist party's 'Orwellian nonsense.'Reuters reports that early this year, China's Civil Aviation Administration sent out letters to foreign airlines demanding they stop referring to Taiwan as a country on websites and promotional materials.Dozens of international airlines gave in to the demand ahead of the July 25 deadline set by Chinese authorities, and now designate Taiwan as part of China.U.S. Airlines have also started to implement changes, taking out 'Taiwan' and listing only the destination city and airport, but stopping short of calling it a Chinese province.The CAAC says 40 out of 44 carriers have already amended site references to Taiwan, but claims United, American, Delta, and Hawaiian Airlines have yet to complete full 'rectification'. The four carriers have reportedly asked for a two-week extension to audit their websites.China had threatened penalties for noncompliance, but did not specify what they would be. A director at the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences speculated that penalties could take the form of fines, restricted entry into the Chinese market, or removal of airlines' apps and booking systems, reports the New York Times.It's basically economic blackmail. China is poised to overtake the U.S. as the world's largest air-travel market, and the only way global carriers can get a slice of that pie is by kowtowing to the powers that be.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/30/3664914/3664914_3F77BC1108AB422F9B41DC116426273D_180730_3664914_U_S__airlines_cave_to_Chinese_pressure__drop_Tai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/900/FDF/900FDF99D6F3CD0FADA0F20C3D5F9D85.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwan, China, China aviation, US airlines, economic blackmail, American airlines, United airlines, Delta airlines, Hawaiian Airlines, CAAC]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3664907</guid>
      <title>Polar bear acts like a polar bear and is shot dead by ship guard</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORWAY   A cruise was at the Arctic Circle to take some tourists sightseeing when a polar bear was killed for attacking a cruise ship guard, reports NBC News.What typically occurs when a vessel arrives is the cruise ship guard disembarks the ship to check if there are any dangers the area.This particular cruise ship guard however failed to notice one polar bear in the vicinity, and was surprised when the bear behaved as bears do, injuring the man's head in the process.A second cruise guard who was accompanying the first the opened fire, all the in the name of "self-defense."The first guard wasn't too badly injured and everyone else remained safe.Hapag-Lloyd Cruises issued a statement apologizing for the incident, and said the intervention was needed "to protect the life of the attacked person."Most people on social media were outraged though, with comedian Ricky Gervais and long-time animal activist chiming in, blaming humans for being "morons" for trespassing into the areas where the polar bears reside.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 14:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/30/3664907/3664907_616A4E6508A84908BBAA63F12C3FBFD9_180730_3664907_Polar_bear_acts_like_a_polar_bear_and_is_shot_de_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/423/C67/423C67DFD9E40AC25E3DCEE570F2AE57.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Arctic circle, polar bears, arctic tourism, cruise ship, cruise ship guard, polar bear attack, polar bear acting like a polar bear, natural instincts, tourists, sightseeing in the arctic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3664693</guid>
      <title>China tries to ban Taiwanese flag from Paris Gay Games</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  China is seeking to ban the Taiwanese flag from the 2018 Paris gay games by pressuring the French Government.The Communist party has lately forced international airlines and companies to change their website classifications of Taiwan. It also got the island's right to host the East Asian Youth Games revoked. And now, it has a new target to further isolate the self-ruled territory.The Gay Games are a sporting and cultural event that seeks to promote sexual diversity. This year, it will be held in Paris from August 4th to August 12th. Around 10,000 athletes from nearly 90 countries are expected. The 28-person Taiwanese squad had first obtained the right to compete under the Taiwanese flag. However the Federation of Gay Games appears to be coming under pressure from the French Government, which doesn't seem so keen on letting Taiwanese athletes display their national flag. According to Taiwanese gay right activist Chi Chia-wei, this can only mean one thing: that China directly protested to the French Government.Taiwan News reports that Chi, who leads the Taiwanese delegation, said he would fight until the last moment for his right to use the national flag during the event. He added that it would be deceiving if an organization that promotes inclusive and progressive values eventually bowed to an oppressive dictatorship.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 10:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/30/3664693/3664693_E239204A6FFD47D7AB6843F9F713B6F0_180730_3664693_China_tries_to_ban_Taiwanese_flag_from_Paris_Gay_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5F8/821/5F88216AA4114C814B431FA12FBFA9FF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Taiwan, China, Taiwanese flag, LGBT, gay, Gay Games, gay games, international pressure, controversy, ban, Taipei, Paris, France, Gay Games 2018]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3664620</guid>
      <title>Emirates forces epileptic teen and family off of flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UAE  Emirates asked a teen suffering from epilepsy and his family to leave a flight against their will last week, reported The Guardian.The move reportedly came despite the family having shown officials a certificate to prove the boy was clear to fly.The Guardian reports Euronews journalist Isabelle Kumar, her 17-year-old son Eli, and the rest of the family last week boarded a flight bound for France from Dubai. Before the trip, Kumar made sure Emirates was aware of Eli's condition, and that he needed a vacant seat next to him in case he had a seizure.When Emirates asked to see a medical certificate, Kumar couldn't find it, so she called her doctor to email the certificate. When Eli's doctor wanted to speak to the flight attendants, they refused. The flight attendants told them the certificate had to be shown to ground staff, despite the fact that the family had spoken to staff at check in and at the departure gate about their son's condition.The attendants then told Kumar and her family that they need to leave the plane or else they would call the police.Kumar posted a video of Eli, who was become anxious under the pressure, biting his arm and holding his head in his hands.After leaving the plane without any further issue, an emergency medical team agreed that Eli was medically cleared to carry on with the trip.Kumar claims the family continued to be treated badly and that the airline didn't do anything to improve their situation. Later, a different Emirates employee suggested that the family fly to Geneva the next day.Kuman said travel is challenging for a child with special needs, especially when the child is being treated unfairly. She added that the incident wouldn't stop them travelling as family, but they will reconsider before travelling with Emirates in the future.Charity group Epilepsy Action told the Guardian that epileptic episodes can be very distressing, and urged travel companies to ensure that their staff are trained to handle such episodes if they arise.An Emirates spokesperson said the airline was very sorry for the distress and inconvenience brought upon Kumar and her family, and that they have offered them a complimentary hotel stay while in transit, and had re-booked them on another flight.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/30/3664620/3664620_40506B5C5BEE470CACD4790C46F6883F_180730_3664620_Emirates_forces_epileptic_teen_and_family_off_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/66E/0EA/66E0EA4E5CBA6DDEEF132FF35788D225.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, epilepsy, epilepsy passenger, epilepsy video, epilepsy video for kids, airlines epilepsy, emirates epilepsy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3664604</guid>
      <title>How cats conquered the world</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD  House cats may seem like they could care less about their owners, but the species and their humans apparently go way back.The Smithsonian reports that a team of scientists mapped out the modern felines' storied history with people, finding that they all descended from a single type of wild cat, Felis silvestris lybica, and spread across the world in two waves.Ten thousand years ago, when agriculture boomed in the Near East, farmers began using cats to drive rodents out of their grain stores. From there, the felines spread north and west to Bulgaria and Romania.The second wave came thousands of years later with the ancient Egyptians, who loved kitties so much they worshipped a cat goddess and mummified their dead pets.Egyptian kitty love spread to Europe during the Roman era, but the cats' popularity really took off with the Vikings, who put them on ships to keep the rodent population in check.A separate study found that in China, cats may well have have been catching pesky mice since 5,300 years ago.Their strategy seems to be just to stick to humans, and clearly that's worked because flash forward to the present and they're on every continent on Earth except for Antarctica.They've even conquered the internet, and are probably already plotting their domination of space.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/30/3664604/3664604_367863524ADE4F64B9EA2A860287D34E_180730_3664604_How_cats_conquered_the_world_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/841/5BB/8415BB79D1B0F9E53D4AC68B011147C3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cats, kitty, kitties, cat videos, cute cats, cat history, how cats spread across the world, how cats spread, cat animation, egyptian cats, viking cats, roman cats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3664597</guid>
      <title>Frozen worms in Russia come back to life after 42,000 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YAKUTIA, RUSSIA    That's a long time to be frozen.A study conducted by Russian scientists in collaboration with Princeton University found 300 prehistoric worms in Yakutia, one of the coldest regions of Russia.Two of the worms were "shown to contain viable nematodes," also known as roundworms, reports the Siberian Times.One worm is estimated to be around 32,000 years old while the other is around 42,000 years old.One of the worms was found in an ancient squirrel burrow's permafrost, while the other was found by the Alazeya River.After being defrosted in a laboratory at The Institute of Physico-Chemical and Biological Problems in Moscow, the worms started to move, eat, and show other signs of life.According to the Siberian Times, both the worms are female and are part of the "oldest living animals on the planet."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/30/3664597/3664597_03DDAE0460E94AAF831E08F0173DE60C_180730_3664597_Frozen_worms_in_Russia_come_back_to_life_after_4_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/942/57D/94257D7BDA6499D5A0B450B4E279CC69.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Russia, permafrost worms, worms frozen in permafrost, worms brought back to life, nematodes, permafrost, roundworms, Siberia, siberian permafrost]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
