<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 15:00:01 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3209560</guid>
      <title>New implant allows ALS patient to communicate using brain activity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers in the Netherlands have developed a brain implant that enables a woman with Lou Gehrig’s disease, also known as ALS, to communicate using brain activity, and without a doctor’s supervision.An electrocorticograph, developed by researchers at the University Medical Center Utrecht, consists of four electrode strips of about 5 cm long, with each holding four small electrodes. The electrode strips are implanted inside the skull against the brain.According to the study published in the New England Journal of Medicine, two of the electrode strips are placed over the region of the left motor cortex that controls hand movements, and the other two are placed over the left prefrontal cortex as a backup. The electrode strips are connected to an transmitter device that is installed inside the left side of the patient’s chest. The implant wirelessly connects to a receiver via an antenna and to a tablet computer mounted on the wheelchair.To activate the electrodes, the patient thinks about moving her right hand, which triggers the electrodes to send signals down to the transmitter in the chest. This eventually resulting in her hand moving a cursor to make an input on the computer screen. If the patient’s motor cortex degenerates over time, she would counter backwards to activate the backup electrodes placed over her prefrontal cortex, as this region is responsible for mental calculation.ALS affects the neurons that are required for voluntary muscle control and causes complete paralysis within a couple of years. According to the ALS Association, about 6,000 people in the U.S. are diagnosed with ALS each year. There is no known cure to the disease.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 20:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/17/3209560/3209560_1E92E18D515445CAA14DEE314F6BA53F_161117_3209560_New_implant_allows_ALS_patient_to_communicate_us_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/29C/9B2/29C9B2FB139240939F55BEE01C7A38C8_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Lou Gehrig,ALS,paralysis,paralyzed,ALS patient video,ALS communication device,brain implant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3209103</guid>
      <title>Chinese doctors craft man&#x2019;s new ear from rib cartilage and the skin on his forearm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Chinese hospital in the process of creating a human ear almost entirely through the human anatomy alone.According to Chinese state media news outlet CCTV, plastic surgeons have grown an ear on a patient’s arm after he lost it in an car accident one year ago. The man, identified only as Ji, is being treated by surgeons at First Hospital Affiliated with Xian Jiaotong University in Xian City, Shaanxi Province.Several months ago, a dilator was inserted into the man’s right forearm, which received daily water injections that created a thin and stretched layer of skin. Next, the hospital removed some of the patient’s rib cage cartilage and modeled them into the shape of an ear.This cartilage model was then inserted into the expanded skin, which has formed around it in the shape of a human ear. “It looks exactly the same as my old ear,” Ji said, according to a China Daily/Asia News Network report on the Strait Times.The next part of Ji’s treatment  transplanting the new ear to the patient’s head  will take around three or four months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 13:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/16/3209103/3209103_9B1BD05900F746DD96FD9065C1D2687D_161116_3209103_Chinese_doctors_craft_man___s_new_ear_from_rib_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8C9/898/8C9898C9CD87425CA9452D4CEEAB0A9C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Strange surgery stories,replacement ear surgery,china growing ear arm,plastic surgery on ear,growing ear on arm,arm used to grow ear,rib used to make ear,ear surgery,xian,china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3209098</guid>
      <title>Electric VTOL craft could make flying cars a reality</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Several companies and venture-backed start-ups hope to bring electric VTOL vehicles to the skies. VTOL stands for vertical take-off and landing.Google co-founder Larry Page has poured money into Zee.Areo, which is developing VTOLs. Other companies such as Boeing are helped by DARPA funding as the US military seeks to develop VTOL aircraft.But experts caution it could be decades before VTOL aviation is fully developed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 13:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/16/3209098/3209098_4C64B43362AB47A4A156F5E071E9EAE4_161116_3209098_Electric_VTOL_craft_could_make_flying_cars_a_rea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C4B/C34/C4BC34035D5947DA8F48A4001E06E79E_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,VTOL,vertical take-off and landing,electric VTOL,Zee.Areo,Larry Page,Google,Uber,Lilium Aviation,Joby Aviation,Boeing,DARPA,Phantom Swift]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3207299</guid>
      <title>KIA swaps wheels for tank treads in concept SUV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Korean car manufacturer KIA unveiled a concept design of its Sorento SUV that drives autonomously using tank treads in place of tires. According to automotive news website Top Speed, the design was shown at the SEMA 2017 car show in Las Vegas earlier this month. Most cars distribute the vehicle’s weight over four wheels. This concept performs well in regular driving scenarios. But when faced with snow, mud or other difficult terrain, the tires can sink  leaving the vehicle stuck.To get around this, KIA’s concept Sorento supplants normal tires with tank treads.Also known as continuous tracks or caterpillar tracks, these distribute weight better over a larger surface than tires, enabling vehicles to traverse difficult terrain. Vehicles such as tanks and tractors use these to maneuver across desert, mud and other obstacles.The concept Sorento features an autonomous driving system and can also be controlled via a tablet rather than a regular steering wheel. The vehicle sports suicide-style doors to make getting in and out easier and seating similar to that of a gondola.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 14:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/14/3207299/3207299_4B01F31AC90142598598E26F5B48C431_161114_3207299_KIA_swaps_wheels_for_tank_treads_in_concept_SUV_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1E8/625/1E862544DF9E49ABA7190478B06B99BE_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Tank car,tank treads on a car,kia gondola,kia gondola car,kia tank tread suv,suv,driving in winter,winter tank treads,stuck in snow,car stuck in snow]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3207298</guid>
      <title>Brain implants help paralyzed monkeys walk again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Paraplegics may soon regain use of their legs, now that scientists have created an implant that proves effective in primates.In a spinal cord injury, brain signals are unable to reach the neurons that activate movement, often resulting in lower limb paralysis. But researchers from the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology in Lausanne may have found a way to bypass this, having successfully restored movement in two paralyzed monkeys.According to the study, published in Nature, the team developed a neuroprosthetic interface that uses two wireless implants. The first is a sensor surgically implanted in the brain’s motor cortex  the area that controls movement. The second is a nerve stimulator that is placed near the spinal injury.The sensor picks up brain signals commanding leg movement and transmits them to a computer. The computer decodes the signals and sends them to the second implant in the spine. From there, pulses of electricity are released to stimulate certain nerves. This in turn triggers muscles in the leg, enabling it to move and flex.CNN reports that the monkeys did not need any training and were able to walk immediately after activation of the interface.The researchers plan to apply the technology to improve human lives, but say this may take several more years to achieve.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 14:11:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/14/3207298/3207298_5DB11E9EB3BD46DABE45A3BCB2247FD4_161114_3207298_Brain_implants_help_paralyzed_monkeys_walk_again_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EA8/DF2/EA8DF22F147B4F61B7028A4ABDFF0FBE_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Brain implants,brain implant,wireless implants,paraplegia,paraplegic,paralysis,paralyzed monkeys,paralyzed,cure for paralysis,medical technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3207297</guid>
      <title>Japanese engineer develops turbines to harness energy from typhoons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Japanese engineer has designed a new type of wind turbine that he believes would be able to harness power from typhoons.Atsushi Shimizu founded a tech company called Challenergy in 2013 and invented a wind turbine that not only can draw power from the force of wind, but can stay functional during typhoons.The typhoon turbine consists of three vertical blades and a central rod. It has an omnidirectional axis so that it can respond to wind coming from every direction.Instead of driven by a propeller, the turbine makes use of the principle of the Magnus effect: air curves when passing by a rotating object, and the downward deflection of the air-flow produces a lifting force that counteracts the force of gravity, enabling the object to remain airborne.The blades are controlled by the central rod, which can be tightened to slow down, or stop the blades regardless of the external forces.Under normal circumstances, the typhoon turbine can achieve about 30 percent efficiency while conventional wind turbine can achieve 40 percent, ScienceAlert reported. However, conventional wind turbines could be damaged by typhoons while the typhoon turbine would be able to function normally."Japan actually has a lot more wind power than it does solar power, it's just not utilized," Shimizu told CNN. "Japan has the potential to be a super power of wind.”According to the Japan Guide, about seven or eight typhoons pass over Okinawa prefecture each year, with about three hitting its main islands. Shimizu believes a single typhoon could generate enough energy to power Japan for 50 years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/14/3207297/3207297_079B1970243C4D728CB4EEC2AA8177E5_161114_3207297_Japanese_engineer_develops_turbines_to_harness_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FDF/124/FDF12420D1D1439BA6071289612D8EA7_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Typhoon turbine,wind energy,wind power,typhoon energy,renewable energy,sustainable energy,japan,atsushi shimizu,challenergy,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3207296</guid>
      <title>Netherlands investing 150 million euros in biogas project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Netherlands has committed to investing 150 million euros in a biogas project to turn cow manure into fuel.Manure processing is important to the Netherlands as about 10% of the country’s greenhouse gas emissions come from agriculture, mostly methane from animal manure. The Netherlands’ livestock produces about 74 million tons of manure a year, according to the International Dairy Federation. This is too much to directly apply to farmlands as fertilizer, as the excessive amount of nutrients could leak underground and cause algae growth and pollution in nearby water sources.A way to solve this problem is by transforming manure into biogas. In one experiment conducted at a farm in the Netherlands, manure is transported into an anaerobic digester, where bacteria transforms solid manures into liquid form. The resulting substance releases biogas, which consists of mostly methane and carbon dioxide. The biogas can then be used as fuel while any left over manure can be used as fertilizer.According to the Guardian, the digester generated 9,342 kWh of electricity in 20 days, which is enough to power three homes for a year. The Dutch government aims to get 1,000 large farms in the country to produce energy from cow manure within four years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 14:08:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/14/3207296/3207296_7D3FC05FB01F40E89526F6085C3672CE_161114_3207296_Netherlands_investing_150_million_euros_in_bioga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AEE/30F/AEE30FE09BD74AE08CB6F22E472C8FBF_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Biogas,netherlands biogas project,dutch biogas project,cow manures into biogas,animal manures pollution,greenhouse gas emission,renewable energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3203982</guid>
      <title>Airbag bike helmets &#x2018;five times safer&#x2019; than foam versions, researchers say</title>
      <description><![CDATA[With millions around the world riding bicycles, accidents are inevitable. Most of us know that wearing a helmet reduces the risk of serious injury, but it turns out the type of helmet also matters.Researchers from Stanford University found that helmets equipped with airbag technology offer five times more protection than standard foam ones, according to Reuters.The test was conducted using two test dummies one wearing a foam helmet, and another with an airbag helmet. Both were then dropped from varying heights to simulate an accident. Conventional helmets may prevent skull fractures during accidents, but don’t often protect against concussions and other similar head injuries.In lieu of foam as protection, airbag helmets are inflated with helium, and worn like a collar around the neck. Sensors monitor the cyclist’s normal movements, and deploy automatically once they detect something abnormal, such as a collision.Upon deployment, an inflated hood is released from the collar. The hood covers most of the head and absorbs shock during impact. The researchers warn however, that airbag helmets may pose a bigger risk if not deployed properly.The helmets are made by Swedish company Hovding and are currently only available in Europe.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 21:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/10/3203982/3203982_8723A4EE879C4FE0BD978F1B0AA9D119_161110_3203982_Airbag_bike_helmets____five_times_safer____than__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/87E/CE3/87ECE3202DE2401F8ED6F23D9A5D5963_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Airbag helmet,hovding,bike helmet,bike safety,bike accident,bike collision,bike crash,safety,head injury]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3203980</guid>
      <title>Startup converts waste plastic into bricks to build affordable housing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A New York startup has developed an innovative way to recycle waste plastic, converting it into an alternative building material that can be used to build affordable housing.The company, called ByFusion, has designed a machine that is highly compact and modular. It can be powered by propane gas or electricity and can process all types of plastic waste, according to the ByFusion website.The plastic waste does not have to be pre-processed. Instead, it is shredded inside the machine before it’s made into a new material called RePlast and compressed into bricks. The RePlast bricks are not as strong as concrete, so are reinforced with steel rods, wire and layers of mortar.The company said RePlast has been used in projects including retaining walls in New Zealand and California, which have withstood environmental tests such as earthquakes.ByFusion has so far raised around $30,000 of a $250,000 target on Indiegogo. On its campaign page, it says the machine will likely be available in the U.S. by May next year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 21:18:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/10/3203980/3203980_5480184208204DFF997E4180D8D4A6A6_161110_3203980_Startup_converts_waste_plastic_into_bricks_to_bu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0D6/7A4/0D67A4B8BAE84D9FA7C08227B337C1D5_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Byfusion,replast,replast bricks,byfusion turns waste plastic into bricks,waste plastic converted into bricks,cheap housing,alternative building materials]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3203977</guid>
      <title>National University of Singapore to test drone delivery service in 2017</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Aircraft manufacturer Airbus is set to trial a drone delivery service which, if successful, could potentially lead to tests of flying taxis for passengers.The technology to be tested in Singapore next year will see drones being used to deliver parcels, according to an article in FORUM, the Airbus Group corporate magazine. During the trial, drones will navigate a network of delivery and pick-up points across the National University of Singapore campus. These drones, also known as octocopters because of their eight blades, will fly automated on routes along interconnecting sky corridors throughout the campus. Upon arrival, the drone will unload the parcel automatically, and its recipient will be sent a delivery notification.Airbus says that if testing shows drones to be safe, this may increase the chances of passenger flight testing being accepted in Singapore. “If the team is able to demonstrate the safe operation of Skyways over NUS, this could help shape the regulatory framework for unmanned aircraft system operations in Singapore and potentially increase acceptance for passenger flight testing, thus giving a boost to urban air vehicle projects,” an excerpt from the FORUM article explains.The company has been developing a electric flying vehicle named CityAirbus for several years, with the aim of reducing traffic congestion in cities. Airbus believes that in the future, people will use such vehicles, which could be operated via transport apps such as Uber.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 21:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/10/3203977/3203977_98F26D034559480BB11047CEC48E5C0E_161110_3203977_National_University_of_Singapore_to_test_drone_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BB5/F84/BB5F84279CF846E2870D10624A9115B5_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Drone delivery service,drones,drone delivery,national university of singapore,the flying car,flying taxi,drone delivery service,Airbus,cityairbus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3202990</guid>
      <title>Tesla unveils solar roof panels that look like ordinary tiles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Tesla has unveiled a solar roof product that doesn’t distract from the aesthetics of a home, as they look just like ordinary tiles.The company unveiled four types of solar tile during a launch event at the “Desperate Housewives” set at Universal Studios last Friday, TechCrunch reported.Each Tesla roof tile is made up of a solar cell, quartz glass and a color louver film that makes it appear opaque from an angle.Tesla CEO Elon Musk said the tiles have 98 percent of the efficiency of traditional solar panels. However, the tiles have the potential to go above normal efficiency if improved coatings can trap light inside to reduce loss of energy.Tesla sees the solar roofs working in tandem with its Powerwall battery unit to provide energy for homes and its electric vehicles.The tiles will be available next year through SolarCity, a solar installation company chaired by Musk, which he is trying to merge with Tesla.Musk didn’t reveal any specific prices but said the Tesla panels would cost less than the full cost of a roof, with the added benefit of being able to generate electricity.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 20:17:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/09/3202990/3202990_496F8E59C82D42E99315B904366A2883_161109_3202990_Tesla_unveils_solar_roof_panels_that_look_like_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3EE/CCA/3EECCA5BE3464D668AA0C9E62895A857_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Tesla solar,tesla solar roof,tesla solarcity,tesla solar panels,tesla solar power,tesla solarcity merger,tesla solar system,solar energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3202984</guid>
      <title>Norway floats $25 billion floating underwater tunnel plan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Norwegian Public Roads Administration believes floating underwater tunnels could be the key to shorter driving times in the country.Norway is home to more than 1,100 fjords, the deep glacial water inlets that divide land masses. Getting over one means taking a ferry, and that can add hours to a car trip.Because fjords can be up to a mile deep, building a bridge over the waterway or tunnel underneath is not very practical.But Norwegian engineers think they can build a quicker way. They want to float concrete tunnels up to 100 feet below the ocean’s surface. This would allow ships to sail unobstructed by bridges. Floating pontoons would hold the concrete tunnels in place. Engineers hope the ambitious $25 billion project will be completed by 2035.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 20:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/09/3202984/3202984_327709DB5E9C4377B34FF36628C4BE95_161109_3202984_Norway_floats__25_billion_floating_underwater_tu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D06/0B5/D060B51C057541A6AD3C6404B56DF048_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,underwater floating tunnels,submerged floating tunnels,norway tunnels,Norwegian Public Roads Administration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3201674</guid>
      <title>National University of Singapore to test drone delivery service in 2017</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Aircraft manufacturer Airbus is set to trial a drone delivery service which, if successful, could potentially lead to tests of flying taxis for passengers.The technology to be tested in Singapore next year will see drones being used to deliver parcels, according to an article in FORUM, the Airbus Group corporate magazine. During the trial, drones will navigate a network of delivery and pick-up points across the National University of Singapore campus. These drones, also known as octocopters because of their eight blades, will fly automated on routes along interconnecting sky corridors throughout the campus. Upon arrival, the drone will unload the parcel automatically, and its recipient will be sent a delivery notification.Airbus says that if testing shows drones to be safe, this may increase the chances of passenger flight testing being accepted in Singapore. “If the team is able to demonstrate the safe operation of Skyways over NUS, this could help shape the regulatory framework for unmanned aircraft system operations in Singapore and potentially increase acceptance for passenger flight testing, thus giving a boost to urban air vehicle projects,” an excerpt from the FORUM article explains.The company has been developing a electric flying vehicle named CityAirbus for several years, with the aim of reducing traffic congestion in cities. Airbus believes that in the future, people will use such vehicles, which could be operated via transport apps such as Uber.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 13:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/07/3201674/3201674_B41CF5C965D54C38A2B4418FD987C114_161107_3201674_National_University_of_Singapore_to_test_drone_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C92/E78/C92E78802BC944DE89C58C1F01F001DB_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Drone delivery service,drones,drone delivery,national university of singapore,the flying car,flying taxi,drone delivery service,Airbus,cityairbus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3201129</guid>
      <title>Norwegian yard building world&#x2019;s first unmanned ship for offshore operations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Norwegian shipyard is planning to build the world’s first autonomous ship for commercial use, Hrönn.As an unmanned vessel, Hrönn will be remotely controlled, keeping humans away from potential dangers at sea. Hrönn could be sent out on a variety of different missions, such as hydrographic surveying and open-water fish farm support.The ship will also be used to transport light intermodal cargo, and make deliveries to offshore installations. When acting as a standby vessel, Hrönn will be able to provide firefighting support to offshore platforms when needed.Construction of Hrönn is scheduled to begin in January 2017. It will then be put through sea trials, with plans to be available for field operations in 2018.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 21:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/07/3201129/3201129_6D4D5054776D464CBC060A43EC1B22C4_161107_3201129_Norwegian_yard_building_world___s_first_unmanned_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/22F/69B/22F69B48746F476E9F8007F36D041CA6_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Unmanned ship,norway ship,robot ship,robot boat,Artificial intelligence,unmanned boat,Fjellstrand,Automated Ships Ltd,Hronn,ROV,AUV,Norwegian Maritime Authority,Kongsberg Maritime,M Subs Ltd,autonomous boats,roboat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3201127</guid>
      <title>First Mars home unveiled at UK exhibition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The first Mars habitat designed for humans will be unveiled at an exhibition in the United Kingdom on November 10 to tie-in with a National Geographic program that imagines colonists from Earth living on the Red Planet.The exhibition in London is based on extensive consultations with astronomers from the Royal Observatory Greenwich and How We’ll Live on Mars author Stephen Petranek, the Mirror reported.The dwelling would be constructed with Martian soil, which would be microwaved until it forms a brick. The Martian soil bricks and recycled spacecraft parts would then be used to build an igloo-shaped dome. The walls of the dome would be around 10-feet thick and the entrance would be double air-locked.The dome could be able to withstand the harsh Martian environment, including extremely low temperatures, micrometeorite impacts, thin atmosphere and cosmic radiation.The exhibition coincides with the launch of a six-part NatGeo docu-drama called MARS, which tells the story of humans’ attempt to colonise the Red Planet in the year 2033.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 21:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/07/3201127/3201127_13C2A5AF0FCB41FEAD9889E159689D6F_161107_3201127_First_Mars_home_unveiled_at_UK_exhibition_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/571/890/57189059C87D4839954E9DF1B589B1C2_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Mars home,home on mars,mars house,national geographic mars,natgeo mars,space,mars,mars show,life on mars,space igloo,red planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3200839</guid>
      <title>Paris to trial flying water taxi in 2017</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Next year Paris will test a futuristic, prototype water taxi that will allow people glide along the Seine River, two feet above the water. The vessel, named Sea Bubble, can travel up to 30 kilometers per hour and can seat five people including a driver. According to the Telegraph, the vessel’s chassis will be made of fiberglass and high density foam.Sea Bubble will also reportedly have foils attached to its hull that will reduce drag and help it ‘fly’ just above the water, reported the Telegraph.The developers also hope that Sea Bubble vessels could eventually be ordered through vehicle-hailing apps like Uber. If successful in France, they also hope to use Sea Bubble vessels in waterways in other cities such as London, Geneva and elsewhere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 15:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/06/3200839/3200839_B346E999EB154456B0A3A87A4F510360_161107_3200839_Paris_to_trial_flying_water_taxi_in_2017_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/3C9/4D0/3C94D00917294D3F90B266D57C92DBAF_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Flying water taxi,paris,sea bubble,seine river,flying taxi,water taxi,uber water taxi,france,innovation,sea transport,france tourism,seine river sights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3197263</guid>
      <title>Toyota tests keyless car-sharing service</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Toyota will test its new Smart Key Box technology in vehicles used by car-sharing service Getaround in San Francisco at the beginning of next year.A Smart Key Box is placed inside vehicles in the car-sharing program. The person who wants to borrow the car receives a code via an app on a smartphone. When the smartphone is brought near the vehicle, the pre-sent code is authenticated via Bluetooth. The user is then given access to the car and its push-button ignition. The code is only valid during the vehicle reservation period.Toyota has invested $10 million in Getaround, a San Francisco-based startup, Reuters reported. Car owners can register their cars on Getaround free of charge and receive a portion of the rental fee when other people choose to rent their vehicles. The service has around 300,000 users in the U.S., USA Today reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/02/3197263/3197263_AC082BB958BF40369A15327E8910AF0F_161102_3197263_Toyota_tests_keyless_car_sharing_service_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B83/6BF/B836BFB961674168B22C1882FC2EBA9F_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Toyota,getaround car sharing service,getaround,getaround toyota,toyota smart key box,toyota keyless car sharing,keyless cars,keyless car,smart key box]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3197259</guid>
      <title>How modified spinach plants can detect explosives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIT researchers have modified spinach plants to turn them into bomb detectors.Explosives such as landmines contain chemical compounds called nitroaromatics. If nitroaromatics are present in groundwater, they are absorbed by the roots of the spinach plant and transported to the leaves in a process called transpiration.Researchers embedded the spinach plant leaves with molecules called bombolitins that bind to nitroaromatics. They also embedded the leaves with carbon nanotubes, which emit a constant fluorescent signal that serves as a reference, MIT News reported.An infrared camera then reads these fluorescent signals.When nitroaromatics are present, the fluorescent signal from the bombolitins decreases. Once the decrease is detected, the device sends a wireless signal to the user.The experiments were conducted within a distance of 3.3 feet but researchers are confident that the radius can be increased and one sensor could monitor multiple plants, the BBC reported.The study is published in the journal Nature Materials.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 19:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/02/3197259/3197259_11BC481402A14C92A44B272275F5E32A_161102_3197259_How_modified_spinach_plants_can_detect_explosive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/214/E05/214E05D7789C4766BFA406713D102F54_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,MIT,spinach plants detect explosives,spinach detects bombs,bionic spinach,technology,spinach with nanotubes,awesome science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3196348</guid>
      <title>Bacteria-infected mosquitoes to be used in fight against Zika</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Health experts fighting Zika plan the large-scale release of mosquitoes infected with a bacteria in South America early next year, in an effort to stop transmission of the virus.Wolbachia is a natural bacterium found in up to 60 percent of insects. However, it is not usually found in the Aedes aegypti mosquito, the main culprit for transmitting the Zika virus.Scientists had to inject the bacteria into mosquito embryos in order to infect the mosquitoes. They succeeded after numerous failed attempts, Time reported.The bacteria is spread from female mosquitoes to their offspring, even if the female mates with an uninfected male, according to the Eliminate Dengue Program, which developed the Wolbachia method. On the other hand, if an infected male mosquito mates with an uninfected female mosquito, their eggs won’t hatch.The bacteria can stop viruses such as Zika from growing inside the mosquito, thus stopping them from being transmitted to people.The Wolbachia-infected mosquitoes will be released in the greater Rio de Janeiro area in Brazil and parts of Antioquia in Colombia, according to the Eliminate Dengue Program.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 20:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/01/3196348/3196348_98792BCB6F2947C6B1AC2EDDC1621D61_161101_3196348_Bacteria_infected_mosquitoes_to_be_used_in_fight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FC8/7FA/FC87FAE8ADF4497990A7B19FA63D125B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Zika,zika virus,wolbachia-infected mosquitoes,wolbachia stops zika,zika transmission,dengue fever,dengue,mosquitoes infected with bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3196345</guid>
      <title>Dutch tech company develops giant air vacuum cleaner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Dutch tech company has unveiled a giant vacuum cleaner that purifies the air by sucking toxic particles out of the atmosphere.The machine can filter 100 percent of fine particles and 95 percent of ultra-fine particles in the air, inventors the Envinity Group wrote on the company’s website. It can clean about 800,000 cubic meters of air an hour.Fine particles in the air are caused by emissions from burning fuels and industrial combustion. Fine particles are particles smaller than 10 micrometers and ultra-fine particles are smaller than 0.1 micrometers. Governments, businesses, and airports have already expressed an interest in the machine, according to RT.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 20:18:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/01/3196345/3196345_B61CD4EAE31743E9B873176E0A75E175_161101_3196345_Dutch_tech_company_develops_giant_air_vacuum_cle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/49B/4A4/49B4A46CE87A421A8EFEB4537DEC090E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Giant air cleaner,giant air vacuum,giant air filter,dutch air vacuum,envinity group,clean air machine,clean air,air purifier,air vacuum cleaner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3193586</guid>
      <title>Colombia cartels use high-tech torpedoes to smuggle drugs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Colombian Navy on Oct. 23 found 73 kg of cocaine submerged and attached to a docked sailboat off Baru island near the coastal city of Cartagena on Oct. 23. Colombian authorities say towing drugs in these so-called “narco torpedos” is a new trafficking technique favored by the country's drug cartels.According to InSight Crime, the drugs are loaded onto a torpedo-shaped container, which is attached to the bottom of a boat by a cable. The drug-carrying boat sets off with other boats. One boat acts as a decoy to divert the authorities’ attention so the other boats, including the one carrying the drugs, can get a away. If the drug-carrying boat is intercepted, it releases the torpedo to avoid detection. The torpedo then releases a buoy that emits a GPS signal, allowing it to be recovered by another boat.Univision reported that the narco torpedo was developed back in 2000. An earlier version used a radio-transmitter. Other variations include attaching the drug-laden torpedoes to the bottom of freight ships to be retrieved by divers at night after the vessel has docked at port.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 20:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/28/3193586/3193586_FA11AEC911924BAF92E31A8E86645BFA_161028_3193586_Colombia_cartels_use_high_tech_torpedoes_to_smug_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D18/97A/D1897A7DE8F3492B8CEF5EEFA316FB38_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Narco torpedoes,narco submarines,high-tech drug smuggling techniques,colombia drug trafficking,colombia,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3193577</guid>
      <title>Ecological burial pod turns bodies into trees</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Two designers in Italy have developed a new way of burying your loved ones that can turn them into trees.The project is called Capsula Mundi. The body is put into a fetal position in order to fit inside the burial pod, which is made of biodegradable materials, according to the Capsula Mundi website. The burial pod is then buried in the soil with a tree seed or a young tree planted directly above. The pods come in smaller sizes that could be used for ashes or even for pets.The burial pod would decompose naturally and provide nutrients for the tree. Each tree is recorded in a GPS system for identification purposes. More burial pods could turn a cemetery into a forest. Thus, friends and family of the deceased would then visit a forest to pay their respects instead of a cemetery full of headstones.This type of burial is prohibited by Italian law but is legal in some places in the U.S. and Britain. The designers hope to produce the industrial prototype by next year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 20:22:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/28/3193577/3193577_95A0C136D3304363A088BFBE7DB85C98_161028_3193577_Ecological_burial_pod_turns_bodies_into_trees_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D6F/E1C/D6FE1CF9B3844B73B7ABDBBE66904A74_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Burial pods,capsula mundi,body turns into trees,ecological burial pod,ecological burial method,new burial method]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3191790</guid>
      <title>Chinese startup develops selfie drone with facial recognition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Chinese startup has developed a drone equipped with facial recognition technology that takes aerial selfies of its user.The drone is dubbed the Hover Camera Passport and was developed by Zero Zero Robotics in Beijing. The Hover Camera Passport can fly up to 17 mph and climb as high as 16 feet, according to Mashable. The device can be remotely controlled by a smartphone. One battery charge can power up to 10 minutes of flight time.The camera has face- and body-tracking functions, according to Hover Camera Passport’s official website. It can also orbit around the user to take photographs from all angles.The Hover Camera Passport costs $599, which Mashable reported is much cheaper than other products on the market with similar functions.The company has labeled the device a “flying camera,” and has been reluctant to call it a drone, Mashable reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/26/3191790/3191790_B13FDFE9DB494820A25BE1483749BD07_161026_3191790_Chinese_startup_develops_selfie_drone_with_facia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/99B/CA2/99BCA2B767234D32B12FEB5E39A914AD_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Hover camera passport,hover camera,zero zero robotics,selfie drone,drone technology,planet drone,technology,drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3191789</guid>
      <title>China plans social credit system to monitor every citizen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[China plans to implement a social credit system that uses big data to monitor the behavior of citizens.The social credit system is likely to track social media activity, career movement, online purchases, financial and criminal records and translate them into a personal credit score, according to BBC News and News.com.au.A person’s social network is also crucial to determining their credit score, as having friends with a low rating will bring one’s own mark down.A person with a low score may be deemed “untrustworthy”, and the consequences could include difficulties in getting loans, hotel rooms or even the denial of the right to travel abroad.The system is in its pilot phase, with eight private companies commissioned to set up their own credit databases. Alibaba’s Sesame Credit system is highly popular and is used to measure users’ honesty on China’s biggest dating website, Baihe. Other private companies involved include internet giant Tencent, and Qianhai Zhengxin, owned by China’s biggest insurance and financial group, Ping An Insurance.The system is expected to cover every Chinese citizen by 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/26/3191789/3191789_593E4BEBACA14574919AC0FBE04051E7_161026_3191789_China_plans_social_credit_system_to_monitor_ever_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FA2/0FA/FA20FA8931DB4F60A479BD8544FBDB64_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,China social credit system,sesame credit,social credit system,big data,minority report,police state,china human rights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3191788</guid>
      <title>Microsoft&#x2019;s underwater data centers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Microsoft is researching ways to move power hungry and heat-prone data centers underwater.Last year, the company sent a server inside a steel hull 30 feet below the Pacific Ocean, off the California coast.Along with pressurized nitrogen to cool computer chips, the temperature at the ocean floor helped keep the server cool. The experiment ran for 105 days, between August and November of 2015. The hull was named Leona Philpot  after a character from the Halo video game series, according to Microsoft Research.Last year’s experiment was powered by a land-based power grid, but Microsoft aims to develop other power sources. The company believes that renewable resources such as tidal energy could power underwater data centers.Microsoft eventually hopes to develop underwater datacenters with a two decade-lifespan. The data centers would be deployed over five-year periods, with computer hardware replaced at the end of each deployment.The company is working on the next phase of the research, which it said includes a vessel that is quadruple the size and will hold 20 times as much compute power.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/26/3191788/3191788_D20D01DAF006463B8B5547068DDD67C2_161026_3191788_Microsoft___s_underwater_data_centers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C4C/FDD/C4CFDD7E9BFE4E4283216DFD4147E31F_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Underwater server,waterproof server,microsoft research,halo,data center,project natick,underwater data center]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3191787</guid>
      <title>Explosion in northwest China kills 10, injures 157</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A powerful blast tore through China’s Shaanxi province on Monday, killing 10 people and injuring scores more.The explosion originated from a building in the town of Xinmin, which residents said may have had illegally stored explosives hidden inside, Xinhua reported.A nearby hospital and several other buildings were damaged by the blast, which left behind a 5-meter wide and 4-meter deep crater.At least 10 people were reported dead, and as many as 157 injured.China has a poor safety record, with improperly stored industrial explosives causing explosions in the past, most notably in the series of blasts that killed 165 people in Tianjin last year, according to Reuters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/26/3191787/3191787_247DDC876F0A440CB2B27A2D3CB6F86D_161026_3191787_Explosion_in_northwest_China_kills_10__injures_1_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D05/E70/D05E70A32F2D4A0C9B3F931DCB77526D_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Xinmin explosion,china explosion,shaanxi explosion,china blast,deadly blast,deadly explosion,disaster,explosives,explosion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3191785</guid>
      <title>Facebook, Google team up on ultrafast Hong Kong-Los Angeles deep sea cable</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Facebook and Google have joined a consortium to develop a hyper-fast trans-Pacific data cable between Hong Kong and Los Angeles.In addition to the two U.S. technology giants, the project involves deep sea cable developer TE Subcom and Chinese firm Pacific Light Cable Network, the Wall Street Journal reported.The cable will be able to handle up to 120 terabits per second. That’s enough bandwidth for 80 million concurrent video conferences between Hong Kong and Los Angeles, according to Google.When it is completed in 2018, the cable network will span some 12,800 km between the two cities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/26/3191785/3191785_2A87E7FEFF544BAC8DA65C468B85001C_161026_3191785_Facebook__Google_team_up_on_ultrafast_Hong_Kong__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/037/7D6/0377D672496F46D386F5DF0BFFF7050B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Underwater cables,deep sea cables,fibre optic cables,google fiber,fiber optic,facebook cable,te subcom cable,transpacific cable,pcln,pacific light cable network]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3191781</guid>
      <title>Three-wheeled vehicle tilts 52 degrees</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Florida inventor has designed a three-wheeled vehicle that can tilt 52 degrees.The vehicle is called Narrow Tilting Vehicle with Non-Tilting Wheels. It is a reverse trike style vehicle with two wheels at the front. According to New Atlas, the vehicle can be manufactured into two, three or four wheel configurations.The vehicle uses flat car tires rather than curved motorcycle tires, as they do not tilt relative to the road. The cabin is managed by hydraulic actuators that create a cradle mechanism, which allows the cabin to tilt when the road surface angle is changing or a cornering G-force is being applied.The designer, Frank Knisley, said the cabin can tilt up to 52 degrees, creating a flying sensation without using one’s own body as a counterbalance. Knisley is currently looking to team up with other people to produce a prototype of the vehicle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/26/3191781/3191781_D18A5CAFB1A3495EB26FA972DA176CE0_161026_3191781_Three_wheeled_vehicle_tilts_52_degrees_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/334/303/334303D73E47436D993DE3EC86C28151_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Narrow tilting vehicle with non-tilting wheels,narrow tilting vehicle,concept cars,Frank Knisley Florida,Automoto Dynamics,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3191779</guid>
      <title>BMW unveils its motorcycle of the future</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BMW revealed its latest concept motorcycle in Santa Monica, California on Oct. 12 as part of celebrations of its 100th birthday.The Motorrad Vision Next 100 boasts a self-balancing feature which BMW says eliminates the need for protective gear  including a helmet.What BMC calls a “digital companion” offers riding information and guidance to the rider. Should the system detect danger and if no action is taken by the rider, the digital companion will kick in and make the necessary corrective maneuvers.The digital companion appears as a heads-up display in an augmented reality visor paired with the motorcycle. Data enters the rider’s field of view when called upon. If the rider looks straight ahead, no information is displayed.The concept also includes clothing inspired by muscle cords that actively supports the rider. The clothes are equipped with vibrating elements on the arms and legs that act as indicators should the bike lean too far in one direction.The Motorrad Vision Next 100 concept design was on display in Los Angeles through Oct. 19.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/26/3191779/3191779_34896992EC774F778E9F85CFA1BF4C8B_161026_3191779_BMW_unveils_its_motorcycle_of_the_future_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B90/BBE/B90BBE53DFDE403DBEA2AC4A70FE234E_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Motorrad Vision Next 100,BMW,BMW bike,BMW motorrad,motorrad,motorrad vision,Holger Hampf,roadster,motorcycles,bikes,bike of the future,BMW motorcycle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3188715</guid>
      <title>Yellow Barnacle windshield blockers could replace parking boots</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Philadelphia and Fort Lauderdale are trying out a new alternative to the parking boot. Jamming a wheel to force a driver to confront unpaid parking fines may have been the norm for a long time, but clunky parking boots are a hassle to deal with, both for traffic enforcers and car owners. Fox News reports that the task could prove easier with a new parking enforcement device called the Barnacle, a lightweight plastic device that immobilizes a car by blocking the driver’s line of sight. The Barnacle comes equipped with two commercial-grade suction cups that allow it to latch on to car windshields, and is attached in place using a pump and lock.Secured by over 750 pounds of force, the Barnacle is virtually impossible to pry off. It’s also sensitive to movement, and sounds an alarm when a car is used while it’s still attached.To safely remove it, drivers pay their parking fines over the phone, and are given a code to release the device.They then have 24 hours to return the Barnacle to the parking authority, or risk being charged with an additional fine.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 17:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/22/3188715/3188715_4865A657F9514EF0ADE3E3852D3F2413_161022_3188715_Yellow_Barnacle_windshield_blockers_could_replac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/061/0AE/0610AEF14E2B4FAD9490AD5064C2E331_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Barnacle,Barnacle windshield blocker,barnacle windshield cover,windshield blocker,windshield cover,parking enforcement,parking authority,parking boot,parking fine,philadelphia,fort lauderdale]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3188004</guid>
      <title>Bat houses to be erected in Miami Beach to combat Zika virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[To combat the spread of Zika virus, small bat houses will be installed in city parks to attract bats looking for a place to roost. Bats prefer warm, narrow spaces that offer shelter from predators and the elements. A good bat house will be built tight to mimic their natural habitats. Mother bats are most attracted to bat houses close to a water source, so they won’t have to travel too far from their young. Bat houses should be positioned for maximum sun exposure, placed 15-20 feet in the air to allow the bats enough room to swoop down and fly away.The bat houses are being implemented because bats are expert mosquito-killers, with the ability to consume as many as 1000 in under an hour. The move is also a nod to environmentalists upset over nearby Miami-Dade county being sprayed with naled, an insecticide used to eradicate the mosquitoes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 17:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/21/3188004/3188004_7B4B78854AA74B66BEDBA444A7629271_161021_3188004_Bat_houses_to_be_erected_in_Miami_Beach_to_comba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C07/9C8/C079C81F14D54D8BB80DA8F7C4629A65_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Zika,bats,mosquitos bats,bats mosquitos,bats zika,miami bats,florida bats,bat house,naled]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3187760</guid>
      <title>Amazon patents voice-controlled miniature drone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Amazon was granted a U.S. patent on Tuesday for a miniature drone that would be fitted with microphones and a camera, according to the United States Patent and Trademark Office.The drone would respond to voice commands, and has several potential functions. It could be used to find a missing child through face recognition, an RFID tag, or barcode on the child’s clothing.Amazon also imagines the pocket-sized drones may help the police catch suspects. It could hover above traffic stops to record interactions between officers and citizens.Firefighters could also use the drones to identify people trapped in burning buildings, or equip the devices with thermal imaging cameras to locate fire “hot spots”.The technology may be used in search and rescue missions, for example, to find a downed airliner.Civilian uses include finding your car when you forget where you parked, or recording daily life on film.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 13:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/20/3187760/3187760_2A246C6D379347C2A45F14A32D737678_161020_3187760_Amazon_patents_voice_controlled_miniature_drone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DD8/DD7/DD8DD793D4A241AE97B59E71C2AB5BCD_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Amazon drone,drones,drones with cameras,drones in action,new amazon drone,miniature drones,voice controlled drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3187245</guid>
      <title>Zume makes pizza with robots cooks the pie while it&#x2019;s delivered</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Silicon Valley startup has developed a new way of making and delivering pizza: using robots.According to the Mercury News, Zuma pizza is in fact made by humans and robots. The pizza dough is kneaded by a human before it is passed on to robots on a conveyer belt. The robots then place sauce onto the pizza and spread it around before a member of the kitchen staff puts toppings onto the pizza. The pizza is then placed into an oven by another robot, where it is partially baked.Zume’s delivery truck is equipped with 56 ovens designed to cook the pizza completely within four minutes before it arrives at its intended destination. This ensures the food stays hot for the customer.The company also uses artificial intelligence to record customers’ ordering habits. This allows them to predict incoming pizza orders and start preparing before the orders actually arrive.According to Electronics 360, Zume is developing new robots in order to automate the whole production line in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 19:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/20/3187245/3187245_14147365884F4BDEA60FD1928602422C_161020_3187245_Zume_makes_pizza_with_robots_cooks_the_pie_while_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2BD/578/2BD578173CE046C1836F82D5A12C0FCB_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Zume pizza,zume pizza mountain view,robot pizza maker,zume pizza delivery,pizza made by robots,technology,mountain view]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3187243</guid>
      <title>Quantum-dot coating can turn window into solar panels</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at the Los Alamos National Laboratory in New Mexico have developed a film of quantum dots that can turn windows into photovoltaic systems.Quantum dots can be used as semiconductors. According to IEEE Spectrum, they consist of a CdSe inner core, a Cd1−xZnxS outer shell and a silica coating that prevents them from oxidation. The quantum dots are spead into a thin sheet that can be placed onto a glass window pane.When photons from sunlight hit a quantum dot, it sends the electron in the valence band into the conduction band, leaving a hole behind. When the electron recombines with the hole in the valence band, a new photon with lower energy is generated.This new photon propagates within the glass via internal reflections. Energy is then generated when the propagating photons reach the window frame, where solar cells are stored.The coating of quantum dots can be used on any window and to turn it into a sunlight harvesters at costs lower than are currently available.The study was published in Nature Energy on Oct 10.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 19:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/20/3187243/3187243_18973BD1657B4EE3919C0217DC9E729F_161020_3187243_Quantum_dot_coating_can_turn_window_into_solar_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/96D/657/96D657CFBFF64DE3A82CF1312692F88C_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Quantum dots,quantum dot technology,quantum-dot coating,quantum-dot solar power,quantum-dot window coating,los alamos national laboratory,new mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3186037</guid>
      <title>Yondr case locks up your mobile phone during concerts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A company called Yondr has created a way of preventing concert-goers from using their phones at performance venues.Before entering a performance venue, attendees would place their cellphones inside a Yondr case. The attendees would be in possession of the Yondr cases at all time, but would not be able to open them to access their phones while they’re located inside the concert venue.To access their phones, the attendees must step outside the concert venue and unlock the Yondr cases at unlock stations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 13:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/18/3186037/3186037_CCEB894CCB9F4E67AAEDEA8415AC62AE_161018_3186037_Yondr_case_locks_up_your_mobile_phone_during_con_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/712/820/71282060C336451F8EE82D983852E961_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Yondr cases,yondr,yondr locks up phones,yondr in concerts,phone-free concerts,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3183479</guid>
      <title>Thailand mourns death of world&#x2019;s longest-serving monarch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Thailand’s King Bhumibol Adulyadej died on Thursday, aged 88. Bhumibol came to the throne in 1946 and was crowned king in 1950. He was the world’s longest-serving monarch.The government immediately ordered all flags to fly at half-mast and told citizens to wear black for 30 days, the Guardian reported.An official mourning period will last for one year, during which big events like music concerts will be postponed. Meanwhile, alcohol sales will be restricted and bars and restaurants will close or shorten their opening hours.King Bhumibol will be succeeded by his only son, Crown Prince Maha Vajiralongkorn, who is far less revered than his father.Under Thailand’s strict lese majeste laws it is a crime to insult members of the royal family, with each charge subject to 15 years in jail.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 20:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/15/3183479/3183479_F3DAD8D443E143E7BE2FC5CA3DFADBCB_161015_3183479_Thailand_mourns_death_of_world___s_longest_servi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/92F/B9F/92FB9F236BC34846B90B30AD3F71FD84_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Thai king,thailand king,thai king died,thai king 2016,crown prince,crown prince thailand,thai crown prince]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3183477</guid>
      <title>Can the human body handle a long journey to Mars?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In a recent opinion article on CNN.com, U.S. President Barack Obama stressed his goal of not only sending humans to Mars, but making it possible for extended stay by 2030.Obama praised NASA for building the groundwork in American space travel and lauded the private sector, which has grown exponentially in the past few years. He also announced that the government is working with commercial partners to make it possible to travel to and stay on Mars.But the journey alone won’t be an easy one. From what scientists already know about space travel, it can have harmful effects on the human body.According to James A. Pawelczyk, Ph.D.  an physiology and kinesiology researcher, who served as a payload specialist aboard the space shuttle Columbia in 1998  one of the dangers of space travel is exposure to radiation.In a 2005 article written for Penn State’s website, Pawelczyk described solar rays passing through metal as something akin to rain passing through chicken wire. Without the protection of Earth’s atmosphere, humans are vulnerable to the sun’s gamma rays and hot neutrons, which can cause cancer. There are two ways to deal with solar radiation during space travel. The first is to create a shield to absorb the radiation and protect the human body.During space travel, humans are also prone to osteoporosis. Astronauts in space have been recorded losing one to two percent of bone mass per month. During a round trip to Mars, which takes about a year, 10 to 25 percent of skeletal mass could be lost. Pawelczyk equates this to being bedridden for about 10 to 15 years.Space causes other complications as well, including alterations to the circulatory system and the immune system.Once on Mars, people will battle with lower temperatures. The thin and low pressure atmosphere also means little oxygen and very dusty conditions. The atmosphere of Mars is about 100 times thinner than Earth’s and is 95percent carbon dioxide. Furthermore, without adequate protection, Mars’ low pressure atmosphere would cause, skin and organs to rupture within minutes, leading to a quick and painful death.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 20:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/15/3183477/3183477_2D36EEFB8AD14AFDB2D95419AF8AF0D9_161015_3183477_Can_the_human_body_handle_a_long_journey_to_Mars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/D2E/0CC/D2E0CC9FF78E48D3A2FC58C6DF3E7BFB_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Mars,nasa,space,astronaut,space travel,outer space,red planet,obama,barack obama,life on mars,osteoporosis,space race]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3182842</guid>
      <title>DEA reverses plan to ban kratom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The United States Drug Enforcement Administration is reversing its decision to ban the use of kratom after a public outcry.According to NPR, kratom is derived from a plant in southeast Asia, which is related to coffee plants. It is often purchased in the form of capsule filled with powdered leaf or made into tea.The drug is said to have been able to help curing addiction to opiates or alcohol and can cure intractable pain. Although the drug is said to be rather mild, it can cause side effects including nausea, sweating, respiratory depression and hallucinations, according to Narconon.Kratom is legal in Canada and the United Kingdom. It is prohibited in Thailand, Malaysia, Burma and Australia.The DEA announced in August that it planned to place kratom in schedule 1 of the Controlled Substances Act, which includes heroin and LSD. It has received numerous oppositions from the public since the announcement.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 20:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/14/3182842/3182842_7DC6D4D96C11499C9273A2066B8BEA32_161014_3182842_DEA_reverses_plan_to_ban_kratom_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2B0/58B/2B058BCE513E4068BC7CB5D7F22A6EB9_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,DEA,kratom,kratom drug,dea bans kratom,dea reverses ban on kratom,kratom ban,kratom legality]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3181009</guid>
      <title>UK scientists develop gene therapy to treat Alzheimer&#x2019;s</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers from Imperial College London have developed a gene therapy that has successfully prevented the development of Alzheimer’s disease in mice.To treat the disease, scientists created a modified a virus using a lentivirus vector in order to target specific cells. This modified virus also contained a gene called PGC1-alpha, which is said to prevent the formation of amyloid-beta peptide, a protein that causes amyloid plaques. Amyloid plaques are commonly found in the brains of those with Alzheimer’s disease, and are said to cause brain cell death.The modified virus was delivered directly into the brains of mice suffering from the early stages of Alzheimer’s.Lab results showed the mice with the PGC1-alpha gene developed very few amyloid plaques, while the untreated mice had multiple plagues after four months.The study was published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 20:18:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/12/3181009/3181009_89C7D787CB7540D7B88A61CA6DC1C4A2_161012_3181009_UK_scientists_develop_gene_therapy_to_treat_Alzh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2D7/A5E/2D7A5E1096BF4C29AD2BE180DFAB5AF8_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Alzheimer’s disease,gene therapy,imperial college london,alzheimer's treatment,curing alzheimer’s,dementia,health,science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3181007</guid>
      <title>Mission launched to capture first picture of Earth-like planet in neighboring star system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Project Blue’s half-meter-wide telescope is expected to be sent into orbit in roughly three years. It’s high-contrast imaging is designed to take pictures of our closest neighboring star system, Alpha Centauri. Alpha Centauri is 4.37 light years away from our solar system.Scientists estimate there is an 85% probability that Alpha Centauri’s sun-like stars have an Earth-like planet somewhere in their habitable zones. If a planet orbiting within the habitable zones is detected with an atmosphere that could allow liquid water to exist on its surface, it may appear as a blue dot in the telescope.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 20:17:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/12/3181007/3181007_83177ADEBE9646358D9D79FA24EBEF46_161012_3181007_Mission_launched_to_capture_first_picture_of_Ear_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5FC/988/5FC9887A332548D390ABD59F23B87B8B_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Exoplanets,alpha centauri,earth-like planets,carl sagan,pale blue dot,project blue,boldlygo institute,mission centaur]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3180221</guid>
      <title>South Africa&#x2019;s first solar powered airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The South African city of George is home to Africa’s first  and world’s second  fully operational solar powered airport.George Airport last September became powered entirely by solar energy. According to an AFP article used by France24, this move lowered its carbon dioxide emissions by more than 1000 tonnes. The hub runs on energy garnered by some 2,000 solar panels. These power everything from the ATMs, restaurants to the check-in desk and airport control tower.  Excess energy is transferred to nearby homes and other places a local power grid. South Africa is already developing two other solar powered airports in the city of Kimberly and town of Upington.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 21:17:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/11/3180221/3180221_8C1C52B4D73041EAB61CAA29000E3A10_161011_3180221_South_Africa___s_first_solar_powered_airport_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/48A/D92/48AD927E17B740ADB1F27EDA799019C3_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Solar power south africa,george airport,solar power africa,solar power system,south africa,carbon dioxide airport,co2 reduction,carbon footprint]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3180218</guid>
      <title>New York&#x2019;s JFK airport tests passenger forecast software designed to stop bottlenecks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Software designed to reduce queues and ensure a smooth experience for passengers has gone on trial at Terminal 4 of New York’s JFK airport.The Beontra system pulls information from the Airport Operational Database. This includes passenger profiles, flight schedules, and real-time info on data such as adverse weather conditions.The system uses the data to produce a graph, showing when waiting times will peak at airport bottlenecks, Wired reported.This information is shared with airlines, immigration, and security officials, so they can deploy enough staff to handle the volume of passengers moving through the airport.Currently the system displays passenger forecasts for today and the next two days, but can potentially provide forecasts up to 90 days in advance.The system is used by more than 30 airports in Europe and Asia, and JFK is the first U.S. airport to test it.Around 20 million passengers pass through JFK’s Terminal 4 each year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 21:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/11/3180218/3180218_A094FEC778FA41FC8AFC19D09DBD139C_161011_3180218_New_York___s_JFK_airport_tests_passenger_forecas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CB1/F93/CB1F93F432CB4852823FD94C64034913_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Airport,jfk,jfk airport,airport software,beontra,smart airport,future technology,airport technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3180217</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover bumblebees can learn and share tool use skills</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at Queen Mary University of London studying bumble bees have observed that the insects were able to share knowledge regarding the use of tools.The publication Science reported that in a series of experiments, scientists placed three sugar-filled artificial flowers underneath a glass table, each tied to a string. Of 110 bees that were put through the test, two managed to use the string as a rope to pull the flower out to get to the sugar.In another test, untrained bees were placed behind a transparent wall, as they watched another bee retrieve the sugar. When put through the same conditions, 60% of the untrained bees were able to successfully navigate the experiment.Even after the trained bees had died, the learned skills remained in the colony. This research demonstrates that bee colonies may have more advanced culture than previously understood, with the ability to pass on knowledge seen as a complex phenomena of social groups.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 21:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/11/3180217/3180217_5927CDB46D0F4007A8CC4E99EA172DAF_161011_3180217_Scientists_discover_bumblebees_can_learn_and_sha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/AF9/B9E/AF9B9E79A4D1489880B5399F997E7568_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Bees tool use,tool use animals,bumblebees experiment,bees string,bees experiment,queen mary university of london,Lars Chittka]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3180216</guid>
      <title>U.S. unlikely to meet 2015 Paris climate agreement targets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent study revealed that the U.S. is highly unlikely to fulfill the greenhouse gas emission targets set at the Paris climate talks last year.The U.S. has pledged to reduce greenhouse gas emissions by 28 percent from 2005 to 2025. However, according to the study published in Nature Climate Change, it would only be able to reduce the rate by about 4.8 percent given current and proposed emissions policies.The study suggested that the U.S. needs to phase-out coal and natural gas power plants more aggressively and increase the use of renewable energy and electric cars, as well as transform oil and gas-based heating systems to electric to come closer to attaining its goals.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 21:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/11/3180216/3180216_9F7147C5A2B44BA88CF8CCCA1C693181_161011_3180216_U_S__unlikely_to_meet_2015_Paris_climate_agreeme_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0D9/1FF/0D91FF90496B492C82FE51913CDFAF9A_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Climate change,global warming,paris climate agreement,us unlikely to meet greenouse gas emission targets,environment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178042</guid>
      <title>Johnson &amp; Johnson insulin pumps are vulnerable to hacking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical giant Johnson & Johnson is warning diabetic patients that hackers could exploit a security flaw in one of its devices to deliver a lethal dose of insulin.The Johnson & Johnson OneTouch Ping system delivers insulin through a catheter. The device is sold with a wireless remote control.The system is vulnerable to hacking because the signal from the remote control to the device is not encrypted, Reuters reported.Tests by the company confirmed that hackers could order the device to pump insulin from a distance of up to 25 feet.Johnson & Johnson advised concerned patients not to use the remote control and to program the pump to limit the maximum insulin dose.In a letter to patients, the company stressed that the threat from hacking was minimal as hackers would require sophisticated equipment and proximity to the pump. It added that no hacking attempts had been reported by the 114,000 patients who use the device in the U.S. and Canada.Diabetic patients use insulin pumps to control blood sugar levels. Giving a patient too much insulin could cause low blood sugar, which in some cases may prove fatal.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/08/3178042/3178042_BAB59DBFAFAA410593FC731A375695A5_161008_3178042_Johnson___Johnson_insulin_pumps_are_vulnerable_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A1E/374/A1E374E93E0948A3B0DBF060893B5DB3_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Insulin pump,diabetes,diabetic,hackers,hacking,cyber security,johnson and johnson insulin pump,insulin pump hack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178040</guid>
      <title>Microwave extraction could be the future of oil production</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Oil industry experts in the United States are developing a technology to beam microwaves into shale rock in order to extract oil.Oil shale is found in more shallow formations, which contains solid organic material called kerogen. Oil can be extracted from oil shale after subjecting it to high heat.Peter Kearl, co-founder and Chiech Technology Officer of Qmast, a Colorado-based company pioneering the use of the microwave tech explained the method to Ozy.com: a microwave beam as powerful as 500 household microwave ovens would be used to extract the oil from oil shale. Once the microwave reaches the oil shale, it would heat up the water in the rock and turn them into steam, which would help releasing the oil. The rock would become transparent after the oil and water has been removed, which allows the microwave beam to penetrate further.According to Ozy.com, a single microwave extraction well could produce about 800,000 barrels of oil. This technology might also produce water while extracting oil with the amount of one barrel of water for every three barrels of oil produced.The Daily Caller reported that microwave extraction technology would have major environmental advantages but would only be about 20 percent more expensive than conventional methods. Qmast is currently planned to deployed in 2017 and is expected to start producing oil by the end of that year, Ozy.com reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/08/3178040/3178040_153C4A43ECFB412DB6DCA280EA9BA2BA_161008_3178040_Microwave_extraction_could_be_the_future_of_oil__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7F6/17B/7F617B29FEEF48DE81E758E7D34EDD29_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Qmast,microwave extraction,oil fracking,oil drilling,microwave extraction oil,us oil industry,us oil drilling,us microwave oil fracking,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178039</guid>
      <title>Smart bandage designed by girl, 13, signals when it needs to be changed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A smart bandage that detects moisture levels and signals when it needs to be changed has helped a seventh grade student impress the judges at the Google Science Fair.Anushka Naiknaware, 13, is a student at Stoller Middle School in Beaverton, Oregon. Her invention finished in the top eight at the competition, according to the event’s official website. Naiknaware won a $15,000 scholarship and a free trip to Lego headquarters in Denmark, with a year of entrepreneurship mentoring from a Lego executive.The bandage uses biopolymer chitosan with carbon nanoparticles to reduce bleeding and measure moisture levels in the wound. A battery and bluetooth chip sit on top of the bandage and are covered by a regular bandage adhesive layer.When the moisture level is high, the electrons inside the bandage experience less resistance; when the bandage dries up, the electrons detect much higher resistance. The change in resistance is noted and can be wirelessly transmitted to a mobile device, which then prompts the user to change bandages.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7B3/67F/7B367FD616EC472A9720D1823BF4C064_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Smart bandage,future tech,health,inventions,google science fair,innovation technology,child genius]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178038</guid>
      <title>Former IndyCar racer and quadriplegic Sam Schmidt gets first semi-autonomous driver&#x2019;s license in U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Late last month, former IndyCar racer Sam Schmidt became the first man in the U.S. to receive a semi-autonomous driver’s license. Schmidt lost control of his arms and legs during a practice lap in 2000. In September, Nevada Lieutenant Governor Mark Hutchison awarded Schmidt the first restricted license in the country to drive a semi-autonomous car.One of Schmidt’s sponsors, Arrow Electronics, had modified a 2014 Corvette Z06 with technology that will allow him to control the car without the use of his limbs.The car, aptly nicknamed the Arrow SAM Car  SAM as in semi-autonomous motorcar   is equipped with a voice command system, infrared camera system, a breath manipulation system, GPS technology and 4G-LTE connectivity.Voice commands allow Schmidt to turn the car off and on and change gears.Infrared cameras mounted on the car’s dashboard pick up sensors mounted onto a hat, which Schmidt wears when driving. When Schmidt turns his head, the infrared camera system picks up the motion and translates it into steering. To control acceleration and braking, a sip/puff system has been installed. A breathing apparatus allows Schmidt to accelerate the car by blowing air into a tube. To engage the brakes, Schmidt sucks air out of the tube. Pressure sensors send signals to the car. GPS technology provides additional guidance assistance. Using sensors on the back of the car, the system will keep the car within 1.5 meters of the edge of the road or track. Schmidt has a virtual envelope of about 10 meters wide within which he can steer.An overall safety system ensures that signals sent by Schmidt are properly translated into the car’s movements.The car is also linked to an Arrow 4G-LTE gateway that runs Windows 10 Enterprise on an Intel server. The Arrow 4G-LTE collects, streams and stores API-accessible data in Microsoft’s Azure cloud service.The license requires Schmidt to have a passenger inside the vehicle at all times. As a result, Arrow has equipped the car with a pilot control option that allows the passenger to take over driving if necessary. Additionally, the license calls for a pilot car to be driven in front of the Arrow SAM Car at all times, acting as a barrier between Schmidt and other drivers on the road. In emergency cases where the pilot driver isn’t able to gain control, the Arrow SAM Car could run into the pilot vehicle.Schmidt was able to attain 152 mph in the car at Indianapolis Motor Speedway in May and drove the Pikes Peak International in June.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/08/3178038/3178038_F4E5B70870454C799ABAFA1D5DDF21C4_161008_3178038_Former_IndyCar_racer_and_quadriplegic_Sam_Schmid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A34/DB2/A34DB2DDE7A84BBD834B62A142276F97_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Corvette,corvette z06,arrow sam,indycar,Sam Schmidt,verizon indycar,Mark Hutchison,Nevada Lt. Governor Mark Hutchison,Schmidt Peterson Motorsports,motorsports,indy racing,racing,Indianapolis Motor Speedway,driver’s license,semi-autonomous vehicle,semi autonomous vehicle,arrow,arrow sam car,sam car,quadriplegic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178036</guid>
      <title>Hawaiian bees added to U.S. endangered species list</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The U.S. government has added seven species of Hawaiian bees to the endangered species list, making them the first bee species to be protected under the Endangered Species Act.The seven endangered species of bees are Hylaeus anthracinus, Hylaeus longiceps, Hylaeus assimulans, Hylaeus facilis, Hylaeus hilaris, Hylaeus kuakea and Hylaeus mana. They live in many habits on the Hawaii islands, including coastlines, wet and dry forests and shrublands.According to the Xerces Society, the Hawaiian bees are threatened by urbanization, fire, wild animals such as pigs, and invasive ants and plant species.Bees are disappearing at an alarming rate on the mainland U.S. as well, with 20 to 40 percent of honeybee colonies collapsing every winter, the Science Alert reported.Bees are vital to human beings as they are one of the world’s major pollinators. Without the bees pollinating, about 30 percent of the world’s crops and 90 percent of wild plants would die.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/08/3178036/3178036_6950E9C0A8934A4DA82E71AA9810048A_161008_3178036_Hawaiian_bees_added_to_U_S__endangered_species_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/2CB/B6B/2CBB6B4EEC7546448C36B86D12F68BCB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Hawaiian yellow-faced bees,hawaiian bees endangered species,bees endangered,bees colony disappearing in us,us bee colonies,save the bees,endangered species in us]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178035</guid>
      <title>Japan&#x2019;s All Nippon Airways announces $22 million Avatar XPRIZE</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The next wave of animatronics is on the horizon. The Avatar XPRIZE challenge, sponsored by Japanese airline All Nippon Airways (ANA), is currently underway and will conclude in 2022 with a “no limits” Olympic-type competition. The challenge asks teams to come up a means to instantaneous and limitless transportation to further expand the reaches of communication. A prize of $22 million will be awarded to the winning team that can develop a system that teleports one’s consciousness into a physical avatar body, which will enable people to instantly be in multiple places at once.Professor Susumu Tachi from the University of Tokyo’s Tachi Lab has already demonstrated a workable avatar called the Telesar V, which stands for Telexistence Surrogate Anthropomorphic Robot. The bare-bones avatar was synced to one of Tachi’s students and interacted with the professor during a recent demonstration.Hiroshi Ishiguro from Osaka University’s Intelligent Robotics Laboratory also recently presented his robot. The robot, named “U,” was dressed as a flight attendant and appeared rather lifelike. U was even capable of making facial expressions and smiled during the demonstration.XPRIZE and ANA hope that the challenge will give birth new ways of traveling, allowing people to not only experience new areas without the time spent on commuting, but to also be able to conduct business, according to the competition’s official website.In 2022, each team’s avatar will compete in the Avatar Games, by conducting a series of activities based on different jobs. For example, they will act as a caretaker and push a wheelchair; shake hands as a public speaker, and play tennis against a trained athlete.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/08/3178035/3178035_680A17EFB45149828DDDA9F5FEE9EDDE_161008_3178035_Japan___s_All_Nippon_Airways_announces__22_milli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/915/99B/91599BA7172B486A9F192B625FAAE38D_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Avatar,avatar x prize,x prize,xprize,avatar xprize,ana,japan,vr,virtual reality,robots,Telesar V,avatars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178034</guid>
      <title>Researchers at MIT have 3-D printed robot skin using viscoelastic materials</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at MIT’s Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Laboratory have developed a 3-D printed skin for robots that acts as a shock absorber. The skin protects robots and helps make their movements more precise. The skin is made of a “programmable viscoelastic material” (PVM). Unlike purely elastic substances, a viscoelastic substance has an elastic component and a viscous component. Viscoelastics are able to dissipate or dampen energy where elastics cannot.The team found that by 3-D printing the skin, they are able to manipulate its elasticity by altering the amount of liquid material inside the layers. Printing was also the most affordable method of manipulation.Researchers tested the skin on their cube robot that moves by bouncing. The team used a solid, a liquid and a flexible rubber-like material called TangoBlack+ to print both the cube and its skins.They found that the robot with the more elastic skin was able to bounce higher and land with more precision.The work was supported by a grant from the National Science Foundation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:27:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/08/3178034/3178034_51E153DB7E2A4ACFA8B4759084470D3F_161008_3178034_Researchers_at_MIT_have_3_D_printed_robot_skin_u_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CBB/23C/CBB23CB29DF847ED934ABB2EA93EC371_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,MIT,CSAIL,3-d printing,3d printing,robot,robots,robot skin,skin,computer science and artificial intelligence laboratory,science,technology,artificial intelligence,viscoelastic,programmable viscoelastic material,PVM,programmable viscoelastic,elasticity,shock absorber,3d print,3-d print]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3178033</guid>
      <title>MIT develops wetsuit material inspired by beavers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by hairy semiaquatic mammals like beavers and sea otters, researchers at MIT are developing a new kind of material for wetsuit, fabricated from the pelts of beavers and otters to improve swimmers’ insulation.Led by MIT professor Anette Hosoi, the team fabricated fur-like pelts to study how beavers and sea otters stay warm while diving underwater. During the study, the team submerged the pelts in silicone oil to observe the formation of air pockets. The result shows that the fabricated pelts with thicker fur that were plunged at higher speeds generally retained a thicker layer of air within their fur.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:26:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/08/3178033/3178033_7E737DC39BC14E63B47698CA3446BBC6_161008_3178033_MIT_develops_wetsuit_material_inspired_by_beaver_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/215/DA4/215DA43C7D8C40D5A29921BE66A78FF6_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,MIT,textile design,beaver,sea otter,wetsuits,water sport,furry wetsuits]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3177426</guid>
      <title>Smart bandage designed by girl, 13, signals when it needs to be changed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A smart bandage that detects moisture levels and signals when it needs to be changed has helped a seventh grade student impress the judges at the Google Science Fair.Anushka Naiknaware, 13, is a student at Stoller Middle School in Beaverton, Oregon. Her invention finished in the top eight at the competition, according to the event’s official website. Naiknaware won a $15,000 scholarship and a free trip to Lego headquarters in Denmark, with a year of entrepreneurship mentoring from a Lego executive.The bandage uses biopolymer chitosan with carbon nanoparticles to reduce bleeding and measure moisture levels in the wound. A battery and bluetooth chip sit on top of the bandage and are covered by a regular bandage adhesive layer.When the moisture level is high, the electrons inside the bandage experience less resistance; when the bandage dries up, the electrons detect much higher resistance. The change in resistance is noted and can be wirelessly transmitted to a mobile device, which then prompts the user to change bandages.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 21:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/07/3177426/3177426_9B055AB1A541461B977A58B166EA2FEA_161007_3177426_Smart_bandage_designed_by_girl__13__signals_when_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CCE/543/CCE54371DF534655AA3DF04F2B01D644_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Smart bandage,future tech,health,inventions,google science fair,innovation technology,child genius]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3177401</guid>
      <title>Johnson &amp; Johnson insulin pumps are vulnerable to hacking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical giant Johnson & Johnson is warning diabetic patients that hackers could exploit a security flaw in one of its devices to deliver a lethal dose of insulin.The Johnson & Johnson OneTouch Ping system delivers insulin through a catheter. The device is sold with a wireless remote control.The system is vulnerable to hacking because the signal from the remote control to the device is not encrypted, Reuters reported.Tests by the company confirmed that hackers could order the device to pump insulin from a distance of up to 25 feet.Johnson & Johnson advised concerned patients not to use the remote control and to program the pump to limit the maximum insulin dose.In a letter to patients, the company stressed that the threat from hacking was minimal as hackers would require sophisticated equipment and proximity to the pump. It added that no hacking attempts had been reported by the 114,000 patients who use the device in the U.S. and Canada.Diabetic patients use insulin pumps to control blood sugar levels. Giving a patient too much insulin could cause low blood sugar, which in some cases may prove fatal.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 20:44:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/07/3177401/3177401_D79CA7ED490842E8B82504CD8BE3E84E_161007_3177401_Johnson___Johnson_insulin_pumps_are_vulnerable_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DAE/1A7/DAE1A7A3B99D4B0CA886F77577679D8B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Insulin pump,diabetes,diabetic,hackers,hacking,cyber security,johnson and johnson insulin pump,insulin pump hack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3177400</guid>
      <title>Microwave extraction could be the future of oil production</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Oil industry experts in the United States are developing a technology to beam microwaves into shale rock in order to extract oil.Oil shale is found in more shallow formations, which contains solid organic material called kerogen. Oil can be extracted from oil shale after subjecting it to high heat.Peter Kearl, co-founder and Chiech Technology Officer of Qmast, a Colorado-based company pioneering the use of the microwave tech explained the method to Ozy.com: a microwave beam as powerful as 500 household microwave ovens would be used to extract the oil from oil shale. Once the microwave reaches the oil shale, it would heat up the water in the rock and turn them into steam, which would help releasing the oil. The rock would become transparent after the oil and water has been removed, which allows the microwave beam to penetrate further.According to Ozy.com, a single microwave extraction well could produce about 800,000 barrels of oil. This technology might also produce water while extracting oil with the amount of one barrel of water for every three barrels of oil produced.The Daily Caller reported that microwave extraction technology would have major environmental advantages but would only be about 20 percent more expensive than conventional methods. Qmast is currently planned to deployed in 2017 and is expected to start producing oil by the end of that year, Ozy.com reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 20:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/07/3177400/3177400_08451C74856E436790D67C759FDE4481_161007_3177400_Microwave_extraction_could_be_the_future_of_oil__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/408/447/40844714839A4CF2B095CF710E5FA500_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Qmast,microwave extraction,oil fracking,oil drilling,microwave extraction oil,us oil industry,us oil drilling,us microwave oil fracking,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3177397</guid>
      <title>Former IndyCar racer and quadriplegic Sam Schmidt gets first semi-autonomous driver&#x2019;s license in U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Late last month, former IndyCar racer Sam Schmidt became the first man in the U.S. to receive a semi-autonomous driver’s license. Schmidt lost control of his arms and legs during a practice lap in 2000. In September, Nevada Lieutenant Governor Mark Hutchison awarded Schmidt the first restricted license in the country to drive a semi-autonomous car.One of Schmidt’s sponsors, Arrow Electronics, had modified a 2014 Corvette Z06 with technology that will allow him to control the car without the use of his limbs.The car, aptly nicknamed the Arrow SAM Car  SAM as in semi-autonomous motorcar   is equipped with a voice command system, infrared camera system, a breath manipulation system, GPS technology and 4G-LTE connectivity.Voice commands allow Schmidt to turn the car off and on and change gears.Infrared cameras mounted on the car’s dashboard pick up sensors mounted onto a hat, which Schmidt wears when driving. When Schmidt turns his head, the infrared camera system picks up the motion and translates it into steering. To control acceleration and braking, a sip/puff system has been installed. A breathing apparatus allows Schmidt to accelerate the car by blowing air into a tube. To engage the brakes, Schmidt sucks air out of the tube. Pressure sensors send signals to the car. GPS technology provides additional guidance assistance. Using sensors on the back of the car, the system will keep the car within 1.5 meters of the edge of the road or track. Schmidt has a virtual envelope of about 10 meters wide within which he can steer.An overall safety system ensures that signals sent by Schmidt are properly translated into the car’s movements.The car is also linked to an Arrow 4G-LTE gateway that runs Windows 10 Enterprise on an Intel server. The Arrow 4G-LTE collects, streams and stores API-accessible data in Microsoft’s Azure cloud service.The license requires Schmidt to have a passenger inside the vehicle at all times. As a result, Arrow has equipped the car with a pilot control option that allows the passenger to take over driving if necessary. Additionally, the license calls for a pilot car to be driven in front of the Arrow SAM Car at all times, acting as a barrier between Schmidt and other drivers on the road. In emergency cases where the pilot driver isn’t able to gain control, the Arrow SAM Car could run into the pilot vehicle.Schmidt was able to attain 152 mph in the car at Indianapolis Motor Speedway in May and drove the Pikes Peak International in June.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 20:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/07/3177397/3177397_E10C0170D33F412EB8D0A8E28C2C3D38_161007_3177397_Former_IndyCar_racer_and_quadriplegic_Sam_Schmid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0C0/F56/0C0F5668C68C49348FB23171CEBFA8E0_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Corvette,corvette z06,arrow sam,indycar,Sam Schmidt,verizon indycar,Mark Hutchison,Nevada Lt. Governor Mark Hutchison,Schmidt Peterson Motorsports,motorsports,indy racing,racing,Indianapolis Motor Speedway,driver’s license,semi-autonomous vehicle,semi autonomous vehicle,arrow,arrow sam car,sam car,quadriplegic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3177394</guid>
      <title>Hawaiian bees added to U.S. endangered species list</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The U.S. government has added seven species of Hawaiian bees to the endangered species list, making them the first bee species to be protected under the Endangered Species Act.The seven endangered species of bees are Hylaeus anthracinus, Hylaeus longiceps, Hylaeus assimulans, Hylaeus facilis, Hylaeus hilaris, Hylaeus kuakea and Hylaeus mana. They live in many habits on the Hawaii islands, including coastlines, wet and dry forests and shrublands.According to the Xerces Society, the Hawaiian bees are threatened by urbanization, fire, wild animals such as pigs, and invasive ants and plant species.Bees are disappearing at an alarming rate on the mainland U.S. as well, with 20 to 40 percent of honeybee colonies collapsing every winter, the Science Alert reported.Bees are vital to human beings as they are one of the world’s major pollinators. Without the bees pollinating, about 30 percent of the world’s crops and 90 percent of wild plants would die.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/07/3177394/3177394_61C78CBF3F7F48719777C1344A6F3323_161007_3177394_Hawaiian_bees_added_to_U_S__endangered_species_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/459/75B/45975B364CD449ACA3A32DA776C61F56_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Hawaiian yellow-faced bees,hawaiian bees endangered species,bees endangered,bees colony disappearing in us,us bee colonies,save the bees,endangered species in us]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3174787</guid>
      <title>First aerial survey of Great Pacific Garbage Patch aims to reveal extent of ocean pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Initial results from the first aerial survey of the Great Pacific Garbage Patch suggest that ocean pollution is worse than we thought.The Ocean Cleanup Foundation is conducting a series of aerial surveys over an area of plastic accumulation in the Pacific Ocean between Hawaii and California, according to a news release on its website.Flying at low altitude and low speed, the survey uses Lidar technology to analyse the density and frequency of plastic ocean debris.Recording the presence of debris larger than 0.5 meters by 1.5 meters, the crew found more than 1,000 pieces of plastic during a 2 ½-hour test flight.The survey also aims to document discarded fishing nets known as “ghost nets”, which are difficult to detect and can ensnare marine life.Researchers from the Great Ocean Cleanup said understanding the scope of the problem would help future efforts to remove trash from the Pacific.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 21:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/04/3174787/3174787_1EB625C960124860B819982ECA1C39BD_161004_3174787_First_aerial_survey_of_Great_Pacific_Garbage_Pat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0C3/5F7/0C35F72A82BD47A09BFF79C87ABEE006_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,great pacific garbage patch,great pacific garbage patch aerial view,ocean cleanup,plastic in the ocean,sea pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3174786</guid>
      <title>Researchers develop method to transmit password credentials through the human body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[University of Washington scientists have developed a way to transmit password data using the human body instead of via wireless air transmission.The researchers used the fingerprint technology to transmit data through the body, reported Engadget. They say this could be used to perform security checks such as authentication for door locks.According to Engadget, the technique uses trackpads and smartphone fingerprint sensors to send low-frequency electromagnetic transmissions through the body instead of the air. The researchers note that these on-body transmissions could also be used to send password information to wearable technology. The findings were presented last month in a paper at the 2016 Association for Computing Machinery’s International Joint Conference on Pervasive and Ubiquitous Computing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 21:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/04/3174786/3174786_6DFE4616BDBB40FAB1B53C1F59744976_161004_3174786_Researchers_develop_method_to_transmit_password__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B81/1E2/B811E2D350B84E47AFBBB773D1F205A1_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Hacking the human body,wireless body password,university of washington,passwords hacks,fingerprint security,trackpad security,wifi secure,on-body transmissions,wearable technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3174785</guid>
      <title>Southern California on alert for powerful earthquake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[People across southern California are on heightened alert for a major earthquake this week, reported the Orange County Register, citing officials.More than 200 earthquakes detected in the Salton Sea last week raised concerns a large earthquake may soon strike parts of California.The Salton Sea quakes temporarily raised the chances of a large earthquake occurring between 0.004 percent and one percent, reported the NBC Los Angeles. The chances of it happening are normally between 1 in 6,000. In 2008, experts reportedly came up with a scenario  called the “Big One”  where the San Andreas fault would rupture and the ensuing 7.8 magnitude earthquake would claim 1,800 lives and wound 50,000 people.The San Andreas fault hasn’t ruptured in over three centuries, and scientists say California is long overdue for a major quake, reported the Ventura County Star.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 21:27:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/04/3174785/3174785_F9C21F49CB604412B16871539742E5EC_161004_3174785_Southern_California_on_alert_for_powerful_earthq_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/427/780/427780E32730470B8B724C16E676D64B_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Major earthquake coming,california earthquake,the big one,salton sea earthquake,cali earthquake,san andreas fault line,san andreas earthquake]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3174783</guid>
      <title>The Svalbard Global Seed Vault is built to withstand doomsday</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep inside a mountain on a remote Norwegian island are more than 860,000 varieties of seeds, kept, literally, on ice for preservation should a global catastrophe occur.Carved into rock and ice, the Global Seed Vault is safely buried into the Plataberget Mountain in Svalbard, Norway, not far from the North Pole. Also known as the “doomsday vault,” the facility was created by scientist, conservationist and biodiversity advocate Cary Fowler to safeguard one of the planet’s most vulnerable and valuable resources: plants. The vault is in essence a fail-safe backup system for the world’s seed banks, a last resort for the preservation of plant genealogy. Currently, 864,309 samples are housed in the vault. The plan is to house 4.5 million varieties of crops, with an average of 500 samples of each variety. The vault can hold a maximum total of around 2.5 billion seeds.The vault opened in 2008 and is nearly 394 feet inside the mountain in Svalbard, the furthest north a person can fly on a scheduled flight, making it both remote and accessible. The facility was designed to last 1,000 years and to withstand a range of catastrophes including climate change. The area is geologically stable, with low humidity levels, and is well above sea level, keeping the seeds dry even if the ice caps melt. Permafrost and thick rock ensure that the seed samples will remain frozen at minus 18 degrees Celsius even without power.  The seeds are stored and sealed in custom-made three-ply foil packages, which are sealed inside boxes and stored inside the vault. Seeds are deposited into the vault following strict guidelines. Seeds can only be deposited if they originate from the country of the depositor (genetically modified crops are not allowed) and are shared under the Multilateral System or under Article 15 of the International Treaty on Plant Genetic Resources for Food and Agriculture, which seeks to guarantee future food security. And, like a bank, deposited seeds can only be withdrawn by the depositor. Security at the vault is state of the art and fully automated. There are no full-time staff, and no single person with all the keys necessary for entrance. New seeds are also only accepted a few days a year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 21:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/10/04/3174783/3174783_67B3EF555C0246348F376FEBB2357EF5_161004_3174783_The_Svalbard_Global_Seed_Vault_is_built_to_withs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/9C1/52E/9C152EE97A0C411DB63BFB2607F13639_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Svalbard,norway,seed vault,doomsday vault,life vault,seeds,seed storehouse,norway seed vault,seed vault norway,global seed vault,svalbard global seed vault,global crop diversity trust,food supply,seeds on ice,cary fowler,crop trust,seed bank]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3171873</guid>
      <title>Shipping containers become floating dorms for students in Denmark</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Copenhagen start-up has created an innovative student dormitory that floats on water.The floating student dormitory is called the Urban Rigger. The structure is made of nine containers stacked in two levels on a concrete pontoon, which creates 12 rooms. Each room is a studio setting with bedroom and living room areas.The structure has an open-air courtyard in the middle and storage zones and a laundry room in the basement. It uses sustainable technologies such as solar panels and hydro source heating to provide energies. The rent for one room will be roughly about $600 per month, which is a bargain in Copenhagen. Urban Rigger has already received over 3,000 applications from students who are interested in living on water.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 20:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/30/3171873/3171873_AD6ED7266B854CA2AF1B706866AD3288_160930_3171873_Shipping_containers_become_floating_dorms_for_st_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/40A/469/40A469DFE9F64B4F8FA39901F4282923_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Urban rigger,shipping containers become floating dorms,floating dorms in copenhagen,copenhagen urban rigger,containers turn into dorms,innovation,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3171864</guid>
      <title>How China&#x2019;s Qiantang River Silver Dragon tidal bore is formed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[On the eighth month of the lunar calendar, tourists and locals have flocked to China’s Qiantang River to witness, possibly the largest tidal bore, known as the Silver Dragon.Waves have surged up the river as high as 30 feet tall. Throughout the years, many, who attempt to get close to the monstrous wave, have been swept away and even injured. Not all rivers experience tidal bores and not all have surges as large as that of the Qiantang river.Tidal bores form along a coast where a river empties into the ocean or sea.  According to National Geographic, generally tidal bores form in rivers, like the Qiantang River, that are fairly shallow and narrow narrow until it meets the sea, where its estuary, is large and flat. The Qiantang River’s estuary, the Hangzhou Bay, has the added bonus of being triangular allowing it to act like a funnel, which intensifies the Silver Dragon. When the gravitational pull of a full or new moon raises the water level at the river’s mouth especially high, it triggers a wave that is funneled upstream.While most tidal bores can be predicted, the Silver Dragon rolled in on Sept. 18 this year, one day earlier than usual. Due to Typhoon Meranti and Malakas, the tidal bore this year is higher than those of previous years. According to the South China Morning Post, one man was knocked unconscious by the wave and pushed 16 feet before being rescued.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 20:42:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/30/3171864/3171864_E6082A5A9EE14D748AFD0D409BA3C995_160930_3171864_How_China___s_Qiantang_River_Silver_Dragon_tidal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1EF/892/1EF892F1652E4C11AD654594ABF996EB_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Tidal bore,tidal bores,qiantang river,haining city,china,largest tidal bore,china tidal bore,qiantang river tidal bore,science,waves,coastal waters,positive surge,surges,river,rivers,bore tide,hangzhou bay,surfing,river surfing,qiantang river surfing,the silver dragon,silver dragon,silver dragon tidal bore]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3171857</guid>
      <title>Tesla&#x2019;s Cabin Overheat Protection will keep your kids and pets safe overheating</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Electric car company Tesla has released its version 8.0 update on Thursday morning.According to Tesla’s newsletter, this is biggest UI revamp since the launch of the Model S, this update comes with various updates, from media player, maps, upgraded autopilot system, and a new function called “Cabin Overheat Protection”. The “Cabin Overheat Protection” function is designed to prevent heat stroke death of children and pets in vehicles. This new feature will automatically turn on the vehicle’s ventilation and air conditioning system when the temperature rises to 105 degrees fahrenheit, although at this stage, the function will only activate 12 hours after a driver leaves the vehicle. According to Elon Musk’s twitter updates, the next version of update will include user-definable maximum and minimum temperature function.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/30/3171857/3171857_2A6FF60236A04B16A8F2B18E6633D1C4_160930_3171857_Tesla___s_Cabin_Overheat_Protection_will_keep_yo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EF4/52F/EF452FD59BC0452A82D4D26D2906754F_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Tesla,cabin overheat protection,electric car,tesla update,Elon Musk,Palo Alto,California]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3170891</guid>
      <title>Kellogg recalls eggo waffles due to possible listeria contamination</title>
      <description><![CDATA[American cereal foods maker Kellogg announced a recall of approximately 10,000 cases of Eggo Nutri-Grain Whole Wheat Waffles in 25 states across the United States on Monday due to potential risks of listeria contamination.Listeria monocytogenes bacteria is commonly found in soil and water. Vegetables can become contaminated from the soil; animals can carry the bacteria without appearing ill and can infect meat and dairy products.The bacteria inside the food can spread to the processing facility and can survive there for years, where they can multiply and contaminate other foods that come through the same facility. It can even survive being frozen and can spread to the freezer where the contaminated food is stored.People consume food with listeria monocytogenes would be infected with the bacteria, which would spread beyond the gastrointestinal tract and cause infections such as fever and muscle aches.Listeria outbreak isn’t uncommon in the U.S. In May, CRF Frozen Foods announced a nationwide recall of  almost 360 frozen fruits and vegetables over listeria contamination. Famous ice cream brand Blue Bell recalled its products everywhere after a large listeria outbreak in 2015.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 20:18:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/29/3170891/3170891_5F807D16842B4EA5BD526FFEC853DFDE_160929_3170891_Kellogg_recalls_eggo_waffles_due_to_possible_lis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E4D/4BB/E4D4BBC40AF84AB889AE31F1AD6BF402_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Listeria outbreak,listeria contamination,kellogg recall,kellogg recalls eggo waffle,eggo waffle recall,food safety,us food contamination]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3170888</guid>
      <title>UPS tests drone delivery of medicine in Massachusetts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Package delivery company UPS partnered with drone-maker CyPhy Works to conduct a test delivery using a drone last Thursday.The drone used in the test delivery was CyPhy Works’ Persistent Aerial Reconnaissance and Communications system (PARC). It flew three miles over the Atlantic Ocean from Beverly, Massachusetts to Children’s Island, where it successfully delivered an asthma inhaler to a child at the camp. The PARC drone is battery-powered and equipped with night vision. It also features secure communications system, preventing information from being intercepted or disrupted.“Drone technology used in this way can save lives and deliver products and services to places that are difficult to reach by traditional transit infrastructures, ” Helen Greiner, the founder and chief technology officer of CyPhy Works said in a press release.Greiner told NBC49.com that the drones are not going to replace delivery trucks.The United States Federal Aviation Administration’s rules for commercial use of drones officially took effect last month, which include a number of restrictions on commercial drone operations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 20:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/29/3170888/3170888_38C7674FDB264E07AF7E3D4C27059226_160929_3170888_UPS_tests_drone_delivery_of_medicine_in_Massachu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EC0/D2B/EC0D2B32B5E0413A961292F28873B73B_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Ups tests drone delivery,Cyphy Works drones,UPS drone delivery of medicine,UPS drone delivery,drone delivery,technology,drone delivery to Children’s island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3170886</guid>
      <title>Google self-driving car involved in serious car crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Google’s self-driving Lexus SUV has been involved in a serious car crash last Friday with its front right door completely smashed.The crash took place at the intersection of Phyllis Avenue and El Camino Real in Mountain View, California.The traffic light was green for at least 6 seconds before its self-driving car entered the intersection, Google said in a statement, stressing that its vehicle was not at-fault. Soon after, another car travelling westbound on El Camino Real ran a red light and crashed into the right side of the self-driving car. No one was hurt in the accident. Apart from Mountain view, Google is testing its fleet of 58 self-driving cars in three other locations including Kirkland, Phoenix and Austin.Google had boasted its zero at-fault accident history until one of its self-driving Lexus SUV stuck a bus in February this year, breaking its perfect record.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 20:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/29/3170886/3170886_114553E0CD4B449EAD3A4715D595574D_160929_3170886_Google_self_driving_car_involved_in_serious_car__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/0EE/3D6/0EE3D60724C346179C344D72F9C5FEDE_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Google self-driving car accident,google self-driving suv accident,self-driving car accident,google car accident,mountain view,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3170885</guid>
      <title>NASA study discovers Mercury is shrinking and experiences seismic activity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[New research from NASA suggests that Mercury is shrinking and experiences seismic activity, joining Earth as the solar system’s other tectonically active planet.Prior to crashing on Mercury, NASA’s MErcury Surface, Space ENvironment, GEochemistry, and Ranging (MESSENGER) spacecraft photographed the planet’s surface for the 18 months, reported Space.com, and found long cliffs. These cliffs, or scarps, suggests Mercury may experience seismic activity.The researchers expect that seismic activity on Mercury is similar to the moon’s. The moon is a natural satellite, not a planet.According to Space.com, the planet is still hot enough to keep contracting and have a molten outer core. That same core has helped sustain Mercury’s magnetic field for billions of years.The findings, published in the October issue of Nature Geoscience, was managed by the John Hopkins University Physics Laboratory and funded by NASA.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 20:14:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/29/3170885/3170885_E78E73542F814806ABA5D36D990F3B93_160929_3170885_NASA_study_discovers_Mercury_is_shrinking_and_ex_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CE3/00D/CE300DFE996949E1B835872EDFCE706F_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,NASA mercury,Mercury is shrinking,mercuryquakes,earthquakes on mercury,mercury getting smaller,planet mercury,nasa mercury,messenger nasa mercury,Earth mercury,mercury,moonquakes,mercury and the moon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3170883</guid>
      <title>First baby born with DNA from three parents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A team from the New Hope Fertility Center in New York has created the world’s first three-person baby.New Scientist reports that a 5-month old baby boy was conceived via a new method that uses his birth parents’ DNA, along with that of a second woman.The technique was used to avoid passing on his Jordanian mother’s mitochondrial genes, which carried the DNA associated with Leigh Syndrome. The fatal genetic disorder, which affects the brain, muscles, and nerves of developing infants, had already led to the deaths of the couple’s two previous children.New Hope doctors, led by Dr. John Zhang, used a procedure called the spindle nuclear transfer, which involved taking out the nucleus of the donor egg and replacing it with the mother’s, according to the research published in Fertility and Sterility.The resulting egg, a hybrid containing the mother’s nuclear DNA and the donor’s mitochondrial DNA is then fertilized by the father’s sperm.Five embryos were created using the procedure, but only one developed normally. It was implanted in the mother’s uterus, and the baby was born nine months later.Dr. Zhang later tested the boy’s genes, and found that less than 1 percent carry his mother’s mutation  too low to cause any problems.The controversial method has not been approved in the U.S., so the team had to travel to Mexico to perform it there. A similar procedure is legally approved in the UK, though it involves fertilizing both eggs before swapping the nucleus.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 20:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/29/3170883/3170883_F8F832F8491149FBBE3CC5C8261F64A2_160929_3170883_First_baby_born_with_DNA_from_three_parents_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5C5/309/5C5309EEC28944F88CBE48AC065E03FF_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Three person baby,three parent baby,spindle nuclear transfer,artificial conception,in vitro fertilization,leigh syndrome,genetic disorder,genetic mutation,fertility technique]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3170882</guid>
      <title>Norwegian researchers have taught horses to communicate with people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers in Norway have made a breakthrough in an animal cognition study, using symbols to help horses communicate their level of comfort to humans. In the study published in the journal Applied Animal Behaviour Science, 23 horses were put through a range of hot, cold, and warm temperatures, and given three options to select from based on what they were experiencing. If the horses nudged the board with the horizontal line, they were communicating they felt cold and were asking for their blanket to be applied. If the horses nudged the board with the vertical line, they were communicating they felt hot and were asking for their blanket to be removed. If the horses nudged a board with no symbol on it, they were communicating they felt fine as is. Horses were given a carrot for making the correct choices.It was clear whether the horses were choosing the symbols that corresponded with their comfort, as they were either covered in thick blankets, which made them obviously hot, or taken outside in freezing weather which would call for them to demand a blanket. The horses learned to provide their preferences after only 14 days of 10-15 minutes of training each day.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 20:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/29/3170882/3170882_A61A8691E8E54876B05051721E0BFF25_160929_3170882_Norwegian_researchers_have_taught_horses_to_comm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/567/402/5674027EC663490CAC2C6A0601F787E5_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Horse communication,horses norway,Norwegian Veterinary Institute,animal cognition,horse speaks,horse talks,horse blanket,horse study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3170880</guid>
      <title>Roller coasters can help pass kidney stones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Michigan State University urologist has discovered that riding on a specific type of roller coaster could help people pass kidney stones.“Basically, I had patients telling me that after riding a particular roller coaster at Walt Disney World, they were able to pass their kidney stone.I even had one patient say he passed three different stones after riding multiple times,” David Wartinger, a professor emeritus in the Department of Osteopathic Surgical Specialties told the Science Daily.Wartinger conducted with experiment with kidney stones smaller than the size of 4 mm filled in a 3D model of a hollow kidney. After riding at the Big Thunder Mountain roller coaster at the theme park for 20 times, the stones were successfully passed.He told the Science Daily that a roller coaster which is rough and quick with some twists and turns could successfully help patients to pass their kidney stones, whereas roller coasters that are too fast with upside down or inverted movements would not have the same effect.Furthermore, sitting in the front of the roller coaster only has about 16% success rate of passing the kidney stones while sitting in the last car of the ride increases the rate to 64%.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 20:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/29/3170880/3170880_E57EA2A66A9C46F5959745D8796B8B75_160929_3170880_Roller_coasters_can_help_pass_kidney_stones_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/1DF/324/1DF3246621B942C0A02EB95167A28EE0_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Roller coasters pass kidney stones,big thunder mountain passes kidney stones,new kidney stone treatment,roller coaster and kidney stones,health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3166913</guid>
      <title>California introduces new laws to restrict air pollutants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[California announced new bills earlier this month to restrict environmental pollutants damaging to the air. Under the new laws announced on September 19, carbon emissions stemming from diesel trucks will be reduced by 50 percent. Dairy farmers have been instructed to reduce methane emissions from the state’s 5.15 million cows by 40 percent by the year 2030.Farmers will receive funding from the state to invest in methane digesters, to convert the pollutants from manure into energy to be sold to electrical utilities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 15:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/24/3166913/3166913_169BB47EE96F4FB4ADC6B32B8A639025_160924_3166913_California_introduces_new_laws_to_restrict_air_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/49A/589/49A589823BBD48F1A12DC0BA25163635_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,California energy,cow methane,methane digester,black carbon,carbon emissions,jerry brown,methane gas,california carbon laws]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3166834</guid>
      <title>How Samsung, Apple and Sony make water-resistant phones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Samsung, Apple and Sony all boast a water-resistant feature on their new phones.The phones, Samsung’s Galaxy s7, Apple’s iPhone 7 and Sony’s Xperia XZ, are all designed with similar tricks to prevent water from damaging the the internal circuitry.However, the phones are water resistant, not waterproof. This means they are able to resist some water penetration but not entirely. The developers achieve water resistancy by creating a seal around each phone’s components. Like an egg boiling in water, if a small hole is created in its shell, its internal structure is compromised. The most common seal used is tacky black adhesive that usually attaches the screen to the chassis. The same adhesive is used on circuits near exposed ports.Developers also utilized rubber gaskets, plastic O-rings, around buttons, ports and trays.Silicone rubber boots further help seal buttons. The rubber separates the buttons users push from the components inside.And tiny mesh screens or breathable fabric membranes are used to regulate airflow while keeping water out of speakers by playing on water’s natural cohesion and surface tension properties.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 15:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/24/3166834/3166834_77F8FE4C535443A598016A152DB7A832_160924_3166834_How_Samsung__Apple_and_Sony_make_water_resistant_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/015/5A1/0155A131DF544C5181638406A15A9D82_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Iphone,samsung,iphone 7,samsung 7,galaxy,galaxy 7,samsung s7,samsung galaxy,galaxy s7,water resistant,waterproof,phones,cell phones,iphone 7 water resistant,iphone 7 waterproof,samsung s7 water resistant,samsung s7 waterproof,galaxy s7 water resistant,galaxy s7 waterproof,sony xperia xz,experia xz,sony xperia xz waterproof,sony experia xz water resistant,sony]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3166075</guid>
      <title>Researchers develop new ways to fight superbugs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered two new ways to fight superbugs.Currently, the only treatment for bacterial infections is through the use of antibiotics. Antibiotics release antimicrobial polymers into the body that kill bacteria. Different antibiotics are designed to kill different bacteria in different ways, but all antibiotics must first be absorbed into the bacteria. Once the antimicrobial polymer passes through the bacterial cellular wall, the polymer can go to work to kill the bacteria.  However, bacteria over time can mutate to protect themselves against antibiotics. The most common mutation is the development of an efflux pump, which expel antimicrobial polymers that make it past the bacterial cellular wall before they’re able to cause damage. These immune bacteria have become known as superbugs.Researchers at UT Southwestern Medical Center in Texas have discovered a synthetic compound that blocks efflux pumps, making superbugs once again vulnerable. And researchers at the University of Melbourne in Australia have created a new form of antibiotic. They have developed a star-shaped peptide polymer that fights bacteria in more than one way, one of which is by ripping apart the bacterial cellular wall. This makes it difficult for superbugs to become resistant.The polymer is also nontoxic. A person would have to take 100 times the dosage rate of the star-shaped polymer for it to become toxic.Both methods still need to be refined and both research teams are still working towards human trials.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/23/3166075/3166075_984DB9177C2B405DA1105A10051442C3_160923_3166075_Researchers_develop_new_ways_to_fight_superbugs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E0B/705/E0B70563B5BE4CE2BF097B83E4A53F45_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Antibiotics,bacteria,health,illness,polymer,science,superbug,superbugs,University Of Melbourne,ut southwestern medical center,killing superbugs,peptide polymers,antimicrobials,polymers,UT southwestern medical center,university of melbourne. University of texas,university of texas southwestern medical center,drug-resistant bacteria,antibiotic resistant,synthetic compounds,synthetic drug]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3166057</guid>
      <title>Self-driving boats to sail Amsterdam canals by 2017</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In a collaboration with researchers at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), the Amsterdam Institute for Advanced Metropolitan Solutions (AMS Institute) is currently developing autonomous boats.Roboat is the first large-scale research project that will put self-driving boats on water as early as 2017. The first prototype, a flatbed, six-by-six-foot design was created for basic transportation of people and goods through Amsterdam’s many canals. The flatbed boats can also be utilized as on-demand bridges or water stages, easily assembled within hours to relieve traffic congestion.Researchers are also looking at other designs that could assist in underwater research, detecting waterborne diseases at an early stage. The Roboats also have potential to help clean canal waters by picking up floating debris or waste.The project is currently being backed with $27 million and researchers are hoping the autonomous boats can be utilized in cities across the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/23/3166057/3166057_6A5C1E0563824E7AA88CE917A7559408_160923_3166057_Self_driving_boats_to_sail_Amsterdam_canals_by_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/7AF/DB3/7AFDB3B4C077467EA20B98DF71F625C9_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Roboats,robot boats,self driving,self driving boats,self driving vehicles,ams institute,amsterdam,autonomous,autonomous boats,canals,waterways,research,science,technology,boats,transportation,MIT,Massachusetts Institute of Technology,Amsterdam Institute for Advanced Metropolitan Solutions,AMS Institute]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3166055</guid>
      <title>Newly discovered Mayaro virus in Haiti could be the next Zika</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A mosquito-born virus named Mayaro that experts fear may have as big a global health impact as Zika, has been discovered in Haiti.On January 8, 2015, an 8-year-old boy went to the school clinic for fever and abdominal pain and was diagnosed typhoid. After checking his blood sample, it was found that he had been infected with Mayaro virus.Mayaro virus is a single-stranded positive RNA virus, mainly transmitted by Haemagogus mosquitoes, but Aedes aegypti mosquitoes, known carrier of Zika virus, may also be vectors. Symptoms of mayaro includes abdominal pain and joint pain, which can last for as long as a year.The virus was first discovered in Trinidad in 1954. It was then spread to French Guiana, Suriname, Venezuela, Peru, Bolivia and Brazil.Little is known about the Mayaro virus at the moment. Doctors in Florida warn that the virus may pose future threats.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/23/3166055/3166055_D853C9BB39B04A04AE11DBF34BC391A5_160923_3166055_Newly_discovered_Mayaro_virus_in_Haiti_could_be__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/10D/5A4/10D5A4F683034376B13A81E05703D90D_1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Mayaro virus,mayaro virus in haiti,zika virus,zika outbreak,mosquito-borne virus,health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3166051</guid>
      <title>Researchers produce mice embryos from non-egg cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists at the University of Bath in the U.K. have made a discovery that they say challenges almost two centuries of knowledge on fertilization. It is widely thought that mammals could only be born from an egg fertilized with sperm, but this discovery, published in the journal Nature Communication, bypasses that entirely.According to a University of Bath article on the study, researchers used chemicals to “trick” mouse eggs into developing as if they’d been fertilized. This produced parthenogenotes, an embryo that dies after a few days.At this point the embryos had a half set of chromosomes and were in the stages of cell division, notes an NHS report. It’s here that researchers injected them with sperm. These embryos were then inserted into female mice and the process produced 30 mouse pups with a success rate of around one in four.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/23/3166051/3166051_61F736C95B5A415880A49AF811AC8AE3_160923_3166051_Researchers_produce_mice_embryos_from_non_egg_ce_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5F6/C0C/5F6C0C5AFDB24843BB88DDB99AF7F5F7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Experiments on mice,fertilization experiments,fertilization no egg,fertilization research,university of bath,skipping fertilization,tricking embryos,chromosome]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3166050</guid>
      <title>Global Fishing Watch uses digital monitoring to curb illegal fishing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Tech-environmentalist group SkyTruth, non-profit organization Oceana, and Google have unveiled Global Fishing Watch, a free tool that allows people to track fishing activity worldwide, in a bid to curb the exploitation of marine life.A press release on the Google Maps blog explains that the system uses radio signals emitted by large vessels through the Automatic Identification System, or AIS. Satellites and other terrestrial antenna pick up the signals and store them in a database.An algorithm applied to the data uses vessel movements to determine what type of ship and fishing gear are being utilized. Ship positions are delayed by 72 hours, but can be tracked from as far back as January of 2012.Information is displayed on an interactive Google Earth map, and includes each country’s exclusive economic zones and protected areas, as well as the individual records and identities of more than 35,000 fishing boats.Users need only to have an internet connection to access the free data and remotely monitor any ships that could be fishing illegally.The system is far from perfect. Smaller vessels that don’t require the use of the Automatic Identification System or AIS can’t be tracked, according to Scientific American. The AIS itself can report false locations when tampered with by a crew trying to mask illegal activities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 17:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/23/3166050/3166050_DE7D21A2152E4C2A948BAF8A10AFB2CE_160923_3166050_Global_Fishing_Watch_uses_digital_monitoring_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/625/02C/62502C32F8C94E16928009216ECE871E_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Global fishing watch,illegal fishing,data mining,crowd spying,watchdog,ocean advocacy,environment,skytruth,oceana,google,google earth,leonardo di caprio]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3165891</guid>
      <title>China says Tiangong-1 spacecraft will fall to Earth next year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[China says its first space lab Tiangong-1 will likely fall back to Earth in the second half of 2017, which seems to confirm speculation that it has already lost control of the spacecraft.Tiangong-1 spacecraft is currently orbiting Earth at an altitude of 370 km, which is about 30 km lower than the orbit of the International Space Station. It was launched in September 2011 and has stopped sending data back to Earth since March this year.“Based on our calculation and analysis, most parts of the space lab will burn up during falling,” Wu Ping, deputy director of the manned space engineering office said in a press conference.However, satellite tracker Thomas Dorman thinks such statement has confirmed his view that China has lost control of Tiangong-1 and the country will only inform the world at the very last minute, Space.com reported.According to Xinhua News, China will continue to monitor Tiangong-1 and send out warnings for possible collisions with objects and report internationally if necessary.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 14:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/23/3165891/3165891_D90DB7BC2CC74A9FAE92A125DF946370_160923_3165891_China_says_Tiangong_1_spacecraft_will_fall_to_Ea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/6D8/19C/6D819CD6A3E14857BBDB1E8874858B39_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,China tiangong-1,tiangong-1 fall back to earth,tiangong-1 space lab,tiangong-1 spacecraft,china space industry,china space lab,china space station,space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3163687</guid>
      <title>Amazon is building a gigantic wind farm in Texas to power America</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Amazon Wind Farm Texas is underway. The diameter of each wind turbine will be two times as long as the wingspan of a Boeing 747 plane. The farm in Scurry County, West Texas will be comprised of more than 100 wind turbines in total. The wind turbines will generate an estimated 100,000 megawatt hours of wind energy every year, enough to power close to 90,000 homes in the United States.This latest development by the company, along with four other clean energy projects, will result in 2.6 million megawatt hours each year, powering more than 240,000 homes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 20:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/20/3163687/3163687_3A218DB09F1F46EBB0DEE684795B0504_160920_3163687_Amazon_is_building_a_gigantic_wind_farm_in_Texas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E13/9B4/E139B4987D5F4EFCAD2E47BC50988298_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Amazon wind farm,amazon wind turbines,wind turbines,amazon renewable energy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3163614</guid>
      <title>Scientists propose using lasers to clean up space junk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[German scientists have proposed using laser pulses to clean up small, irregular shaped space debris.The study was published by SPIE, the international society for optics and photonics. The authors propose using high-energy laser pulses to change the orbit of the debris, leading it to re-enter and burn-up in the atmosphere."Laser damage is usually considered to be a negative phenomenon, but this paper considers a significant positive application of laser-induced damage. In this study, the damage produced by laser beams serves a highly useful and positive purpose by cleaning up the space around Earth," Vitaly Gruzdev of University of Missouri commented in a press release.According to NASA, there are nearly 3,000 tons of space debris in the low-Earth orbit. Most spacecraft can be protected from debris up to 1 cm in diameter, thanks to Whipple Shields. However, debris between 1 to 10 cm in size are particularly dangerous as they cannot be dodged or blocked. Space debris can travel at speeds up to 28,000 kph, which is fast enough for a small piece to damage satellite or a spacecraft.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 19:18:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/20/3163614/3163614_677FB102D12143CF89FEDD4F9ECB2D59_160920_3163614_Scientists_propose_using_lasers_to_clean_up_spac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/54E/26B/54E26BFD9B4A44F49E32632E9A3A8CC1_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Space debris,space junk,clean up space debris with laser,laser broom,space,nasa,german aerospace center,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3163603</guid>
      <title>Anti-drone system SkyDronder protects against surveillance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Singaporean company has designed an anti-drone surveillance system that protect one’s privacy and safety against invading drones.The SkyDroner is an anti-drone surveillance system that can detect drone activities within 1km radius. It has multiple sensors that allow it to identify the characteristics of an anonymous drone, such as its model.“The increase in recreational drone activities in the past two years has sparked concern of drone invasion in the airspace,” Robyn Tay, the founder of the SkyDroner, told CNBC.The SkyDroner can also distract and take over the command of the drone’s radio frequencies, such as sending it back to its operator or making it land at a designated location.According to CNBC, the system is intended to be used by places such as police departments, defense departments and airports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 19:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/20/3163603/3163603_C9FD8AA7E87C49E0B69C413055C53A39_160920_3163603_Anti_drone_system_SkyDronder_protects_against_su_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BEB/E24/BEBE2422F90A43BAB96D89FED80F703B_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Skydroner,anti-drone surveillance,drones,drone surveillance,skydroner500,skydroner1000,technology,surveillance,planet drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3161534</guid>
      <title>Self-driving maglev vehicle can also be a living room</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Canadian company has released an innovative idea that expands the concept of self-driving cars into self-driving rooms.The self-driving room is known as Tridika. It is co-developed by Charles Bombardier and his company Imaginactive and Ashish Thulkar, a vehicle designer at the Indian Institute of Science.The Tridika can be configured into a car-setting or an office, depending on the user’s liking. It is completely driverless and works like a maglev train, with the magnets elevates and propels the box.It would become attached to the other wall of the building by a ramp, which lifts it up in front of the user’s apartment unit. The door of the apartment unit would open once detects the Tridika.There’s no known date or plan for whether this concept would become a reality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 15:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/17/3161534/3161534_DE49404D08BD40648AA69F42D054D840_160917_3161534_Self_driving_maglev_vehicle_can_also_be_a_living_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/17F/738/17F738E9D869416296C432BA32F03AE3_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Tridika,self-driving rooms,self-driving living room,self-driving cars,technology,future technology,imaginactive,science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3161034</guid>
      <title>World&#x2019;s first large-scale tidal energy farm to be installed in Scotland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The world’s first large-scale tidal energy farm will soon be installed off the Scottish coast.Four turbines, measuring up to 16 meters tall with 8-meter-long blades will be installed  off the northern coast of Scotland between Caithness and Orkney in the initial phase of the project.“I am incredibly proud of Scotland’s role in leading the way in tackling climate change and investment in marine renewables is a hugely important part of this,” the Guardian quoted Nicola Sturgeon, the First Minister of Scotland as saying.According to the Guardian, developer Atlantis Resources hopes to install a total of 269 turbines, a move that could provide energy for 175,000 homes. According to the Scottish Government, the country holds one quarter of the Europe’s offshore wind resources.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 19:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/16/3161034/3161034_3EFA26B2878E4533B601897E4F22EC22_160916_3161034_World___s_first_large_scale_tidal_energy_farm_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8BF/065/8BF0656F7B8A42529C3B74F6B3B47695_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Meygen project,meygen scotland tidal power,atlantis resources ar1500,ar1500 turbines,tidal energy,tidal power,scottish tidal power,tidal energy farm scotland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3161030</guid>
      <title>Walmart develops self-driving shopping carts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Walmart has received a patent last week for its self-driving shopping carts system.According to the US Patent & Trademark Office, the shopping carts will be equipped with detachable motors with video cameras and sensors. Customers can request a cart using a user interface device, potentially a smartphone.Supermarket employees usually have to round up abandoned carts. With the new system, the carts will be able to return to the docking station automatically. The carts can also be used to restock products that are low in stock.It is not yet known when or where the new system will be applied in Walmart supermarkets.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 19:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/16/3161030/3161030_4381F5EF63BE4A89AD04991FDE6FD432_160916_3161030_Walmart_develops_self_driving_shopping_carts_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EED/7BB/EED7BB206C1041FCB6F29D61CE8FAB58_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Walmart,walmart self-driving shopping carts,self-driving shopping carts,walmart robotic shopping carts,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3160308</guid>
      <title>China to launch Tiangong-2 space station next week</title>
      <description><![CDATA[China will send its second space lab, Tiangong-2 into space next week, as part of its plan to field a manned space station that is expected to be in service around 2022.According to CCTV America, Tiangong-2 will orbit 393 kilometers above the earth. The Shenzhou 11 spacecraft, carrying two astronauts, will dock with Tiangong-2 in October. The cargo ship Tianzhou-1 will dock with Tiangong-2 next year to resupply the space station.Tiangong-2 is expected to monitor the earth while conducting conducting scientific experiments. It will also measure the topography of the oceans in order to study earth’s gravitational field, the TeCake reported.China’s first space laboratory, Tiangong-1, was launched in 2011 and has been in good working condition ever since.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/15/3160308/3160308_F24602DFC2C64AC8B332EA1C319D9AD7_160915_3160308_China_to_launch_Tiangong_2_space_station_next_we_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/A13/058/A13058BC711B45DB8C1AD7254542CDA2_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,tiangong-2,tiangong-1,shenzhou-11,tianzhou-1,china,chinese space station,space,space station]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3160306</guid>
      <title>New York to reintroduce 50,000 oysters to Jamaica Bay with the help of recycled toilets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[New York has teamed up with the Billion Oyster Project to embed 50,000 oysters in Jamaica Bay with the use of recycled toilets.The New York/New Jersey Harbor Estuary was once filled with oysters, but due to over harvesting, dredging and pollution, the bivalves died out in the area.Oysters are considered keystone species. A single oyster can filter as much as 50 gallons of water a day, removing chemicals and other pollutants. And oyster reefs stabilize shorelines, prevent erosion and act as a buffer against hurricanes and tropical storms.New York City and the Billion Oyster project will build one central donor oyster bed with 50,000 adult and spat-on-shell oysters, along with four receiver beds. Oysters normally embed themselves on old shells. With oysters extinct in the harbor for sometime, officials are utilizing a mixture of introduced oyster and clam shells along with old toilets, broken into small pieces, to help create a foundation on which new oysters will cling  at least for the four smaller beds.Once the oyster installation is complete, water quality will be monitored for future improvements. The beds will also be evaluated for the recruitment of new oysters. The project is being funded with a $1 million grant from the U.S. Department of Interior, administered by the National Fish and Wildlife Foundation. New York City’s Department of Environmental Protection is contributing $375,000. The Billion Oyster Project and students from the Urban Assembly New York Harbor School are assisting with the installation and monitoring of the oyster beds.The project is coordinated by the New York Harbor School and aims to restore one billion live oysters to New York harbor by 2030.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/15/3160306/3160306_2AA17E3D371F45F38AAF093BC7841646_160915_3160306_New_York_to_reintroduce_50_000_oysters_to_Jamaic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/EE2/B29/EE2B299FF7B54FBA943E33ABFF985F42_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,New york,jamaica bay,oyster,oysters,oyster farm,oyster habitat,oyster rehabilitation,billion oyster project,Bill de Blasio,Department of Environmental Protection,oyster beds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3159585</guid>
      <title>NEW YORK FIRE DEPARTMENT TO DEPLOY DRONES</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The New York City Fire Department is currently testing out drones to help firefighters on the ground get a better look at how to fight fires before sending in humans. The $85,000 drones, painted fire-engine red, weigh roughly eight pounds. The drones can move in the up and down directions, and can toggle 360 degrees to adjust viewpoint. They will each have a 200 foot tether attached so as to prevent them from getting stuck in trees. From high up in the sky, they can capture both standard video and infrared images, which are then transmitted to a portable command center on the ground, so firefighters can see what they’re up against. It takes two firefighters to operate each drone -- a pilot to man the controls, and an observer to keep the area clear. The first drone will be deployed in the coming weeks, followed by two more before the end of the year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 20:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/14/3159585/3159585_B74603E6581947A0A3FE958AA378D81D_160914_3159585_NEW_YORK_FIRE_DEPARTMENT_TO_DEPLOY_DRONES_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/938/BEA/938BEAB8690D4CBEAD68F5402467DB24_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,NYFD drone,firefighting drones,drone fire,New York drones,best drone footage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3159540</guid>
      <title>Scientists record dolphins having a conversation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[For decades, we’ve known dolphins were one of the more intelligent species on the planet, but new research may reveal they share a level of communication similar to our own. At the Karadag Nature Reserve in Russian-held Crimea, scientists used an underwater microphone to record the speech patterns between two Black Sea bottlenose dolphins. Expressing themselves with a series of whistles and clicks, the subjects, Yasha and Yana, were found to adjust the volume and frequency of each sound, forming individual words and sentences.In addition, the researchers also noticed the dolphins would take turns speaking, waiting for each other to finish their messaging without interruption, which may indicate they were listening.Yasha and Yana were found to create sentences of up to five words, though they have not deciphered the content of the conversations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 20:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/14/3159540/3159540_8145EE0BD11248B2B62DE58031FBE61F_160914_3159540_Scientists_record_dolphins_having_a_conversation_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/E81/D8F/E81D8F03CCC84E72AE9559D9374CDDE6_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Dolphin conversations,dolphins talking,dolphins communicating,Karadag Nature Reserve,black sea bottlenose dolphins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3159508</guid>
      <title>Indonesia repatriates 200 Vietnamese detained for illegal fishing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Indonesia has been waging a war on illegal fishing since 2014, claiming the practice negatively impacts the local economy.The Wall Street Journal reports that the country has seized and destroyed more than 170 trespassing foreign boats. The vessels are often blown up as part of the crackdown, in an effort to prevent precious ocean resources from being taken.In recent years, a growing number of Vietnamese nationals have been fishing illegally in Indonesian waters, according to the Vietnam News Agency.Three hundred and twelve fishermen have been arrested and are currently being detained, though around 200 will soon be repatriated back to Vietnam.Both countries are reportedly working together to curb the influx of offenders, which Vietnamese authorities blame on the fishermen’s limited knowledge of geography and the law.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 19:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/14/3159508/3159508_1DABFA85A7C9433FAEA1C9238E0DE2BC_160914_3159508_Indonesia_repatriates_200_Vietnamese_detained_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/81F/B5E/81FB5EC3B82D4348BE79A8F6BE895C3F_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Vietnam illegal fishing,vietnamese fishermen,indonesia illegal fishing,sink the vessel policy,indonesia illegal fishing crackdown,indonesia illegal fishing war]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3159504</guid>
      <title>Blue Origin&#x2019;s escape system launch test could destroy its rocket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Private space company Blue Origin will be conducting its next round of testing on its New Shepard rocket in October.The reusable rocket is designed to take paying passengers to the edge of space. New Shepard consists of a crew capsule that can carry up to six passengers and a rocket booster. Once near its destination, the capsule separates from the booster. The capsule will then deploy its parachutes and sail down back to earth, while the booster will deploy its drag brakes and refire its engine making a vertical landing. Blue Origin has already successfully completed four test flights of its rocket booster. The fifth test to be held at the company’s testing facility in West Texas, near El Paso, will check its emergency escape system during flight.The New Shepard’s capsule is equipped with a rocket motor that will fire for two seconds should the booster fail after launch. The motor will quickly separate the capsule from the booster. Once away, the capsule will undergo its standard descent pattern. Blue Origin has already tested the system on the ground, but has yet to experiment during flight. At about 45 seconds after launch, when the New Shepard is at 16,000 feet up, the company will intentionally start the capsule’s escape sequence.Unfortunately, if the emergency testing succeeds, firing the rocket motor could possibly destroy the rocket booster.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 19:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/14/3159504/3159504_3FB07E153B054C7E9B35C4D5122D905C_160914_3159504_Blue_Origin___s_escape_system_launch_test_could__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/DA3/795/DA379550A3884C25B9344C2A75E593A2_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Blue origin,space,rocket,space travel,blue origin space,blue origin landing,blue origin rocket,blue origin rocket landing,new shepard,blue origin new shepard,blue origin launch and landing,rocket test,escape system,rocket escape system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3159502</guid>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz launches drone delivery cargo van</title>
      <description><![CDATA[German automaker Mercedes-Benz has unveiled an electric van equipped with package delivery drones.The Vision Van is an electric vehicle with a range of up to 270 km. Its rooftop serves as a launch and landing pad for Matternet M2 drones, which can carry a package of 4.4 pounds.All packages are scanned and sorted by robots before loading on to the van by a driverless handling vehicle. The onboard robotic shelving system then automatically locate and prepare the packages for the drone or the driver inside the cargo compartment.The van is installed with innovative algorithms that can calculate the best delivery route for the driver, who would steer the van using a joystick.The company said it will continue to explore the opportunities of innovative van-related business therefore it created a new organisational unit called Future Transportation Systems, which involve research teams in Stuttgart, Berlin and Silicon Valley.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 19:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/14/3159502/3159502_F824DE50EF69480F912826644D1EA963_160914_3159502_Mercedes_Benz_launches_drone_delivery_cargo_van_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/FF8/7AB/FF87AB8CA3C84503A92F23704FED7D37_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Mercedes-benz vision van,vision van,innovative van mercedes-benz,mercedes-benz innovative cars,vision van with drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3158478</guid>
      <title>Chinese company linked to huge aluminum stockpile in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[One of China’s richest men has been linked to a massive stockpile of aluminum in the Mexican desert that U.S. aluminum executives say is part of a scheme to game the global trade system, according to a report in the Wall Street Journal.The stockpile was discovered two years ago when aluminum executive Jeff Henderson hired a pilot to shoot aerial photos of a factory near the town of San Jose Iturbide, 500 miles south of the Mexican border with Texas, the Wall Street Journal reported.There, the pilot found a stockpile of nearly one million metric tons of aluminum, or roughly 6 percent of the world’s total inventory, according to the the Wall Street Journal’s report.Rerouting Chinese aluminum through Mexico into the U.S. allows Chinese companies to benefit from the North American Free Trade Agreement between Canada, Mexico and the U.S., which eliminates most of the tariffs on products traded among the three countries.According to the Wall Street Journal, Chinese billionaire Liu Zhongtian, the chairman of China Zhongwang Holdings, has denied the allegations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/13/3158478/3158478_766ECD8DDA0A4208993C223E6064E4D7_160913_3158478_Chinese_company_linked_to_huge_aluminum_stockpil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F5B/0C5/F5B0C5A4984845B6AAF85C9459A7B511_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Aluminium stockpile in mexico,san jose iturbide aluminium,china aluminium exports,china zhongwang holdings,liu zhongtian,nafta]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3158477</guid>
      <title>Why the Samsung Galaxy Note 7&#x2019;s battery explodes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration has advised passengers not to turn on or charge Samsung Galaxy Note 7 smartphones on aircraft, after faulty battery packs caused some of the phones to explode while charging.Due to the battery crisis, Samsung was forced to recall 2.5 million units of the Galaxy Note 7, its new flagship phablet.The faulty battery packs were made by Samsung SDI, a subsidiary of Samsung. Samsung has indicated it will no longer use Samsung SDI batteries in the Note 7.According to the Wall Street Journal, roughly 65 percent of Galaxy Note 7 batteries were made by Samsung SDI. Thirty-five percent were made by Chinese company Amperex Technology Limited, or ATL.The Samsung SDI batteries in the Note 7 were found to have faulty separators, which allow the two electrodes to touch. This redirects energy to chemicals called electrolytes, which help to conduct the current.When the battery is hot, the electrolytes react with other chemicals to release gas in a feedback loop called “thermal runaway,” which can lead to a fire.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 19:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/13/3158477/3158477_D0AA86F3737748A18D12E53CDD9E1CD7_160913_3158477_Why_the_Samsung_Galaxy_Note_7___s_battery_explod_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5D5/A15/5D5A15BAD5CC40BD97CD16EB0E62C19B_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Samsung galaxy note 7 explodes,galaxy note 7 explosion,samsung smartphone explodes,samsung,samsung sdi batteries,galaxy note 7 batteries,smartphone explodes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3158475</guid>
      <title>Scientists develop new clothing material to help skin stay cool</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists at Stanford University have developed a material that can help the skin stay cooler than conventional fabrics.According to the university, a material known as nanopolyethylene has pores that measure 50 to 1,000 nanometers across. It allows the heat emitted from the body by infrared radiation to pass through while it is also able to reflect 99% of visible light.Cotton clothing, though good at reflecting visible light, only allows 1.5 percent of infrared waves to penetrate, meaning most of the body heat is either absorbed by the fabric or reflected back onto skin. Polyethylene clothing allows infrared waves to penetrate but it also allows most visible light to penetrate as well.Experiments show nanopolyethylene is able to keep the skin much cooler than cotton or polyethylene.“If you can cool the person rather than the building where they work or live, that will save energy,” Yi Cui, associate professor of materials science and engineering at Stanford and of photon science at SLAC National Accelerator Laboratory was quoted in the university's press release.The scientists are working on adding more colors, textures and cloth-like characteristics to the material to make it ready for the textile industry.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 19:58:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/13/3158475/3158475_E0CD11BB877148959EE563E20D965530_160913_3158475_Scientists_develop_new_clothing_material_to_help_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/706/316/7063160C72B84FB0A3F8E16ABDD16E9A_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Stanford university,cool clothing fabric,nanopolyethylene,climate change,clothing material to make body cool,extreme weather]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3156177</guid>
      <title>Google files patent for light-sensing technology to help self-driving cars yield to police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Google has submitted a new patent as part of its self-driving car project for technology that will allow cars to yield to emergency and police vehicles.In the patent that was submitted in 2014, but published earlier this month, Google outlined the need for its self-driving cars to be able to respond appropriately to emergency and police vehicles. Google plans on outfitting its cars with scanners that will be able to detect and identify light sources, colors and patterns. When a Google self-driving car is on the road, one or more computing devices will allow it to detect light and identify if that light is stationary, like that of a street light, or moving, like those on vehicles. It will then determine if the light is flashing. Should the light be both moving and flashing, the Google car will then identify the colors and pattern of flashing lights. Emergency and police vehicles have different light and patterns. Police vehicles also utilize unique patterns for various offenses. Based on the patterns of lights, the Google car can make the appropriate maneuver, such as yielding to an ambulance or stopping completely for a police vehicle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 20:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/10/3156177/3156177_23CA5C0A9D8A459BAA8B408DEC9B91D5_160910_3156177_Google_files_patent_for_light_sensing_technology_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/506/AD3/506AD3064B134844B88245A28156AC0F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Google,google self driving car,self driving car,patent,us patent,us patent and trademark office,police lights,ambulance lights,emergency vehicles,google self driving car project]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3156174</guid>
      <title>Mercedes-Benz launches drone delivery cargo van</title>
      <description><![CDATA[German automaker Mercedes-Benz has unveiled an electric van equipped with package delivery drones.The Vision Van is an electric vehicle with a range of up to 270 km. Its rooftop serves as a launch and landing pad for Matternet M2 drones, which can carry a package of 4.4 pounds.All packages are scanned and sorted by robots before loading on to the van by a driverless handling vehicle. The onboard robotic shelving system then automatically locate and prepare the packages for the drone or the driver inside the cargo compartment.The van is installed with innovative algorithms that can calculate the best delivery route for the driver, who would steer the van using a joystick.The company said it will continue to explore the opportunities of innovative van-related business therefore it created a new organisational unit called Future Transportation Systems, which involve research teams in Stuttgart, Berlin and Silicon Valley.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 20:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/10/3156174/3156174_E762A0E48EDC4D0DA87C63A90EF6D08F_160910_3156174_Mercedes_Benz_launches_drone_delivery_cargo_van_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/307/07D/30707DA0AECD4E7D9D224AC5D34D9EA7_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Mercedes-benz vision van,vision van,innovative van mercedes-benz,mercedes-benz innovative cars,vision van with drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3154905</guid>
      <title>New iPhone ditches the headphone jack, gets telephoto lens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Apple’s new iPhone 7 has many new features including improved battery life, fancy screen, stereo speakers, more memory and a better CPU   but, controversially, no headphone jack. Apple decided to eliminate the traditional headphone jack from the device to free up space for other components. To listen to audio, consumers will need to use the Lightning connector with Lightning earbuds, or an adapter for current headphone jacks.The company is banking on the hope people will buy new Apple AirPods, rechargeable wireless earbuds with a five-hour battery life. The AirPods won’t come with the iPhone 7 and will sell separately for $160   that’s in addition to the $650 or $770 for the base or Plus model.Apple has a history of abandoning older technologies from its products long before the competition, such as its elimination of built-in optical drives from its iMac computers in 2012.According to Forbes, the new iPhone model is water and dust resistant and sports a new 12 megapixel camera. The iPhone 7 Plus camera features dual telephoto and wide-angle lenses.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 13:26:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/09/3154905/3154905_510128CFD15D409F8CA2C0C7022E58F6_160909_3154905_New_iPhone_ditches_the_headphone_jack__gets_tele_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/763/3EE/7633EE31596C43598490A7FDDE7A8BB7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Iphone 7,i phone 7 launch,iphone 7 headphone jack,iphone 7 telephoto lens,iphone 7 camera,apple kills the headphone jack,wireless headphones,apple,san francisco]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3152520</guid>
      <title>British navy tests speedboat spy drone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RESTRICTIONS: NONE For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twAn experimental robot speedboat drone was unveiled by the British navy in tests on London’s River Thames on Monday.The prototype Maritime Autonomy Surface Testbed (MAST) drone can be sailed by a pilot, remote control or be programmed to operate on its own, the Telegraph reported.The vessel weighs 2 tons, is 34 feet long and 9 1/2 feet wide. It can reach top speeds of more than 50 knots.The speedboat drone has a collision avoidance system and sensors, which help it to avoid other vessels.Much of the technology on board the vessel remains top secret. However, sources told the Telegraph the tests could lead to a new generation of robotic vessels designed to track or spy on enemy boats.British military bosses fearful of legal challenges and public opinion are unsure about arming unmanned speedboats, defense experts told the Telegraph.The British navy will host a competition called Unmanned Warrior next month in which the MAST speedboats will battle it out with more than 40 other maritime drone systems.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. Drone speedboat driven by pilot, controlled by remote control2. Drone navigating by itself at 50 knots3. Length and height of the drone speedboat4. Drone surveils target, uses sensorsVOICEOVER (in English): “This experimental robot speedboat was unveiled by the British navy on Monday.”“The prototype Maritime Autonomy Surface Testbed, or MAST, is a drone that can be sailed by a pilot or by remote control.”“It can also be programmed to operate on its own and can reach top speeds of more than 50 knots.”“The speedboat drone is 34 feet long and 9 ½ feet wide.”“It has a collision avoidance system and sensors, which help it to avoid other vessels.”  “Much of the robotic technology on board the ship remains top secret.”“But reports said the tests could lead to a new generation of robotic vessels designed to track or spy on enemy boats.”“According to experts, British military bosses fearful of legal challenges and public opinion...… are unsure about arming unmanned speedboats.”“The British navy will host a competition called Unmanned Warrior next month …… in which the Mast speedboats will battle it out with more than 40 other maritime drone systems.” SOURCES: The Telegraph, The Guardianhttp://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/09/05/navy-unveils-robot-spy-speedboat/https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/sep/05/royal-navy-tests-unmanned-speedboat-ahead-of-drone-exercises***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 20:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/06/3152520/3152520_098998FF84D248FB88E1B47E7F2F437F_160906_3152520_British_navy_tests_speedboat_spy_drone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5AC/28E/5AC28E4958E44E22A95149665518F5FC_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Speedboat drone,drone,drones,future of warfare,robot,navy robot,navy drone,drone boat,future tech,navy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3152489</guid>
      <title>SpaceX rocket explodes on launch pad in blow for Facebook satellite plan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RESTRICTIONS: NONE For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twA SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket and its cargo were destroyed in an explosion at Cape Canaveral on Thursday.The blast occurred as the rocket was being fueled, but the cause of the explosion was not immediately known, Reuters reported.The $62 million rocket was scheduled to launch on Saturday.  It was carrying an Amos-6 satellite owned by Israeli company Spacecom. Facebook planned to use the satellite’s bandwidth to boost internet connectivity in Africa. The SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket is designed to transport satellites and spacecraft into space. It has nine first-stage engines, which can sustain two engine shutdowns during flight without compromising the mission, according to SpaceX.The second stage delivers the payload into orbit. Its single engine can be reignited several times to send multiple payloads into space.The first stage of the rocket is designed to return to Earth so it can be reused. Rocket burns decelerate the Falcon 9 before four landing legs deploy.Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg wrote on Facebook that he was “deeply disappointed” by the mission’s failure.RUNDOWN SHOWS:1. SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket blasts off, highlight nine engines2. Falcon 9 first stage separates, second stage ignites, boost payload towards space3. Falcon 9 first stage lands on4. Facebook Amos 6 satellite in space sending internet signals to Africa.VOICEOVER (in English): “Face-boom … sorry … Face-book head honcho Mark Zuckerberg must be pissed with his SpaceX counterpart Elon Musk today …… after a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket carrying a satellite that FB was planning to use exploded on the launch pad at Cape Canaveral.”“The blast occurred as the rocket was being fueled on Thursday, but the cause of the explosion was not immediately known.”“The SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket is designed to transport satellites and spacecraft into space. It has nine first-stage engines, which can sustain two engine shutdowns during flight without compromising the mission.”“The second stage delivers the payload into orbit. Its single engine can be reignited several times to send multiple payloads into space.”“The first stage of the rocket is designed to return to Earth so it can be reused. Rocket burns decelerate the Falcon 9 before four landing legs deploy.”“The Falcon 9 that exploded on Thursday was carrying an Amos-6 satellite, which Facebook planned to use to boost internet connectivity in Africa.”“The $62 million Falcon 9 rocket was due to launch on Saturday.”“Mark Zuckerberg wrote on Facebook that he was ‘deeply disappointed’ by the mission’s failure.” “And, Elon Musk aside, he definitely won’t be the only one.”“Facebook is a customer of Israeli company Spacecom, which owns the Amos-6 satellite.”“It remains to be seen if the blast will scupper Spacecom’s $285 million sale to a Chinese company, which was announced last week.”“Conditions attached to the deal said the satellite had to be launched successfully and complete in-orbit tests.”“Whoops!”SOURCES: SpaceX, Reutershttp://www.spacex.com/falcon9http://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-x-blast-idUSKCN11750U***For story suggestions please contact tips@nextanimation.com.twFor technical and editorial support, please contact:Asia: +61 2 93 73 1841Europe: +44 20 7542 7599Americas and Latam: +1 800 738 8377]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 19:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/09/06/3152489/3152489_B6A76008CA3F44FD974593A531ADB670_160906_3152489_SpaceX_rocket_explodes_on_launch_pad_in_blow_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/498/18C/49818C18015D4725995346DDCAA0967A_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,spaceX,spaceX explosion,falcon 9,spacex explodes,spacex rocket explosion,spacex blows up,spacex explosion 2016]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3211932</guid>
      <title>Chicago may build floating, solar-powered bike path along Chicago River</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Chicago may consider building a floating bike path along the edge of the Chicago River in an effort to become the most ‘bike-friendly city’ in the U.S.Known as the RiverRide, the proposed bike path would float on the Chicago River between Horner and Ping Tom Parks, according to architecture firm Second Shore, which proposed the idea.The bike path is built on steel-reinforced concrete pontoons, which are secured with pilings driven in the riverbed. Each 82-foot long by 12-foot wide segment is equipped with solar panels to generate power for lighting. More segments can be connected to extend the path.The path is also embedded with a heating conduit to prevent icing on the surface. It also has retractable awnings that can roll out to shelter riders from rain and snow.Each mile of the bike path might cost between $5 to $10 million. According to Co.Exist, Second Shore hopes a half mile of the bike path will be built in a pilot project by the summer of 2017.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 23:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/20/3211932/3211932_7BF3D2A0F5E44E8890208BD953BB41D0_161120_3211932_Chicago_may_build_floating__solar_powered_bike_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BCE/0D5/BCE0D537F863463F83B4F7AB7394288C_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Second shore,riverride chicago,chicago bike path,chicago floating bike path,chicago solar powered bike path,chicago bike friendly,cycling,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3209560</guid>
      <title>New implant allows ALS patient to communicate using brain activity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers in the Netherlands have developed a brain implant that enables a woman with Lou Gehrig’s disease, also known as ALS, to communicate using brain activity, and without a doctor’s supervision.An electrocorticograph, developed by researchers at the University Medical Center Utrecht, consists of four electrode strips of about 5 cm long, with each holding four small electrodes. The electrode strips are implanted inside the skull against the brain.According to the study published in the New England Journal of Medicine, two of the electrode strips are placed over the region of the left motor cortex that controls hand movements, and the other two are placed over the left prefrontal cortex as a backup. The electrode strips are connected to an transmitter device that is installed inside the left side of the patient’s chest. The implant wirelessly connects to a receiver via an antenna and to a tablet computer mounted on the wheelchair.To activate the electrodes, the patient thinks about moving her right hand, which triggers the electrodes to send signals down to the transmitter in the chest. This eventually resulting in her hand moving a cursor to make an input on the computer screen. If the patient’s motor cortex degenerates over time, she would counter backwards to activate the backup electrodes placed over her prefrontal cortex, as this region is responsible for mental calculation.ALS affects the neurons that are required for voluntary muscle control and causes complete paralysis within a couple of years. According to the ALS Association, about 6,000 people in the U.S. are diagnosed with ALS each year. There is no known cure to the disease.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 20:24:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/17/3209560/3209560_1E92E18D515445CAA14DEE314F6BA53F_161117_3209560_New_implant_allows_ALS_patient_to_communicate_us_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/29C/9B2/29C9B2FB139240939F55BEE01C7A38C8_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Lou Gehrig,ALS,paralysis,paralyzed,ALS patient video,ALS communication device,brain implant]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3209103</guid>
      <title>Chinese doctors craft man&#x2019;s new ear from rib cartilage and the skin on his forearm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Chinese hospital in the process of creating a human ear almost entirely through the human anatomy alone.According to Chinese state media news outlet CCTV, plastic surgeons have grown an ear on a patient’s arm after he lost it in an car accident one year ago. The man, identified only as Ji, is being treated by surgeons at First Hospital Affiliated with Xian Jiaotong University in Xian City, Shaanxi Province.Several months ago, a dilator was inserted into the man’s right forearm, which received daily water injections that created a thin and stretched layer of skin. Next, the hospital removed some of the patient’s rib cage cartilage and modeled them into the shape of an ear.This cartilage model was then inserted into the expanded skin, which has formed around it in the shape of a human ear. “It looks exactly the same as my old ear,” Ji said, according to a China Daily/Asia News Network report on the Strait Times.The next part of Ji’s treatment  transplanting the new ear to the patient’s head  will take around three or four months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 13:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/16/3209103/3209103_9B1BD05900F746DD96FD9065C1D2687D_161116_3209103_Chinese_doctors_craft_man___s_new_ear_from_rib_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/8C9/898/8C9898C9CD87425CA9452D4CEEAB0A9C_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Strange surgery stories,replacement ear surgery,china growing ear arm,plastic surgery on ear,growing ear on arm,arm used to grow ear,rib used to make ear,ear surgery,xian,china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3209098</guid>
      <title>Electric VTOL craft could make flying cars a reality</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Several companies and venture-backed start-ups hope to bring electric VTOL vehicles to the skies. VTOL stands for vertical take-off and landing.Google co-founder Larry Page has poured money into Zee.Areo, which is developing VTOLs. Other companies such as Boeing are helped by DARPA funding as the US military seeks to develop VTOL aircraft.But experts caution it could be decades before VTOL aviation is fully developed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 13:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/16/3209098/3209098_4C64B43362AB47A4A156F5E071E9EAE4_161116_3209098_Electric_VTOL_craft_could_make_flying_cars_a_rea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/C4B/C34/C4BC34035D5947DA8F48A4001E06E79E_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,VTOL,vertical take-off and landing,electric VTOL,Zee.Areo,Larry Page,Google,Uber,Lilium Aviation,Joby Aviation,Boeing,DARPA,Phantom Swift]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3211932</guid>
      <title>Chicago may build floating, solar-powered bike path along Chicago River</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Chicago may consider building a floating bike path along the edge of the Chicago River in an effort to become the most ‘bike-friendly city’ in the U.S.Known as the RiverRide, the proposed bike path would float on the Chicago River between Horner and Ping Tom Parks, according to architecture firm Second Shore, which proposed the idea.The bike path is built on steel-reinforced concrete pontoons, which are secured with pilings driven in the riverbed. Each 82-foot long by 12-foot wide segment is equipped with solar panels to generate power for lighting. More segments can be connected to extend the path.The path is also embedded with a heating conduit to prevent icing on the surface. It also has retractable awnings that can roll out to shelter riders from rain and snow.Each mile of the bike path might cost between $5 to $10 million. According to Co.Exist, Second Shore hopes a half mile of the bike path will be built in a pilot project by the summer of 2017.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 23:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/20/3211932/3211932_7BF3D2A0F5E44E8890208BD953BB41D0_161120_3211932_Chicago_may_build_floating__solar_powered_bike_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BCE/0D5/BCE0D537F863463F83B4F7AB7394288C_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Second shore,riverride chicago,chicago bike path,chicago floating bike path,chicago solar powered bike path,chicago bike friendly,cycling,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3211932</guid>
      <title>Chicago may build floating, solar-powered bike path along Chicago River</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Chicago may consider building a floating bike path along the edge of the Chicago River in an effort to become the most ‘bike-friendly city’ in the U.S.Known as the RiverRide, the proposed bike path would float on the Chicago River between Horner and Ping Tom Parks, according to architecture firm Second Shore, which proposed the idea.The bike path is built on steel-reinforced concrete pontoons, which are secured with pilings driven in the riverbed. Each 82-foot long by 12-foot wide segment is equipped with solar panels to generate power for lighting. More segments can be connected to extend the path.The path is also embedded with a heating conduit to prevent icing on the surface. It also has retractable awnings that can roll out to shelter riders from rain and snow.Each mile of the bike path might cost between $5 to $10 million. According to Co.Exist, Second Shore hopes a half mile of the bike path will be built in a pilot project by the summer of 2017.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 23:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/20/3211932/3211932_7BF3D2A0F5E44E8890208BD953BB41D0_161120_3211932_Chicago_may_build_floating__solar_powered_bike_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/BCE/0D5/BCE0D537F863463F83B4F7AB7394288C_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Second shore,riverride chicago,chicago bike path,chicago floating bike path,chicago solar powered bike path,chicago bike friendly,cycling,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3213094</guid>
      <title>Bill Gates works with Swiss perfume company to make toilets smell better</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Bill Gates has partnered with a perfume company in Switzerland in an effort to find a way to get rid of the repulsive smell of toilets. The project is aimed at encouraging people in the developing world to use toilets rather than defecate in open areas.Scientists at Firmenich, a 120-year-old fragrance company, discovered that bad toilet odors are primarily made up of four chemical compounds: indole, butyric acid, p-cresol and dimethyl tri-sulfide. According to Bill Gates’ blog, Gates Notes, scientists recreated toilet smells using these chemical compounds and tested out which olfactory receptors typically respond to the bad odors.The team then developed a fragrance that can block these receptors. As a result, the bad odor molecules would not be able to bind to the blocked receptors, and consequently the brain would not receive the signal that triggers the perception of the bad smells. Instead, the brain would only identify a floral scent created by the fragrance.The Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation has been supporting initiative focused on creating better toilets for the developing world for the past few years, including the Reinvent the Toilet Challenge in 2012.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 13:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/21/3213094/3213094_8C3DAD54219D451BAFDAF3FD81029BA7_161121_3213094_Bill_Gates_works_with_Swiss_perfume_company_to_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/634/906/6349065D243C4FB08459BF8338997EBA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Bill gates,bill gates toilet challenge,bill gates foundation,firmenich,switzerland,bill gates reinvent the toilet,world toilet day]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3213094</guid>
      <title>Bill Gates works with Swiss perfume company to make toilets smell better</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Bill Gates has partnered with a perfume company in Switzerland in an effort to find a way to get rid of the repulsive smell of toilets. The project is aimed at encouraging people in the developing world to use toilets rather than defecate in open areas.Scientists at Firmenich, a 120-year-old fragrance company, discovered that bad toilet odors are primarily made up of four chemical compounds: indole, butyric acid, p-cresol and dimethyl tri-sulfide. According to Bill Gates’ blog, Gates Notes, scientists recreated toilet smells using these chemical compounds and tested out which olfactory receptors typically respond to the bad odors.The team then developed a fragrance that can block these receptors. As a result, the bad odor molecules would not be able to bind to the blocked receptors, and consequently the brain would not receive the signal that triggers the perception of the bad smells. Instead, the brain would only identify a floral scent created by the fragrance.The Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation has been supporting initiative focused on creating better toilets for the developing world for the past few years, including the Reinvent the Toilet Challenge in 2012.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 13:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/21/3213094/3213094_8C3DAD54219D451BAFDAF3FD81029BA7_161121_3213094_Bill_Gates_works_with_Swiss_perfume_company_to_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/634/906/6349065D243C4FB08459BF8338997EBA_5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Bill gates,bill gates toilet challenge,bill gates foundation,firmenich,switzerland,bill gates reinvent the toilet,world toilet day]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3214116</guid>
      <title>Pneumatic vacuum tubes suck trash away</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Swedish company Envac has designed an underground pipeline system that can collect trash by vacuum.According to the company, the waste inlets can be located outdoors or indoors. When the waste is being thrown into the inlet, it will then slide down a pipe and enter a waste tank underground. The waste tank is emptied by a vacuum truck when it reaches its capacity.The truck empties the tank via a docking point, which is often located outside residential areas. It has a vacuum system on board, which sucks the waste out of the tanks and into the truck, where it is compressed.The waste collection system can be upgraded to include a pay-as-you-throw function that charges users on what they throw into the inlets.The vacuum waste collection system was developed in the late 1980s. It has since been installed in countries such as Sweden, Denmark and Norway.According to Waste360, Coney Island and a new development in Chelsea district in New York are considering installing the vacuum system.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 15:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/23/3214116/3214116_C17B564A513D439E802113C5B797C5C6_161123_3214116_Pneumatic_vacuum_tubes_suck_trash_away_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/095/7B3/0957B355B58843A88E1FD32A87976BF5_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Envac,pneumatic vacuum tube,vacuum tube sucks trash away,mobile vacuum trash collection,envac vacuum trash collection,underground trash pipeline,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3213981</guid>
      <title>Hyperloop One to build the world&#x2019;s first hyperloop system in the UAE</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Los Angeles-based start-up Hyperloop One has signed an agreement with Dubai’s Roads and Transport Authority to build the world’s first Hyperloop system, which will connect Abu Dhabi and Dubai in the United Arab Emirates.The stations for Hyperloop One’s system, called Hyperportals, will be located in the city centers. The Hyperportal in Abu Dhabi will be located near the Etihad Towers, while the one in Dubai will be located near the world’s tallest building, the Burj Khalifa.Passengers will travel in pods, which come in four different configurations: cargo, coach, meeting, and lounge. The pods will pick up passengers at gates and travel autonomously to an underground level. There, they will be loaded inside a transporter capsule. Each transporter capsule will carry four pods.The capsules will be propelled by compressed air using magnetic levitation, which eliminates friction, inside a tube kept at a near-vacuum, to eliminate air resistance. They can travel at a speed up to 1,200 km per hour. The Hyperloop will reduce the normal two-hour travel time by car between Abu Dhabi to Dubai to just 12 minutes.The capsules will stop at the Hyperportal upon arrival, while the autonomous pods can either stop at the gates or continue beyond the Hyperportal to take the passengers to destinations in the city.Hyperloop One said in a press release that the infrastructure does not have to work with the pods alone and could work with other self-driving vehicles in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 12:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/23/3213981/3213981_E10F6CC5E042407EB7813D9048CC2CA4_161123_3213981_Hyperloop_One_to_build_the_world___s_first_hyper_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Hyperloop one,hyperloop,hyperloop system,hyperloop in UAE,hyperloop dubai and abu dhabi,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3213971</guid>
      <title>Uber lays out vision for flying urban transportation system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Ride hailing company Uber released a white paper in October that envisions a future where commuters jetting city from to city in compact aircraft is as normal as taking the train.Uber’s prediction of a world with commonplace urban air transit systems relies heavily on the widespread use of small self-flying electric aircraft with vertical takeoff and landing capability. Also known as VTOL, it is most commonly used by helicopters, as well as a small number of military aircraft.According to the Uber white paper, a network of VTOL hubs or landing pads, dubbed “vertiports” and “vertistops”, could be used as terminals to ferry passengers. Unlike cars, buses and trains, VTOLs aren’t susceptible traffic jams or delays   they can fly from A to B with no fixed route. The company estimates the cost of a 15-minute flight may eventually reach as low as $21.The aircraft would fly at cruise speeds of around 150 miles per hour and won’t go above 10,000 feet. The VTOL would be powered by rechargeable batteries that’d maintain 30-minutes of reserve energy. Uber won’t manufacture the aircraft, but reckons the market will create them in the next five years, reported Wired, citing the white paper.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 12:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/23/3213971/3213971_09C64DB44A3A4F57809FB56DF7494A88_161123_3213971_Uber_lays_out_vision_for_flying_urban_transporta_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/898/EDB/898EDBB7ED5040BDBBAFF334C79D0998_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Uber,The flying car,flying car,flying taxi,flying uber,vtol,uber vtol,uber vtol services,flying uber explained,urban air transport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3214915</guid>
      <title>Space elevator tower would reach 20 kilometers high</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Canadian space company wants to build a space elevator that reaches 20 kilometers high.The company is called Thoth and the concept is called the Thoth X tower. The idea is to build a tower with reinforced inflatable sections. The middle is hollow.  An elevator car would encircle the tower until it reaches the top.Thoth estimates the tower would cost $5 billion to construct. As a demonstration project, it would build a precursor tower measuring 1.5 kilometers tall.One feature of the project is the wind farm about three quarters of the way up. The 50 turbines could produce 1 gigawatt of continuous energy. That’s enough to power about 700,000 homes.The main purpose of the tower is to provide a take-off and landing platform for spacecraft. If your aircraft takes off at a 20 kilometer altitude, you can get to space in a single stage without the need for additional fuel stages.Thoth estimates this would save 30% on energy costs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 13:56:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/24/3214915/3214915_07F3638A95084EA2A92A5384D487D9E3_161124_3214915_Space_elevator_tower_would_reach_20_kilometers_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/635/C42/635C426BFB1945E4A7D57BBA7C25AEB8_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Space elevator,space tower,Thoth,ThothX]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3215733</guid>
      <title>Dakota Access pipeline protester could lose arm after being hit by police concussion grenade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The father of a woman protesting the Dakota Access pipeline says her arm was severely injured by a concussion grenade thrown by police at 4:30 a.m on Monday.Lawyer Wayne Wilansky said the grenade exploded at his daughter Sophia’s left forearm. The blast destroyed all of the muscle, soft tissue, nerves and arteries between the elbow and wrist, and some of the bone. According to the Los Angeles Times, police denied using grenades, instead suggesting Wilansky may have been injured by propane bottles made by protesters.In another incident, on Monday at 3 a.m officers noticed two men and a woman behind a barricade near a burned vehicle left over from a previous clash on Backwater Bridge. According to local TV station Valley News Live, they didn’t comply with police orders to come out, so officers fired non-lethal rounds to force them out. Police saw more people approaching the area, including someone rolling silver cylinders. It was here police saw an explosion. The protesters then reportedly pulled a women from under the vehicle.On investigation of the area authorities discovered propane tanks rigged as improvised explosive devices, slingshots, and rocks. Police are investigating if the explosives are related to injuries suffered by a female protester.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 11:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/25/3215733/3215733_4DE818D27AB74C879FB4E7FCBAA33ABC_161125_3215733_Dakota_Access_pipeline_protester_could_lose_arm__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/019/EE8/019EE8DC577C43B99ED893FFF956CAA7_3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3215732</guid>
      <title>Two students die as rare thunderstorm asthma triggers massive attacks in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Four people died on Monday night and hundreds more were hospitalized after a thunderstorm triggered massive asthma flare-ups in Melbourne.A storm that raged through the city shortly before 6 p.m. brought with it extreme levels of rye grass pollen  a rare phenomenon known as thunderstorm asthma, the Australian Broadcasting Corporation reported.Whole pollen fragments typically released on hot, windy days are usually large enough to be trapped by nose hairs before they can get into the airways.But sudden weather changes can cause the larger pollen fragments to be swept up into storm clouds, where they absorb moisture and explode into thousands of tiny particles.The allergens are carried back to the ground and easily dispersed by the wind over long distances.When inhaled, they can trigger attacks in those who suffer from asthma or pollen allergies, though even non-sufferers can struggle to breathe.Victims Hope Carnevali, Omar Moujalled, Clarence Leo, and Apollo Papadopoulos all died after suffering horrific asthma attacks, while 8 more people were in intensive care, according to the Herald Sun. Experts said there is no way to predict the phenomenon, since storms on high pollen count days don’t always result in thunderstorm asthma.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 11:26:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/25/3215732/3215732_7E667B3A5DA14132B0C895D1DDF9C75D_161125_3215732_Two_students_die_as_rare_thunderstorm_asthma_tri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/B49/D1B/B49D1BE934974D4A95EE981E48BCF564_8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3218827</guid>
      <title>UK insurer develops mobile drones that bring illumination when requested</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UK insurer Direct Line has developed a mobile street lighting system that can be requested by users.According to the company, the drones  called Fleetlights  are fitted with powerful lighting units that can provide 200W of Tungsten light. User can request the drones through an app.The request would be processed at a local control center, where an operator would assign and dispatch available drones to the user’s location.The drones would fly autonomously to the user’s location. A lead drone communicates with the user’s smartphone while the other drones would continually reposition themselves to light up the user’s path, the New Atlas reported.The user could send the drones back to the control center via the app when they no longer need the lighting.Fleetlights have trialled in the English town of Petworth, which the company says has the most dangerous roads in the country. The company added that there have already been inquiries as to whether their drones can aid in search-and-rescue operations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 14:51:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/29/3218827/3218827_C8458F359F3440C684A54735565C5349_161129_3218827_UK_insurer_develops_mobile_drones_that_bring_ill_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/CC3/19A/CC319AEF03404115BAEDF1C220F5CC5F_7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Fleetlights,drones with torches,uk insurer direct line,direct line fleetlights,technology,drones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3218822</guid>
      <title>Cyborg cockroaches could be used as mapping tool</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers at North Carolina State University have developed a mapping system that would make use of the remarkable survival skills of cockroaches.According to New Atlas, cockroaches are fitted with electronics connected to their antennae and cerci. Scientists can remotely steer the cockroaches by stimulating their antennae and accelerate their movements by stimulating their cerci.The cyborg cockroaches’ movements are restricted by a UAV via radio signal, which contains their movements to within 20 meters. The UAV signal is able to penetrate buildings, the university said in a press release.The insects would move freely within the defined area and would emit radio waves, which would translate into a map of the area. The UAV would move to unexplored sections until all sections are mapped.“This has utility for areas – like collapsed buildings – where GPS can’t be used,” Edgar Lobaton, an assistant professor of electrical and computer engineering at NC State and co-author of two papers describing the work said in the press release.The researchers hope the system will help rescue teams locate survivors after a disaster and to provide a safe way for officials to rescue victims.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 14:47:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/29/3218822/3218822_A4A6CFAC745646C69EAD9FB93EF682AC_161129_3218822_Cyborg_cockroaches_could_be_used_as_mapping_tool_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/5CA/030/5CA030F049374F73A56E4695E580C200_4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Cyborg cockroaches,biobot cockroaches,cyborg cockroaches as mapping tool,nc state university,biobot,cyborg,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3218820</guid>
      <title>How to harvest stem cells from teeth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Many parents bank stem cells from blood in the umbilical cord when their baby is born and store it for their child’s potential future medical use, but some are now looking to another source for this  the human tooth. Stem cells from tissue inside the tooth are mesenchymal stem cells. These are traditionally found in bone marrow. Also known as MSCs, these cells are multipotent and can differentiate into cells that repair muscles, bone and cartilage, the heart and blood vessels, among others.According to Euro stem cell, a partnership made up of 400 European stem cell and regenerative medicine labs, more research is needed before MSCs can be used in medical treatments. They may potentially help treat autoimmune disorders as well as the circulatory and skeletal systems.U.S. companies such as Store A Tooth and The Tooth Bank offer to store teeth cryogenically, especially baby teeth and wisdom teeth. This could allow people to use them later if the need for stem cell therapy arises.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 14:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/753/16/11/29/3218820/3218820_87DD6EEACFD449DD929AB82D0BCCB497_161129_3218820_How_to_harvest_stem_cells_from_teeth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/F4A/FDF/F4AFDF048C2F4250AC462E314F73B993_6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[next animation studio,tomonews,Teeth,stem cell teeth,stem cell process,stem cell in teeth,dentistry,stem cell applications]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
